those boys are just gonna get
in the
trouble the way they think Adam
Curry
John C. Dvorak this is no
agenda and
from northern Silicon Valley
where I
have the exact right amount of
clips I
can explain why later I'm John
C Devorah
[Music]
well I know the feeling when
you wake up
and everything's there and
you're like
oh my god have the exact right
amount of
claps yeah the last show and
now we
don't play everything but we
came to the
party with almost 70 clips yeah
we came
with too many that's quite a
lot of
quite a lot of clips yes do you
want to
expand on why it's just the
right amount
of will that come later yeah
what I've
did my newest process is I take
the
clips and I print them on a
sheet on the
left hand side landscape style
oh okay and so that leaves a
bunch of
room on the page usually have
to have
two sheet for taking notes
writing down
potential titles things like
this stuff
yeah yeah and when I folded the
paper in
half it usually has the clips
or there's
a lot of little white space
over there
there was a it's perfect it's
like when
you fold it in half to create a
you know
landscape Felipe's piece of
paper fold
in half the the length of
everything is
just perfect it fit on the sheet
perfectly well so this is the
exact
right amount of clips that is an
interesting observation I have
something
very similar I have a window
open and
it's the clip bin and I tossed
like so I
have your clips in the morning
that's in
a folder it's closed but then
when that
when that bin is filled to the
bottom
before it starts to scroll
that's my
sign that I have the ideal
amount of
clips
there you go this is everybody
out there
is fascinating
inside the podcasters studio
everybody
without of Korean Jon sliver
egg so
we're almost well we're on our
road to
recovery here tomorrow make
Texas in
Texas yes tomorrow May 8th
barbershops
and hair salons may commence
Louis about
time well this through
everybody fairly
everybody needs a haircut oh do
I ever
oh man I look scraggly Tina's
complaining about her about her
roots
well that's what women do but I
understand so I immediately
texted my my
hair gal she's like well
because this
was Friday yeah Friday so we've
been
totally blindsided by this we
don't know
what to do we're not ready they
were I
think that the the hair
industry was
kind of kicked back like the
month
whatever I'm flying goodbye
haircut so I
guess we should immediately
talk about
the haircut of the Chicago
mayor which
she did despite actually telling
everybody that you shouldn't go
to the
hair salon he or she is the
whole
thing's kind of explained in
this clip
you hadn't heard it yet Mayer
Lightfoot
facing criticism tonight after
getting
her hair done a photo surfaced
of the
mayor with a hairdresser but she
appeared to ignore social
distancing
efforts standing right next to
them for
the picture when asked about
that photo
today this is what the mayor
had to say
I'm the public face of this
city I'm on
national media and I'm out in
the public
eye and you know I map I'm I'm
a person
who I take my personal hygiene
very
seriously as I said I felt like
I needed
to have a haircut I'm not able
to do
that myself and so I got a
haircut
I'm going to talk more about
that part
of the criticism came from the
fact that
the mayor had called on people
not to go
out and get their hair done in
one of
her stay home save lives PSA so
that
pissed people off and I kind of
liked
how she takes her personal
hygiene very
seriously it's important to her
is it
personal hygiene really
involved with
washing your hair as opposed to
getting
a cut well maybe it was more
than that
for her did you use the word
hygiene
personal appearance different
yes what's
great though and all of this is
in the
show notes the videos in there
as well
and it's in a show notes calm
what's
great to watch is when she's
saying that
this the the woman who was
signing next
to her is making these horrible
faces
you know how they they really
do a lot
of the expression when they're
signing
and and they and they mimic
some of the
words and and she actually was
looking
at the mayor going like
grimacing her
face like I'm a portent it's
something
that has to be seen it's very
very funny
once you take your attention off
Lightfoot herself so in Texas
Governor
Abbott said okay me these the
the broad
announcements May 8th hair
salons
barbershops I think nail salons
as well
on the 18th
Jim's other types of athletic
places and
I think on the 18th and
restaurants can
go to 50% so that's moving
along but oh
no we can't have that with our
mayor
adlet here in Austin no no oh
no this is
wrong
yeah you know it's a way too
early of
course how could we go back to
the
Abbott and Abbott specifically
said you
this supersedes everything but
everybody
here in Austin wants to have
masks on
outside it's 99 degrees I'm
barely
surviving let alone some
coronavirus in
the air it's not happening so
Adler well
since you can't find you he'll
guilt you
into wearing a mask clear this
up for me
are we still required to wear
the masks
in Austin or did the governor's
order
supersede that well
Gunnar's order said that we
weren't
allowed to have a penalty of a
civil or
criminal penalty associated
with not
wearing masks but yet he
recommended me
whereas the lieutenant governor
recommended we wear masks every
public
health official that I talked
to says
people should wear masks
so in Austin in the city I'm
going to
keep it mandatory now the
penalty for
not wearing a mask is that more
people
are going to be infected and
some people
are going to die so the penalty
is
justice now I'm hoping that
people will
take this particular penalty
very
seriously we should all still
be wearing
masks yeah you got me into two
clips I
got a play I wasn't meaning a
blame
right away about a play okay
both about
masks uh-huh let's start with
Trump in
Arizona no mask democracy now
big deal
it's a reopening of our country
who
would have ever thought we were
going to
be saying that a reopening
reopening
president Trump made the
remarks during
a trip to Arizona where he
toured a
Honeywell aerospace plant
that's now
producing a 95 facemasks Trump
wore
safety glasses but no masks
during the
tour
ignoring a sign in the factory
ordering
everyone inside to wear facial
covering
as a Honeywell executive showed
president Trump n95 masks loud
speakers
blared a cover of the song Live
and Let
Die by the band Guns and Roses
Wow they stoop to this level
this is
this is like face bag level
reporting oh
my god
[Applause]
Trump also wore no mask during a
roundtable discussion Tuesday
with
Native American leaders at the
meeting
Trump promised to send a half
billion
dollars to the Navajo Nation
which has
been devastated by kovat 19
more than a
month after Trump signed the
Kara's Act
into law tribes still haven't
received
some eight billion dollars and
promised
relief funds okay so that where
that
leads me to this wait can I
just make a
quick observation about this
sure that
is Trump's tape that's the one
he plays
at the rallies that's the one
with tiny
dancer that's the one with an
in fact
right after he was done at the
plant
they played that can't always
get what
you want and it's not Guns and
Roses
it's wings
shut up Amy Amy Amy
we got Amy there so this came
up and
this just caught my attention
and
brought me back to the clip we
just
played this is Kaley new
secretary yes
this is good
she's great by the way she is
now she's
real mean she's a mean girl I
had no I
had my doubts about Kaley
mackaninee I'm
like she's gonna get eaten
alive she
comes out with just tons of
makeup and
hair also I mean really
hammered on
thick because she's changes her
entire
appearance it really does she
looks
entirely different and then
yeah I
thought this was a great mic
drop me one
this is the one on masks oh oh
oh the
master one I haven't heard the
mask one
okay what do we got play this
is Kayla
and the politics of mass now
she doesn't
really answer this question but
it
brought up an interesting point
which
relates to the fact that
Austin's all
bent out of shape
Amy's all bent out of shape and
the
question is we do have to
discuss this
but you've I'm sure you've seen
the
number of holes there's a huge
difference between Democrats and
Republicans over whether or not
they
think it's necessary to wear
masks no
sense as to why that would be
that's the
choice to the American public
choice to
the individual as to whether to
wear a
mask or not but again I'd
praise the
extraordinary work of this
administration and distributing
those
masks and ensuring health care
providers
son get them okay so she
doesn't answer
the question but now this guy
did bring
up the point and this point is
reflected
in all the clips you're gonna
get the
Democrats all we gotta wear a
mask we
gotta wear our masks were told
to wear a
mask we have to wear a mask
we're gonna
kill each other they're all
gonna die if
we don't wear a mask yeah the
Republicans are hey I wear a
mask 'its
are somebody around and they
don't worry
I have to wear a mess I wear a
mask if I
have to wear a mask I'm not
gonna wear a
mask if I don't have to wear a
mask I'm
not gonna wear a mask when I'm
walking
down the street and it's a
political
thing so this whole thing's
become
politicized and the mask is D
is the
kind of this symbol well it was
it was
ventilators before that now
it's gone
now it's gone to the next level
and I think I know why but I'm
interested to hear your further
thoughts
I don't really have any serious
i but I do know that I have a
basic
thought mm-hmm I think the
Democrats are
the Liberals in Canada would be
a good
example they're more compliant
they
fought they're more route
they're
rule-followers they can't think
for
themselves oftentimes I think I
mean I
hate to say it but that just
seems to be
the case and they and their
virtue
signaling and the virtual
signal is a
big part of it all we've got a
mask on
look at me I got a mask on it's
it's the
blotter and people so you don't
have a
mask on you should have a mask
on they
like the lecture people yes
it's all
it's all so go ahead well I
don't have
anything deeper than that's
kind of a
shallow I know it's very
obvious besides
the virtue signal which in fact
shows
other people that you have the
same
irrational thinking at this
moment if
it's outside now if someone has
a
business and they want me to
wear a mask
in their business fine I really
don't
care if I want to get something
if not
if I don't want to do business
with them
I won't but outside no you're
not gonna
shame me in and into any of
this but the
reason for it is also
the symbolism of a muzzle shut
up slave
it's a muslin er yes I like it
and
that's why people who are mad
about the
whole thing really refused to
wear it I
think subconsciously we're like
no I'm
not going to be muzzled by this
that's a
good I like this a lot thank
you now I
will say that Mimi has a mess
that she
had made I think J made it for
which
goes over the nose and mouth
and this is
a break limits when the cloth
vest was
painted and I recommend people
try this
I mean we do have some matching
just buy
from the Zoe she's sniffing
she's
sniffing the paint is she
breathing that
rue this name is not just paint
it it's
got a big red nose and a
stupid-looking
clown smiling too big giant
teeth
hanging out of it mmm so just
it's the
stupidest looking thing you've
ever I
have to take a picture put it
in the
newsletter I'll wear it it's
it's she
won't wear she's embarrassed by
it but
I'd wear it and it's very funny
and it's
like makes it it really was just
ridicules the whole system since
graduation but just from you
know I
okay I'm biased now because I
think of
it as it's a really as a muzzle
as a I
mean there's so much that goes
along
with the mask yeah but I when
people
come in an opposite direction
for me but
also in Texas I smile you know
now all
you got to work with is your
eyes and I
got a really bad eye today so
people
would always see was a mask in
this
pussy right eye and they'd be
freaked
out but you can have some blood
painted
on your chin like on your neck
like it's
dripping I saw a commercial
yesterday
from dull no sense to clip it
because
it's only text on the screen
masks are worn by superheroes
and they
show of course first responders
and
nurses and doctors there is
there's
another part to it perhaps and
it's it's
purely about the response
an NBC of all of all they
published a
poll of which country scores
best with
their citizens as it pertains
to their
response to the corona virus
outbreak
and if you look at the list and
remember
NBC who do you think is the
number one
country with coronavirus
response
ranking according to well this
global
law survey NBC mate would
probably pick
China yup 86 Vietnam was 77
then we get
UAE India Malaysia New Zealand
Taiwan
Philippines Indonesia Singapore
South
America Australia Germany then
we get
the United States where Sweden
under
this Sweden is of course not on
the list
but that no well that's
interesting
isn't it that brings up
something else
and I do it oh do you want to
get back
to to the opening up stuff
remember
Apple released their data of
how many
times people requested
directions on the
Apple Maps app which a lot of
people
emailed me saying hey man just
because
they're you're publishing that
doesn't
mean that tracking is not your
personal
information it doesn't matter
the
promise was you share nothing
you're
sharing something you're
sharing me
touching my screen I don't like
that but
anyway they publish this data
so I go
and look and you can see it's
really
about mobility so that guests
they say
if you ask for directions you
were going
to travel they claimed they
didn't track
that part in these numbers and
you see
everybody has an L it's the
famous L
drops down goes boo boo
doubloon and
idea it starts to tail up a
little bit
and you can drill down by cunt
like in
the United States you can drill
down by
state go to Sweden there's an L
it's not
true that they didn't do
anything they
definitely had a significant -
fifty
percent in transit activity
they weren't
locked up at home though that's
what
makes it different and people
did it and
I know a lot of companies did
that so
you know I'm we're not out of
the woods
on
this was a good idea or not
particularly
now that New York has seen 60%
of all
transmissions occurred where in
the home
people at home giving each other
coronavirus so it might not
have been
such a good idea anyway there's
a reason
why and it's gone full-on
political so
I'm not too worried about
coronavirus
anymore I mean yes people will
still die
there will be putt we're doing
a lot of
testing so you see lots of
positives we
have no idea if people are
being marked
up is truly dead from kovat 19
or not
doesn't matter it's B
everything's
politicized now so there's
clearly no
one else in Washington
certainly is
worried about it but we have
all this
this these things coming out
now all of
a sudden we have a report that
was MIT
that wasn't a report it was a
draft
created inside the habit here
it was the Harvard Public
Health Harvard
Bloomberg public school no I'm
saying it
wrong John Hopkins Hopkins
Bloomberg
School of Public Health the
same guys
who did event 201 somehow some
internal
document from one guy who's
himself says
in the Washington Post he has
no idea
how that draft model which was
not by
any means done or ready for
publication
or even the model wasn't
completed how
that got leaked to the
Washington Post
he doesn't understand this the
mutant
strain memo no no this is this
is the
model that Johns Hopkins
Bloomberg to
the Washington Post that says
the true
deaths will be 200,000 in the
United
States by the end of June so
everyone
started freaking out and it was
all
that's all it was Monday and
all that
everyone's going nuts they're
like oh we
can't open up and stop
protesting and
Jake Tapper does I mean leading
the
witness
has Michigan Governor Whitmer
who of
course had huge protests she's
very
unpopular she's been doing all
kind of
crazy things telling people
they can't
buy certain things and stores
has to be
roped off but just it's nuts
so Jake Tapper wants her to
describe the
citizens who came to protest
outside of
I guess the state the state
capitol
ordered her man the governor's
mansion
but listen to how he frames the
question
is disgusting these protests
came after
President Trump tweeted liberate
Michigan he tweeted quote the
governor
of Michigan should give a
little put out
the fire he said that these are
very
good people about the
protesters that
were featured in the video to
which the
executive director of the Jewish
Democratic Council of America
Haley so
far who's from Lansing Michigan
she
compared those comments to
president
Trump referring to those
marching
alongside neo-nazis in
Charlottesville
as very fine people is that how
you see
these protesters in that vein
and that
extreme can you believe that
question
that guy is the debt is the
douchiest
question you could possibly ask
and
here's her answer and he knows
that the
debt very fine people thing
relating it
to Charlotte is just pathetic
that's exactly what he was
going for
phil has very fine people don't
tell me
is that isn't that come on come
on
Whitmer is that how you see
these people
don't you think in that extreme
well
some of the outrageousness of
what
happened at our Capitol this
week you
know depicted some of the worst
racism
and awful parts of our history
in this
country sure the Confederate
flags and
nooses the swastikas the you
know
behavior that you've seen in
all of the
clips is not representative of
who we
are no I didn't see any nooses
and
swastikas please show me
evidence of
this horrible it's just
horrible there's
any swastikas it would have
been a
reference to her exactly no
serious yes
I
but this is exactly what the
Nazis did
they locked everybody up took
away their
livelihood bankrupted the small
the
small businesses now maybe
they're just
using a couple of tactics but
yeah so
anyway back to that to the
bogut of
report it was so bad that
secretary of
human health and services a
czar had to
come on fox and friends go into
the
friendly trenches to disclaim
it which i
think he did a really poor job
of yeah
mr. secretary the other question
obviously this morning and many
Americans are waking up and
wondering
about is are these various news
reports
suggesting there's at least a
draft
report from CDC FEMA officials
and
others predicting that you and
others in
the White House the
administration have
to prepare for the possibility
of up to
two hundred thousand deaths of
Americans
by June 1st that there's going
to be
3,000 deaths a day it's going
rising is that true have you
seen such a
report and if it's not true
what are you
preparing for sir so I've not
seen that
report I've heard about it
obviously
this is there are hundreds of
models
that are it was in The
Washington Post I
find that to be an insufficient
answer I
haven't seen it yet dude it was
the
front page of The Washington
Post
bad answer so I think it was
refrigerated hasn't seen that
literally
have the reported as hands I
know but it
just like it comes across as
weak you
know it didn't didn't bother
you that
the way minute I didn't hear
anything
negative about that don't let
him finish
so I've not seen that report
I've heard
about it obviously this is
there are
hundreds of models that are
drafted up
to look at various
contingencies out in
the private public health world
as well
as within our agencies this
apparently
is a draft modeling report of
various
contingencies prepared by Johns
Hopkins
this was not reviewed by the
White House
or senior leadership or the
Task Force
the president's recommendations
on
reopening the American economy
are based
on the soundest scientific
evidence and
modeling and forecasting not
draft
initial projections that just
are
floating out there see what the
problem
I have with this is that
I don't understand how any
citizen this
is probably the same around the
world
with these experts and and the
and the
leaders of these different
departments
it's very difficult for me to
follow
what the numbers are and what
the model
is and it's okay if you change
it but
stick to one and say here's
them don't
tell me there's all kinds of
models
floating out there that we may
pick from
this one or that one I don't
want to
hear that what are the numbers
why does CDC have different
kovat 19
deaths versus the so-called
67,000 I
don't even know where to find
those
numbers anymore that chart has
just been
given away it's bullcrap you're
all full
of crap when it comes to these
models
no obviously to add insult to
add insult
to this Neil Ferguson the man
behind the
original we're all gonna die
two million
deaths in America model the man
responsible for millions of
cattle being
unnecessarily killed during
Hooven mouth
disease who was wrong every
single time
by a factor 10 on all of the
crises but
still we used his model Neil
Ferguson
resigned from the advisory
group because
he broke the lockdown rules in
the UK
because he knows his bullcrap
it's
unbelievable you know I broke
the
lockdown rules right yeah
because he had
a date with his his tinder
girlfriend I
know it makes it that's very
British of
course you know if it's a
scandal it's
always about his penis oh we're
good at
that here too but what's nicer
the work
that has been done
independently is a
code review of Ferguson's model
as you
recall this model the 2-million
model
later revised to 200,000 to
80,000 to
60,000 now apparently revised
back up
who knows what was created using
thirteen-year-old undocumented
code so
the lockdown skeptics which is
a group
you can find at I think it's
locked
locked locked down skeptics
calm just
check
org they did a code review a
professional code review of
what they
could and this is such a piece
of crap
they can't even run it on a
multi-core
process you have to run it in
single
thread mode otherwise it
doesn't work
with the same inputs outputs
are not
repeatable or Purdue or
reproducible no
regression testing after
changes the
whole thing makes no sense
it's very poorly developed and
you can
read it for yourself I mean
anything I
say will go too deep for most
and I'll
just sound foolish but these
guys seem
like they're pretty Pro and
then the one
thing I can do is I can look up
a word
it says because they this group
went
back and forth with the
Imperial College
reviewing the software and they
said
well you know it's really
intended to
often provide as very
stochastic results
like what is stochastic do you
know have
you heard of the word
kostik yeah it's a very it's
used all
the time in computer science
randomly
determined so the results are
determined they say it right in
black
and white you have to remember
it Bill
Gates is behind this I'm not
sure what
it means but okay mr. coder
luckily dr.
Drew is is still on the scene
we know he
is on foul she sphere squad but
he still
has his own opinion and one of
our
producers handed over three
short clips
worth listening to the first
one regards
outdoor transmission of the
virus dr.
drew
research has shown there's been
only one
documented case that was in
China of
outdoor transmission all other
cases
have been indoor transmission
which is
interesting there's also good
evidence
that the virus dies very
quickly out in
sunlight so outdoor looks like
a safe
place for us to be but we
shouldn't be
outdoors without masks and we
shouldn't
be outdoors
shoulder-to-shoulder so then
that seems stupid to be doing
that and
that seems silly to me
uh-huh thank you very much masks
outdoors everybody don't walk
shoulder-to-shoulder tell us
about
shutting down drew what kind of
experience do you have with
that what is
this all based on does it
really work is
it the way to go I mean it
seems like
everyone got infected at home
the idea
of shutting everybody down is a
new idea
that was developed in the 2006
Bush
administration provisional plan
on
pandemics based on a high-school
students science project so the
idea
that this is the way to go
shutting
everything down is is not true
it's not
scientifically true it may be
superior
but we don't know yet
so it may just be that when we
go back
to masks and social distancing
in the
world
there will be no uptick in the
cases so
this idea of a second wave may
never
happen that we will have some
uptick
some little outbreaks but the
idea will
be to isolate and contain those
outbreaks
okay there you go never been
proven
never been tested I'm kind of
interested
you know as we move into the
next phase
of tracking and tracing we're
supposed
to learn things from that and I
have not
seen one report about South
Korea if
they've learned anything I
would have
expected some kind of
information coming
back by now but we continue
with dr.
drew final clip here about
social
distancing that one's nervous
because
people are beginning to pile
out of
their their isolation but you
gotta
remember we don't know that
isolation is
superior to social distancing
we don't
know that now isolation
certainly
superior to nothing but they've
never
studied the difference between
social
distancing and masks done
properly and
quarantine never been done so
we will
find out soon enough
[Music]
well I want to go back to what
you were
talking about with these models
okay
there seems to be a this is Chi
I don't
know when it changed or how it
changed
and I'd have a sense it has
something to
do with the way they're gonna
keep us on
the global warming tract yeah
that well
that's got to come but we have
to keep
all focused on impeaching Trump
with
more important to get impious
of course
but if you remember the last I
think
it's probably the last three or
maybe
even the last four or five
hurricanes
when they showed the the
predictions
nowadays they don't just show a
prediction they used to always
do that
the news guys would rather guy
here's
what's predicted to do know now
they
show about 30 tracks and they
show them
on the screen on the weather
screen they
sir that could do this it could
do that
it could yes mighty says it's
gonna do
that yeah the Western alliance
of
weather caster says he's gonna
do this
and they have all these
different
companies that's what that's
what the
one where Trump took one of the
things
that's gotta hit in Atlanta
right
remember that model that was
the Sharpie
model and so you have all these
models
now and they're scrolling
around all
over the map it's there's a
couple of
things that says to me one is
that this
has changed we've never seen
anything
like this before and they could
have
been doing this for a long time
but they
haven't they just started
recently it's
because and I think global
warming's got
something to do with it because
there's
a lot of models and and they
don't
nobody wants to talk about the
Russian
model which we've talked about
an
emphasize which seems seems to
be
tracking are very mild increase
in
temperatures and this is got
nothing to
do with much of anything but
they're
getting to the point where
they're gonna
do this because they can did
now there's
no responsibility right well
that was
one of the models yeah
well that was one of the most
well
that's not them yeah well there
was 30
models and gray this is the one
that
happened there's always the the
model
always works as the is the
least complex
when it's a simple one but they
it's
just solving themselves have any
responsibilities are the models
models
well along with social
distancing has
come something new which is also
excepted and that social
censorship and
I just coined that myself I
don't know
if anyone ever thought of it
but that's
really what we're witnessing
where there
is a social agreement
apparently that certain types of
information should be censored
because
it's very dangerous in in our
current
climate because we need to
listen to the
experts with their multiple
models this
is why David Icke has been
completely
removed over an interview in
where and
I've watched it I've watched
all of his
interviews and clips from it
well let's
go through that and I'll just
preface
this by saying what Google and
YouTube
and I think Spotify Spotify
removed the
David Icke podcast
Oh boohoo this thank God we
made that
shit open people you really
think you
can you can silence people by
kicking
them off Spotify and it looks
really
dumb Spotify but they're all
making the
AOL mistake America Online was
safe
you're safe with us well we'll
give you
this little window with a
crappy browser
to that scary Internet but you
really
don't want to go there stay
with us use
a keyword that's what they're
trying to
do is trying to keep people
safe and it
doesn't work people want to go
out they
want a bit they want to find
out crazy
stuff they need alternative
information
so they're going to leave these
platforms anyway social
censorship
that's in full play like yeah
like your
little theory there like that
may even
be a show title I'll flip over
this
perfectly folded sheet and
write it down
oh it's the shownotes side of
the page
very lovely lovely now Mike
talks about
let's go over some of this I
only have
them 5g think that's
interesting but
then I have another only have
two clips
so we're not gonna bore people
stuff
with David Icke but David Ickes
whole
thing he goes on and on for
about an
hour but it would everything we
talked
about on this show yeah pretty
much it's
not it's nothing new or even I
mean it's
interesting on the show but we
talked
about in the show months ago
and it's so
it's kind of like oh geez David
where
you been everybody ever listen
to no
agenda
and then he does his little
crazy stuff
with this five Gina the five G
thing is
also misinterpreted he never
says to
everyone like because there was
something that went around
about five
g's gonna trigger the corona
it's out
there and then the five G hits
and you
get it no he's saying that five
G is is
going to make people sick and
Corona
coincidentally can be used as
the excuse
oh they're sick because of
Corona not
because of 5g but I'll play
this clip
this is david icke of comm
story 5g a
government sensor called Ofcom
Office of
Communications
which is the regulator of
British
broadcasters they have said and
it's
it's run by a lady called
Melanie doors
and we need to note these names
down
ladies and gentlemen and when
we're
through this at some at some
level
through it these people have to
be
called to account we have a
situation
where this lady and her
organization
which is a government
department has
told British broadcasters and
of course
they've complied spineless ly
as usual
that they will face serious
sanctions if
they allow any discussion on
their
television stations and radio
stations
about any connection between 5g
and
so-called copied 19 the British
government through this other
idiot the
health secretary Matt Hancock
you know
people are sitting there all
over the
house is 66 million people in
this
country oh shit near me else in
doing as
I'm told
because this this guy you you
wouldn't
let run a you know a Lego house
Hancock
he's saying that everyone must
do that I
mean what are we doing anyway
people like him are now saying
to the
the Giants of Silicon Valley
years aku
Berg's at Facebook your Bryn's
and pages
at Google and you know which
house keys
at Google owned YouTube etc
that they
should ban people who are
making a
connection between Phi
gee and this co bid nineteen
crisis so
that tells you one they
couldn't care
less about freedom and the
right to free
debate thus they have no right
to be in
government and no right to be
running a
broadcast regulator but he told
you
something else
number two it tells you there
is a link
between Phi G and this health
crisis
there's only one reason they
don't want
it discussed because there is a
link and
who's been promoting Phi G and
the
rollout of Phi G who runs the
licenses
for Phi G Ofcom same woman in a
different interview he went a
little bit
more in depth than ID and I
looked up
the studies and what he claims
and the
claim is correct I don't know
if it is
true for five G depending on the
frequencies power etc but
indeed effects
of electromagnetic field
exposure can
create oxidative stress and acts
antioxidant defense system
issues and I
he talked about it in this one
to go to
this one
and said it's completely valid
that and
and the thing with these
theories which
is always with Ike it's always
the case
if you listen to what doctors
are saying
people are turning blue it's
like
they're not getting enough
oxygen I
think we had a clip of that ER
doctor in
New York who said to me it
looked like
someone was at you know 20,000
feet
without oxygen and they were
just
literally dying because of a
lack of
oxygen in their lungs and in
their blood
and so that could be that
absolutely if
someone's immune system is
compromised
and there's a 5g tower next
door and
possibly I don't know but it's
certainly
he I don't think he ever said
coronavirus is caused by 5g but
it
doesn't matter no he never says
that it
doesn't matter its social
censorship if
it if it deviates at all it
must be
eliminated yes I'm I'm I'm gall
wood
this is why our show existed
of course let's play the let's
play the
other one which is DVID I get
left there
sorry this is this is an
interesting
clip because I hate gives me an
anecdote
I can I can talk about this
David Icke
towers going up while this
lockdown has
been going on I know from
communications
to to me and Gaz and Jamie at
some David
Wright comm I know from all the
postings
on the Internet not just in
Britain but
around the world in America but
while
this lockdown has been going on
5g masts
are being rolled out at a very
rapid
rate in the same period of this
lockdown
something like another 21 towns
and
cities have been opened in
Britain - 5 g
a5 G is being rolled out all
over the
world at a very great rate of
knots this
is a time where everything is
supposed
to be stopped yeah and they're
still
building towers overnight yes
because
that's considered yeah yeah we
okay so I
saw one row up here right like
five
minutes from our house I was
like what
that's new well Mimi drove down
from
Washington last I guess Monday
but no
but maybe you last Friday I'm
not read
one of these days before it's
been
around because traffic is just
there's
no traffic and go back before
it yeah so
she comes down this last time
and she
says holy crap all I saw coming
down
were people putting up 5g
towers yeah
all along a highway us
interstate 5 yeah
well and you know when you
think about
it and they are of course
essential
personnel this is
infrastructure it's a
great time from the do anything
what
they should be doing is fixing
the
potholes that's what I've been
waiting
for
oh yeah no pothole fixing
whatsoever
see that that would have
endeared the
community but no but no but no
but no so
so Ike effectively really D
platformed
it just and you're right that's
that's
why our show is here and we're
completely independent and
thank God we
don't have to rely on a youtube
or
anything else like that and in
that and
I gotta say bitch shoot some of
these
you know be that all these
different
alternative video sites they're
that
they're winning with this
they're
gaining well we'll see what if
this is a
good strategy for them but I
think that
when you it's one thing to have
your
people you know to socially
censor
content on your platforms when
people
are running their regular lives
but when
they're at home all day you
know they
start to wander then they're not
entirely your slaves anymore
they're
thinking for themselves maybe a
little
bit so not one but the point is
you
can't start taking this stuff
down I
mean what's that they're just
you're
gonna hurt you two-bit long
term of
course you can't get
advertisers anyway
but if the Russian car cam
videos moved
to a separate platform boom and
once the
cats are gone after that the
cats
changed so that once the cats
leave then
you got no platform left cats
and car
crashes is that's the end funny
moment
in West Virginia although it's
kind of a
blue dress silver dress moment
the
governor of West Virginia
accused of an
expletive again I encourage all
businesses that are allowed to
open to
do so only if they fucking
follow the
guidelines to keep West
Virginians safe
now he claims he didn't use an
expletive
today at her news briefing
there was an
audio glitch and it sounded
like that I
had said a bad word a word that
I was I
would never say nor have I ever
said no
possibility in any way shape
form or
fashion okay yeah
bullcrap but I there is a
glitch and
that and you're allowed to say
that when
it comes to audio there is an
actual
glitch in that but it's after
the F word
and I can't make anything
outside of it
I don't know when then what was
he
saying if it wasn't
I'll listen to it one more time
again I
encourage all businesses that
are
allowed to open to do so only
if they
fucking follow the guidelines
to keep
West Virginia safe I don't know
at least
it gave us another five minutes
of
entertainment you know this
denial he
should just apologize for
saying it I
think so too I just looked up I
mean
this is the kind of thing I got
yeah
yeah let's move over to
pharmaceutical
stuff and the President did
eight it was
a virtual town hall of the
Lincoln
Memorial this was a Fox
exclusive very
interesting setting I'm not
quite like
what are you trying to say here
hmm I
wonder
Trump Lincoln and you trying to
connect
something here in my brain and
he took
questions and you also took
questions
from Martha and from Brett and
the
question came up about the
pharmaceutical companies and
the need
for them to be really you know
we need
our medications our essential
medications created in the
United States
maybe not in China or other
countries
and so it was kind of a
two-parter in
the second part I think she
rattles the
president a bit and here's his
part one
there's a lot of people who say
why you
talk about making it here in
America
why are all of the antibiotics
made in
China can you give me a date by
which we
will be self-sufficient in
antibiotics
in this country and what kind of
incentive would you give
manufacturers
of pharmaceuticals to make sure
that we
are not dependent on China
anymore for
this so the reason it took
place is
because other people that sat
in this
chair maybe not right here but
this is a
beautiful place because they
were
foolish you could even say
because they
were stupid because they
allowed this to
happen and it's not only China
you take
a look at Ireland they make our
drugs
everybody makes our drugs
except us and
we've already done it what
coming out with things numbers
you're
seeing numbers of innovations
that we've
made in the past and things are
being
announced already but we're
bringing
that whole supply chain back
nobody has
to tell me to do it I've been
talking
about that for years now the
one that
you see you don't see you see
it with
cars you see it with other
things people
never looked at medicine but
it's always
been about medicine because we
have at
least 94 95 percent of our
medicines are
made important to do the
vaccine watch
an incredible thing there
American
companies well I'd like to be
able to do
it here I don't want to do it
in China
don't want the vaccine in China
that's
for sure but then Martha
follows up and
I want you to give me your
impression
after you listen to the clip
whether
this was a setup whether he
knew it was
coming if if he turned it
around and may
turn it into something to his
advantage
I think we need to talk through
it
because she presses him and she
uses
something and that's why I'm
suspicious
of the question well when will
we get to
that 95 percent everything made
here and
he seemed rattled when we get
94 percent
of antibiotics made in this
country do
you have a target date for that
I think
we will have it done within two
years
you know it doesn't go that
quickly and
frankly you put me in a very bad
negotiating position by asking
me those
questions you know we're
talking about
this now I'm supposed to call
up my guys
I mean you put me in a very bad
negotiating position and I'm
not blaming
you that's you that's your job
you know
you're taking my cards away
because I
don't want to be talking this
way I've
done a lot but it gets exposed
when you
answer I assume the show is a
big show
right it's going to do very
well tonight
but you do take away a lot of
my cards
when you're answering asking me
a
question like that you
understand that
yes here's the bottom line I
met with a
drug company six months ago I
said you
got to stop making the drugs
here
you're gonna start making them
here and
they do it for two reasons
a cost reason but it's no
longer so much
cost because we can do things
here for
the same price and in some
cases less
and then you don't have the
transportation problems we're
taking
care of our look another reason
I got
elected and some people don't
like the
sound of it and other countries
don't
like it but I said I'm sorry
it's called
America first and we're all
about
America first that's what we're
it was protest protesting a bit
much I
felt he's got a tell which is
he which
is the term that we're always
ridiculing
people for doing it he doesn't
normally
do it but when he does it I
believe this
is when he says look yeah yeah
exactly
yeah so he said look I met with
the with
the pharma guys six months ago
so I've
been telling them you got to
bring it
back and I'm sure that you know
similar
to what has happened in the
past they're
waiting for something to
sweeten the
deal and that's why I think he
protests
too much I think it this was
maybe the
whole thing was part of his
negotiating
it could be I haven't figured
it out
what could be cuz he did you
know oh no
you're gonna ruin I only have
one other
question from this but it's a
good one
and his answer was very
complete and
this comes on the heels of at
least the
knowledge being out there
according to
The Spectator in Australia that
there is
a five eyes intelligence report
so
that's the UK the United States
Canada
Australia and New Zealand that
Australia
has and there's a 15-page is
floating
out and about let's say you
know hey
yeah the Chinese are really
responsible
for this and we don't know
exactly how
much is true or how deep it
goes but
Trump has a very outspoken
opinion on
this and he got a question
about it from
some dude who called in it was
black guy
and he he looked and he well he
sounds
as stoned as he looked mr.
president I
have a question for you is
there enough
evidence that China made a
global
community of by the scorn of our
if it's so hot your global
community
respond yeah well I don't lose
any
question about it we wanted to
go in
they didn't want us to go in
early very
early you'll see that because
things are
coming out that are pretty
compelling
now so I don't think there's any
question don't forget China
tried to
blame it first on some of our
soldiers
that turned out did not go too
far I'm
sorry I do need to mention I
have edited
this clip in two spots because
Trump
I've learned speaks and what I
call
hanging chads so he'll talk
he'll be
he'll be talking about
something then
all sudden he drops down into a
repetitive sentence about how
he looks
oh and I closed it up on time
and they
told me not to and then they
closed it
and then he comes back to the
stores
like this is like one of his
rallies
yeah so it's a hanging Chad
thing so I
just snipped it off and I
really got
very upset with that that was
not right
China tried to blame Europe for
this no
I know you saw evidence that
gave you a
high confidence that the virus
came from
the Wuhan lab we got that it
was created
there perhaps but that it came
from
there at the right day we can
illuminate
any more about that yeah we're
gonna be
giving a very strong report as
to
exactly what we think happened
and I
think it'll be very conclusive
is there
any suggestion that it was
anything
nefarious or that it was just a
mistake
so I think they made personally
I think
they made a horrible mistake
and they
didn't want to admit it we
wanted to go
in they didn't want us there
even world
health wanted to go in they were
admitted but much later you
know not
immediately and my opinion is
they made
a mistake they tried to cover
it they
tried to put it out it's like a
fire you
know it's really like trying to
put out
a fire they couldn't put out
the fire
what they really treated the
world badly
on they stopped people going
into China
but they didn't stop people
going into
the USA and all over the world
so you
could fly out of Wuhan where
the primary
problem was all of the problem
essentially also where the lab
is
but you could fly out of war on
and you
could go to different parts of
the world
but you couldn't go to Beijing
and you
couldn't go to any place in
China so
what's that all about
in other words they
they had a problem I think they
were
embarrassed by the problem very
embarrassed and you know the
case could
be made they said hey look this
is gonna
have a huge impact on China but
here's
the thing they allowed this to
go into
our country they allowed it to
other countries they change how
you feel
about president G does it
change your
relationship with him I'm not
going to
say anything I had a very good
relationship he's a strong man
he's a
tough man and a very good
relationship
with him but this should never
have
happened
this should never have happened
this
virus should not have spread
all over
the world they should have put
it out
they should have let us and
other people
in other countries go in and
put it out
because people knew what was
happening
so that is a pretty clear
opinion and a
lot of people heard it and saw
it I
think it was almost four
million people
who viewed that Town Hall which
was huge
for Fox News on cable I was
very big for
them yeah why well Pompeo made
some
comments about this which took
a very
strange
turn because it sounds like he
was
contradicting himself and so I
have this
clip of him answering the wuhan
origin
question 200 in a press
conference and
mr said you seen anything that
gives you
high confidence that it
originated in
that Wuhan lab Martha there's
enormous
evidence that that's where this
began
we've said from the beginning
that this
was a virus that originated in
Wuhan
China we took a lot of grief
for that
from the outset but I think the
whole
world can see now remember
China has a
history of infecting the world
and they
have a history of running
substandard
laboratories these are not the
first
times that we've had a world
exposed to
viruses as a result of failures
in the
Chinese lab and so while the
intelligence community
continues to do
its work they should continue
to do that
and verify so that we are
certain I can
tell you that there is a
significant
amount of evidence that this
came from
that laboratory in one do you
believe it
was man-made or genetically
modified
that the best experts so far
seem to
think it was man-made have no
reason to
disbelieve that at this point
your
office of the DNI says the
consensus the
scientific consensus was not
man-made or
genetically modified that's
right I I
agree with that yeah
obviously I've seen their
analysis I've
seen the summary that you saw
that was
released publicly I have no
reason to
doubt that that is accurate
okay so just
to be clear you do not think it
was
man-made or genetically
modified I've
seen what the intelligence
committee has
said I have no reason to
believe that
they've got it wrong you have
to put
this in context here I think
that
there's confusion in the
question and
the answer and when he's saying
when
she's asking about if it was
created so
clearly wasn't synthetic but in
his mind
I believe he's answering the
question if
it's a bio weapon
No No if you listen to this very
carefully at the very end the
very end
of that clip he says you got to
take
this in context he says I
believe what
the DNI said but you got to
take it in
context that's what he said and
what he
and I do i imaginated over this
particular clip for a while
before I
realized what context meant the
DNI
report stated that the a bunch
of
scientists and other people
agreed that
it was all was a natural form
element
and it was and in that that was
the
reports about the agreement was
solid
that it was naturally formed it
came out
of no bad or whatever and in
context
what he was saying why he could
agree
with the DNI report is that
they were
reporting on what the
scientists said
reporting on the reality of it
okay okay
right and that's what he meant
by you
gotta take this in context well
the
context was the DNI was not
discussing
how this virus came about or
there's
other probably other
intelligence
reports that came out that
indicate
because he's very strong that
this is
man-made genetically engineered
or
whatever from the lab that made
words
escaped from which brings me
back to
what I think that would the
French guy
the guy who had discovered the
AIDS
virus
said and I'm gonna subscribe
her to him
even though it was says he's
nuts he's
nuts What did he say so so I
listened
this over and over again I
realized that
you could yes you can't say
that it was
man-made and you can agree with
the DNI
report because the DNI report
is just
stating that all these
scientists have
said the following yes I agree
that the
DNI reports got that right those
scientists did say that well
that makes
sense because the last thing he
wants to
do is supersede because the
president
also didn't say man-made he
said come
from he didn't get into that so
they
Pompeii yeah yeah well not it
not a
great replicating into any have
any
trouble agreeing with the DNI
report
which
it wasn't it was I don't think
it was
well done no but I think it'd
be but
when he says in context that
was the key
work I got yeah so anyways like
I think
he's not lying
no but it's confused the
reporters and
he never really got it went out
of his
way to explain it I'm not
helpful not
help it's not helpful
the Chinese hear it loud and
clear
though especially when it comes
that
five eyes report this is from
60 minutes
in Australia how's this for
slap this
week Australia was described as
chewing
gum on the boot of China that
needed to
be scraped off on a rock the
insult came
from an influential Chinese
newspaper
editor backed by the Communist
Party our
crime we're troublemakers
because our
government is calling for an
independent
inquiry into the origins and
spread of
coronavirus it's fair to say our
relationship with Beijing is
currently
fractured but understanding why
China is
so defensive
not to mention petulant is
difficult
because the regime is so
suspicious of
the Western media chewing gum
huh stuck
to the shoe that's gotta stood
that is
not that's not gonna play well
that's
international words of war my
friend you
can't just say that is great
especially
in context of Eastern culture
and
chewing gum like chewing gum is
really
low low on the polls so there's
there
isn't an attack on China
there's a
there's polls everywhere saying
overwhelming majority of
people's and
here's the term here's the term
we
should be on the lookout for D
couple we
want to consciously decouple
from China
think this is going to be the
term
decoupling yeah that's been
that's not
it that spin I'd say around for
a couple
months it doesn't go yeah I'm
hearing it
I'm hearing it it's a good term
it is
maybe it's catching on here's
what you
think yeah it could be catching
on
uncoupled tuples Ted Cruz is on
his own
little mission
he's doing the rounds and he
wants to
force Hollywood to stand up to
Chinese
censorship and at first I was
kind of
puzzled like why are you so
interested
in this it gives a crap but
then I
realized what he's really doing
he's
saying we can't have these
movies which
have a permanent desk at the
Pentagon
using our military equipment ie
Top Gun
if they're also going to if
these
productions are also going to be
involved in censorship and in
Top Gear's
spit upon specific instance Tom
Cruise's
flight jacket had a Taiwanese
flag it
had to be removed
so for some reason Ted Cruz is
spending
a lot of time on that and I
think that
it may it's it's meant to
cripple China
in in multiple ways but I think
they do
have such huge investments in
in movies
and Hollywood that he's trying
to hurt
them there but it's just an odd
thing to
do it's like even more to it
than that
what you got
he knows the connection I don't
know I'm
not a mind reader I don't know
what Ted
Cruz is thinking he may have
nefarious
scheme under foot under way
mm-hmm maybe
under foot he said something
offensive
too right now we're trying to
get Taiwan
to get involved into
whu-oh and some other things
would we're
moving to get Taiwan's
independence
recognized I mean there's a
million
things that we've been trying
to do at
Taiwan for ever since the 1940s
right
when they you know ran off and
you know
the government really Republic
of China
ran off and to become the
Republic of
China on Taiwan they run off to
off the
mainland by Mao and so there's
there's
that element and so this any
pushback by
the Chinese on stuff like that
little
flag is going to be rejected but
especially when yeah the
Chinese invest
a lot of money how much money
do you
think the State Department or
the
Defense Department spends on
one of
these war movies in terms of
just fuel for the Jets and I
think oh
yeah that's a lot of money it's
Millions
yeah and so why are we you know
taking a
backseat to the Chinese
investment when
we're making these investments
and these
movies actually can't be done
without an
investment I agree I'm just
kind of
confused as to why Ted Cruz is
in this
but maybe it maybe he's trying
to create
a squeeze and and he's really
going
after Hollywood and not China
I think it's possible he's
going after
Hollywood yeah that's what that
that
would make more sense I would
make more
sense so meanwhile we have on
the
medical front we have multiple
trials
going we know REM dis aveer is
is now in
trial which have all these all
these
great stats it's all in the
show notes
you know the cost of REM dis
severe it's
like it's like $400 a day versus
hydroxychloroquine at the
pennies a day
it's really quite an incredible
and it
just seems like anything that
is not
approved by doctor dr. death
himself
doctor foul Qi that it has to
be pushed
back in them and quiet and be
suppressed
let's not talk about it and
then all of
a sudden we get this over the
over the
past few days out of Pittsburgh
Ross
Township police believe two men
found
shot to death over the weekend
was a
murder-suicide
the body of 37 year old being
Lou was
found Saturday at his home at
the muse
of town north
police believe loose killer
left the
town home went back to his car
and
killed himself that man has not
been
identified but police say they
believe
that Lou and the man did know
each other
well so this research have been
research
have been working on a cure a
treatment
for kovat 19 any and he goes
out in a
murder-suicide what are the
chances but
that brings us to the planned
Demick
quote-unquote documentary that
has been
socially censored they're still
available on multiple platforms
have you
seen this John's about 20
seconds woman
has lots of videos that have
come and
gone they all get censored I
always
download them mm-hmm very
copies very
good cuz I figure you know this
things
aren't gonna last and this
latest one
though I have to say the one
with the
ominous opening and the guy
interviewing
uh yeah I think it's the best
produce
and the and the most impactful
cuz this
the one mimi's all you got to
watch this
yes yes and I said well you
know I'm
very familiar with this woman
and she's
been bitching and moaning about
one
thing or another for a long
time long
time long time well we we
actually
discussed her probably about
ten by
decade a decade ago but we just
started
the show now I'll just want to
say this
about the documentary I did not
pull any
clips from that because it's
great as a
piece and I think it's
fantastic to make
people aware of of this story
and of end
of this doctor story in
particular but
you know you get all the scary
music
it's very dressed and there's a
lot of
manipulation going on so I
found an
interview that she did with it
was just
her a Skype call but the the
quality is
good and the questions she
speaks in in
answer blocks she's fantastic
for media
but we knew about her when we
first
started talking about vaccines
on this
show 10 11 years ago I'll just
be
somewhat repetitive that we had
found
documentation from a big
Goldman Sachs
and JP Morgan Chase I think
medical
conference that all the
pharmaceutical
companies were all jacked up
because
vaccines was the future it's a
you know
in some cases they're mandatory
so it's
a guaranteed paycheck and
they're
identified they're indemnified
they
don't have to go to the same
test ii
because it's called the
biologic and
there's so many great reasons
for this
and we got a lot of contact
which i
don't think I quite understood
at the
time about dr. Mike Ovitz as it
pertains
to chronic fatigue syndrome and
people
were trying to communicate
something to
us and we dice or
was just not my headspace was
not there
we just kind of started
deconstructing
stuff and I was a little naive
to some
things that were going on so it
comes to
the medical community but in
this first
clip she addresses that and
what she had
figured out back in the day is
that
there were what are called XM
RVs which
is Mouse raira viral viral
retrovirals
excuse me extra cross were
showing up in
in different people and for
reasons that
were very unclear but what this
was
creating was a chronic fatigue
syndrome
not dissimilar to HIV actually
in many
ways in fact the and we'll get
to that
later testing for HIV showed
people with
these xmrv zyi this chronic
fatigue
syndrome show tested positive
for HIV
even though I didn't have HIV
so it's a
mess and she was a part of it
she's been
part of fout she's system for
many years
and she has her own story about
how she
was kicked out and and jailed
and
accused of fraud and and that
certainly
stuff you can look into I'm more
interested in what she's saying
she
sounds credible she certainly
has the
curriculum to back her up and
let's take
go back to that initial issue
when we
were first introduced to her
but this is
a current interview
this is dr. Judy Michael it's
Mike Ovitz
we we isolated a new family of
retroviruses called XMRV that
means Zeno
trophic Mouse related
retrovirus so it
was very clear that you know
the human
by room doesn't have Mouse
retroviruses
therefore we thought perhaps as
in the
days of HIV that this virus
could have
been spread through biological
therapies
because we use a lot of mice in
therapy
in our lab we also remembered
back to
the days of HIV
when when HIV spread through the
population from a contaminated
blood
supply when it became clear by
the way
that very bit there Alex Jones
has been
yelling about that for for
maybe 20
years vaccines being
transporting
contaminated blood and that's
where he
got it from spread through the
population from a contaminated
blood
supply when it became clear in
2010 and
11 that in fact the blood
supply was
heavily contaminated and in
fact the
most likely way that these
mouse viruses
of many strains not just one
got into
humans it was almost certainly
from
biological therapies and the
most likely
the most prominent one was
vaccine that
that in fact that we were
injecting in
mouse tissue
you know hisses pieces into
into immune
incompetent little babies
people and and
we had actually literally
caused a
number of diseases including
this is a
this is a family of mouse
cancer-causing
viruses so cancers and neuro
immune
diseases including chronic
fatigue
syndrome autism anomaly Lou
Gehrig's
disease others are associated
with with
retroviruses and it was very
clear in
2011 in the summer of 2011 this
wasn't
just one but many and and the
most
likely way they got into humans
was a
contaminated blood supply and
contaminated vaccines so
contaminated
vaccines as some so any stories
you've
heard in the past likely stem
from her
because that's where I remember
it from
and that's where that chronic
fatigue
syndrome came from but there we
did have
lots of clips if you recall
during the
swine flu bullcrap mm-hmm there
was a
contaminant there was a
huge set of vaccines that went
out that
had live swine flu in him and
would have
contained would have given
people swine
flu you know to push the
numbers up I
don't know I mean it seems like
you know
the carelessness was weird and
there was
some cross-contamination of
other
vaccines that nothing to do
with swine
flu but the swine flu was in
there and
these were caught at the border
kind of
azor being shipped out but dude
you
don't know it because there's
this or
not there indemnified from any
damages
no matter what's in the shot
they give
you anything could be in there
that's
why I think a lot of people are
I I for
example do give I got a vaccine
for I
got the Prevnar 13 back so you
know a
couple months back yeah before
a kovat
broke out because I figure well
you know
let's get I because my doctor
said I
should get it and everybody
said you
should get this if you're
getting older
you want to get this and this
is the flu
vaccine
notice the Prevnar 13 it stops
different kinds of pneumonia
hmm and but
but at the same time I'm very
dubious
about any of these things
because
there's now something going
right
because there was a new of
experimental
pneumonia vaccine that floated
around I
got a bunch of people sick even
though
this is well established so I
wasn't too
worried about it was very
expensive so I
wasn't you know I said well
they're not
they've got me how many people
are gonna
be spending this much money for
this
vaccine and but I'm always
skeptical I'm
very nd if you look at the
stuff that
Robert Kennedy jr. said about
the Gates
Foundation bills experiments on
babies
and they're all in Africa and
India I
mean most of his vaccine
experiments
have gone south you're not
gonna like
this a couple weeks ago we
discussed the
study that was a published
account the
Medical Journal published
account it's
in the show notes once again
that a
number of
military personnel who the
2017-2018 flu
vaccination was tested on from
that test
group that turned out that you
those who
had been administered the
2017-2018
season seasonal flu vaccine had
a 36%
chance
higher chance of contracting a
respiratory disease from some
other
virus specifically corona virus
do you
remember that that report they
do
remember that okay and it's
called it's
called whether there's a term
for it
it's like interference I think
it's a
vaccination interference it's
mentioned
in this clip because this is
where it
gets pretty messed up
as this is the crux of what dr.
Mike
Ovitz is really saying is going
on with
kovat 19 what dr. pouchy has
been saying
is get the influenza vaccines
the live
attenuated influenza vaccines
and and
there have been several
publications but
one in 2017 at 18 among the
military
which actually said the flu
vaccine
promotes the spread that is
your 36
percent more likely to get Koba
19 or an
infection with SARS code two if
you get
the influenza vaccine so it is
advice to
the country you know is totally
against
published literature that says
it's
dangerous that yet that you
don't you
know that you're driving the
disease
with the influenza vaccine and
that
would spread it easier to them
across
nations because those know that
you shed
those viruses that is you
express those
viruses and you'll actually you
know can
get an influenza the same kind
of
symptoms the same kind of upper
respiratory infection and now
you're
more like
li to to spread from human to
human
the coronaviruses and in fact
other
microbial agents other viruses
respiratory syncytial virus
rhinoviruses
that that cause upper
respiratory
diseases including influenza
and what
she's saying here is if you had
the flu
shot in 2017-18 and possibly
with any
flu shot or with any
vaccination which
may have some contamination in
it that
seems to be prevalent but in
what
there's evidence that the
actual flu
shot could make you very
susceptible to
this and she explains how this
works
because it sounds very familiar
and even
worse the vaccines for
covin 19 the vaccine that would
target
directly SARS Cove 2 has been
studied
some since the original SARS
outbreak in
the original MERS which is
Middle East
respiratory syndrome outbreak
since that
time the vaccine development
has gone on
and in every case and in every
study
there the vaccine actually
drives the
death by by literally turning
on the
fire they you know exploding
the fire of
the immune the overreaction of
the
immune system
that is what we call the
signature of
disease it's that inflammatory
cytokine
storm and and the vaccine
itself can
drive that storm such that it
if you are
reexpose it can lead to rapid
death yeah
by the way as I'd listened to
that clip
I'm reminding us I didn't
record it but
they're talking about actually
I do have
a clip they see if I can find
it it's
the clip that says because I was
watching this clip as they were
doing it
this is the not the source of
mutants I
wanted to get unto that but
mystery cord
allowance can't find it
instantly but
it's they show that they're
working on a
dr. Britax dr. bright ignored
maybe no
no they're working it no that's
an all
right they're working on a
vaccine
and they did their showing they
say
human testing has begun I don't
wish I
had this on here
human testing has begun and
they show
some poor poor schlub shot of
something
human just go goodnight damn
thinking
what maniac is signing up for
this have
you ever even listening
alternative
media I'm serious I'm like
screaming at
this guy screaming at the
television so
that kills the kill shot from
from dr.
Mike Ovitz and then you know at
least
you know what's going on but I
think she
puts a lot of reputation on the
line
here for whatever she has left
he's
written several books about
this about
this topic and how she was and
it has a
lot to do with money and
patents and and
this this cabal of foul Chi and
Burkes
lieutenant commander Colonel
Burks
ambassador and Redfield from
the CDC
these and and bright all these
guys have
been are been around with Gates
Foundation I mean it's great to
see
pictures of pouchy and Burks
without and
John at the AIDS gala I mean
they they
these are celebreties they are
very big
in their world but along the
way we've
seen or as the doctor will
Chronicle
there's been a lot of cover-ups
and
lying to push agendas and get
things
that don't work to work so
people can
make money there's a published
study
from 2005 about the effectivity
the efficacy of
hydroxychloroquine that
a foul she is a he he's aware
of these
studies it's his own its own
group of
the government that's done
these yet
when it comes to this
particular illness
no no no it's now it's just
anecdotal
evidence I believe they did
some fudging
on the numbers or change some
the the
test goals to push the remedy
severe
through and of course
ultimately it's
all to really have nothing that
works
well in the people's mind then
the
vaccine which is inevitable the
push is
real but she feels that doctor
foul she
should go to jail do you think
that
doctor thought she played a
part in
kovat 19 then you
think that he should be held
accountable
or responsible or criminally
responsible
for the corruption with covet
19 or even
tracing back as far as 30-plus
years oh
absolutely
he should be held criminally
responsible
all the way back to the spread
of
hiv/aids through the country at
the same
time he did the same thing he's
doing
now in koban 19 that is prevent
the use
of therapies like
hydroxychloroquine or
type 1 low dose type 1
interferon alpha
or any number of natural things
prevent
people you know from doing the
appropriate testing the FDA
didn't do
the appropriate serology
testing that
that would have shown that in
fact we
know the virus had been through
this
country earlier than thought
and we may
have actually had in many
places a
natural herd immunity that
isn't it
occurring with the lockdown and
that
people aren't being who are
being
prevented from you know even if
they
were exposed from from getting
the
disease with prophylactic
measures
that's preventative measures
like
hydroxychloroquine and and all
the same
time promoting drug use in
research in
clinical trials which he's also
doing a
similar thing to what he did on
what he
directed to be done in the case
of the
XM rvs that's that's fraudulent
studies
that that show you know that
that a drug
works when it really doesn't
work and
how they manipulate the study
design and
in order to you know to drag it
out so
and and then because we're not
developing a natural herd
immunity the
the amount of disease and death
that's
being caused while while people
are well
he's promoting measures that
that not
only don't work but it cause
literally
the devastation of our economy
and and
and we won't even be able to
count the
number of deaths from people who
couldn't get adequate care for
things
like cancer and and and
cardiovascular
disease just simple care for
things that have nothing to do
with Koba
19 i demand an investigation
yeah you're
gonna get an investigation
alright
you're gonna get an
investigation as to
why they fired the move
dr. bright is gonna be done by
Adam
Schiff alright alright let's
get into it
fat Jerry Adler yeah that's
where your
investigations going cuz
already they're
talking I don't let Dad even
want to
switch subjects had some other
sub today
but let's talk about the bright
guy
emerges CBS clip this is thing
we talked
about this guy week at months
months ago
this guy got kicked out of the
he was
bitching and moaning about
using oxy
chloroquine and chloroquine
which nobody
uses and he says they any and
just
listen to the this idiot listen
to these
two clips this is the bright
gyri
emerges as dr. bright Gary oxy
chloroquine and chloroquine he
just
decided he could no longer
remain silent
learn bright has agreed to
testify on
Capitol Hill next week and he
hopes to
get his old job back tonight an
HHS
official says that he was
transferred to
a critical role at NIH and they
are
disappointed he hasn't shown up
for work
which I'm gonna call him that
because
the following clip this clip is
this the
doctor burse under dr. bright
ignored
his term democracy now - just
kind of
set it up this is a Darrell
course all
in because this guy was wrong
we let's
start with this premise he's a
government worker not
necessarily the
best known in this field for
anything
he's just the guy is running
this one
this very small branch of some
very
small branch of another
division and he
is what I've seen these guys
I've worked
in the government long enough
to run
into guys like this everybody
in that
governments are running
cover-your-ass
memos and they're just that's
what you
do you do just in case and so
this guy
is just really a nudnik out of
the blue
there's nobody's ever heard of
him until
this he's made this big fuss
and now
they're gonna bring him in for
so he can
testify against Trump basically
even
though Trump doesn't know
really what's
going on I don't think well
let's play
this clip and I yeah i'll tell
you
what's goal
me about this and instead to
award
lucrative contracts based on
political
connections in other words I was
pressured to left politics and
cronyism
drive decisions over the
opinions of the
best scientists we have in
government
dr. bright also says he
repeatedly and
urgently demanded action in
January to
address the looming pandemic
including a
critical shortage of personal
protective
equipment for doctors like n95
face
masks but was ignored it was
ignored
because he's like most people
in the
government you're ignored
because
everybody's bitching and
moaning about
one thing or the other so this
guy going
on I was ignored that was
ignored that's
what he's gonna testify against
I wrote
a memo on January 5th saying we
don't
have enough and why would he
even have
anything to do with n95 face
max the
stats how many there are what
the
hospitals have it doesn't make
any sense
but okay I was ignored I wrote
this man
when I was ignore all you wrote
this
memo was and you were ignored
nobody
said anything yo well my boss
has told
me to stop writing memos it's
just
ridiculous this guy and they're
gonna
make a mountain out of a
molehill as
best they can try to impeach
Trump again
the end and so the theory is
because
this guy wrote a memo which was
ignored
thousands died is that it and
that's the
idea
blood on your hands yes exactly
just briefly on the testing you
know
testings ramping up so and and
I am
still surprised how many people
are so
poorly informed that they read
in the in
our local news here at Austin
oh we have
you know 60 new cases oh my god
there's
a stay in sight no no listen
we're
testing more and it's good news
the more
people who are asymptomatic aliy
infected the lower the actual
chance you
have of dying you had have more
information but the tests are a
problem
and I think one of the one of
the main
points of David Ickes theory is
that the
test is for a just a corona
virus but
not necessarily the kovat 19
creating
corona virus
and we know from dr. Mike Ovitz
that
there were positive tests on
people who
had they were supposed to have
had AIDS
which they didn't they had
these excess
XMRV virus mouse crap in your
in your
veins but the tests are a real
issue
this is only a report you I'm
sure you
won't get this on the mainstream
you won't from Reuters so take
that for
what you will coronavirus test
kits used
in Tanzania were dismissed as
faulty by
President John Magoo Magoo Fuli
on
Sunday he said they had returned
positive samples and he is a
chemist by
the way that's why he ordered
it so they
had received positive samples
positive
results on samples taken from a
goat and
from a pawpaw which is a fruit
so both the goat and the pawpaw
tested
positive for kovat 19 I mean
I'll even
take the goat but you're gonna
tell me
that's a fruit tasty fruit the
proper
you should have heard what the
goat had
to say about the whole ordeal
yeah so
and and and now I'm in contact
with one
of our producers who was
working with
antibodies and tests and this
lab person
has told me that there's been
some
issues getting you know the
right I
guess they'll you need the
spiked
poached protein or whatever and
they're
different labs from overseas it
may be
India it could be China I mean
this I
can't get answers to everything
because
of secrecy and NDA's and things
and so
it's hard to get full info but
I finally
just said is it possible that
whatever
the hell they're sending you is
just not
really the right one and that's
something that our producer
could not
answer is no way to know that
so there's
a lot of you know because you
can put
perhaps the AC e to Trump is
right we
got to bring the stuff back
here we
don't know what the hell is
going on
it's crazy a scammer
starting to give our own
scammers that
the cash exactly and with that
I'd like
to thank you for your courtesy
in the
morning to you the man who put
the see
in social censorship John C
Dvorak Linda
Marni UMich Adam curls in the
morning
ships to see boots on graphene
the
aero-subs of our dams the
nights out
there hey trolls in the morning
to you
y'all let me see how many
trolls we can
count today we've got 1570 it's
a
Thursday it's about right
almost 1600
you could you two can be a
troll and you
will feel right at home if you
live
under a bridge currently but
it's really
nice at No Agenda stream calm
you
control along they've been very
helpful
this morning actually handed
some
one-liners and ideas and
thoughts where
we take the conversation and of
course
some people just a holes and
they troll
no agenda stream comm go there
hang out
with your fellow friends excuse
me you
can also get an invitation
there it's
free for no agenda social calm
so then
you can hook up with our little
part of
the Federation in addition to
that it
big in the morning to comic
strip
blogger whose artwork was
selected for
the episode titled the beaches
are open
episode 12 hundred and thirty
nine and
this was the Apple logo pooping
out
location apparently the the
there was
some scatological joke with the
government because they are the
ones
receiving the information from
Apple and
it was the it was good I don't
know why
it wasn't the best was it was
the best
but there were other choices
didn't
quite make what happened
something it
was one that was the best oh
right I
remember what it was when we go
in and
take a look unfortunately it
was it was
two rulings by Darren who just
must have
been beside himself with the
chuckling
to himself you know behind the
mic he
see these guys picked this it
was well
done
why can't I find it now and
that's
interesting hmm did it get
taken off
well we had the you know what
we had the
comics different one from
comics or blog
or we might use this dead the
other one
I actually come a strip blogger
got a
twofer cuz I gave him the I put
that on
the newsletter no nice the
other one and
but this other one I was almost
tempted
to use the lewd oh we liked
well we like
Tommy the heretic with
operation warp
speed which was cool because it
was a
syringe like the Starship
Enterprise
yeah it was well done
but then he had a but a female
too but
we long with the thong it's
like no it's
just put that in there well I
mean we
don't mind a good-looking but
but it's
good but if it's gratuitous
necessary
but j-- it was just not no
wave this
buddish belongs on this art so
they got
kicked from it for that just
from that I
can't find the one that was the
other
one that was so offensive it's
still
there I can't find him no no I
think and
I think it got removed oh no no
I
remember I remember what it was
it was
the best piece of art and and
even we
could I don't think we could
discuss it
well yeah I can just tell you
what it
was it was a Kentucky Fried
Chicken logo
turned into Joe with Biden
instead of
Kentucky Fried Chicken it was
Joe Biden
president finger lickin good
and now yeah we felt that was
not
appropriate
no and Darren no he knows that
he knows
that it's not purpose just to
see if you
get went through I mean is what
you
always do creative types are
always
trying to sneak something
through oh
yeah you know it doesn't fly
with other
creative types who know what
you're up
to
yeah like it's like Disney you
know
trying to hiding penises and
snow white
dress and stuff like that and
we're on
to get talented artists there
let's
start with thanking a few people
including oh do we have a
little theme
music for Dave do you know I
don't think
I mean we don't have one
special forum I
don't think do we Duke of
America's for
heartland and the REA bein
Peninsula and
Gladstone Missouri well he's
not there I
think he's still in Saudi
Arabia that's
six 66.6 six he always has a
note that's
interesting dear ma kettle and
mother
Teresa you know which ones you
are today
I learned that and Jarvis the
woman Lara
largely credited for creating
what we
now know as Mother's Day later
become so
disgusted by its
commercialization that
she boycotted it and tried to
suit
companies who were profiting
off the
holiday no jingle the more you
know Oh
No Agenda anyways since I
become I
recall that I was one of the
two ish
producers whoops sorry I was
one of the
oops what do you what are you
opening
about why hit that I hit a
button on
here and it took the whole
screen off
did you drop your your your
knitting a
lot of censorship control-z
brings him
back doc there it is
control-z it old control-z i
was one of
the two ish producers who
supported
their mothers the past five
years she
had to I think that's right I
figured I
should continue my yearly habit
with
another one six 6.66 in the
traditional
number associated with
others I guess being that but
got
inconclusive data donation
represents
22222 for each of day melody my
mom
Pauline and Melody's mom
Yolanda the
best mom's a guy could have in
his life
if you got a good mother-in-law
you got
it man you do I really hit the
jackpot
when it comes to mothers and I
love you
all a Mother's Day goat karma
for all
the mothers out there please
and thank
you for your courage
damn thank you for your courage
and yes
indeed it is Mother's Day and
typically
on the no agenda show there's
no love
for moms but the tide might be
turning
you've got in the morning
and comfort comes in from
Indianapolis
Indiana with $333 here we are
sitting on
the deck of the Sunday
afternoon during
the quarantine my wife asks
well this is
thought this was his wife this
is an
okay maybe they're married did
they're
married women could be my wife
asked why
are you freeloader why are you a
freeloader it's embarrassing we
had just
listened to the no agenda
showing you
were discussing the highlights
I quickly
told her she made her point
after 41
years of marriage you learn
stuff like
that then I came up with the
idea to
make her a dame ah here's the
beginning
of our tribute to reach that
goal we
also ordered awesome no agenda
masks a
couple of weeks ago like and
like Adam
are still awaiting their
arrival get
these masks out well that's not
just so
you know that's not no agenda
shop it
was a different mask and I'm
regretting
it as I should have just gone
for the
Gator from the shop it was dumb
I should have J paint something
everybody for every order for
every when
you mention something here I
want to
explore this we could have
custom
painted no agenda mass this is
a huge
premium yes we could we could
all shed
that clutter yes what else is
Jay doing
she's just hanging around the
house no
she's up no she took a drive
with Nick
up to the Washington even
better they've
written their historical boxes
off laws
apparently now I'm exempt I
could do
these yes we can do we are we
are we are
podcasters by law exempt your
essential
personnel so if anybody's a
podcaster
and making a big stink about
staying at
home then they're just virtue
signaling
cuz we don't have to stay at
home or do
anything but after wear a mask
in a
store obviously because they're
gonna
kick you out but besides that
anyway
please give some jobs karma to
the
people negatively affected by
quarantine and deduce my wife
so she can
hear that's true keep up the
good fight
and thanks from
by cub be luckily Kurt's
circle black our future game
swanee
Bleeker Blackard Bleeker black
art
lacquered I'm not familiar with
this
name that's definitely
interesting all
right
yes of course we can do that d
douching
first of you you've been
deduced jobs
jobs jobs and jobs let's vote
for job
you've got karma alright so
that was I
guess that's France this is
good future
Dame swanee very nice time a
Khmer hen
333 it's funny there's no 33333
s that's
weird I TM in 73 from Terrell
kx4 mq 73
his former producer of the
business the
business poland for CNBC in
poland all
right
oh good for you as a former
fight m5 am
i can say you guys are spot-on
he has a
great name your analysis he has
a great
name ty McMahon and everybody
how you
doing ty your timing man yeah
that
should be a radio job yes you
probably
is keep up the good work the F
that's
right v FV works all value for
value the
I'd like Adam to call out my
buddy LAN
as a douchebag okay in Dutch
and English
okay I'll do it in Dutch I'll
do an
English first and then in Dutch
I
douchebag I was in the mouth by
Sir
Tripp Mazurek of Memphis four
clips
I'd like a Trump Pelosi jobs
karma with
a goat scream for everyone
trying to get
back to work
amidst this cluster of a mess
73 73 see
you kilo 5 alpha Charlie
Charlie jobs
jobs jobs jobs jobs jobs
and jobs let's vote you thought
was a
former member of the m5m he's
going to
enjoy that clip from Kaley
that's great
coming up in the second half
yeah sir Rock so Raleigh of
Weybridge in
London 333 another 333 this is
interesting
hi G I'm John and am sir
Raleigh of
Weybridge here died due to some
failed a
relationship karma requiring a
name
changed to of Crystal Palace
let me just
lay over the concrete dinosaurs
and if
possible
oh uh but do a name change you
want to
write it down this donation is
in memory
of my father he was a Vietnam
vet who
met my mother in London and
moved to
Northern Ireland where his
unique skills
and weaponry in war served him
well cool
in the Irish Republican Army
what what
he always taught me to question
our
governments agenda a lot of
stories I
dismissed his paranoia crazy
old man but
lo and behold more and more of
the there
skullduggery has been revealed
he would
have loved your show anyway this
donation is from some shares
cashed in
from a company named ITM so I
thought
you'd better get your cut I
just would
like a goat karma and an F
cancer for my
mum thankfully this is one
karma that
has worked Cheers
yes and I will officially
bestow the new
title upon you you turn from
sir Rolly
of Weybridge to sue Rolly of
Crystal
Palace layer of the concrete
dinosaurs
on the way
[Applause]
you've got all right drew
sampled
322 72 jingles he's got we're
gonna die
we're not happy yeah this and
it's true
you can do that he wants three
times I
don't know if you want to do
that or not
it's up to you first off I'd
like to
thank you for your twice weekly
dose of
sanity it is needed more than
ever I'm a
small-scale urban farmer in
North Linden
Columbus Ohio when our douchebag
governor decided to shut down
that
state's restaurant for dying in
all all
of my income disappeared huh
making the
high-end food for the
restaurants of my
small this is guys Cano so did
you make
it I just would ask him just
rhetorically did you make a
switch to
get to sell directly to the
public cuz a
lot of people did that for meat
and
produce is you know that there
are
billions of pounds of potatoes
and if if
they gave it that they can't
that are
just gonna rot if they could if
they
gave it all away I was reading
they gave
every single potato away to the
food
bank which serves two million
people
each person would have to buy
500 or
have to take home 500 pounds
that's how
many potatoes there are that
just really
produce a lot of potatoes we
have this
is a disaster his resort by the
way
where this I'm in need of more
than ever
and more than ever of some small
business car might also like to
offer
home deliveries for microgreens
to the
No Agenda producers in both
Columbus and
Toledo metropolitan areas if
they're
interested they can email me at
Capital
City Gardens all one word
capital city
Gardens at gmail.com as capi
tal garde
City Gardens okay or a contact
made drew
sample at No Agenda social com
ah no
drew sample note I recommend
people do
this and give this guy some
some direct
income second I would like to
thank both
Alex Bell and just more for
hitting me
in the mouth at our
pree no agenda meetup brunch in
April of
2018 I am looking forward to
hosting a
meet up after the Covent
insanity is
over for this donation I'm
going to use
1216 of my donation to D douche
my
smoking-hot girlfriend Corsica
please
oops what's her name
Corsica Lynn you've been
deduced I call
out Jacob Ramirez and new
listener
Nathan Fraser as douchebags
thank you both again for
everything you
guys do please give small
business karma
to all the other small business
who are
sharing my pain in the no agenda
community have you got it
use the sequins you've got
karma we have
a lot of Ohio listeners I
should make
help this guy out
we do this a couple of them
just by out
every I mean by a bunch stuff
for your
friends no nothing like a good
small a
small provider of green classy
little
green like yes Scott part
porter becomes
our first associate executive
producer
$250 with today's donation i
have
reached knighthood I'd like to
be known
fourth fourth known as Sir for
died they
could be fourth known as Sir
Scott of
the High Plains I'd appreciate
some jobs
karma a Trump Pelosi combo and
Merkel's
Arbeit I don't know if we had
it all
about
do we have Merkel with our I
still miss
the Delta Sierra Charles Delta
Sierra
Charlie yes daily source I'm
sorry yeah
that would be the district
source code
or whatever yes yeah daily
thanks daily yeah Adam Carolla
hosted
that surely you know I'm the
pod father
him and Ricky Gervais Saul
those guys
yeah well Gervase is the pot
father and
I'd not Corolla you're getting
mixed up
I don't have that I don't know
what the
the Arbeit are but I don't
remember it
or bite the are by to our bite
yeah but
I don't have
yes I remember it but you can't
find it
well how was it labeled it was
either
Labor's are you I'm assuming
already
looked at Merkel and Arbeit yes
can't
find it's just the way it goes
I said
that's exactly the problem so
what he
does want is Pelosi Trump jobs
karma and
we'll start it off with a
little bit of
Merkel for you
jobs jobs jobs jobs jobs jobs
and job
[Laughter]
job I see Sir
Joe be one of a week Apple
weekapaug
think 247 16 I can't thank you
enough
for continuing in the info
segment I
need some jobs cover for me my
wife and
all the out-of-work all out of
workers
affected by this pandemic lady
karma is
a dental hygienist and it's
very nervous
about returning to work in such
a high
exposure profession working
inside
people's mouths everyday I also
potentially I'm switching jobs
doing
these during these crazy times
and some
Wow have to convince my current
company
to utilize me by paying my new
time to face up my Browns face
have to
lace up my brown shoes
[Music]
can I get a title change for my
lovely
wife she also wishes to be lady
karma
Kara lady kara of the clean
tooth
instead of Lady Kara of
weekapaug you
want to put that I got it it's
down it
was already on the list she's
good in
regards to that my previous
note my name
is not Joe bisexual John did
you say
that I don't know it's possible
now no I
did make it did make me laugh
to hear
you say it and Adam I thought
you were a
pothead but you were confused
at my
roundtable request of sticky
green
doesn't that prove your point
a kind of a I guess it's been
almost 30
years since the term was first
popularized by Snoop Dogg
lastly despite the running
belief of the
show I indeed love my mother
but the
chances of her listening to any
product
podcast I'm okay with not that
it makes
a little more sense it's not
that she
their mom's hate the show
those boys those boys are just
gonna get
into trouble the way they think
now that
is a good mom voice and so that
would be
the rationale we're using but
but what's
the podcast is probably the
real reason
okay so such an ageist old man
aren't
you oh yeah absolutely
well thank you Joe bus se and
the change
will be made you got it and he
wants his
name changed to Joe bisexual is
that
what he wants I don't think so
okay all
right onward with anonymous 200
bucks
what could be better to give
from my
locked down self than my finally
attaining knighthood from the
best
podcast in the universe's world
goes
completely nuts I seek the
sanctuary of
sanity at the No Agenda
roundtable on
behalf of both me and my
amygdala thank
you I would like to ascend from
anonymous in San Francisco to
captain
Luke Knight of the Barbary
Coast mm-hmm
please play the classic fear is
freedom
followed by it's true followed
by
boom-shaka-laka and then
provide covet
karma for all for all for the
round
table I'd like to add ghurabaa
and
manicotti okay hold on a second
I need the
this one I didn't have where
didn't we
have Corona karma I'm pretty
sure we had
that Corona I don't recall it
personally
but I'm not to keep her at the
karma
yeah let me see if I can find
this real
quick cuz you want because we
don't have
Co vid karma we had Karuna
karma well I
guess I can't find that one
either then
just feel it's got a stupid I
should be
able to find that and then we
only have
one eye yes anyone's gruff
Monica the
daewoo yes I'm working on
trip
all right if that's what you
wanted you
got Corona that's what he gave
it David
Walsh and Gold Coast Queensland
$200
that's in Australia hi John and
Adam I'm
David Walsh from the Gold Coast
ql'
Queensland Australia to
celebrate my
10th anniversary of listening
to the
greatest podcast in universe I
figure I
get off my arse which is what
they say
in some countries including
Australia
arse and complete my knighthood
I have a
long message plan but decided
against it
so I'll summarize it was longer
than
this follow jcd here and after
listening
to him on twit I did take a 2.5
year
hiatus from 2015 in mid 2017
due to my
amygdala shrinking so much that
it
became cynical and day and
jaded with
everything if that's a danger
that is
that is a real danger some
people have
that and they just they because
it once
there explodes these guys I
could do
this on my own I don't need any
hand-holding thing is this is
like a
part of like how Hollywood and
the other
media work you have to it has
to be
collaborative even means one of
us could
do shows yeah between the two
of us it's
the same thing yeah we can't do
the show
it we could but it wouldn't be
as good
and we'd be making mistakes
constantly
and it would be it wouldn't
work out as
you know and we wouldn't
definitely get
on just the kick that we're on
of
correcting people's use of at
the end of
the day look at things like
that because
you know you hear it on
television all
the time just distressing and
so that
includes the audience the
audience is
the third element of the of the
collaboration and so it all
works
together and that keeps you
ever from
you know that's why you
shouldn't stop
which is a minor which is why
it's obvious that we all
produce this
show it's a it's a it's a tribe
effort
he continues by saying I think
it was
over the Obama era I have been
far more
entertained in the Trump era so
you as a
voters please go he's in
Australia we
got to remember that yeah so
USA voters
please keep him in for another
term it
makes me smile to see the media
go nuts
I wish to thank you for your
courage and
wish you all the best of year
for years
to come and uh so all the
listeners pony
up for a subscription even five
bucks a
month helps jingle trains good
planes
bad train FOMA the whoo-hoo
listen to
the horn Karma for all
listeners and
producers birthday it's my 46th
and may
6th please add me to the list
you're on
the list
knighthood names her dame of
the Gold
Coast sir day was my root
username
assigned to me in 1998 on a
FreeBSD box
please regards okay graduate
you have
sent to MIT for yes yes these
nuts
always uh David wash PS your
non-us a
listeners use the date format
date month
year use the date format date
month year
and so I feel like you miss out
on some
good numbers yes there's one
coming up
that if you reverse it against
the
European yet we usually we can
do that
we'd do it once in a while I'm
sure you
have thought about it though
and I would
like to raise it just in case
PBS all
money in USD I do appreciate
the gesture
to match Aussie and Z Canadian
he's got
south african dollars bucks
though i
just thought that means iran so
it's
gotta mean something else i
know what
he's talking about anyway so i
thank you
for the note I think southern
Australia
Disney from southern ass no
he's from
the gold buy OC it's southern
Australia
it's not they're using
different money I
don't know who knows you don't
they are
chewing gum underneath the shoe
of China
who knows what I do know thank
you very
much David and we'll see you
later on at
the roundtable all aboard
[Music]
you've got karma Sonia bozan
Burgin
Madison Wisconsin jingles rub
Eliezer
and the old the old donate to
no agenda
in the Gregorian chant style
which we
need to use that more in the
end of the
show
request combo health and
relationship
Karma for my son thank you for
all your
continued hard work the BS is
getting
thick out there and having you
guys
makes me able to turn it all
off love
and light
so the rub Eliezer number
station and
what else
oh the old donate to no agenda
or the
Gregorian oh geez I wasn't
ready for
that one starts over the snare
drum
that's not it I got it here we
go no
agenda they give us the speaker
we don't
want it too but no agenda is
the show
that's really unique donate to
a no
attending ah listen to Don and
Adam
speak to the horn a to a no
agenda
science is turning into a leak
you've
got karma
that's our Gregorian monks
right there
and that's the our producers and
executive producers right there
associate and executive and
associate
executive and how everyone want
to put
it want to thank them for
making this
show possible this is show 1240
and they
this is a very generous of them
and we
appreciate it yeah it helps us
go for
the next show which will be on
Sunday
yes thank you very much we are
still
continuing and it is because
indeed of
these people who have fresh
titles as
they can now proudly display
them as
either executive producer of No
Agenda
show episode 1240 or associate
executive
producer if you're looking for
a job a
lot of people will be I think
things
will stand out and stuff like
that but
also the knowledge that you
actually add
John you're just explaining
this is not
radio this is something
completely new
and you can call the podcast
but it's
different when you have the
audience
actively participating in it
you call it
the the third leg what are the
other two
besides us the other two
besides us a
third live or there'd leg one
were their
lives okay that's right yes so
together
we are all three I gotcha
kickstands all
three you are our kickstand and
we
appreciate it we also
appreciate to
everyone who was supports the
show by
producing a buy donate will be
thanking
more of them in our second half
and
please remember we will be back
on
Sunday to do it all over again
with
whatever else comes out we'll
be there
to hold each other's hands and
yours
just go to to Vollrath org
slash naa and
remember
is Michael bitch whose object
our
formula is this we go out or
hit people
in the mouth
what
[Music]
went wrong here today
okay sorry about that it's my
eye man I
can't see I have a couple of
series play
here I wanted to place as there
first of
all I think let me skip to
something
that's a little lighter the
they're
trying to scare us with this
meat
shortage things that can make
us freak
and I want to just point out
that of
this show weeks ago we had a
producer
from a meatpacking outfit give
us some
very clear warnings that this
was coming
yeah it's coming it's here yeah
and of
course they're doing what they
can and
Trump did an executive orders
they want
to keep the meat flowing but so
they did
a report on CBS Nora and I want
to play
this is the intro to the report
and then
she kicks it to one of our
reporters to
do that you know the stand-up
this meat
shortage tonight grocery giants
are
putting a cap on how much meat
customers
can buy as the pandemic forces
more
processing plants to shut down
and at
hundreds of Wendy's restaurants
managers
are asking that famous question
the ad
campaign where's the beef I
like that
you say meat must flow it's
like liquid
meat so she goes on and on and
then she
cuts it says and so-and-so is
gonna
report on this and this they
bring it to
a guy who goes on about the
Tyson he
starts reporting on the whole
thing and
then right in the kind of right
that the
judge sees as he wraps it up I
would bet
money although they would never
admit to
this but ABC does this all the
time and
they're very obvious because
their time
perfectly there's a native add
not
dropped into the middle of this
report
just right at the point where
you want
to hear it and I don't think
it's gonna
help sell anything but if this
isn't a
native ad because you got to
remember
they're talking about all the
closures
and this is he's guys wrapping
it up and
this is it and as a sign of the
times
the impossible Foods Company
announced
that it's impossible burger
which is
made with plants will be
available in
2,700 grocery stores nationwide
starting
this week and it says it's
ready to
expand to meet the growing
demand
Nora well this would be one
heck of a
battle and if the meat guys got
defeated
by that the only thing that was
left on
the shelves during actual
pandemic where
people possibly could starve
they didn't
buy that crap they didn't so
they throw
this little gem at the end and
I'm
thinking I wonder what they
paid it's a
15 second ad it's just a spot
cheaper
and 15 second has to exist
that's J and
it's just like oh brother I
just rolled
my eyes I killed the rest of
the report
anyone play anybody's wanted to
play the
native had to point out that
these guys
are douche bags oh yeah
oh yeah no you know who are
douche bags
the news reporters at home who
have the
Apple earpods
in their ears Oh doesn't work
doesn't
look like you got cigarette
butts
hanging out of their head it's
not a
good look I can't get over it
I'm like
then they will have won have
distracted
like why only one you know why
didn't
you want to and can you hear
yourself or
what's going on it's a dumb
look look
most of the looks and sounds
from these
at home guys in the beard to
grow in a
beard and all the rest are in
the books
they got books behind them all
the time
that looks smart Knoll thing it
there's
some it is so odd that people
think
that's a good look with books
his books
rarely look good in the
background
they just don't well I would
like to
death I was doing this I was I
was
working for me I would do one
of these
desks that is just an
outrageous mess I
wouldn't have to do a lot
exactly just
turn the camera on you're done
yeah I'm
good to go I could do it like
you use
this my little studio set here
and have
this Gong in the background and
do it
here's a I could have a couple
of these
crushed cans yeah mm-hmm got a
couple
crushed can you just look like
a you
know like you're just hanging
out
I have you know I just I'm s I
think
that's the way to go no one has
the guts
to do that do you have you have
crushed
cans just in case in your
studio well
here's what I know I have these
these
Pellegrino cans and I crushed
them and
then I noticed that they were
good for
if you were good little devices
for
making more sounds and I was I
told you
this before I thought just to
make a
good Geiger counter sound that's
actually pretty good Geiger
conscious
you you have you have these
things since
the Geiger counter comparison
the cans
have been there yeah I can't
right here
sits in the sound effects bin
you are a
special individual Jhansi
Dvorak you are
a special man interesting
article that
showed up but I think it came
well zero
heads they always have some
kind of I
like how they pull stuff think
you got a
link out of them though they're
good for
headlines but apparently
Reuters is
reporting that the Trump
administration
is getting ready to release
plans to
initiate a pact among several
nations
our allies for mining the moon
and
there's going to be a so it'll
be a an
international agreement that it
will be
called the Artemis Accords now
Artemis I
think is the name of this
mission or the
name of the of the next of the
next
mission to the moon yeah I have
so much
trouble believing all this I
mean 50
years ago we landed a tinkertoy
wrapped
in tinfoil on the moon it's
since then
we have we went from a phone
that if you
if you touch the wires it could
actually
shock YouTube a phone that is
now a
supercomputer in your pocket
that the
advance is the Internet all
this stuff
why isn't Elon Musk already
spinning
doughnuts on the moon in his
Tesla I
just don't understand what
happened and I wonder if we're
ever
going to get to the moon again
anyway
that's all I had to say on that
okay I
think that's valid as a valid
opinion
yeah I wanted to play these
three clips
because this is the media is
losing
their kind of their people are
interest in kovat oh no got to
bring
them back in the fold so let's
go with
this one this is Nora opens
with mutant
virus-- Wow
hold on a second where is yes
got it as
we come on the air tonight
coronavirus
infections are still growing in
much of
the country just as we're
learning there
is now a more powerful mutant
strain of
the virus that is even more
difficult to
treat there are now more than
20,000 new
confirmed cases every day here
in the
United States and while cases
are
declining in the New York City
area the
epicenter of the crisis
elsewhere the
rate of infection is rising
still 44
states are moving forward with
lifting
restrictions and tonight
President Trump
is acknowledging those moves to
reopen
could lead to even more deaths
telling
reporters today that Americans
should
quote think of themselves as
warriors
okay couple of things first of
all the
way she does that report it
makes it
sound just 20,000 new cases of
the
mutant virus term mutant virus
whoever
put this this story together
had her
read it across information so
she went
from one subject to another
she says the difference I want
you to
play the beginning of this
again and
listen to this where she is
claiming if
the waves just listened to her
that
there's 20,000 new cases of the
mutant
virus as we come on the air
tonight
coronavirus infections are
still growing
in much of the country just as
we're
learning there is now a more
powerful
mutant strain of the virus by
the way
mutants drain mutant strain of
the
viruses that is even more
difficult to
treat there are now more than
20,000 new
confirmed cases every day here
in the
United States
and while cases are to the
right of
course of course
this poor copy never follows up
on the
information so I have an old
herbs clip
from democracy now this is this
the clip
is called source of mutant
strain a new
study finds the novel
coronavirus that
emerged in China mutated in
Europe in
February to become more
contagious
speeding it's spread around the
globe
the report from the Los Alamos
National
Laboratory also warns the
mutated strain
could leave people vulnerable
to a
second infection of kovat 19
the finding
has not been peer reviewed and
the
director of the National
Institutes of
Health
urge caution saying the study
draws
sweeping conclusions about the
virus
that might not hold up to
further
scrutiny the authors of the
study said
they release the study early so
that
people who are working on
vaccines could
see their results what this is
Lamy
people working on vaccines can
see their
results this is bullcrap
stretch this
out a little more well if you
can't do
it with the new do I love the
way Nora
pronounces mutant mutant yeah
you can't
whoops there goes his effort
well how we
doing seven cars yeah it was
really late
that is effort is hours late so
that is
not a good sign we would like
to see a
solid nine cars is a stable
good economy
eight is made is ok it's ok
we've had a
ten in the past seven I mean at
least
it's running it may be late but
it's
running happy about way they
weren't
gonna be so late
okay so here's it's not bad
enough that
the mutant just drained the
virus is
gonna kill you try this one
mystery
kovat children's disease now to
a
mystery illness that's putting
otherwise
healthy children in the
hospital more
than a dozen children in the
New York
City area have ended up in
intensive
care with severe symptoms
possibly
linked to corona virus all this
as
parents start thinking about
camp and
school here's our chief medical
correspondent dr. John
Pook 14 year old jack McMorrow
loves
music and video games two weeks
ago a
rash on his hands quickly led
to a fever
of over a hundred and four
degrees he
was rushed to the ICU and tested
positive for kovat 19 john
McMorrow is
his father his heart rate was
over 160
it was the scariest point in my
life I
do as nothing anyone can do it
he
prepared me for the worst Jack
finally
responded to steroid treatment
and
doctors continued to monitor
his heart
function at Morgan Stanley
Children's
Hospital in New York I'll have
a very
fast heart rate they'll be
they'll have
a high fever and if their heart
rate
still stays very high they will
oftentimes come to the ICU for
extra
support researchers are now
investigating COBIT cases like
Jack's
and the symptoms of a
mysterious illness
it resembles Kawasaki disease
the New
York City Health Department
sent out an
alert last night describing a
pediatric
multi-system inflammatory
syndrome
symptoms include persistent
fever rash
swollen lymph nodes and
inflammation of
the heart eyes mouth and skin
hmm all gonna die yeah or at
least the
kids will know anyway that's
kind of
distressing jeez
uh here's what we should do I
think
there's always time in fact
more and
more people are interested in
our our
way of living these days and we
should
start with the tracing and
tracking apps
mentioned earlier hmm I wish
we'd have
seen something out of South
Korea by now
what is the point if it's only
to alert
people and throw them into
quarantine
maybe we could learn something
there are
people who are positive walking
around I
mean release some data please
yeah maybe
we'll get more from Kanda
Naevia Alberta
has launched its tracking and
tracing
program go big nineteen remains
a threat
but there's a drive to get out
to get
back to normal
well AHS says there's now an
app that
could help providing this
information
voluntarily is crucial to our
work to
prevent the spread of kovat 19
Alberta
trace together is the first
contact
tracing app available in North
America
every time users pass one
another their
phones record the encounter
using
Bluetooth encrypted data will
be stored
on the phone now if one of
those users
tests positive for kovat 19 the
user can
upload their interactions to
AHS and a
contact tracer would call the
numbers
the phone registered telling
them to
self isolate like bringing a
camera into
focus these techniques give us
a far
clearer picture that helped us
to inform
our actions going forward now
the app
stores only phone numbers no
locations
it doesn't use GPS but tracking
still
raises privacy questions
Alberta's
Privacy Commissioner says she
has been
involved and she supports
enhanced
contact tracing in a statement
she adds
in my view Alberta Health has
chosen a
less intrusive approach in
deploying
this app
okay what is happening is in
every
country the app the same
conversations
being had apps are being made
and
governments are telling their
citizens
you need to give up some of
your privacy
so you can do so you don't die
and
pretty much is everyone's going
along
with it yeah that's right
sounds right
to me
in the Netherlands literally the
government is in the newspaper
this
morning and an interview with
some
muckety-muck and said I'm
translating on
the fly well we'll have to know
everything and we'll probably
even have
to know who you're who your
secret lover
is but don't worry we'll keep
it secret
that's the headline because of
course
they're gonna know who your
lover is
because you want to be around
that
person singapore's these phones
are good
for Singapore is going to
require
smartphone check-ins at all
businesses
and will log visitors identity
numbers
but that of course is Singapore
so
that's kind of to be expected
what I
think they're doing wrong is
there and
they're calling it tracing and
tracking
and you and they we've done so
well
we've done social censorship hey
everyone understands that we
have social
distancing I would recommend as
a
representative of the creative
or a
consulting group social
surveillance use
that too I don't like the word
surveillance I would I would
not that I
think social surveillance I
think it
will work I think not again I
don't like
to I think you're onto
something here is
to come up with the term and I
think the
two of us can do it but that's
not I I
like the social part of it yeah
unless
so no social social must be
good let's
look at some synonyms okay
synonyms for
okay Luthi social sleuthing we
could
also use let's see contact
social
snitching oh that's a good one
I like social
hissing yeah you like it okay
we got
inspection mm-hmm
monitoring is no good I don't
like that
either I like inspection
supervision is
a word that's kind of a synonym
spying
and espionage those are out
social
supervision
no one's good no one's gonna
fall for
that bit superintendence no no
no no
that observation social
observation
mm-hmm
yeah that's getting there
that's that's
new or new world order how
about social
supervision that's what I said
oh I
missed it I didn't hear that
one that's
pretty good then social super
VIP mm-hmm
what made me work on it trolls
aren't
helping us socially no they're
no good
you haven't graduated the top
podcast
spot we can do this we can come
up with
the word that means
surveillance which
is what we're talking about
maybe you're
not it being surveillance or
what's the
other one they're doing in a
spying
snooping snitching how about a
synonym
for tracking maybe there's one
there how
about this for an idea how
about doing
what they like to do in
Washington where
you change that just change the
titles
of the bill means it's nothing
like the
title yeah you could do that
but how
about social awareness we do
something
with that okay let's start with
let's
use the word awareness but put
it at the
beginning
so it'd be awareness um not
awareness
monitoring I don't like that no
where's
my social awareness protection
okay I
think we've you know what we'll
we'll
come back to the to the
brainstorm a
little bit later on we'll work
on this
well we will get it meanwhile
companies
are also creating their own
social so
I'm just going to use it for
for now
social surveillance inside
their own
organizations several organs as
this
according to The Wall Street
Journal
several organizations
are going to be tracking
location within
people within corporations
within the
building to make sure people
here the
company aims have its social
distancing
app ready at the end of May
workers
movements are tracked through
their
smartphones and you get a
higher score
the more time in the office you
are
farther than six feet from
another
person so they've gained the
phone in
the drawer they're gonna get a
raise no
you have to be around people
but it has
to be six feet so you're
standing up on
your desk in the cubicle
yelling at
people oh man oh by the way I
you know I
had this desktop machine in the
studio
which really runs runs lubuntu
in a
virtual machine but we were
scanning
some documents yesterday and
this then
the window side of that
computer is
still configured to this or
when the
scanner starts it sends it to
that
machine and it's fine that's
good but
then I had to email that to to
myself
and to Tina and I so I fire up
Outlook
the machine does is maintained
it's a
continuously updated with the
Windows 10
you know virus that comes in on
Tuesday
to update it for your
experience and I
got a new experience as I found
out
Outlook is now part of
Microsoft 365 and
a part of 365 for a long 12 but
a window
popped up telling me this and
told me in
order to send an email I had to
send I
had to log into Microsoft 365
so now I
just want to use Outlook no no
and so
and I tried to click new message
no it's grayed out yeah you
can't do
that what are you trying to do
you're
trying to foil the way this is
working
I thought Outlook was outside
of that
you could use it for free I
didn't have
to pay for outlook you paid for
that's
old Outlook Express oh no no
well I don't know what happened
but I
don't like having to sign into
Microsoft
to you to send an email yeah I
don't
blame you i wouldn't do it i use
squirrel mail no it's not gonna
we know
what you use
I am fully back to mutt I map
filter and
VI baby I love it and then
finally this
is a hot off the press I do not
believe
it has it has been mentioned
anywhere
yet but there is a class-action
suit
that's been filed against plaid
networks
for selling people's bank
information to
third parties illegally and
it's a class
action this could be now that
it's a
part of visa with all the all
the
different venmo and all this
stuff that
fits in that that's connected
through
the plaid network into banks
and just a
reminder plaid sits in between
your
venmo app or your cash app and
there's
many more to make it easy for
you to
access your bank account you
give that
app your login and password for
your
bank account I know you've all
done it
and then that app logs in as if
it's you
and then acts as if it's on the
website
as a person and can make
transactions
but can do anything it wants and
apparently it has been so this
should be
they would sign up for
something like
this well you people don't know
they're
signing up for it because they
sign up
for venmo when they think okay
I'll just
put in my bank password and I
can trust
VIN Milo you keep the bank
password to
anybody else's soft millions of
people
have done it
milah I don't know why they
would do it
they'd just be forbidden yeah
people
should they need to be taught
in school
in high school yeah yeah not to
do that
don't give your bank password
to anybody
I always got a kick what was
that
software that came out some
years back a
there's like about eight years
ago it
was some sort of it managed all
your
money and it did all these
crazy things
and it was like and it required
you to
turn over your bank pass well
there's a
number of these their plugins a
lot of
Millennials use them and that
it'll
manage you'll say oh I can get
you a
cheaper deal on this and looks
like
you're paying too much for your
insurance let me find you a
cheaper deal
because it's
continuously in your account
looking at
your transactions I don't think
so oh
yes what do you mean your right
mind
would give that you have no
idea how
successful these companies are
oh yeah
this should be investigated
Shoop you
hmm all right let's play the
Kaley that
one thing that the one kind of
offbeat I
could say that to the end well
no now
let's fight now do you have the
whole
thing even when the journalize
don't
have to hold the yelling at the
end when
the journalists are yelling at
her at
the end yeah all right all
right so this
is Kaley taking a question now
I'm
thinking this woman who I like
she is a
little bit over made out but
it's just
funny yeah but I like her
because she's
not putting up with any bull
crap and
she decided you wishing me that
we're
gonna to see if she has a
pattern here
but I think the pattern would
be the
following I think this is what
she
should adopt somebody has a
snarky
question that's got nothing to
do with
anything it's just a stupid
snarky
question so you answer it with
a blast
that you have pre-prepared
because you
know that you can see the
question
coming you have it pre-prepared
and then
because it was a snarky
question and
because you blasted them you
finish with
a big blast and you leave the
room I'm
out of here folks I'm here all
the way
can walk out on him and that's
what she
did previous life before you
were press
secretary work for the campaign
and you
made a comment I believe on Fox
president Trump will not allow
the
coronavirus to come to this
country
given what has happened since
then
obviously would you like to
take that
back well first let me note I
was asked
a question on Fox Business about
president's travel restrictions
I noted
what was the intent behind
those travel
restrictions which is we will
not see
the coronavirus come here
we will not see terrorism come
here
referring to an earlier set of
travel
restrictions I guess I would
turn the
question back on the media and
ask
similar questions does Vox want
to take
back that they proclaim that the
coronavirus would not be a
deadly
pandemic does the Washington
Post want
to take back that they told
Americans to
get a grip the flu is bigger
than the
coronavirus which is the
Washington Post
likewise want to take back that
our
brains are causing us to
exaggerate the
threats of the coronavirus does
the New
York Times want to take back
that fear
of the virus may be expressive
spreading
faster than the virus itself
does NPR
want to take back that the flu
was a
much bigger threat than the
corona virus
and finally once again the
Washington
Post would they like to take
back but
the government should not
respond
aggressively to the corona
virus I'll
leave you with those questions
and maybe
you'll have some answers then a
few days
so what you didn't hear at the
end we've
got cut off right the end one
of the
journalists was yelling you you
you were
prepared for the question how'd
you know
I think I watched I would got
decided
the actual press conference
yeah it's
right at the end and I never
heard that
wait might have heard that I
was left it
on well I'd see it's
interesting because
I heard it and I saw you had
the clip so
then I decided not to clip it
but you
can hear that question right
the last
thing you hear are you're
prepared yeah
which she was obviously so
that's kind
of fun to show the press corps
that they
have leaks as well it does work
and
ravit reverse because she
absolutely
knew that was coming she didn't
hesitate
for a second on that no she
went right
to it
she had a page of all the notes
so well
the hostility has started them
with her
that should be interesting I I
was not I
expected her to get steamrolled
and I am
clearly wrong and we'll see how
she does
I looked at her background I
didn't
think so she she has one of
those she
has a certain mean girl style
that is
usually can take it and she's
smart if
you look at her background
she's smart
so she's a smart mean girl this
is not
that somebody you're gonna be
able to
blow blow away Lucy well at
least we
have a different setting you
know at
least someone else is answering
some
questions a little tired of the
president and it's hanging
chads but the
media is theirs it's kind of I
guess
it's been happening for a while
but I
only put the two together and
realize
that there's a new style in
news opinion
shows although they appear on
news
networks specifically CNN and
MSNBC
though these are news news
outfits and
and it goes like this you talk
to the
president for some reason these
Talking
Heads now believe that it's
they should
be telling the president what
to do and
there they're looking into the
camera
and
looking to the president have
you seen
this Don Lemon does this Don
Lemon and
he did a very interesting one
the other
night
and I just went up it's 45
seconds but
you can he's looking right in
the camera
and it's just yeah I saw that I
didn't
clip it by should've that you
this is a
good clip what is it about
President
Obama that really gets under
your skin
is it because he's smarter than
you
that are educated
made it on his own didn't need
daddy's
help not bathing at all
wife is more accomplished this
is the
kind of thing you don't say to
a guy's
face you could beaten
better-looking I
don't know what is it what is
it about
it he's a black man that's
accomplished
any president Wow
and he punked you on the whole
or a
certificate thing what is it
about him
just wondering
this is a very odd thing he's
doing but
I believe it's very successful
with the
audience he has I think they
like it I
think they really dig that he's
doing
this I think it brings a new
audience
though I mean them no no no
they're
locking their audience down and
the
audience is small yes it is
it's about
half of MSNBC which is half of
Fox
but speaking of MSNBC Morning
Joe is now
doing the same thing and
Morning Joe and
this is just a minute but it
went on for
five six minutes is talking to
the
president obviously Donald you
didn't
want to hear that again I know
I've been
saying it a lot and you
actually tweeted
something extraordinarily cruel
he's
literally talking as if he's
talking to
someone on a video chat it's
very odd
and meek is going like like
diamond and
pearl oh yeah mm-hmm preach
yeah you go
I know you meant to be
extraordinarily
cruel to me by attacking me
that is
leaking my god diamond itself
you were
supposed to have a working
weekend you
got it wrong again you said
50,000
deaths 60,000 deaths now you're
saying a
hundred thousand deaths what
was your
working weekend what did you do
during
your working weekend well you
know you
tweeted more hateful things
about
colleagues of ours you tweeted
conspiracy theories about
Jeffrey
Epstein will you have time for
this you
tweeted conspiracy theories
about Barack
Obama will you have time for
this
you attacked George W Bush for
simply
sending out a unifying message
just
president I ask that you get
checked out
I ask that you take a rest I
ask that
you take care of yourself and
maybe let
Mike Pence run things for the
next week
you're not well it's a very odd
form of
journalism that is taking place
well
it's obviously not journalism
as these
guys that they think so highly
of
themselves they feel obliged to
do this
and everybody wants to be wants
to
editorialize I mean you can go
Lionel's nation if you want to
hear this
sort of thing
from Lionel the crazy lawyer
who likes
to scream at the camera yeah
and he's
got some very good rants on
there and
he's holed up at like in his
basement
much like Biden is in his
basement the
it but they're more
entertaining than
this because the guy knows what
he's
doing
I had this reminded me of the
clip of
morning in America which I
don't have
the whole thing I do have I
have the
Democracy Now report of it and
this is
that group the Lincoln project
oh this
is the George Conway's George
Conway and
so at a me the way she
structures her
her commentary on this she
thinks this
morning report is great because
all
these smart Republicans hate
Trump and
then of course she uses the
word lashes
out and then she gives an
example at the
end which is not Trump lashing
out at
all in fact this whole lashing
out thing
with Trump is nonsense but this
is a I'm
gonna play this clip this isn't
a me
talking about the but a that
includes a
small clip of mourning in
America and
then she reads a trump a trump
tweet
yeah I don't know if these
people know
that these tweets are extremely
funny
and but they see him as like
some
negative horrible thing and I
think
morning Joe was everybody hates
these
tweets yeah here we go
President Trump
is lashing out against a new
advertisement by a
republican-led group
called the Lincoln project
calling out
his mismanagement of the corona
virus
pandemic the one minute ad is
titled
morning in America spin on
Ronald
Reagan's 1984 campaign slogan
there's
morning in America under the
leadership
of Donald Trump
our country's weaker if we have
another
four years like this that
morning in
America ad spelled mo you are
in NJ in a
series of angry tweets posted
just after
midnight Tuesday morning Trump
attacked
the makers of the ad singling
out George
Conway longtime Trump critic
husband of
white house councilor Kellyanne
Conway
Trump tweeted quote I don't
know what
Kellyanne did to her deranged
loser of a
husband moon face but it must
have been
really bad Trump tweeted he
said that
before but to hear Amy say it
is better
[Music]
read Trump tweets is just
dynamite isn't
this just pure controlled
opposition if
you really look at it I mean
that that's
that's I keep thinking this is
controlled opposition I don't
think it
is I think is because that
controlled
opposition really resides on
MSNBC which
is more representative the
Democrat
Party as a whole well Amy may
be a
Democrat she's really a Bernie
bro and
the Lincoln group the Lincoln
group is
real for sure that's controlled
opposition isn't it I mean
there's my ID
but who's controlling the
control
Kellyanne Conway I don't know
maybe okay
this could not be a healthy
relationship
I don't there may be something
to the
theory that this is all planned
and
controlled because - he's
insulting
Kellyanne and George in that
little
tweet in a funny kind of way
calling me
a loser and you know your
husband you
don't to hit if you work for
someone you
called somebody calls your
husband a
loser moon face moon face loser
of a
husband I don't know maybe I
find it
amusing
I like that the tweets are
funnier than
that stupid morning in America
thing
it's morning in America and
there's
thousand points of light
I was I was shocked I will say
shocked
that Project Veritas comes out
with the
big news with undercover video
and voice
altered witnesses that CBS
faked a shot
Oh No
yes I'm shocked shocked this is
so what
a waste
so the and I got a minute from
their
from their teaser report well
just
listen to it this happens five
times a
day at least you're telling me
you're a
hundred percent certain that
CBS News
CBS News Corporation national
staged a
fake event they fake the news
they faked
the reality and broadcasted
that to all
of their audience last Friday
on CBS
this morning only six states
have
reported more cases than
Michigan but
fewer than 2% of its people
have been
tested for the virus in our
series on
the state of coronavirus
testing Adriana
Diaz shows how Michigan is
trying to
improve a system that has
failed some of
its people but the governor
says testing
above all else will help
determine when
to fully reopen
all right so the whole report
is this
bad and and what happened is
they were
going to do a shot of a line of
cars
waiting to test to be tested for
coronavirus and there was
almost no one
there so CBS arranged a whole
bunch of
fake cars and patients and of
course
sadly there were some actual
people who
were waiting for about an hour
because
of the shenanigans who really
were
patients to be tested yeah I
drove past
the Berkeley testing thing
which is that
no cars zero not even one car
was gonna
drive through it just asked him
a few
questions I should have when
you brought
my little camcorder but this
Veritas
would like the heartbeat music
you know
women that one woman who I can't
remember her name but she does
a bunch
of videos on YouTube but-- she
did the
expose and showing all these
the day
before shot you know all these
people
lined up the ambulances are
coming in
the next day a bunch of locals
yeah here
we go it was unbelievable we
went to the
site of the CBS news crew there
lining up cars but they weren't
cars of
patience no there were cars of
endurance
they were manipulating the
media to make
it look like there was a lot of
people
being tested this was false we
have an
eyewitness
[Music]
come on he's insulting me it
would have
been better if it was like then
all that
course they were all driven by
the dead
and that is exactly why we are
non-commercial we don't have to
do dumb
crap to get people to watch or
pay
attention I'm gonna show my
food by
donation to no agenda imagine
all the
people who could do with us oh
yeah
that'd be fab
[Music]
but one thing we have to do is
thank
those who helped us get show
going and
that's a pleasure that's the
best the
highlight of the show for me
often it is
especially with Joseph Salazar
in in
India Atlantic in the Atlantic
where's
that in Florida
I don't know but she does have
a call
out I want to call out Doogie
fresh as a
douchebag claymation uh the
corona
survivor can you please tell me
the show
number where clips of the Johns
Hopkins
virus pandemic walkthrough
meeting book
took place if you can get a
chance go to
the show notes explain how to
do that at
him yeah go to any show notes
talk to
him look it up look it up yes
and look
it up damn it
there you go yeah just shown us
and
there's a search engine you can
look up
are well you know what I'm
sorry to say
the search engine has been
abandoned by
its developer oh yeah being at
dot IO
I've redirected that there
there is
another place that's pretty
good if you
if you actually go to being at
dot IO or
Rona radio.com there's and
there's a new
no agenda it's actually no jet
experience it's just a
placeholder but
there's transcripts in there
you can
search very easily just you
know fine
control F in your search and
then you
click on that link and
immediately it
starts playing on that word so
it's a
search and it's a player
all-in-one
can't beat it
not really and the point is is
that we
don't know what when they're we
ran it
we do we don't do that we know
we're not
archivists in that sense we
have these
systems we provide all of our
data in
structured format opml it's
available
the show notes and everything is
available and people put that
together
can create great things except
we are
developer just lost interest I
guess
and as of January 1st it hasn't
been
updated now oh poor thing
Christopher kessler's next on
the list
from Marshfield Wisconsin $124
Casilla
uh Grizz gizelle scott grisel
Skye think
an effort Pennsylvania - one
two three
nine nine I think it's true
isn't like a
grizzly grizzly kheh
Davers like a Drake yeah it's a
tough
one shut to run into a
pronounced
theater David Drake in
Midlothian
Virginia 1 2 3 4 5 Daniel
Walraven 1 2 3
4 5 and I'm Hoeven ball R album
Daniel
wall actually from his wife he
says
after hitting her in the mouth
for
months well thank you Daniel's
wife no
anonymous in Colorados spit
that must be
Colorado Springs mrs. Collins
100 101 Meredith Talbot 100 my
fianc
brandon loves your show he
planned to
donate to become a knight but
he passed
away oh my god for 2120 please
accept
this donation in his honor okay
Oh Meredith no that's terrible
well we need emergency karma for
Meredith and and all the family
this is
horrible news and thank you
very much
but Wow
sorry sorry about that you've
got karma
to probably say love and light
stuff
like that he would get a
chuckle out of
it
they probably Serb even our or
Biba knew
her not sure he's in East Berlin
Pennsylvania $100 it's got a
birthday
coming up he also has he has a
call-out
for butch
huh yeah I see the becau Dutch
bags he's
got written under and Andy says
value
for value got it you know he
got an F
cancer call I would put that at
the end
for you
I was friend Ryan who also
recently lost
this lies battle with cancer huh
and he says Jen yeah Genosha
Moser on
Frankford I'm on main $93
Deutschland
mm-hmm
ally Breedlove in Columbia
Virginia 85
Deana Isabel got a birthday
Sisters
Oregon 6033 mica Meyers and
Brennan
Bremen Alabama 600 six me
Meghan Kendall
in Sandy Utah 58 85 got another
birthday
a lot of birthdays today yeah
Danny load
juice us watch South Australia
I thinks
of Cork I don't think she's in
Cork in
Ireland 55 55 and has a
call-out I would
like to call out mark Romans as
a douche
bag douche he's been listening
for a
year and to my knowledge has
not yet
donated I've been keeping an
eye in the
sale for his donations but
haven't seen
any and that is a Dutch ism
keeping an
eye in the sale an okay oops I
oversee
louder
talking about Dutch yep
jean-paul de
loja delahaye in Burford dis
Slaven okay
in bright dis laughing Bev
right like
dis Lavin which is actually not
a place
he just tricked you into saying
free the
slaves you tricky Dutch Steven
Shevlin
in Southampton teased by the
way he's in
for 5555 Steven Shevlin in
Southampton
Massachusetts 55:20 Sir
Christopher
Baron of Brown County Green Bay
Wisconsin 5510 and I'll bet you
that
your quarterback are you gonna
lose your
quarterback sir Shonda Santa's
knight of
the northern Everglades Fort
Pierce
Florida 5510 lurid michael
gates baron
of the rest of Colorado in
Colorado
Springs 5280 Jason Dean in Mesa
Arizona
51 51 Justin and he's got a
birthday
Justin Boots in ski in Mishawaka
Mishawaka Indiana
51:23 Jason de Lewis sir
Jason deluzy on chat stirred
Pennsylvania 50 and these are
all $50
donors from here on out name and
location starting with Jason
then
baronet sir lineman of the net
Raleigh
Hawk in Anna Illinois Glen
Graham sir
Matthew Janiszewski who's been
with us
forever
you know Christopher Rivera in
Austin
your buddy in Austin Texas
Edward
Mazurek and Memphis Tennessee
brave
bread Brady
Schroder in Milton Georgia and
marry Hui
a great name Scott Grice in
Starkville
Mississippi sir Jonathan Mayer
in Xenia
Ohio and last but not least
Jeff Neff Oh
James Neff and I was just
looking for a
rhyme James Neff in hanover
pennsylvania
in n3i ln 70
he's a man over I want to thank
all
these folks for making a show
for 1240
worth doing thank you very much
well
worth doing yes thank you to
all of
these producers and to the
producers who
came in under $50 that's a sure
way to
keep your name off the list
because
that's what we cut off for for
mentions
for anonymity but also there's
many with
these subscriptions the plans
that
eventually get them tonight the
hood and
Dame hood and it's extremely
important
if you can to do one of those
it has to
base that keeps us rolling
throughout
the high times and the low
times and
thank you again for all of your
courage
we will be here again
on Sunday you can support us
please go
to to Vollrath dot org slash
and and
some jobs and Kent F cancer
requests
here we go jobs and jobs let's
vote for
job karma
[Music]
again the right side the
jingles icon
can't see out of that eye right
here we
go here's your birthday is
today being
of course the seventh of May
2020 we say
happy birthday to David Walsh
she
celebrates tomorrow sir be one
hour says
happy birthday was smoking hot
girl my
wife Carrie she turned 42 today
Dennison
Dennehy Sibel a happy birthday
to her
husband who's turning 60 Meghan
Kendall
to the love of her life John
Kendall 35
tomorrow and finally Jason Dean
says
happy birthday to his son Ryan
he'll be turning 20 tomorrow
happy
birthday for everybody here at
the best
podcast in the universe
[Music]
[Applause]
for title changes today for the
patrons
lady Cara of the weekapaug
becomes lady
Cara of the clean tooth with
her new
occupational hazard job and sir
olya
Weybridge not become sir Olli
of Crystal
Palace Slayer of the concrete
dinosaurs
and we have one - we've got
four or know
what we have three three
knighting for
today so we've got a Rona blade
at my
three first sword here you go
wait a
minute
yes ok I got it let's go
[Applause]
all three if you are about to
join the
illustrious club known as the
No Agenda
nights and names of the
roundtable
because of your support in the
amount of
$1,000 or more and we are very
very
proud to pronounce the Kate you
guys sir
Scott of the High Plains
captain Luke
Knight of the Barbary Coast and
sir Dave
of the Gold Coast for you
hookers and
blow
red boys and Chardonnay grappa
and
manicotti rabbit meat and goat
milk
brown cheese aquavit
and smut a whole bed dices and
tock a
vodka vanilla vodka gin bourbon
sparkling cider now scores gin
trailing
Charles breast milk at pablum
Reuben s
woman in Rose a the mutton and
the mead
it's always here it is a round
table
favorite and thank you for
supporting
the show is great and really is
it's
unexpected often well but
please go to
no agenda nation comm / rings
and give
Eric the shill all your info so
we can
get that to you as soon as
possible I
have one important topic for
for these
remaining moments we have and
it's an a
dose related topic American
descendants
of slavery this came up on the
mo show
and of course it didn't hit my
Twitter
and didn't hit your Twitter but
this is
about a move in the political
space or a
move at a movement and we've
been
tracking that the Democrats
need the
black vote they lost some of it
I think
not a a substantial enough
amount during
the previous election that it
made
people pay attention but as you
know
there are a lot of African
American
descendants of slavery who are
considering not voting for the
Democrat
Party doesn't mean they're
voting for
somebody else but that they
will no
longer hand over their vote
without and
here the key words to look out
for
tangibles like give us
something that's
really for us or reparations I
would say
that is that as the big ask and
it's not
being listened to it's not being
discussed Joe Biden came out
with his
that Biden for black America
plan which
believe it or not mentioned the
word
reparations and but it was in
the
context of doing another study
to see if
what what should be done who
should get
it so that that's not gonna fly
we need
more studies but did he came
out on he
was doing which is funny if you
know did
he but he was on a livestream
with Naomi
Campbell some kind of Rona
let's hang
out together and do a zoom video
everyone can participate in and
here's
what he said the black vote is
not going
to be for free we're gonna have
to see
some promises you know what are
we
getting in return for both and
nothing
has changed for black America
and in
order for us to vote for Biden
we can't be taken for granted
like we
always are because we're
supposed to be
Democrats or because people are
afraid
of trouble this weathers going
to take
care of our community whoever
wants to
make a deal it's business at
this point
you know we can't trust
politicians you
know so we want to know very
clearly
just like Trump made it clear
that he
wanted to build the wall the
body needs
to make it clear that he's
gonna change
the lives and quality of life
of black
and brown people obviously
can't get the
boat I will hold the boat
hostage if I -
he said it here said it first
breaking
no no no Diddy is no stranger
to to the
voting process he's done a lot
of a lot
of campaigns over the years
people do
listen to him he's no slouch
I think it's they should be
worried
about him
I got a lot to be worried about
yeah
yeah maybe I should be I don't
know what
they're gonna do I think about
this is
like what are these guys gonna
do they
got this they got it they got
the
country on a you know just
beaten by
this virus and shut down
everything that
I mean that that's weakens
Trump's
position but then they've come
up with a
candidate like Biden although I
think
it's you know you could point
out that
most the people they're gonna
vote for
but bite him don't even know of
what a
bumbling idiot that he is
because they
don't get to see those clips
because
they won't show them to him to
mainstream media is all in for
bite into
Democratic bigwigs are all in
for Biden
and they just hoping for the
best
they're hoping for a fluke and
then of
course the peel die and the the
vice
president become president so
that's the
first you got ready to keep an
eye on
did you see the I don't think
any of
this is gonna happen to be
honest about
it I think it's gonna be a
one-sided
slaughter and Biden's out did
you see
the New York Times opinion
letters to
the editor and this was Joe
Biden and
Tara Reid whom to believe and
the
letters to the editor included
I mean
this is the one they published
the New
York Times published these
letters to
the editor and you know it was
very
clear that Ted there's you know
you
gotta listen to something's
going on
here so we have to investigate
this
thank you for this editorial
for the
record I'm a lifelong Democrat
and we'll
vote Democrat this fall
regardless
defeating Donald Trump and
saving our
democracy is the most important
thing
however we do still need a full
transparent investigation I
totally
agree with this editorial I
don't want
an investigation
I want a coronation of Joe
Biden would
he make a great president
unlikely would
he make a good president good
enough
would he make a president
better than
the present occupant absolutely
I don't
want justice whatever that way
maybe I
want to win the removal of
Donald Trump
from office and mr. Biden is
our best
chance by the way that's Martin
tulchyn
who was a former reporter for
the New
York Times and they published
it with
his name and it says the writer
is a
former reporter from the New
York Times
well they probably felt obliged
to do
that because of the disclosure
stuff
they like to do that's crazy
and so
there's probably two here's who
had the
discussion when you're in the
minute you
know you're putting it just one
person
usually the actually the editor
does
take part in some of these
letters
because they like to slant the
perspective and so they have
this
discussion this oh this is a
great
letter look at this he slams
Trump to
all things isn't that one of
our old
writers oh shit
just pull this one and run a
different
one now you know I kind of like
it all
we have to do just put the
disclaimer in
there that good letter that we
wanted to
put it in there no one's good
nobody
reads us is gonna think
anything about
it
whereas anybody who is not a
normal
stood for the time to think
what it kind
of corruption is this why don't
you just
have the editor write-up phony
letter to
herself or himself sorry yeah
well I got
some news I got some news
mm-hmm I have
a well I got a kind of a kick
out of the
well here's the well here's
that except
I wanted to play earlier in the
show
this is the New York dead and
the
vaccine this is the one I was
cringing
his twenty-first second clip
okay CBS's
Milegi is gonna lead us off
tonight in
New York City mola well Nora
well deaths
in New York are down
significantly from
their peak just a few weeks ago
we're
still losing more than 200
people a day
to this virus so many that
bodies are
being stored in makeshift
morgues like
those white refrigerator trucks
that you
see behind me there and that is
why
there is so much hope in this
experimental new vaccine that
could be
ready by this fall up with it
I'm
cringing watching this clip oh
brother
okay so my end unless you have
something
for the industry I got two
clips I've
finished things off I just want
to know
what commentary I would just
like to run
through one bit of information
then both
of your clips are good to go
now I have
one bit of information and the
clip then
you're good to go
will that work Zion fine okay
bit of
information why Michael Flynn
remember
we asked this question why was
he so
data theories are rolling yes
well this
is from our military
intelligence who
knows Flynn personally I can
attest to
that
this is Agent Orange and he
says here is
why it's a one to five point
list one
I'm glad that he's chimed in by
the way
yeah one he knows what happened
in Libya
and how Hillary Clinton moved
weapons
from Libya to Syria when she
was running
the state two
- he knows how Ukraine played
of em and
this is verbatim he knows how
Ukraine
played a vital role in supplying
moderate rebels in Tunisia and
Egypt for
the Arab Spring pen three
he knows the lost man pads in
Libya were
repurchased and the CIA gave
them to
Qatar who sold them to the
Taliban that
shot down a US chopper with him
with a
whole SEAL team on him for
heinous oops
for he knows who gave the
stand-down
order regarding Benghazi and
finally he
was going to audit the
intelligence
agencies I think that says
enough that
sounds right I like the whole
list it's
a good it's a good list
anything to keep
us from speculating is a plus
yep and
then this is my final story
where
political correctness and over
socialization has just gone too
far in
my book this is Alaska hated
Alaska vote
by the mat-su borough School
District
Wednesday night did two things
that
removed the New York Times
Learning
Network from teacher resources
and
getting more attention it
removed five
books from the curriculum the
controversial because of words
like rape
and incest and sexual
references and
language and things that are
pretty
serious problems especially in
our
teenage world the novels in
question I
Know Why the Caged Bird Sings
catch-22
Invisible Man things they
carried and
that scott Fitzgerald's The
Great Gatsby
which is one of the top ten
most read
books amongst high school
students in
the nation it's really baffling
that
this is taking place well those
are
seminal books well they've been
taken
out of the curriculum Catcher
in the Rye
which is a very important book
that kids
read no no catch 20 catch 22
not catch
her in their eye catcher in the
wrong
catch-22 catch-22 is a
fantastic course
it's a great book it shows you
the
ludicrous nature of certain
kinds of
bureaucracies
that would be the problem and
then you
have the Invisible Man which is
a I'm
assuming it's the Invisible Man
that
would be a great novel by Ralph
Ellison
yes and ya know this is ludica
they
didn't catch 22 still okay
no catch no I'm sorry I'm get
deep eyes
still okay
yeah but Maya Angelou is not
okay and
the great gatsby because
because of the
great gatsby is minor and I
mean it's a
great book it's a great
structure but
there's always taught in
English classes
for its balance it's one of the
best
structured novels ever written
but it
but in terms of the rape and
all the
rest of it it's like it's gonna
it's not
with the books about okay well
they got
something wrong with him up
there then
sounds like Texas I don't think
so take
that back I'm sorry Texas yes
okay I get
the two clips I wonder if I
meant to
play last night last year I'm
playing it
now this is a San Francisco
protests
over hotels mmm Dookie in
California
medical students and doctors
with the UC
San Francisco do not harm
coalition
staged a die-in outside the
home of San
Francisco mayor London breed
Wednesday
to protest her refusal to
swiftly move
unhoused people into hotel
rooms the
dying lasted thirty minutes to
symbolize
thirty thousand vacant hotel
rooms in
the city that could be used to
how is
the homeless during the
pandemic the
protesters also hold a moment
of silence
for three unhoused people in San
Francisco who've died of kovat
nineteen
so that's because the hotels
have heard
about this scheme and they said
no now
we're not going to do that and
they Bri
does know how to make him do it
they
can't make him do it they don't
and they
can't make him do it so the
whole things
that fell apart that whole idea
now the
last one which is the best flip
aha is
the California beaches clip of
course it
is in California Governor Gavin
Newsom
has ordered beaches in Orange
County
closed after crowds defied
social
distancing rules California
reported
ninety-five
more coronavirus deaths over
the most
recent 24-hour period except in
Orange
County
Scrooge on Republicans are so
you close
those beach of course of course
you're
gonna close that all right well
keep
your social distance everybody
so these
social surveillance can make
sure that
you are good to go and will
take care of
the social censorship and we
will return
here will we guess we'll return
here on
Sunday we will bring you another
jam-packed show no doubt
deconstruction
whatever takes place in the
next two
days and I will do it here from
Austin
Texas where I am it's the
frontier
opportunity zone 33 FEMA region
number
six and all the governmental
maps
remember us that Dvorak dot org
slash n
a in the morning everybody
I'm Adam curry and from
northern Silicon
Valley where I don't know it's
a nice
day and people should be out
I'm John
see tomorrow we return Sunday
right here
on no agenda again remember us
at Dvorak
org slash na until then adios
mofos
[Applause]
oh by the way I should mention
we have
Jesse coy Nelson and a mix and
after the
show on No Agenda stream calm
random
thoughts where's the beef adios
everybody both the mayor and the
governor only had the right to
enforce
the 30-day stay who lives there
now
abusing their power we mean
business and
we are going to shut this down
one way
or the other
don't be stupid
we will cite you and if we need
to we
will arrest you and we will
take you to
jail
what are you trying to do you
call
yourself a progressive but you
shall
throw yourself to Brooklyn yeah
seriously you guys have a part
you live
in the middle of the park you
don't need
to not essentially travel to
Brooklyn
this is the epitome of
non-essential
travel you're too close to me
to be
especially distant now y'all
can we just
get real do we really care
about our
fans there's this just another
deal
another way socials about the
people
remember we are people do you
really
need another life perish here
so we need
another pose to show up
everywhere I
hope that's read scatter that
we never
forget
then I first live forever even
when we
go to bed
[Music]
give it up merry McCoy
mofo Dvorak dot org slash and a
space
force