Unknown: Those boys are just gonna get in trouble the way they think.
Adam: Adam Curry, John Dvorak is Thursday, May 7 2020. This is your award winning gitmo-nation Media assassination Episode 1200 40. This
is no agenda ready for my haircut and broadcasting live from opportunity zone 33 here, here in the front air of Austin, Texas capital of the drone
stars thing in the morning, everybody.
John: I'm Adam Curry, and from Northern Silicon Valley where I have the exact right amount of clips. I can explain why later. I'm Jhansi devorah.
Adam: Well, I know the feeling when you wake up and everything's there, and you're like, Oh, my God, I have the exact right amount of claps. Yeah. I
the last show. And now we don't play everything. But we came to the party with almost 70 clips.
John: We can't wait too many.
Adam: That's quite a lot. Quite a lot of clips. Yes. Do you want to expand on why it's just the right amount of will that come later? Yeah,
John: what I've did my newest process is I take the clips, and I print them on a sheet on the left hand side landscape style.
Adam: Oh, okay.
John: And so that leaves a bunch of room on the page usually have to have to sheet for taking notes writing down potential bit titles, things like
that stuff. Yeah. Yeah. And when I folded the paper in half, it usually has the clips or there's a lot of little whitespace over there was a it's,
it's perfect. It's like when you fold it in half to create a you know, landscape full peeps piece of paper folded in half the length and everything is
just perfect and fit on the sheet perfectly. Well, this is the exact right amount of clips. That
Adam: is an interesting observation. I have something very similar. I have a window open and it's the Clip Bin. And I toss Mike so I have your clips
in the morning that's in a folder it's closed. But then when that when that bin is filled to the bottom before it starts to scroll, that's my sign
that I have the ideal amount of clips.
John: There you go. This is for everybody out there is fascinating. Inside the podcasters
Adam: studio everybody with Adam Curry and John Dvorak. So we're almost we're on a road to recovery here tomorrow. May Texas in Texas. Yes, tomorrow
may 8. barber shops and hair salons may commence.
John: Well, it's about time.
Adam: Well this through everybody
John: fairly everybody needs a haircut. Oh, do
Adam: I ever?
Unknown: Oh man.
Adam: I look scraggly. Tina's complaining about her about her roots. Well, that's what women do. But I understand. So I immediately texted my, my hair
gal. She's like, well, because this was Friday. Yeah, Friday. We've been totally blindsided by this. We don't know what to do. We're not ready. They
weren't there. I think that the the hair industry was kind of kicked back like, end of the month, whatever. I'm fine. got my hair cut. So I guess we
should immediately talk about the haircut of the Chicago mayor. Which she did, despite actually telling everybody that you shouldn't go to the hair
salon. Here she is. And the whole thing is kind of explained in this clip. If you hadn't heard it yet,
Unknown: Mayor Lightfoot facing criticism tonight after getting her hair done a photo surfaced of the mayor with a hairdresser. But she appeared to
ignore social distancing efforts standing right next to them for the picture. When asked about that photo today, this is what the mayor had to say.
I'm the public face of the city. I'm on national media, and I'm out in the public eye. And you know, I'm a I'm a person who I take my personal hygiene
very seriously. As I said, I felt like I needed to have a haircut. I'm not able to do that myself. And so I got a haircut.
To talk more about that
part of the criticism came from the fact that the mayor had called on people not to go out and get their hair done and one of her stay home save lives
PSA.
Adam: So that pays people off and I kind of liked how she takes her personal hygiene very seriously and it's important to
John: her isn't personal hygiene really involved with washing your hair as opposed to getting a cut?
Adam: Well, maybe it was more than that. For her.
John: You used the word hygiene, personal appearance. Different.
Adam: Yes. What's great though, and all of this is in the show notes, the videos in there as well as in a show notes calm. What's great to watch is
when she's saying that the woman who was signing Next to her is making these horrible faces, you know how they they really do a lot of the expression
when they're signing and, and they and they mimic some of the words and and she actually was looking at the mayor going like he just grimacing her
face like I made Porton was it is something that has to be seen is very, very funny. Once you take your attention off Lightfoot herself. So in Texas
Governor Abbott said okay, maybe these are the the broad announcements may 8 hair salons, barber shops, I think nail salons as well on the 18th gyms,
other types of athletic places, and I think on the 18th and restaurants and go to 50%. So that's moving along, but oh, no, we can't have that with our
mayor Adler here in Austin. No, no, no. Oh, no, this is wrong. Yeah, you know, it's way too early. Of course. How can we go back to Abbott? And Abbott
specifically said you this supersedes everything. But everybody here in Austin wants to have masks on outside. It's 99 degrees. I'm barely surviving
let alone some Coronavirus in the air. It's not happening. So Adler? Well, since he can't find you, he'll guilt you into wearing a mask clear this up
for me. Are we still required to wear the masks in Austin? Or did the governor's order supersede that?
Unknown: Well, the governor's order said that we weren't allowed to have a penalty of a civil or criminal penalty associated with wearing masks. But
yeah, he recommended we were by us the Lieutenant Governor recommended we wear masks. Every public health official that I talked to says people should
wear masks. So in Austin in the city, I'm going to keep it mandatory. Now the penalty for not wearing a mask is that more people are going to be HIV
infected and some people are going to die. So the penalty is now
I'm hoping that people will take this particular penalty very seriously. We should all still be wearing masks.
Adam: Yeah.
John: You got me into two clips. I got a play I was wasn't meaning to play him right away, but I'm gonna play him. Okay. Both about masks. Uh huh.
Let's start with Trump in Arizona. No mass democracy now. Big deal. So reopening of our country Who would have ever thought we were going to be saying
that a reopening reopening.
Unknown: President Trump made the remarks during a trip to Arizona, where he toured a Honeywell aerospace plant that's now producing in 95 face masks.
Trump wore safety glasses but no mask during the tour. Ignoring a sign in the factory ordering everyone inside to wear facial covering, as a Honeywell
executive showed President Trump and 95 masks loudspeakers blared a cover of the song Live and Let Die by the ban Guns and Roses.
material.
Adam: They stoop to this level this is this is like face bag level reporting. Oh my god.
Unknown: Trump also wore no mask during a roundtable discussion to say with Native American leaders at the meeting, Trump promised to send a half
billion dollars to the Navajo Nation which has been devastated by COVID-19. More than a month after Trump signed the cares Act into law tribes still
haven't received $70 billion and promised relief funds.
John: Okay, so that would that leads me to this.
Adam: Can I just make a quick observation about this? Sure. That is Trump's tape. That's the one he plays at the rallies. That's the one with Tiny
Dancer that's the one with an in fact right after he was done at the plant they play the can't always get what you want. And it's not Guns and Roses.
its wings. Shut up. Amy.
Unknown: Amy,
John: Amy, we got Amy that so this came up and this just caught my attention and brought me back to the clip. We just play. This is Kaylee. Our new
secretary. Yes, this is good. She's great. By the way. She is now she's she's real mean.
Adam: I had no I had my doubts about Kaylee McInerney. I'm like she's gonna get eaten alive. She comes out with just tons of makeup and hair all I
mean really hammered on thick because she changes her entire appearance. It really does. She looks entirely different. And then yeah, I thought this
was a great Mic drop mode. This
John: is the Andy one this is the one on masks.
Adam: Oh, I Oh, the master one. I haven't heard the mask one. Okay, what do we got play? This
John: is Kaylee on the politics of math. Now, she doesn't really answer this question. But it brought up an interesting point, which relates to the
fact that Austin's all bent out of shape, Amy's all bent out of shape. And the question is, we do have to discuss this, but you've I'm sure you've
seen in a number of folds, there's a huge difference between
Unknown: democratic To the republicans over whether or not they think it's necessary to wear a mask in public.
Adam: As to why that would be
Unknown: no sense as to why that would be. That's the choice of the American public's choice of individual as to whether to wear a mask or not. But
again, I'd praise the extraordinary work of this administration and distributing those masks and ensuring health care providers on get them.
John: Okay, so she doesn't answer the question, but I did bring up the point. And this point is reflected in all the clips you're gonna get to
Democrats. Oh, we got to wear a mask. We got to wear a mask. We're told to wear a mask, we have to wear a mask, we're gonna kill each other. We're all
gonna die if we don't wear a mask. Yeah, dude, Republicans or Hey, I wear a mask or somebody around and they don't have to wear a mask or a mask. If I
have to wear a mask. I'm not gonna wear a mask. If I don't have to wear a mask. I'm not gonna wear a mask when I'm walking down the street. And it's a
political thing. So this whole thing's become politicized. And the mask is the is the kind of this symbol
Adam: but it was it was ventilators before that not now it's gone. Now it's gone to the next level. And I think I know why. But I'm interested to hear
your further thoughts.
John: I don't really have any serious thoughts. I but I do know that I have a basic thought. I think the democrats the liberals in Canada would be a
good example. They're more compliant. They thought they're more rude. They're rule followers. They can't think for themselves oftentimes, I mean, I
hate to say it, but that just seems to be the case. And they and their virtue signaling. And the virtue signaling is a big part of it. Oh, we got a
mask on. Look at me, I got a mask on. It's, it's a blot. And people still you don't have a mask on? You should have a mask on. They like to lecture
people. Yes.
Adam: It's all it's awesome. Go ahead.
John: I don't have anything deeper than that. It's kind of a shallow Oh, no, I
Adam: like that. It's very obvious besides the virtue signal, which in fact shows other people that you have the same irrational thinking at this
moment if it's outside. Now, if someone has a business, and they want me to wear a mask in their business, fine. I really don't care if I want to get
something if not, if I don't want to do business with them. I won't but outside No, you're not going to shame me in into into any of this. But the
reason for it is also the symbolism of a muzzle shut up slave.
Unknown: It's a mama's letter.
Adam: Yes. I like it. And that's why people who are mad about the whole thing really refused to wear it. I think subconsciously we're like no, I'm not
going to be muzzled by this
John: is a good time. I like this a lot. Thank you. Now I will say that Mimi has a mask that she had made I think Jay made it for which goes over the
nose and mouth and disability limits when the cloth masks was painted. And I recommend people try this. I mean, we do have some matching just buy from
this
Adam: place is she's sniffing she's sniffing the paint is she breathing through this?
John: Now it's just paint. It's got a big red nose and a stupid looking clown smile in two big giant teeth hanging out of it. So it's the stupidest
looking thing you've ever seen. I have to take a picture and put it in a newsletter. I'll wear it it's she won't wear it. She's embarrassed by it, but
I'd wear it and it's very funny and it's like makes it really rich just ridicules the whole system
Adam: as well. But just from I you know I okay I'm biased now because I think of it as it's a really as a muzzle as a I mean there's so much that goes
along with a mask you know, I when people come in an opposite direction for me but also in Texas I smile you know now all you got to work with is your
eyes and I got a really bad eye today's people would always see was a mask and a pissy right eye and they'd be freaked out. But you can have some
blood painted on your chin on your neck like is dripping. I saw commercial yesterday from dole no sense to clip it because it's only text on the
screen masks are worn by superheroes. And they show of course, first responders and nurses and doctors. There is there's another part to it perhaps.
And it's it's purely about the response. In NBC of all of all. They published a poll of which country scores best with their citizens as it pertains
to their response to the coronavirus outbreak. And if you look at the list, and remember NBC Who do you think is the number one country with
Coronavirus response ranking according to Well, this global survey
John: NBC make would probably pick China yep
Adam: 86 Vietnam was 77 then we get UAE India, Malaysia New Zealand, Taiwan, Philippines Indonesia, Singapore, South America, Australia, Germany then
we get the United States Where's Sweden on the list? Sweden is, of course not on the list. But that oh, well, that's
John: interesting is a debt
Adam: that brings up something else. And I do. I do want to get back to the opening up stuff. Do you remember Apple released their data of how many
times people requested directions on the Apple Maps app, which a lot of people emailed me saying, Hey, man, just because they're publishing, that
doesn't mean that tracking is not your personal information, it doesn't matter. The promise was you share nothing, you're sharing something, you're
sharing me touching my screen. I don't like that. But anyway, they publish this data. So I go and look. And you can see it's really about mobility. So
I guess they say if you ask for directions, you are going to travel, they claim they didn't track that part in these numbers. And you see, everybody
has an L, it's the famous l drops down goes boo, boo boo, and at the end starts to tail up a little bit. And you can drill down by count like in the
United States, you can drill down by state, go to Sweden, there's an L. It's not true that they didn't do anything. They definitely had a significant
minus 50% in transit activity. They weren't locked up at home, though. That's what makes it different. And people did it. And I know a lot of
companies did that. So you know, I'm, we're not out of the woods on on if this was a good idea or not, particularly now that New York has seen 60% of
all transmissions occurred were in the home. People at home, giving each other Coronavirus, so it might not have been such a good idea. Anyway.
There's a reason why it's gone full on political so I'm not too worried about Coronavirus anymore. I mean, yes, people will still die there will be
but we're doing a lot of testing. So you see lots of positives, we have no idea if people are being marked up as truly dead from COVID-19 or not
doesn't matter. It's everything's politicized now. So there's clearly no one else in Washington certainly is worried about it. But we have all this,
this these things coming out. Now all of a sudden we have a report that was that wasn't a report, it was a draft created inside the habit here. It was
the Harvard public health school, Harvard, Bloomberg public school. Now I'm saying it wrong. john hopkins, there we go. Johns Hopkins, Bloomberg.
School of Public Health, the same guys who did event 201. Somehow, some internal document from one guy who was himself says in the Washington Post, he
has no idea how that draft model, which was not by any means done or ready for publication, or even the model wasn't completed. How that got leaked to
the washington post that he doesn't
John: understand. And is this the mutant strain memo?
Adam: No, no, this is this is the model that Johns Hopkins Bloomberg leaks to The Washington Post that says the true deaths will be 200,000 in the
United States by the end of June. So everyone started freaking out. And it was all like, that's all it was Monday and all that everyone's going nuts.
Like, oh, we can open up and stop protesting. And Jake Tapper does, I mean, leading the witness. He has Michigan governor Whitmer, who of course, had
huge protests. She's very unpopular. She's been doing all kinds of crazy things, telling people they can't buy certain things in stores has to be
roped off, but it's nuts. So Jake Tapper wants her to describe the citizens who came to protest outside of, I guess the state, the state capitol or
her man the governor's mansion. But listen to how we framed the question is disgusting. These protests came after President Trump tweeted
Unknown: liberate Michigan he tweeted quote, the governor of Michigan should give a little put out the fire. He said that these are very good people
about the protesters that were featured in the video, to which the executive director of the Jewish democratic Council of America
Haley sofa who was from Lansing, Michigan, she compared those comments
Adam: to President Trump referring to those marching alongside
Unknown: neo nazis in Charlottesville as very fine people. Is that how you see these protesters in that vein and that extreme?
Adam: Can you believe that question?
John: That guy is the dead is the douchiest question you could possibly ask. And here's
Adam: her answer
John: and he knows that the dead very fine. People think that relating it to Charlotte is just pathetic.
Adam: Oh, this is exactly what he was going for.
Unknown: It's Phil as very fine people. Is that how you see these protesters in that
Adam: is that Don't tell me just isn't that isn't that come on? Come on. It's not how you see these people don't you think?
Unknown: Well, some of the outrageousness of what happened at our Capitol this week, what you know depicted some of the worst racism and and awful
parts of our history in this country. Sure, the Confederate flags and nooses, the swastikas, the, you know, behavior that you've seen in all of the
clips is not representative of who we are in Michigan.
Adam: No, I didn't see any nooses and swastikas. Please show me evidence of this horrible it's just
John: horrible. It was any swastikas? It would have been a reference to her. Exactly. No serious. Yes,
Adam: I know. But this is exactly what the Nazis did. They locked everybody up took away their livelihood bankrupted the small, the small businesses.
Now, maybe they're just using a couple of tactics. But anyway, back to that to the Bogut of report. It was so bad that Secretary of human health and
services, HR had to come on fox and friends go into the friendly trenches, to disclaim it, which I think he did a really poor job of. Yeah, Mr.
Secretary. And the other question, obviously, this morning, and many Americans are waking up and wondering about is are these various news reports
suggesting there's at least a draft report from CDC, FEMA officials and others, predicting that you and others in the White House administration have
to prepare for the possibility of up to 200,000
Unknown: deaths
Adam: of Americans by June 1, that
Unknown: there's going to be 3000 deaths a day? It's going to be rising? Is that true?
Have you seen such report? And if it's not true? What are you preparing for sir?
So I've not seen that report? I've
heard about it. Obviously, this is there are hundreds of models that are
Adam: it was in the Washington Post? I find that to be an insufficient answer. Oh, I haven't seen it yet. Dude, it was the front page of The
Washington Post. Bad answer.
John: So I've not seen that. Thank you, as you for God hasn't seen that literally have the report in his hands.
Adam: I know. But it just, it comes across as weak.
John: You know, it didn't didn't bother you that way. Man. It I didn't hear anything negative about that
Unknown: dog. Let him finish. So I've not seen that report. I've heard about it. Obviously, this is there are hundreds of models that are drafted up
to look at various contingencies out in the private public health world, as well as within our agencies. This apparently is a draft modeling report of
various contingencies prepared by Johns Hopkins. This was not reviewed by the White House or senior leadership or the task force. The President's
recommendations on reopening the American economy are based on the soundest scientific evidence and modeling and forecasting, not draft initial
projections that just are floating out there.
Adam: See what the problem I have with this is that I don't understand how any citizen This is probably the same around the world with these experts
and and the and the leaders of these different departments. It's very difficult for me to follow what the numbers are, and what the model is. And it's
okay if you change it, but stick to one and say, Here's them not, don't tell me there's all kinds of models floating out there that we may pick from
this one or that one. I don't want to hear that. What are the numbers? Why does CDC have different COVID-19 deaths versus the so called 67,000? I
don't even know where to find those numbers anymore. That chart is just been given away. It's bull crap. You're all full of crap when it comes to
these models. No. need to add inside note all to add insult to this. Neil Ferguson, the man behind the original we're all gonna die 2 million deaths
in America model the man responsible for millions of cattle being unnecessarily killed during Hoeven mouse disease, who was wrong every single time by
a factor 10 on all of the crises, but still we used his model Neil Ferguson resigned from the advisory group because he broke the lockdown rules in
the UK because he knows his bullcrap. It's unbelievable.
John: You know, I broke the lockdown rules, right? Yeah,
Adam: because he had a date with his his Tinder girlfriend. I know it makes it that's very British. Of course. You know, if it's a scandal, it's
always about his penis. We're good at that here too. But what's nicer? The work that has been done independently is a code review of Ferguson's model.
As you recall, this model the 2 million model later revised to 200,000 to 80,000 to 60,000. Now apparently revised backup who knows what was created
using 13 year old undocumented code So the lockdown skeptics, which is a group you can find at thing, it's locked, locked, locked down, skeptics calm,
just check.org, they did a code review a professional code review of what they could and this is such a piece of crap, they can't even run it on a
multi core processor, you have to run it in single thread mode. Otherwise, it doesn't work with the same inputs. outputs are not repeatable or produce
a reproducible. No regression testing after changes. I mean, the whole thing makes no sense. It's very poorly developed. And you can read it for
yourself. I mean, anything I say will go too deep for most, and I'll just sound foolish. But these guys seem like they're pretty Pro. And then the one
thing I can do is I can look up a word. It says, because he this group went back and forth with the Imperial College reviewing the software. And they
said, Well, you know, it's really intended to often provide a very stochastic results. Like what is stochastic? Do you know have you heard of the word
stochastic?
John: Yeah, it's a very, it's used all the time in computer science,
Adam: randomly determined. So the results are randomly determined. They say it right in black and white.
John: You have to remember Bill Gates is behind this is funny.
Adam: I'm not quite sure what it means. But okay.
John: This decoder, luckily,
Adam: Dr. Drew is, is still on the scene we know he is on Fauci sphere squad, but he still has his own opinion. And one of our producers hands over
three short clips worth listening to the first one regarding outdoor transmission of the virus. Dr. Drew's
Unknown: research has shown there's been only one documented case that was in China of outdoor transmission. All other cases have been indoor
transmission, which is interesting. There's also good evidence that the virus dies very quickly out in sunlight. So outdoor looks like a safe place
for us to be. But we shouldn't be outdoors without masking. We shouldn't be outdoors shoulder to shoulder so that seems stupid to be doing that. It
seems silly to me.
John: Haha,
Adam: thank you very much. Masks outdoors. Everybody. Don't walk shoulder to shoulder. Tell us about shutting down Drew, what kind of experience do
you have with that? What is this all based on? Does It Really Work is that the way to go? I mean, seems like everyone got infected at home.
Unknown: The idea of shutting everybody down is a new idea that was developed in the 2006 Bush administration, provisional plan on pandemics based on
a high school students science project. So the idea that this is the way to go shutting everything down. Is is not true. It's not scientifically true.
It may be superior, but we don't know yet. So it may just be that when we go back to masks and social distancing in the world, there will be no uptick
in the cases. So this idea of a second wave may never happen, that we will have some upticks and little outbreaks, but the idea will be to isolate and
contain those outbreaks.
Adam: Okay. There you go. Never been proven never been tested. I'm kind of interested. You know, as we move into the next phase of tracking and
tracing. We're supposed to learn things from that. And I have not seen one report about South Korea if they've learned anything. I would have expected
some kind of information coming back by now. But we continue with Dr. Drew final clip here about social distancing. Everyone's nervous
Unknown: because people are beginning to pile out of their their isolation, but you gotta remember, we don't know that isolation is superior to social
distancing. We don't know that. Now, isolation, certainly superior to nothing. But they've never studied the difference between between social
distancing and masks done properly. And quarantine never been done. So we will find out soon enough.
John: Well, I want to go back to what you were talking about with these models. Okay. There seems to be a this is Chad. I don't know when it changed
or how it changed. And I have a sense that has something to do with the way they're gonna keep us on the global warming tract.
Adam: Yeah, that will that's got to come. But we have to keep all focus on on impeaching Trump with
John: Trump's more important to get MPs course. But if you remember, the last I think is probably the last three or maybe even the last four or five
hurricanes. What They showed the predictions nowadays, they don't just show a prediction. They used to always do that the news guys were the guy who
here's what's predicted to do no. Now they show about 30 tracks. And they show them on the screen on the weather screen this or that could do this. It
could do that it couldn't, yes, MIT says he's gonna do that. Yeah, the western alliance of weathercasters, he's gonna do this. And they have all these
different companies doing all these guys would. That's what the one where Trump took one of the things is gonna hit Atlanta, right? If you remember
that that was based on
Adam: one model, that was the Sharpie model.
John: And so you have all these models now. And there's squirreling around all over the map. It's there's a couple of things that says to me, one is
that this has changed. We've never seen anything like this before. And they could have been doing this for a long time, but they haven't they just
started recently, is because and I think global warming has got something to do with it. Because there's a lot of models and they don't nobody wants
to talk about the Russian model. Right? We've talked about a number of times, which seems, seems to be tracking a very mild increase in temperatures,
and it's got nothing to do with much of anything. But they're getting to the point where they're going to do this because they can date now there's no
responsibility, right? Well, that was one of the models. Yeah. Well, that was one of the most well, that's not them. Yeah, well, there was 30 models
in red. This is the one that happened, it was always the the model, it always works is the is the least complex one, it's a simple one. But they, it's
just absolving themselves of any responsibility of it. So the models models,
Adam: well, along with social distancing has come something new, which is also accepted. And that's social censorship. And I just coined that myself,
I don't know if anyone ever thought of it. But that's really what we're witnessing. Where there is a social agreement, apparently, that certain types
of information should be censored, because it's very dangerous in in our current climate, because we need to listen to the experts with their multiple
models. This is why David Ike has been completely removed. over an interview in where and I've watched it, I've watched all of his interviews and
clips from it. Well, let's go through that. And I'll just preface this by saying what Google and YouTube and I think Spotify, Spotify, remove the
David Ike podcast. Oh, boohoo, this, thank God, we made that shit open people you really think you can you can silence people by kicking them off
Spotify, and it looks really dumb Spotify, but they're all making the AOL mistake. America Online was safe. You're safe with us? Well, we'll give you
this little window with a crappy browser to that scary internet. But you really don't want to go there. Stay with us use a keyword. That's what
they're trying to do is trying to keep people safe and it doesn't work. People want to go out. They want to they want to find out crazy stuff. They
need alternative information. So they're going to leave these platforms. Anyway, social censorship that's in full play.
John: Like Yeah, like your little theory there. Okay, that may even be a show title. I'll flip over this perfectly folded sheet and write it down.
Adam: It's the show notes side of the page. Lovely. Lovely.
John: Now, I talks about let's go over some of this I only have them five gt that's interesting. But then I have another clip. I only have to clip so
we're not gonna bore people. Steven David Ike. But David ickes whole thing. It goes on and on for about an hour about everything we talked about on
this show. Pretty much. And it's not It's nothing new or even. I mean, it's interesting on the show, but we talked about in the show months ago, and
it's so it's kind of like, Oh, geez, David, where you been? Have you ever listen to no agenda? And then he does his little crazy stuff with this 5g.
Now the 5g thing is also misinterpreted. He never says to everyone, like because there was something that went around about 5g is gonna trigger the
Corona, it's out there and then the 5g hits and you get it? No, he's saying that 5g is going to make people sick. And Corona coincidentally can be
used as the excuse Oh, they're sick because of Corona not because of 5g, but I'll play this clip. This is David Ike, of calm story 5g, a government
sensor called off core Office of Communications, which is the regulator of British broadcasters.
Unknown: They have said and it's it's run by a lady called Melanie doors. And we need to note these names down ladies and gentlemen. And when we're
through this, at some some level through it, these people have to be called to account. We have a situation where this lady and her organization which
is a government department, has told British broadcasters and of course they've complied spinelessly As usual, that they will face serious sanctions,
if they allow any discussion on their television stations and radio stations, about any connection between 5g and so called COVID-19. The British
government through this other idiot, the health secretary, Matt Hancock, people are sitting there all over the house is 66 million people in this
country, sitting in the house and doing as I'm told, because this, this guy, you wouldn't let run a, you know, a Lego house. Hancock is saying that
everyone must do that. I mean, what are we doing? Anyway, people like him are now saying to the, the giants of Silicon Valley, he has bugs at
Facebook, your brains and pages at Google and Yo, which housekeys, Google own YouTube, etc, that they should ban people who are making a connection
between 5g and this COVID-19 crisis. So that tells you one, they couldn't care less about freedom, and the right to free debate. Thus, they have no
right to be in government and no right to be running a broadcast regulator. But it tells you something else. Number two, it tells you there is a link
between 5g and this health crisis. There's only one reason they don't want it discussed, because there is a link and who's been promoting 5g and the
rollout of 5g who runs the licenses for 5g off comm same woman
Adam: in a different interview, he went a little bit more in depth and I looked up the studies and what he claims and the claim is correct. I don't
know if it is true for five g depending on the frequencies power etc. But indeed, effects of electromagnetic field exposure can create oxidative
stress and antioxidant defense system issues. And he talked about it in the initial one to go to this one. And it's completely valid that and and the
thing with these theories, which is always with it, it's always the case. If you listen to what doctors are saying people are turning blue it's like
they're not getting enough oxygen. I think we had a clip of that ER doctor in New York who said to me It looked like someone was at you know 20,000
feet without oxygen and it would just literally dying because of a lack of oxygen in their lungs and in their blood. And so that could be absolutely
if someone's immune system is compromised, and there's a 5g Tower next door and possibly I don't know. But it certainly he I don't think he ever said
Coronavirus is caused by 5g but it doesn't matter No
John: He never says that.
Adam: It doesn't matter it's social censorship. If it if it deviates at all, it must be eliminated.
John: Yes, I'm, I'm I'm bald. This is why our show exists. Of course so let's play the Let's Play the other way which is dv ID I get lefty sorry.
Unknown: This is this is an interesting clip because I have it gives me an anecdote I can I can talk about this david i towers going up while this
lockdown has been going on. I know from communications to me And guys, Jamie at David act.com. I know from all the postings on the internet, not just
in Britain, but around the world in America. But while this lockdown has been going on 5g masks are being rolled out at a very rapid rate in the same
period of this lockdown, something like another 21 towns and cities have been opened in Britain to 5g 5g is being rolled out all over the world at a
very great rate of knots. This is
a time where everything is supposed to be stopped. Yeah. And they're still building towers. overnight.
Yes. Because that's considered essential work. Yeah,
Adam: yeah. We Okay, so I saw one go up here. Right. like five minutes from our house. That's what that's new.
John: Well, Mimi drove down from Washington last, I guess Monday, or maybe last Friday. I'm not one of these days. Going back and forth has been
around because traffic is just there's no traveling go back and forth. Yeah. So she comes down this last time. And she says holy crap. All I saw
coming down were people putting up 5g towers. Yeah. All along. Highway, US interstate five. Yeah,
Adam: well, and you know, when you think about it, and they are, of course essential personnel, this is infrastructure, this is a great time for them
to do anything. what they should be doing is fixing the potholes. So that's what I've been waiting for.
John: Oh, yeah. No pothole fixing whatsoever.
Adam: See that? That would have endeared the community. But no, but no, but no, but no. So, so like, effectively, really deep platformed. And just and
you're right, that's, that's why our show is here. And we're completely independent. And thank God, we don't have to rely on a YouTube or anything
else like that. And, and, and I gotta say, bitch, shoot. Some of these, you know, bit that all these different alternative video sites, they're,
they're winning with this, they're gaining. Oh, we'll see what if this is a good strategy for them. But I think that when you It's one thing to have
your people, you know, to socially censor content on your platforms when people are running their regular lives, but when they're at home all day, you
know, they start to wander. They're not entirely your slaves anymore. They're
John: thinking for themselves, maybe a little bit. So not one. But the point is, you can't start taking this stuff down. I mean, what's gonna hurt
YouTube in long term course you can't get advertisers anyway. But if the Russian car cam videos moved to a separate platform, boom is dead. It's all
over.
Adam: And once the cats are going after that the cats don't the cats leave, then you got no platform left
John: cats and car crashes is
Adam: a funny moment in West Virginia. Although it's kind of a blue dress silver dress moment the governor of West Virginia accused of an expletive.
Again, I encourage all businesses that are allowed to open to do so only if they can follow the guidelines to keep West Virginia safe. Now, he claims
he didn't use an expletive
Unknown: today in our news briefing, there was an audio glitch.
And it sounded like that I
had said a bad word. A word that I was I would never say nor have I ever seen.
John: no possibility in any way shape, form or fashion.
Adam: Okay. bullcrap. But I there is a glitch in it. And you're allowed to say that when it comes to audio, there is an actual glitch in that, but
it's after the F word. And I can't make anything outside of it. I don't know what then What was he saying? If it wasn't that he listened to it one
more time. Again, I encourage all businesses that are allowed to open to do so only if they fuckin follow the guidelines to keep West Virginia safe.
Unknown: I don't know.
Adam: At least it gave us another five minutes of entertainment.
John: Though, you know, this denial. He should just apologize for saying it.
Adam: I think so too. It just slipped out. I
John: mean, this is the kind of thing I got. Yeah. Yeah.
Adam: Let's move over to pharmaceutical stuff. And the President did a it was a virtual Town Hall at the Lincoln Memorial. This was a fox exclusive.
Very interesting setting. I'm not quite as like, What are you trying to say here? I wonder Trump Lincoln, are you trying to connect something here my
brain? And he took questions. And you also took questions from Martha and from Brett. And the question came up about the pharmaceutical companies. And
the need for them to be really, you know, we need our medications are essential medications created in the United States, maybe not in China or other
countries. And so it was kind of a two parter. And the second part, I think she rattles the president a bit. And here's, here's part one.
Unknown: There's a lot of people who say why you talk about making it here in America? Why are all of the antibiotics made in China? Can you give me a
date by which we will be self sufficient in antibiotics in this country? And what kind of incentive would you give manufacturers of pharmaceuticals to
make sure that we are not dependent on China anymore for this? So
John: the reason it took place is because other people that sat in this chair, maybe not right here, but this a beautiful place? Because they were
foolish, you could even say because they were stupid, because they allow this to happen. And it's not only China, you take a look at Ireland, they
make our drugs and everybody makes our drugs except us. Then we've already done it. We're coming out with things, numbers, you're seeing numbers of,
of innovations that we've made in the past, and things are being announced already, but we're bringing that whole supply chain back. Nobody has to
tell me to do it. I've been talking about that for years. Another one that you see, you don't see you see it with cars, you see it with other these
people never looked at medicine. But it's always been about medicine, because we have at least 94 95% of our medicines are made for to do the vaccine.
Well, it's an incredible thing. They're American companies. Well, I'd like to be able to do it here. I don't want to do it in China, I
Adam: don't want the vaccine in China, that's for sure. But then Martha follows up. And I want you to give me your impression after you listen to the
clip, whether this was a setup, whether he knew it was coming. If if he turned it around, and may turn it into something to his advantage, I think we
need to talk through it because she presses him. And she uses something. And that's why I'm suspicious of the question. Well, when will we get to that
95% everything made here. And he seemed rattled
Unknown: when we get that 94% of antibiotics made in this country? Do you have a target date for that?
John: I think we will have it done within two years. You know, it doesn't go that quickly. And frankly, you put me in a very bad negotiating position
by asking me this question. You know, we're talking about this. Now, I'm supposed to call up, my guys. I mean, you put me in a very bad negotiating
position. And I'm not blaming you, that's you. That's your job. You know, you're taking my cards away, because I don't want to be talking this way.
I've done a lot. But it gets exposed when you answer I assume the show is a big show, right? It's gonna do very well tonight. But you do take away a
lot of my cards, when you're answering asking me a question like that, you understand that? Yes. Here's the bottom line. I met with the drug company
six months ago, I said, you got to stop making the drugs here. You're going to start making them here. And they do it for two reasons, a cost reason.
But it's no longer so much cost, because we can do things here for the same price. And in some cases less and then you don't have the transportation
problems. We're taking care of our look. Another reason I got elected, and some people don't like the sound of it, and other countries are like it,
but I said I'm sorry. It's called America first. And we're all about America first. That's
Unknown: what we're about.
Adam: It was protest protesting a bit much I felt.
John: He's got to tell, which is he, which is the term that we're always ridiculing people for doing and he doesn't normally do it. But when he does
it, I believe this when he says look, yeah, yeah, exactly. Yeah.
Adam: So he said, Look, I met with the farmer guy six months ago. So I've been telling them, you got to bring it back. And I'm sure that, you know,
similar to what has happened in the past. They're waiting for something to sweeten the deal. And that's why
John: I think he protests too much. I think this was maybe the whole thing was part of his negotiating tactic could be,
Adam: I haven't figured it out, but could be
John: does he does, you know, say, Oh, no, you're gonna ruin my negotiating position. Oh, stop, stop, stop hitting me. That's what I like that sounds.
Adam: That sounds kind of like bull. I only have one other question from this, but it's a good one. And his answer was very complete. And this comes
on the heels of at least the knowledge being out there, according to the spectator in Australia that there is a five eyes intelligence report. So
that's the UK, the United States, Canada, Australia, and New Zealand, Australia, as and there's a 15 pages floating out and about that say, you know,
hey, the Chinese are really responsible for this. And we don't know exactly how much is true or how deep it goes. But Trump has a very outspoken
opinion on this. And he got a question about it from some dude who called in. It was black guy. And he's he looked and he's, like, sounds as stoned as
he looked. Who's the president? I have a question for you.
Unknown: Is there enough evidence that China is a global community by this Coronavirus?
If so, how should global community respond?
Adam: Yeah.
John: Well, I don't think there's any question about it. We wanted to go in they didn't want us to go in early very early. You'll see that because
things are coming out that are pretty compelling now. So I don't think there's any question Don't forget, China tried to blame it first on some of our
soldiers that turned out to not go too far.
Adam: I'm sorry. I didn't do need to mention I've edited this clip in two spots, because Trump I've learned speaks in what I call hanging chads. So
he'll talk he'll be he'll be talking about something. Then all sudden, he drops down into a repetitive sentence about how he looks Oh, and I closed it
up on time and they told me not to and then they close it. And then he comes back to the store
John: that this is like one of his rallies.
Adam: Yeah, so it's a hanging Chad thing. So I just snipped it off.
Unknown: And I really got very upset with that. That was not right. China tried to blame Europe for this. Now he told john Robbins As you saw evidence
that gave you a high confidence that the virus came from the Han lab, we thought that it was created there, perhaps, but that it came from there at
the right time, we're
gonna illuminate any more about that we're
John: gonna be given a very strong report as to exactly what we think happened. And I think it'll be very conclusive. Is there any suggestion that it
was anything nefarious or that it was just a mistake? So I think they made Personally, I think they made a horrible mistake. And they didn't want to
admit it, we wanted to go in, they didn't want us there, even World Health wanted to go in. They were admitted, but much later, you know, not
immediately. And my opinion is they made a mistake, they tried to cover it, they tried to put it out, it's like a fire. You know, it's really like
trying to put out a fire, they couldn't put out the fire, what they really treated the world badly on, they stopped people going into China, but they
didn't stop people going into the USA and all over the world. So you could fly out of Wu Han, where the primary problem was all of the problems
essentially, also where the lab is, but you could fly out of Warren, and you could go to different parts of the world. But you couldn't go to Beijing,
and you couldn't go to any place in China.
Unknown: So what's that all
about? In other words,
they knew they had a problem. I think they were embarrassed by the problem very embarrassed. And that, you know, the
case could be made, they said, hey, look, this is gonna have a huge impact on China. But here's the thing. They allow this to go into our country,
they allowed it to go into other countries, all of
us how you feel about presidency is to change your relationship with him.
John: I'm not going to say anything. I had a very good relationship. He's a strong man, he's a tough man could have very good relationship with him.
But this should never have happened. This should never have happened, this virus should not have spread all over the world, they should have put it
out. They should have let us and other people in other countries go in and put it out. Because people knew what was happening.
Adam: So that is a pretty clear opinion. And a lot of people heard it and saw it. I think it was almost 4 million people viewed that townhall which is
huge for Fox News on cable. I was very big for them.
John: Yeah. Why? Well, pompeyo made some comments about this, which took a very strange turn because it sounds like he was contradicting himself. And
so I have this clip of him answering the Rouhani origin question 200 in a press conference,
Unknown: and Mr. said, You've seen anything that gives you high confidence that it originated in that lab,
Adam: where there's enormous evidence that that's where this began. We've said from the beginning that this was a virus that originated in Wuhan,
China. We took a lot of grief for that from the outset. But I think the whole world can see now, remember, Chen has a history of infecting the world.
And they have a history of running substandard laboratories. These are not the first times that we've had a world exposed to viruses as a result of
failures in the Chinese lab. And so while the Intelligence Committee continues to do its work, they should continue to do that and verify so that we
are certain, I can tell you that there is a significant amount of evidence that this came from that laboratory in one,
Unknown: do you believe it was manmade or genetically modified?
Adam: That the best experts so far seem to think it was man made? I have no reason to disbelieve that at this point.
Unknown: Your your office of the DNI says the consensus the scientific consensus was not manmade or genetically modified.
Adam: That's right. I agree with that. Yeah, I've seen I've seen their analysis, I've seen the summary that you saw that was released publicly, I have
no reason to doubt that that is accurate.
Unknown: Okay, so just to be clear, you do not think it was manmade, or genetically modified. I've seen
Adam: what the Intelligence Committee has said, I have no reason to believe that they've got it wrong. You have to put this in context here. I think
that there's confusion in the question in the answer. And when he's saying when she's asking about created so clearly wasn't synthetic. In his mind, I
believe he's answering the question if it's a bio weapon.
John: No, no. If you listen to this very carefully, at the very end, the very end of that clip, he says, You got to take this in context. He says, I
believe what the DNI said, but you got to take it in context. That's what he said. And what he and I do, I've imaginated over this particular clip for
a while before I realized what context meant. The DNI report, stated that the a bunch of scientists and other people agreed that it was all was a
natural form element. And it was and in that that was the reports about the agreement was solid that it was naturally formed. It came out of no bad or
whatever. And in context, what he was saying why he could agree with the DNI report is that they were reporting on what the scientists said. reporting
on the reality of
Adam: it, okay. Oh, Okay,
John: right. And that's what he meant by you got to take this in context. Well, the context was the DNI was not discussing how this virus came about,
or there's other probably other intelligence reports that came out that indicate because he's very strongly that this is man made, genetically
engineered, or whatever, from the lab that words escaped from. Which brings me back to what I think would the French guy, the guy who discovered the
AIDS virus, said, and I'm a subscriber to him, even though everyone says He's nuts, He's nuts. What did he say? So, so I listen to this over and over
again, I realized that ups you can say that it was man made and you can agree with the DNI report, because the DNI report is just stating that all
these scientists are said the following. Yes. I agree that the DNI reports got that. Right. Those scientists did say that.
Adam: Well, that makes sense. Because the last thing you want to do is supersede because the President also didn't say man made he said he didn't get
into that. So the bump pay Oh, yeah. Well,
John: and not not not a great job or getting into any trouble agreeing with the DNI report, which it wasn't it was. I don't think it was well done.
No, but I think but when he says it in context, that was the key word that I got. Yeah. So anyway, so I, I think he's not lying. No, but it's confused
the reporters and he never really got I went out of his way to explain it.
Adam: not helpful.
John: not helpful. It's not helpful. The Chinese
Adam: hear it loud and clear, though, especially when it comes to that Five Eyes report. This is from 60 minutes in Australia.
Unknown: How's this for slap? This week, Australia was described as chewing gum on the boot of China that needed to be scraped off on a rock. The
insult came from an influential Chinese newspaper editor, backed by the Communist Party, our crime. Were troublemakers because our government is
calling for an independent inquiry into the origins and spread of Coronavirus. It's fair to say our relationship with Beijing is currently fractured.
But understanding why China is so defensive. Not to mention petulant is difficult because the regime is so suspicious of the Western media.
Adam: Chewing gum Hmm. stuck to the shoe
John: that's got us that is not that's not gonna play. Well.
Adam: That's international words of war. My friend. can't just say that
John: is great,
Adam: especially in context of Eastern culture and chewing gum, like chewing gum is really low. Low on the poll.
John: It is very low.
Adam: So there there isn't an attack on China. There's a there's polls everywhere saying overwhelming majority of peoples and here's the term here's
the term we should be on the lookout for decouple. We want to consciously decouple from China. I think this is going to be the term decoupling. Yeah,
that's
John: been. That's not it. That's been around for a couple months.
Adam: Yeah, I'm hearing it. I'm
John: hearing it. It's a good term it did. Maybe it's catching on is what you think, yeah. Could be catching on a couple couple.
Adam: Ted Cruz is on his own little mission. And he's doing the rounds. And he wants to force Hollywood to stand up to Chinese censorship. And at
first I was kind of puzzled, like, Why are you so interested in this? Who gives a crap? And then I realized what he's really doing. He's saying we can
have these movies, which have a permanent desk, at the Pentagon using our military equipment, ie, Top Gun, if they're also going to if these
productions are also going to be involved in censorship and in top gears, Top Gear Top Gun specific instance, Tom Cruise's flight jacket had a
Taiwanese flag it had to be removed. So for some reason, Ted Cruz is spending a lot of time on that. And I think that it may it's it's meant to
cripple China in in multiple ways. But I think they do have such huge investments in in movies, and Hollywood, that he's trying to hurt them there.
But it's just an odd thing to do. It's like Well,
John: yeah, there's even more to it than that.
Adam: What you got.
John: He knows the connection. I don't know. I'm not a mind reader. I don't know what Ted Cruz is thinking he may have nefarious scheme under foot
under way. Maybe under foot. He says something offensive to right now we're trying to get Taiwan to get involved and who and some other things. We're
moving to get Taiwan independence record. eyes. I mean, there's a million things that we've been trying to do a Taiwan for, ever since the 1940s.
Right when they, you know, ran off and, you know, the Government of the Republic of China ran off into become the Republic of China, Taiwan. They run
off off the mainland by Mao. And so there's that element. And so this any pushback by the Chinese on stuff like that little flag is going to be
rejected, but especially when, yeah, the Chinese invest a lot of money. How much money do you think the State Department or the Defense Department
spends on on one of these war movies in terms of just fuel for the Jets? And I think it's a lot of money. It's millions. Yeah. And so why are we you
know, taking a backseat to the Chinese investment when we're making these investments. And these movies actually can't be done without an investment.
Adam: And I agree, I'm just kind of confused as to why Ted Cruz is in this, but maybe it may be he's trying to create a squeeze. And he's really going
after Hollywood and not China.
John: I think it's possible he's going after Hollywood.
Adam: Yeah, that's what that that would make more sense. I would make more sense. So Meanwhile, we have on the medical front, we have multiple trials
going we know remdesivir is is now in trial, which I have all these all these great stats, it's all in the show notes, you know, the cost of
remdesivir. It's like, it's like $400 a day, versus hydroxychloroquine at pennies a day. It's really quite incredible. And it just seems like anything
that is not approved by Dr. Dr. Death himself, Dr. Fauci that it has to be pushed back and quiet and be suppressed. Let's not talk about it. And then
all of a sudden we get this over the over the past few days out of Pittsburgh
John: Ross township police believe two men found shot to death over the weekend was a murder suicide. The body of 37 year old being Lou was found
Saturday at his home at the muse of town north. Police believe Luce killer left the town home, went back to his car and killed himself that man has
not been identified. The police say they believe that Lou and the man didn't know each other.
Adam: So this research has been well researched. I've been working on a cure a treatment for COVID-19 any any goes out in a murder suicide? What are
the chances? But that brings us to the planned demick quote, unquote, documentary that has been socially censored. This is still available on multiple
platforms. Have you seen this john is about 20.
John: Part One woman has lots of videos that have come and gone they all get censored I always download them.
Adam: Very, very copies,
John: Mary good. Because I figured you know this things aren't gonna last this latest one, though. I have to say, the one with the ominous opening and
the guy interviewing her. Yeah, I think is the best produce in the end, the most impactful because it's the one Mimi's Oh, you gotta watch this. Yes,
yes. And I said, Well, you know, I'm very familiar with this woman. And she's been bitching and moaning about one thing or another for a long time.
Long time, long time. Well, we
Adam: we actually discussed her probably about a decade, a decade ago. And we just started the show. Now, I'll just want to say this about the
documentary. I did not pull any clips from that because it's great as a piece and I think it's fantastic to make people aware of, of this story and of
this doctor story in particular. But you know, you get all the scary music. It's very dressed and there's a lot of manipulation going on. So I found
that interview that she did with it was just her a Skype call, but the the quality is good and the questions she speaks in, in answer blocks. He's
fantastic for media. But we knew about her when we first started talking about vaccines on this show 1011 years ago, and they'll get they'll just be
somewhat repetitive that we had found documentation from big goldman sachs and JP Morgan Chase, I think medical conference at all the pharmaceutical
companies were all jacked up because vaccines was the future. It's, you know, in some cases, they're mandatory. So it's a guaranteed paycheck
John: and they're indemnified. They're indemnified.
Adam: They don't have to go to the same testing because it's called a biologic. And there's so many great reasons for this. And we got a lot of
contact, which I don't think I quite understood at the time about Dr. mikovits as it pertains to chronic fatigue syndrome. And people were trying to
communicate something to us and we I certainly was just not my headspace was not there. We just kind of start deconstructing stuff and I was A little
naive to some things that were going on. So when it comes to the medical community, but in this first clip, she addresses that. And what she had
figured out back in the day, is that there were what are called x m RVs. Which is mouse, right arrow, viral, viral, Rich retrovirals, excuse me, x for
cross, we're showing up in, in different people and for reasons that were very unclear, but what this was creating was a chronic fatigue syndrome not
dissimilar to HIV, actually, in many ways. That in fact, the and we'll get to that later testing for HIV showed people with these x Mr. vs. ie this
chronic fatigue syndrome showed tested positive for HIV, even though it didn't have HIV. So it's a mess. And she was a part of it. She's been part of
FAO cheese system for many years, and she has her own story about how she was kicked out and jailed and accused of fraud and, and that's certainly
stuff you can look into. I'm more interested in what she's saying. She sounds credible. She certainly has the curriculum to back her up.
Unknown: And let's take go back to that initial issue when we were first introduced to her but this is a current interview. This is Dr. Judy mikovits
Mike ovitz we we isolated a new family of retroviruses called xmrv. That means Xena tropic mouse related retrovirus. So it was very clear that, you
know, the human virome doesn't have Mouser, retroviruses. Therefore, we thought perhaps as in the days of HIV, that this virus could have been spread
through biological therapies. Because we use a lot of mice in therapy in our lab, we also remembered back to the days of HIV when, when HIV spread
through the population from a contaminated blood supply. When it became clear, by the
Adam: way, that very bit there, Alex Jones has been yelling about that for for maybe 20 years. The vaccines being transporting contaminated blood. And
that's where he got it from
Unknown: spread through the population from a contaminated blood supply, when it became clear, in 2010, and 11, that in fact, the blood supply was
heavily contaminated. And in fact, the most likely way that these mouse viruses of many strains, not just one got into humans, it was almost certainly
from biological therapies, and the most likely the most prominent one was vaccines, that that in fact, that we were injecting in mouse tissue, you
know, meses pieces, into into immune in competent little babies. People and and we had actually literally caused a number of diseases including this
is a this is a family of mouse cancer causing viruses. So cancers and neuro immune diseases, including chronic fatigue syndrome, autism, and Lou
Gehrig's disease, others are associated with, with retroviruses. And it was very clear in 2011, in the summer of 2011, this wasn't just one but many
and and the most likely way they got into humans was a contaminated blood supply and contaminated vaccines.
Adam: So contaminated vaccines is some so any stories you've heard in the past likely stem from her because that's where I remember it from and that's
where that chronic fatigue syndrome came from. But
John: there we did have lots of clips. If you recall, during the swine flu. Bull cram, there was a contaminant there was a huge set of vaccines that
went out that had live swine flu in them, and would have continued would have given people swine flu to push the numbers up. I don't know. I mean, it
just seems like you know, the carelessness was weird. And there was some cross contamination of other vaccines that have nothing to do with swine flu,
but the swine flu was in there. And these were caught at the border kind of as they're being shipped out. But Dude, you don't know it because there's
this they're not they're indemnified from any damages, no matter what's in the shot they give you. Anything could be in there. That's why I think a
lot of people are I, for example, Do give I got a vaccine for I got the Prevnar 13 vaccine a couple months back. And before COVID broke out because I
thought, well, you know, let's get I because my doctor said I should get it and everybody said you should get this if you're getting older you want to
get this and this is the flu vaccine know this the Prevnar 13. Stops 13 different kinds of pneumonia. Hmm. And, but, but at the same time, I'm very
dubious about any of these things, because there's now something going wrong because there was a new experimental pneumonia vaccine that floated
around and get a bunch of people sick. So this is well established, so I wasn't too worried about is very expensive. So I wasn't, you know, as you
well, they're not gonna how many people are gonna be spending this much money for this vaccine? And but I'm always skeptical. I'm very nd if you look
at the stuff that Robert Kennedy Jr. said about the Gates Foundation Bill's experiments on babies and ever all Africa and India. I mean, most of his
vaccine experiments have gone south.
Adam: You're not going to like this. A couple weeks ago, we discussed a study that was a published account, medical journal published account, it's in
the shownotes. Once again, that a number of military personnel who the 2017 2018 flu vaccination was tested on from that test group. It turned out
that you those who had been administered the 20 1728 c 18 season seasonal flu vaccine had a 36% chance, higher chance of contracting a respiratory
disease from some other virus specifically Coronavirus. Do you remember that that report?
John: I do remember that.
Adam: Okay. And it's called. It's called we have there's a term for it. It's like interference. I think it's a vaccination interference. Well, it's
mentioned in this clip, because this is where it gets pretty messed up. As this is the crux of what Dr. microbeads is really saying is going on with
COVID-19.
Unknown: What Dr. Fauci has been saying is get the influenza vaccines, the live attenuated influenza vaccines, and and there have been several
publications, but one in 2017 and 18. Among the military, which actually said, the flu vaccine promotes the spread, that is your 36% more likely to
get COVID-19 or an infection with SARS code to if you get the influenza vaccine. So his advice to the country, you know, is totally against published
literature that says it's dangerous that you that you don't you know that you're driving the disease with the influenza vaccine, and that would spread
it easier to across nations because those that use shed those viruses, that is you express those viruses and you'll actually you know, can get an
influenza the same kind of symptoms, the same kind of upper respiratory infection, and now you're more likely to to spread from human to human. That
Coronavirus isn't in fact other microbial agents, other viruses respiratory syncytial virus, rhinoviruses, that that cause upper respiratory diseases,
including influenza.
Adam: And what she's saying here is if you had the flu shot in 20 1718, and possibly with any flu shot or with any vaccination, which may have some
contamination in it that seems to be prevalent, but in what there's evidence that the actual flu shot could make you very susceptible to this and she
explains how this works because it sounds very familiar.
Unknown: And even worse, the vaccines for COVID-19 the vaccine that would target directly SARS code two has been studied since since the original SARS
outbreak in the original MERS which is Middle East Respiratory Syndrome outbreak. Since that time the vaccine development has gone on and in every
case and in every study there. The vaccine actually drives the death by by literally turning on the fire they you know, exploding the fire of the
immune the overreaction of the immune system. That is what we call the signature of disease. It's that inflammatory cytokine storm and now and the
vaccine itself can drive That storm such that if you are reexpose it can lead to rapid death.
John: Yeah, but by the way, guys, I've listened to that clip. I'm reminded, I didn't record it, but they're talking about I've actually I do have a
clip. They can find it. It's the clip that says, because I was watching this clip as they were doing it, this is the not the source of mutants. I
wanted to get into that, but mystery COVID can't find any instantly. But it's they showed that they're working on a bright x Dr. Bright ignored maybe?
No, no, no, no, no, that's an All right. They're working on a vaccine. And they they're showing this a human testing has begun. I don't wish I had
this on here. Human testing has begun and they show some poor, poor schlub luck. No shot is some cumin, just COVID-19 I'm thinking, what maniac is
signing up for this? Have you ever even listened to any alternative media? I'm serious. I'm like screaming at this guy, Doug screaming at the
television.
Adam: So that kills the kill shot from from Dr. Mike of it. And then you know, at least you know what's going on. But I think she puts a lot of
reputation on the line here for whatever she has left. She's written several books about this, about this topic and how she was. And it has a lot to
do with money and patents. And this this cabal of Fauci and Burke's Lieutenant Commander Colonel Burke's ambassador, and red field from the CDC. These
end and bright all these guys have been been around with Gates Foundation. I mean, it's great to see pictures of Fauci and birch without him, john at
the AIDS Gala. I mean, they these are celebrities, they are very big in their world. But along the way, we've seen or as the doctor will Chronicle
there's been a lot of cover ups and lying to push agendas and get things that don't work to work so people can make money. There's a published study
from 2005, about the activity, the efficacy of hydroxychloroquine, that Fauci is, is, you know, he, he's aware of these studies, it's his own its own
group of the government that's done these yet, when it comes to this particular illness? No, no, no, it's now it's just anecdotal evidence, I believe
they did some fudging on the numbers or change some, the the test goals, to push the remdesivir through and of course, ultimately, it's all to really
have nothing that works well in the people's mind, then the vaccine, which is inevitable, the push is real, but she feels that Dr. Fauci should go to
jail.
Unknown: Do you think that Dr. Fauci played a part in COVID-19, then do you think that he should be held accountable or responsible or criminally
responsible for the corruption with COVID-19? Or even tracing back as far as 30 plus years? Oh, absolutely. He should be held criminally responsible
all the way back to the spread of HIV AIDS through the country at the same time, he did the same thing he's doing now in COVID-19. That is prevent the
use of therapies like hydroxychloroquine, or type one low dose type one interferon alpha, or any number of natural things, prevent people, you know,
from doing the appropriate testing, the FDA didn't do the appropriate serology testing that that would have shown that, in fact, we know the virus had
been through this country earlier than thought and we may have actually had, in many places a natural herd immunity, that isn't it occurring with the
lockdown, and that people aren't being groomed are being prevented from you know, even if they were exposed from from getting the disease with
prophylactic measures, that's preventative measures like hydroxychloroquine. And all at the same time promoting drug use in research and clinical
trials, which he's also doing a similar thing to what he did, what he directed to be done in the case of the xmrv. That's, that's fraudulent studies
that that show, you know, that that a drug works, when it really doesn't work and how they manipulate the study design in order to, you know, to drag
it out, so and then, because we're not developing a natural herd immunity that the amount of disease and death that's being caused, while while people
are well, he's promoting measures that that not only don't work, but it caused, literally the deficit of our economy and and we won't even be able to
count the number of deaths from people who couldn't get adequate care for things like cancer and cardiovascular disease just simple care for things
that have nothing to do with COVID-19
Adam: demand an investigation
John: yeah you're gonna get an investigation alright you're gonna get an investigation as to why they fired Dr. Bright is going to be done by Adam
Schiff all
Unknown: right all right let's get on to it that
Adam: was good into it Fat
John: Fat Jerry Adler and that's where your investigations going cuz already they're talking I didn't want anyone to switch subjects had some other
stuff to say but let's talk about the bright guy emerges CBS clip. This is thinking we talked about this guy weeks months, months ago this guy got
kicked out of the he was bitching and moaning about using oxy chloroquine and chloroquine which nobody uses. And he says that any. Just listen to the
this idiot listen to these two clips is the bright guy re emerges as Dr. Bright
Unknown: Quinn and chloroquine he just decided he could no longer remain silent. CBS News has learned bright has agreed to testify on Capitol Hill
next week. And he hopes to get his old job back tonight and HHS officials says that he was transferred to a critical role at NIH and they are
disappointed he hasn't shown up for work Nora
John: Okay, so now this douchebag which I'm gonna call him that because the following clip this clip is this the doctor was under Dr. Bright ignore it
is a term Democracy Now I'm gonna just kind of set it up. This is a Darrell course all in because this guy was wrong. We Okay, let's start with this
premise. He's a government worker, not necessarily the best known in his field for anything. He's just the guys running this one very small branch of
some very small branch of another division. And he is what I've seen these guys, I've worked in the government long enough to run into guys like this.
Everybody in the government's running cover your ass memos. And they're just that's what you do. You just in case. And so this guy is just really a
nude Nick, out of the blue. There's nobody's ever heard of him until this he's made this big fuss, and now they're gonna bring him in for two so he
can testify against Trump. Basically, even though Trump doesn't know really what's going on, I don't think but let's play this clip. And I gotta tell
you what galling me about this,
Unknown: and instead to award lucrative contracts based on political connections. In other words, I was pressured to let politics and cronyism drive
decisions over the opinions of the best scientists we have in government.
Dr. Bright also says he repeatedly and urgently demanded action in January to address the looming pandemic, including a critical shortage of personal
protective equipment for doctors like in 95 face masks, but was ignored.
John: He was ignored because he's like, and like most people in the government, you're ignored because everybody's bitching and moaning about one
thing or the other. So this guy going on I was ignored, I was ignored and that's what he's going to testify against. I wrote a memo on January 5,
saying we don't have enough and now why would he even have anything to do with the end? 95 face max the stats how many there are what the hospitals
have? It doesn't make any sense but okay. I was ignored. I wrote this memo and I was ignored. You wrote this memo was and you were ignored? Nobody
said anything you know, well, my bosses told me to stop writing memos it's just ridiculous this guy and they're gonna make a mountain out of a
molehill as best they can try to impeach Trump again
Adam: the and and so the theory is because this guy wrote a memo which was ignored 1000s died. Is that it? That's the idea.
John: blood on your hands.
Adam: Yes. Exactly. Just briefly on the testing, you know, testings ramping up so and and I am still surprised how many people are so poorly informed
that they read in the in our local news here at Austin. Oh, we have, you know, 60 new cases. Oh, my God. Stay inside. No, no, listen, we're testing
more. And it's good news, the more people who are asymptomatically infected duckula lower the actual chance you have of dying. You have more
information. But the tests are a problem. And I think one of the one of the main points of David ickes theory is that the test is for a, just a
Coronavirus, but not necessarily the COVID-19 creating Coronavirus. And we know from Dr. Mike ovitz that there were positive tests on people who had
were supposed to have had AIDS which they didn't they had these exit x x MRV mouse virus mouse crap in your in your veins. But the tests are a real
issue. This is only report I'm sure you won't get this on the mainstream. You won't from Reuters. So take that for what you will Coronavirus test kits
used in Tanzania were dismissed as faulty by president john magufuli. On Sunday. He said they had returned positive samples. And he is a chemist By
the way, that's why he ordered it. So they had received positive samples, positive results on samples taken from a goat. And from a pawpaw, which is a
fruit. So both the goat and the pawpaw tested positive for COVID-19. I mean, I'll even take the goat. But you're gonna tell me that fruit tasty fruit?
You should have heard what the goat had to say about the whole ordeal. Yeah, so And now I'm in contact with one of our producers, who was working with
antibodies and tests. And this lab person has told me that there's been some issues getting, you know, the right. I guess you need the spike poked
protein or whatever. And they're different labs from overseas and maybe India, it could be China. I mean, there's I can't get answers to everything
because of secrecy and NDA and things. And so it's very hard to get full info, but I finally just said, is it possible that whatever the hell they're
sending you is just not really the right one. And that's something that our producer could not answer. There's no way to know that. So there's a lot
of you know, because you can put perhaps the AC E to
John: this is out of control. Trump is right we got to bring this stuff back here.
Adam: We don't know what the hell is going on.
John: It's crazy as scammer at least starting to give our own scammers the cash.
Adam: Exactly. And with that, I'd like to thank you for your courage and say in the morning to you the man who put the C in social censorship john C.
De veau RAC
John: Linda Morning, Mr. Adam Curry also in the morning shifts to see boots and graphene the dames and knights out there.
Adam: Hey, trolls in the morning to you y'all. Let me see how many trolls we can count today. We've got 1500 70 It's a Thursday it's about right
almost 1600 you could do to can be a troll and you will feel right at home if you live under a bridge currently but it's really nice at no agenda
stream.com you can troll along they've been very helpful this morning actually. Hand in some one liners and ideas and thoughts where we take the
conversation and of course some people just a holes and they troll. No agenda stream.com go there hang out with your fellow friends. Excuse me, you
can also get an invitation there. It's free for no agenda social.com so then you can hook up with our little part of the Federation. In addition to
that it big in the morning to Comic Strip blogger whose artwork was selected for the episode titled The beaches are open Episode 12 139. And this was
the Apple logo. pooping out location apparently the the it was some scatological joke with the government because they are the ones receiving the
information from Apple. And it was the it was good. I don't know why it wasn't the best or was it was the best but there were other choices didn't
quite make what happened.
John: Something it was one that was the best.
Adam: Oh, right. I remember what it was. And we go in and take a look.
John: Unfortunately, it was it was to rule issue, which was rude.
Adam: We're throwing was it again? I can't remember.
John: Exactly. And it was by Darren who just must have been beside himself chuckling to himself you know behind the mic. He these guys pick this it
was well done.
Adam: Why can't I find it now? That's interesting. Did you get taken off when we had the yo yo well we had the comics different one from comics or
blogger we
John: used is dead the other one I actually comic strip blogger got a twofer because I gave him the put down on the newsletter.
Adam: Oh nice the other one and but to Southern I was almost tempted to use dilute oh we liked well we like Tommy the heretic with Operation warp
speed, which was cool because it was a syringe like the Starship Enterprise. Yeah, but that was well done. But then he had a but a female but with
with a thong. It's like no, it's gonna put that in there it is.
John: I mean, we don't mind a good looking but but it's particularly good if it's gratuitous,
Adam: unnecessary bondage. It was just not to waive
John: this bondage belongs on this art. So they got kicked from that for that just from that.
Adam: I can't find the one that was the other one. That was so offensive.
John: It's Still there.
Adam: I can't find it. I don't know. I think I got removed. Oh, no, no, I remember I remember what it was. It was the best piece of art. And, and even
we could
John: I don't even think we could discuss it.
Adam: Well, yeah, I can just tell you what it was it was a Kentucky Fried Chicken logo turned into Joe with Biden instead of Kentucky Fried Chicken.
And was Joe Biden president finger licking good. And now Yeah. We felt that was not appropriate.
John: No. And Darren know, he
Adam: knows that he knows that
John: it's on purpose. Just to see if you can get went through I missed what you always do. creative types are always trying to sneak something
through. Oh, yeah. You know, it doesn't fly with other creative types. You know what you're up to?
Adam: Yeah. Like, it's like Disney, you know, trying to hiding penises and snow white dress and stuff like that. And we're
John: welders to get talented artists. Let's start with thanking a few people including Oh, do we have a little theme music? For sure. Dave. Do No, I
Adam: don't think. I mean, we don't have one special for him. I don't think Do we? Yes, we do. What are you talking about?
Unknown: Oh, God.
John: Yes. Sir David, Duke of America's Heartland in the Arabian Peninsula in Gladstone, Missouri. Well, he's not dead. I think he's still in Saudi
Arabia. That's 6666 always says a note. That's interesting. Dear Ma Kettle and Mother Teresa. You know which ones you are. Today I learned that and
Jarvis, the woman Laura largely credited for creating what we now know as Mother's Day later become so disgusted by its commercialization that she
boycotted it and tried to sue companies who were profiting off the holiday. No. Jingle The more you know, oh, no agenda. Anyways, since I recall, I
recall that I was one of the two ish producers whoops. Sorry. I was one of the whoops. What do you what do you think about when I hit that I hit a
button on here and it took the whole screen off.
Adam: Did you drop your your your knitting?
John: Well, I say this Shift Ctrl Z brings it back that there it is
Adam: girl control Z
John: it all controls control Z. I was one of the Jewish producers who supported their mothers the past five years to I think that's right. I figured
I should continue my yearly habit with another 16666 in the traditional number associated with mothers I guess being dead but God inconclusive data
donation represents to 20 to 22 for each of day melody my mom Pauline and Melody's mom Yolanda. The best moms a guy could have in his life you got a
good mother in law you got it man you do. I really hit the jackpot when it comes to mothers and I love you all Mother's Day goat karma for all the
mothers out there please. And thank you for your courage. Damn, thank
Adam: you for your courage and yes indeed it is Mother's Day and typically on the no agenda show there's no love for moms but the tide might be
turning.
Unknown: You've got
karma
in the morning.
John: And comfort comes in from Indianapolis, Indiana with $333. Here we are sitting on the deck of Sunday afternoon during the quarantine my wife
asks, well, this is a thought this was his wife. This is an okay, maybe they're married. They're married women could be my wife asked why are you
freeloader? Why are you a freeloader? It's embarrassing. We had just listened to the no agenda show and you're discussing the highlights. I quickly
told her she made her point. After 41 years of marriage you learn stuff like that. Then I came up with the idea to make her a dame. Ah, here's the
beginning of our tribute to reach that goal. We also ordered awesome no agenda masks a couple of weeks ago like and like Adam, are still awaiting
their arrival to get these masks out.
Adam: Well, that's not just you know, that's not no agenda shop. It was a different mask and I'm regretting it. I should have just gone for the Gator
from the shop. It was dumb.
John: I should had Jay paint something. Please get everybody for
Adam: every order for every order actively affected
John: by the quarantine. wipe up stop. Hold
Adam: on a second. But when you mentioned something here, I want to explore this. We could have custom painted no agenda mass. This is a huge premium.
John: Yes, we could we could all said that. Yes.
Adam: Yeah. What else is Jay doing? She's just hanging around the house.
John: No, she's up north. She took a drive with Nick up to the Washington
Adam: even better they have room there to store the
John: boxes office laws apparently. Now I'm exempt I could do these things.
Adam: Yes, we can do we are we are we are podcasters by law exempt your essential personnel.
John: So if anybody's a podcaster and making a big stink about staying at home, then they're just virtue signaling because we don't have to stay at
home or do anything. I had to wear a mask in a store obviously because they're gonna kick you out but besides that, anyway, please get some jobs karma
to the people negatively affected by the quarantine and de-douche my wife so she can hear That's true. Keep up the good fight and thanks from bike
locker Lee Kurtz zirkel black card future Dame Swanee,
Adam: bleaker and bleaker black card lacquered. I'm not familiar with this name. That's definitely interesting. All right. Yes, of course, we can do
that deducing first if
Unknown: you've been d deuced.
jobs, jobs, jobs and jobs. Let's vote for jobs.
Adam: Karma All right, so that was I guess that's for him. This is good. Future Dame Swanee, very nice.
John: Tie make may have been 330-323-3333 That's weird. ITM and Debbie 73 HK x four mq 73 former producer of the business to business Poland for CNBC
in Poland
Unknown: All right.
John: Oh good for you. As a former phi m five m i can say you guys are spot on. First we are he has
Adam: a great new year analysis. He has a great name Ty McMahon everybody How you doing? Ty you're
John: typing man. Yeah, it should be a radio jockey. Yes. You probably keep up the good work f the f up FIVF v works. Oh value for value the I'd like
Adam to call out my buddy land as a douchebag okay in Dutch and English.
Adam: Okay, I'll do it in Dutch. I'll do an English first. And then in Dutch, I douchebag. Nailed it.
John: I was hitting the mouth by Sir Tripp mazurek of Memphis. For clips, I'd like to Trump Pelosi jobs karma with a goat scream for everyone trying
to get back to work amidst this cluster of a mess. 7373 to yukito five
Adam: alpha Charlie Charlie jobs,
Unknown: jobs,
jobs,
jobs, jobs and jobs. Let's vote.
Karma
John: was a former member of the M five m he's going to enjoy that clip from Kaylee McInerney.
Adam: No kidding. That's great.
John: Coming up in the second half. Yeah, sir. Rod to Raleigh of Weybridge in London. 333 another 333 This is interesting. IDM Gianna namsa Raleigh of
Weybridge here due to some failed relationship karma requiring a name change to have Crystal Palace. Let me just play around with a concrete dinosaurs
possible.
Adam: Oh, ah,
John: but do a name change you want to write it down? This donation is in memory of my father. He was a Vietnam vet who met my mother in London and
moved to Northern Ireland where his unique skills and weaponry in war served him well. Cool. In the Irish Republican Army what what he always taught
me to question or government's agenda a lot of stories. I dismissed his paranoia crazy old man, But lo and behold more and more of their skullduggery
has been revealed he would have loved your show. Anyway, this donation is from some shares cashed in from a company named ITM so I thought you'd
better get your cut. I just like a goat karma in an F cancer for my mom. Thankfully, this is one karma that has worked. Cheers.
Adam: Yes and I will officially bestow the new title upon you you turn from sir Raleigh of Weybridge to sue Raleigh of Crystal Palace Slayer of the
concrete dinosaurs on the way
Unknown: you've got
karma
John: All right, Drew sample 322 72 jingles he's got we're gonna die. We're not happy. This is true. You can do that. He wants three times. I don't
know if you want to do that or not. It's up to you. Sure. First off, I'd like to thank you for your twice weekly dose of sanity. It is needed more
than ever. I'm a small scale urban farmer in North Linden columbus ohio when our douchebag governor decided to shut down that state's restaurant for
dine in all all of my income disappeared making the high end food for the restaurants and the small guys So did you make it I just would ask him just
rhetorically did you make a switch to get to sell directly to the public because a lot of people did that for meat and produce and you
Adam: know that there are billions of pounds of potatoes and if if they gave it that they can't they're just gonna rot if they if they gave it all
away I was reading they gave every single potato away to the food bank which serves 2 million people each person would have to buy 500 or have to take
home 500 pounds that's how many potatoes there are they're just going to
John: produce a lot of potatoes we know this is a disaster in this regard. By the way, just make sure you are aware of this I'm in need of more than
ever and more than ever have some small business karma I'd also like to offer home deliveries for microgreens to the no agenda producers in both
Columbus and Toledo metropolitan areas if they're interested they can email me at Capital City gardens all one word capital city gardens@gmail.com
that's ca p i t a l Garden City gardens okay or contact me drew sample at no agenda social.com Ah, no drew sample note I recommend people do this and
give this guy some some direct income. Second, I would like to thank both Alex Bell and Jess more for hitting me in the mouth that are pre no agenda
meetup brunch in April of 2018. I am looking forward to hosting a meetup after the COVID insanity is over. For this donation I'm going to use 1216 of
my donation to de-douche my smokin hot girlfriend, Corsica.
Adam: Oops, what's her name?
John: Corsica Lin.
Unknown: You've been de douche.
John: I'd like to call out Jacob Ramirez. And new listener Nathan Frazier as douchebags douchebag douchebag thank you both again for everything you
guys do. Please give small business karma to all the other small businesses who are sharing my pain in the no agenda community.
Adam: Yep, you got it. Here's the sequence.
Unknown: We are not happy. That's true. That's
true.
You've got karma.
John: Ohio listeners I should help this guy out. We do this. A couple of them should just buy out I mean buy a bunch of stuff for your friends. Yeah,
nothing like a good small a small provider of green glossy little green microbial. Yes, it's got part Porter becomes our first associate Executive
Producer $250 with today's donation, I have reached knighthood like to be known fourth, fourth known as surfboard I think the fourth known as sir
Scott of the High Plains. I'd appreciate some jobs karma, Trump Pelosi combo and Merkel's Arbeit
Adam: I don't know if we had all about do we have Merkel
John: with our little miss the Delta Sierra Charles.
Adam: Delta Sherif, Charlie. Yes, daily source. I'm
John: sorry. Yeah, that would be the direct source code or whatever. Yeah,
Adam: yeah. Daily source code.
John: Thanks, Dad daily.
Adam: Yeah, it's Adam Carolla hosted that surely you know, the pod father him and Ricky Gervais so all those guys?
John: Yeah, well, your vase was the pod pod. And I'm not currently you're getting it mixed up.
Adam: I don't have that. I don't know what the the arbeite arbeid are, but I don't remember it. Arbeit the
John: arbeite. The arbeite.
Adam: Yeah, but I don't have Yes, I remember it.
John: But you can't find it.
Adam: Well, how was it labeled?
John: He was hidden labor. Are you assuming he looked up Merkel and Arbeit? Yeah, we can't find it just the way it goes.
Adam: I said it just that's exactly the problem. So what he does want is Pelosi Trump jobs karma and we'll start it off with a little bit of Merkel
for you.
Unknown: jobs, jobs, jobs, jobs, jobs, jobs and jobs.
Adam: The roundtable Scott.
John: Job by ceci sir Joby one of week upon week pogge. Think 247 16 I can't thank you enough for continuing the infotainment I need some jobs cover
for me, my wife and all the out of work are all out of workers. affected by this pandemic lady karma is a dental hygienist is very nervous about
returning to work in such a high exposure profession working inside people's mouths every day. I also potentially am switching jobs during these
during these crazy times in some how have to convince my current company to utilize me by paying my new company time to face up my brown face fo the
lace up my brown shoes. A sales sales sales Can I get a title change for my lovely wife? She also wishes to be lady karma Cara lady care of the clean
tooth instead of Lady Cara of weekapaug you want to put
Adam: this down who's already on the list She's
John: good. In regards to the my previous note, my name is not Joe bisexual john,
Adam: did you? Did you say that?
John: I don't know. Now No, I didn't make it didn't make me laugh to hear you say it. And Adam, I thought you were a pothead. But you were confused at
my roundtable requests of sticky green.
Adam: Doesn't that prove your point?
Unknown: That kind of man I was.
John: I guess it's been almost 30 years since the term was first popularized by Snoop Dogg. Lastly, despite the running belief of the show, I indeed
loved my mother. Ah, but the chances of her listening to any product podcasts I'm okay with that. That is makes more sense. It's not that she the moms
hate the show those boys
Unknown: those boys are just gonna get in trouble the way they think.
Adam: And now that is a good mom voice
John: and so that would be the rationale we're using but but ah watch the podcast is probably the real reason Okay, this
Adam: association ages old man aren't you?
John: Oh yeah, absolutely.
Adam: Well, thank you job assessee and the change will be made you got it and he wants his name changed to Joe bisexual. Is that what he wants?
John: I don't think so. Okay. All right, onward with anonymous 200 bucks. What gave me better to give from my lockdown self than my finally attaining
knighthood from the best podcast in the universe as the world goes completely nuts. I seek the sanctuary of sanity it's a no agenda roundtable on
behalf of both me and my amygdala. Thank you. I would like to ascend from anonymous in San Francisco to Captain Luke Knight of the Barbary Coast. Oh,
please play the classic fear is freedom followed by it's true followed by boom shaka laka and then provide COVID karma for all for all for the
roundtable. I'd like to add garapa and Monaco D Okay,
Adam: hold on a second I need the this one I didn't have where do we didn't we have Corona? karma? I'm pretty sure we had that.
John: Corona. I don't recall it personally. But I'm not the keeper of the karma.
Adam: Let me see if I can find this real quick. Because you want cuz we don't have COVID karma we had Corona karma. I guess I can't find that one
either, then. Just feels kind of stupid. I should be able to find that. And then we only have one eye. Yes. anyone's gruff. Today? Well, yes, I'm
working on.
Unknown: Freedom.
Adam: That's true. Bingo. Boom. You've found that the last minute
Unknown: All right.
John: I don't know if that's what he wanted. You got Corona. That's what he got. David Walsh and Gold Coast, Queensland. $200. That's in Australia.
Hi, john and Adam. I'm David Walsh from the Gold Coast qL, Queensland, Australia. To celebrate my 10th anniversary of listening to the greatest
podcast in the universe. I figured I'd get off my arse, which is what they say in some countries, including Australia, ours and complete my
knighthood. I have a long message plan but decided against it. So I'll summarize
Adam: was longer than this.
John: pretty long. Thanks,
Adam: man.
John: I'm a dude named Ben and follow Jcd here and after listening to him on twit I did take a 2.5 year hiatus from 2015 to mid 2017, due to my
amygdala shrinking so much that I became cynical and date and jaded with everything. Yeah,
Adam: that's a danger. That is that is a real danger. Some people have that. And they just they, because once they're exposed these these guys, I
could do this on my own. I don't really handholding.
John: In fact, the thing is, this is like a part of like, well, how Hollywood and other media work. You have to it has to be collaborative. Each one
of us could do shows,
Adam: yeah, between the two of us, it's the same thing.
John: Yeah, we can't do the show, we could, but it wouldn't be as good and we'd be making mistakes constantly. And it'd be we'd be it wouldn't work
out, as you know, and we wouldn't definitely get onto the kick that we're on correcting people's use of that the end of the day look and things like
that, because, you know, you hear it on television all the time, which is distressing. And so that includes the audience, the audience is the third
element of the, of the collaboration. And so all works together and that keeps you ever from you know, that's why you shouldn't stay away, which
Adam: is, which is why it's obvious that we all produce this show. It's a it's a it's a tribe effort.
John: He continues by saying I think it was over the Obama era. I have been far more entertained in the Trump era. So you as a voters please go he's
in Australia we got to remember that Yeah, so USA voters please keep him in for another term. It makes me smile to see the media go nuts. I wish to
thank you for your courage and wish you all the best of you for years to come and so all the listeners pony up for a subscription even five bucks a
month helps jingle trains good planes bad train foma the woohoo listen to the horn karma for all listeners and producers birthday it's my 46th and may
6 please add me to the list you're on the list. knighthood name sir Dave of the Gold Coast. Sir Dave was my root username assigned to me in 1998 on a
FreeBSD box please regards Okay, I'm glad you have sentiment for the
Adam: OBS. As always.
John: David wash PS your non USA listeners use the date format date month year use the date format date month year so I feel like you miss out on some
good numbers yes there's one coming up that if you reverse it he gets a European Yeah, we usually we can do that. We do it once in a while. I'm sure
you have thought about it though. And I would like to raise it just in case PPS all money in USD. I do appreciate the gesture to match Aussie and z
Canadian. He's got South African dollars bucks though and South Africans are ran so it's gonna mean something else. I know what he's talking about.
Anyway, so thank you for the note.
Adam: I think southern Australia is new from
John: southern Australia. Okay, Southern Ross.
Adam: No, he's from the gold.
John: Oh see in southern Australia is that they're using different money?
Adam: I don't know. Who knows. You don't know they are chewing gum underneath the shoe of China who knows what they're doing over there. Thank you
very much, David. And we'll see you later on the roundtable
Unknown: All aboard trains. Planes ban.
Oh my god.
You've got karma.
John: loud. Sonia, bosun Berg in Madison Wisconsin. A jingles rebel Iser and the old the old donate to no agenda in the Gregorian chant style. We need
to use that more in the end of the show request combo health and relationship karma for my son thank you for all your continued hard work the BS is
getting thick out there and having you guys makes me able to turn it all off love and light
Adam: so the rub lizer number station and what else
John: so the old donate to know a jet do that or the Greg Gordon Oh
Unknown: um no agenda.
Adam: I think Is it this one? No. Cheese ahead. I wasn't ready for that one
John: starts out with the snare drum that's not it.
Adam: I got it. Here we go.
Unknown: say give us as we get there we no need to know gentlemen. Is the show that's really donate to you know this the john adams be donate to and
no agenda. sciences.
You've got karma. That's our gorian
Adam: monks right there.
John: And that's our producers and executive producers right there. associate an executive and associate executive. And however we want to put it one
to thank them for making this show possible. This is show 1240. And they, this was a very generous of them, and we appreciate it. Yeah, it helps us go
for the next show, which will be on Sunday.
Adam: Yes. Thank you very much. We are still continuing. And it is because indeed, of these people who have fresh titles, as they cannot proudly
display them as either executive producer of no agenda Show Episode 1200 40 or associate executive producer. If you're looking for job a lot of people
will be I think things that'll stand out and stuff like that. But also the knowledge you actually had. JOHN, you were just explaining. This is not
radio. This is something completely new. And you can call the podcast but it's different when you have the audience actively participating in it. You
call it the third leg. What are the other two besides us?
John: The other two besides us a third level the third leg one where the legs.
Adam: Okay, that's right. Yes. So together we are all three. I gotcha. kickstands, all three, you are our kickstand. And we appreciate it. We also
appreciate to everyone who supports the show by producing it by donate. We'll be thinking more of them in our second half. And please remember we will
be back on Sunday to do it all over again. with whatever else comes out. We'll be there to hold each other's hands and yours Just go to John
dvorak.org.
Unknown: Slash and a and
Adam: remember, it is Mike events.
Unknown: Our formula is this. We go out. We hit people in the mouth.
Adam: Everything went wrong here today. Okay, sorry about that. It's my man. I can't see zero.
John: I have a couple of series in play here. I wanted to place as the first of all, let me skip to something a little lighter. The they're trying to
scare us with this meat shortage thing that can make us freak.
Adam: And I want to just point out that on this show weeks ago, we had a producer from a meatpacking outfit. Give us some very clear warnings that
this was coming.
John: Yeah, it's coming at us here. Yeah. And it did, Chris. They're doing what they can and Trump did in executive orders. They want to keep the meat
flowing. But so they did a report on CBS, Nora, and I want to play this is the intro to the report. And then she kicks it to one of our reporters to
do that, you know, the stand up, there's meat shortage.
Unknown: Tonight grocery giants are putting a cap on how much meat customers can buy as the pandemic forces more processing plants to shut down. And
at hundreds of Wendy's restaurants managers are asking that famous question. ad campaign. Where's the beef?
Adam: I'd like now I'd like that you say meat must flow. It's like liquid meat.
John: So she goes on and on. And then she cuts it says and so and so is going to report on this and does they bring it to a guy who goes on about the
Tyson he starts reporting on the whole thing. And then right in the kind of right did Jesse Jesse wraps it up? I would bet money. Oh, they would never
admit to this. But ABC does this all the time. And they're very obvious because their time perfectly there's a native ad got dropped into the middle
of this report just right to the point where you want to hear it. And I don't think is going to help sell anything. But if this isn't a native ad
because you gotta remember they're talking about all the closures and this is these guys wrapping it up. And this is it.
Unknown: And as a sign of the
Adam: times the impossible foods Company
Unknown: announced that it's impossible burger which is made with plants will be available at 2700 grocery stores nationwide starting this week. And
it says it's ready to expand to meet
the growing demand.
Adam: Nora Well, this would be one heck of a battle and if the meat guys got defeated by the The only thing that was left on the shelves during an
actual pandemic where people possibly could starve they didn't buy that crap.
John: They didn't so they throw this little gem at the end and I'm thinking I wonder what they paid is a 15 second ad it's just a spy cheapo and 15
second has to exist. And it's just like Oh brother I just rolled my eyes I killed the rest of the report. Anyone play anybody want to play the native
ad? to point out that these guys are douchebags
Adam: Oh yeah. Oh yeah. No, you know who are doing begs the news reporters at home who have the apple air pods in their ears. Oh, doesn't it look
John: worse doesn't
Adam: look like that cigarette butts hanging out of their head yet. It's not a good look. I can't get over it. I'm like, then we'll have one and I'm
distracted. Like, why only one you know? Who's Why didn't you want to? And can you hear yourself and what's going on? It's a dumb look.
John: The look most of the looks and sounds on these at home guys and the beard growing the beard and all the rest of the books. They get books behind
them all the time. They look smart and the whole thing. There's an analyzer. Very funny. I got some books. I gotta read a book.
Adam: It is so odd that people think that's a good look with books. His books rarely look good in the background. That just don't
John: Well, I would like to if I was doing this I was I was working for I would do one of these desks that is just an outrageous mess. I wouldn't have
to do a lot
Adam: I would exactly just turn the camera on you're done.
John: Yeah, good to go. And I have I would like to use this my little studio set here and have this the gong in the background and here's a couple of
these crushed cans. Yeah. Got a couple crushed Can you just look like a you know, like you're just hanging out of you know, just a mess. I think
that's the way to go. No one has the guts to do that. Do
Adam: you have you have crushed cans just in case in your studio?
John: Well, here's what I know. I had these dish Pellegrino cans, and I crushed them and then I noticed that they were good for if they were good
little advices for making more sounds. And I was I told you this before I thought this would make a good Geiger counter sound.
Adam: That's actually pretty good guy. You're conscious. You you have you have these things since the Geiger counter comparison. The cans have been
there.
John: Yeah, I can't right here. It's in it's in the sound effects bin is radioactive.
Adam: You are a special individual John Dvorak. You are a special man. interesting article that showed up. I think it came well, Zero Hedge they
always have some kind of I like how they pull stuff to get you got a link out of them, though the good for headlines. But apparently Reuters is
reporting that the Trump administration is getting ready to put to release plans to initiate a pact among several nations are allies for mining the
moon. And there's going to be so it'll be a an international agreement that it will be called the Artemis accords. Now Artemis, I think is the name of
this mission or the name of the of the next of the next mission to the moon. Yeah, I have so much trouble believing all this. I mean 50 years ago, we
landed a Tinker toy wrapped in tin foil on the moon. It since then. We have we went from a phone that if you if you touch the wires, it could actually
shock you to a phone that has now a supercomputer in your pocket. The advanced is the internet all this stuff? Why isn't Elon Musk already spinning
donuts on the moon in his Tesla? I just don't understand what happened. And I wonder if we're ever going to get to the moon again. Anyway, that's all
I had to say on that. Okay,
John: I think that's valid. It's a valid opinion. Yeah, I wanted to play these three clips because this is the media is losing their kind of their
people are losing interest in COVID.
Adam: Oh, no. gotta bring them back in the fold.
John: So let's go with this one. This is Nora opens with mutant virus.
Adam: Oh. Hold on a second. Where is yes, got it.
Unknown: As we come on the air tonight Coronavirus infections are still growing in much of the country. Just as we're learning there is now a more
powerful mutant strain of the virus that is even more difficult to treat. There are now more than 20,000 new confirmed cases every day here in the
United States. And while cases are declining in the New York City area, the epicenter of the crisis elsewhere, the rate of infection is rising. Still
44 states are moving forward with lifting restrictions. And tonight President Trump is acknowledging those moves to reopen could lead to even more
deaths. telling reporters today that Americans should quote think of themselves as warriors.
John: Okay, couple of things. First of all, the way she does that report, it makes it sound like there's 20 1000 new cases of the mutant virus
Adam: just the term mutant virus,
John: whoever put this this story together, had her read it across information. So she went from one subject to another. She says that I want you to
play the beginning of this again and listen to this, where she is claiming if the waves just listen to her that there's 20,000 new cases of the mutant
virus.
Unknown: As we come on the air tonight Coronavirus, infections are still growing in much of the country. Just as we're learning there is now a more
powerful mutant strain of the virus.
Adam: By the way, mutant strain mutant strain of
Unknown: the viruses that is even more difficult to treat. There are now more than 20,000 new confirmed cases every day here in the United States. And
more cases are to the
Adam: right, of course, of course, this poor copy
John: never follows up on the information so I have an older clip from democracy now. This is This clip is called source of mutant strain.
Unknown: And a study finds the novel Coronavirus that emerged in China mutated in Europe in February to become more contagious speeding it's spread
around the globe. The report from the Los Alamos National Laboratory also warns the mutated strain could leave people vulnerable to a second infection
of COVID-19. The finding has not been peer reviewed and the director of the National Institutes of Health urge caution saying the study dress sweeping
conclusions about the virus that might not hold up to further scrutiny. The authors of the study said they released the study early so that people who
are working on vaccines could see their results.
John: What to slay me people working on vaccines can see their results. This is bull crap. And stretch this out a little more. Well, if you can't do
it with the new I love the way Nora pronounces mutant. You can't Yeah, you can't. Whoops it goes to Zephyr 167 cars. It was really late that Zephyr is
hours late.
Adam: So that is not a good sign. We like to see a solid nine cars is a stable good economy eight is made is okay is okay. We've had a 10 in the past
seven. I mean at least it's running. It may be late but it's running happy about that later.
John: Why can it be so late? Okay, so here it says it's not bad enough that the mutant strain of the virus is gonna kill you try this one mystery
COVID children's disease.
Unknown: Now a mystery illness that's putting otherwise healthy children in the hospital. More than a dozen children in the New York City area have
ended up in intensive care with severe symptoms, possibly linked to Coronavirus. All this is parents start thinking about camp and school. Here's our
chief medical correspondent dr. john Luke
14 year old jack McMorrow loves music and video games. Two weeks ago a rash on his hands quickly led to a fever of over 104
degrees. He was rushed to the ICU and tested positive for COVID-19. John McMorrow is his father.
John: His heart rate was over 160 it was the scariest point in my life I do is nothing anyone can do. And he prepared me for the worst
Unknown: jack finally responded to steroid treatment. And doctors continue to monitor his heart function at Morgan Stanley Children's Hospital in New
York
will have a very fast heart rate. There'll be they'll have a high fever and if their heart rate still stays very high, they will oftentimes come to
the ICU for extra support.
Researchers are now investigating COVID cases like Jack's and the symptoms of a mysterious illness. It resembles Kawasaki disease. The New York City
Health Department sent out an alert last night describing a pediatric multi system inflammatory syndrome.
Symptoms include persistent fever,
rash, swollen lymph nodes, and inflammation of the heart, eyes, mouth and skin are
John: all gonna die.
Adam: Yeah. Or at least the kids will
John: know kind of distressing shoes.
Adam: Here's what we should do. I think there's always time. In fact, more and more people are are interested in our our way of living these days.
Come on sing along. Hello, DJ.
Unknown: dg
Adam: going off the grid everybody OTG going ot we are going off the real tg we go off the grid we go. And we should start with the tracing and
tracking apps mentioned earlier. Huh. I wish we would have seen something out of South Korea by now what is the point? If it's only to alert people
and throw them into quarantine? Maybe we could learn something thing, there are people who are positive walking around I mean released some data,
please get him Maybe we'll get more from Canada navia. Alberta has launched its tracking and tracing program COVID-19 remains a threat. But there's a
drive to get out to get back to normal. Well, he
Unknown: says, there's now an app that could help.
providing this information voluntarily is crucial to our work to prevent the spread of COVID-19.
Alberta trace together is the first contact tracing app available in North America. Every time users pass one another, their phones record the
encounter using Bluetooth, encrypted data will be stored on the phone. Now if one of those users tests positive for COVID-19, the user can upload
their interactions to HS and contact tracer would call the numbers the phone registered, telling them to self isolate.
Like bringing a camera into focus. These techniques give us a far clearer picture that help us to inform our actions going forward. Now, the
app stores only phone numbers, no locations, it doesn't use GPS. But tracking still raises privacy questions. Alberta's Privacy Commissioner says she
has been involved and she supports enhanced contact tracing. In a statement she adds, in my view, Alberta Health has chosen a less intrusive approach
in deploying this app.
Adam: Okay, what is happening is in every country, the app the same conversation is being had apps are being made and governments are telling their
citizens, you need to give up some of your privacy. So you can whistle you don't die. And pretty much as everyone's going along with it.
John: Yeah. sounds right.
Adam: Sounds right to me. In the Netherlands, literally the government is in the newspaper this morning and an interview with some muckety muck and
said, I'm translating on the fly. Well, we'll have to know everything. And we'll probably even have to know who your who your secret lover is. But
don't worry, we'll keep it secret. That's the headline, because of course, they're gonna know who your lover is because you want to be around that
person.
John: Singapore, these phones are good for
Adam: Singapore is going to require smartphone check ins at all businesses and will log visitors identity numbers. But that, of course, is Singapore.
So that's kind of to be expected. What I think they're doing wrong, is they're they're calling it tracing and tracking. And you and they we've done so
well. We've done social censorship. Right. Everyone understands that. We have social distancing, I would recommend as a representative of the curry
devorah Consulting Group, social surveillance used
John: to I don't like the word surveillance. I would I would think that I
Adam: think social surveillance, I think it will work.
John: I think not. And again, I don't like it. I think you're onto something here is to come up with the term and I think the two of us can do it. But
that's not I like the social part of it. Yeah, when let's show social social must be good. But let's look at some synonyms. Okay?
Adam: synonym for okay. luthy, social sleuthing. We could also use, let's see, contact. Social snitching. Well, that's a good one. I like social
snitching.
John: Yeah, you like it. So okay, we got inspection. Mm hmm. Monitoring is no good. I don't like that either. I like inspection. supervision is a word
is kind of a synonym. spying and espionage. Those are out
Adam: social supervision. No one's gonna no one's gonna fall for that bit.
John: superintendence.
Adam: Now, now that
John: observation, social observation.
Adam: Hmm, yeah, that's getting there. That's that's new or new world? Or, how about social supervision?
John: Well, that's what I said.
Adam: Oh, I missed it. I didn't hear that one. That's pretty good. Then social supervision. What maybe work on trolls aren't helping us socially.
John: They're no good. They're no good at this. This is high level stuff that
Adam: you haven't graduated to top podcast spot.
John: Yeah, we can do this. We can come up with the word that means surveillance, which is what we're talking about. Maybe a synonym without it being
surveillance or what's the other one they're doing? You know, spying, snooping, snitching.
Adam: How about a synonym for tracking? Maybe there's one.
John: How about this for an idea? How about doing what they like to do in Washington where you change the just change the title, so the bill means
it's nothing like the title.
Adam: Yeah, you could do that. But how about social awareness? We do something with that. Okay, let's
John: Start with, let's use the word awareness but put at the beginning. So it'd be awareness. Not awareness monitoring. I don't like that. No, we're
just monitoring social awareness protection.
Adam: Okay, I think we've, you know, what we'll, we'll come back to the, to the brainstorm a little bit later on, we'll work on this,
John: well, then we will get it. Meanwhile,
Adam: companies are also creating their own social, so I'm just going to use it for for, for now, social surveillance inside their own organizations.
several organizations, according to The Wall Street Journal, several organizations are going to be tracking location within people within corporations
within the building to make sure people hear the company aims to have its social distancing app ready, at the end of May, workers movements are
tracked through their smartphones, and you get a higher score, the more time in the office, you are farther than six feet from another person, so
they've gained
John: a phone in the drawer, you're gonna get a raise, you're gonna get a raise.
Adam: No, you have to be around people, but it has to be six feet. So
John: you're standing up on your desk, and the cubicle yelling at people.
Adam: Oh, man, oh, by the way, I, you know, I have this desktop machine in the studio, which really runs runs a boon to in a virtual machine. But we
were scanning some documents yesterday and this, then the windows side of that computer is still configured to this, when the scanner starts it sends
it to that machine. And that's fine, that's good. But then I had to email that to, to myself and to Tina. And so I fire up outlook the machine does is
maintained. It's continuously updated with the windows 10 virus that comes in on Tuesday to update it for your experience. And I got a new experience.
As I found out outlook is now part of Microsoft 365.
John: And we've been a part of 365 for a long
Adam: time, but a window popped up telling me this and told me in order to send an email I had to send I had to log into Microsoft 365. No, I just
want to use Outlook. Well, no. And so and I tried to click New Message. No, it's grayed out.
John: Yeah, you can't do that. What are you trying to do? You're trying to foil the way this is working? I want you to log in.
Adam: I thought outlook was outside of that you could use it for free. It didn't have to pay for Outlook you paid for Well, that's old
John: Outlook Express. No,
Adam: no, no, no. Well, I don't know what happened. But I don't like having to sign into Microsoft to you to send an email.
John: Yeah, I don't blame you. I wouldn't do it. I use squirrel mail.
Adam: Yeah, it's not good. We know what you use. I am fully back to Mutt I map filter and vi baby I love it. And then finally, this is a hot off the
press I do not believe it has. It has been mentioned anywhere yet. But there is a class action lawsuit that's been filed against plaid networks for
selling People's Bank information to third parties. illegally. And it's a class action. This could be now that it's a part of visa with all the all
the different Venmo and all this stuff that fits in that it's connected through the plaid network into banks. And just a reminder, plaid sits in
between your Venmo app or your cash app. And there's many more to make it easy for you to access your bank account, you give that app, your login and
password for your bank account. I know you've all done it. And then that app logs in as if it's you and then acts as if it's on the website as a
person and can make transactions but can do anything at once. And apparently, it has been so this should be the hell with
John: sign up for something like this.
Adam: Well, you people don't know they're signing up for it because they sign up for Venmo and they think okay, I'll just put in my bank password and
I can trust Venmo
John: you give the bank password to anybody else's software. Millions
Adam: of people have done it. Mila I don't know
John: why they would do it. They just be forbidden. Yeah, people should be they need to be taught in school in high school. Yeah, yeah. Not to do
that. Don't give your bank password to anybody. I always got a kick. What was that software that came out some years back I there's I but eight years
ago, it was some sort of it managed all your money and it did all these crazy things. And it was like and it required you to turn over your bank pass.
Well,
Adam: there's a number of these there plugins. A lot of millennials use them and then it'll manage they'll say, Oh, well I can get you a cheaper deal
on this. And looks like you're paying too much for your insurance. Let me find you a cheaper deal, because it's continuously in your account looking
at your transactions?
John: I don't think so. Oh, yes.
What do you mean? nobody in their right mind would give that.
Adam: You have no idea how successful these companies are.
John: Oh, yeah. They should be investigated. Pew pew. Alright, let's play the Keighley that one thing that did one count off be I can say that to the
end?
Adam: Well, no, no, let's play not Do you have the whole thing even when the journalists don't
John: have to hold the yelling at the
Adam: end when the journalists are yelling at her at the end?
John: Yeah. All right. All right. So this Kaley taking a question? And I'm thinking this woman by like, she is a little bit over made out. But it's
it's funny. But I like her because she's not putting up with any bullcrap. And she decided I think you should meet. We're gonna have to see if she has
a pattern here. But I think the pattern would be the following. I think this is what she should adopt. Somebody has a snarky question. That's got
nothing to do with anything. It's just a stupid snarky question. So you answer it with a blast that you have pre prepared because you know that you
see the question coming. You have it pre prepared. And then because it was a snarky question, and because you blasted them, you finished with a big
blast, and you leave the room. I'm out of here, folks. I'm here all the week and walk out on them. And that's what she did.
Unknown: previous life before you were press secretary work for the campaign.
And you made a comment I believe on Fox in which you said President Trump will not allow the Coronavirus to come to this country.
Given what has
happened since then, obviously.
Adam: Would you like to take that back?
Unknown: Well, first let me note I was asked a question on Fox Business about presidents travel restrictions. I noted what was the intent behind those
travel restrictions which is we will not see the Coronavirus come here. We will not see terrorism come here referring to an earlier set of travel
restrictions. I guess I would turn the question back on the media and ask similar questions does Vox want to take back that they proclaim that the
Coronavirus would not be a deadly pandemic? Is the Washington Post's want to take back that they told Americans to get a grip the flu is bigger than
the Coronavirus which is the Washington Post likewise want to take back that our brains are causing us to exaggerate the threat of the Coronavirus to
the New York Times want to take back that fear of the virus may be spread spreading faster than the virus itself. Does NPR want to take back that the
flu was a much bigger threat than the Coronavirus. And finally, once again, the Washington Post would they like to take back but the government should
not respond aggressively to the Coronavirus? I'll leave you with those questions and maybe you'll have some answers. And a few days.
Adam: So what you didn't hear at the end we've got cut off right at the end one of the journalists was yelling you you you weren't prepared for the
question. How'd you know?
John: I didn't I watched it. I would got to the actual press conference. Yes. Right at the end. And I never heard that. Wait, I heard that I left it
on.
Adam: Well, I see. It's interesting, because I heard it and I saw you had the clip. So then I decided not to clip it. But you can hear that question.
Right. The last thing you hear
you started here you were prepared. Yeah. Which he was obviously. So it's kind of fun to show the press corps that they have leaks as well. It does
work in reverse reverse because she absolutely knew that was coming. She didn't hesitate for a second on that.
John: No, she went right to it. She had a page of all the notes.
Adam: So well. The hostility has started them with her that she'll be interesting. I I was not I expected her to get steamrolled. And I am clearly
wrong. We'll see how she does.
John: I I looked at her background I didn't think so she she has one of those. She has a certain mean girl style that is usually can take it and she's
smart. If you look at her background, she's smart. So she's a smart mean, girl. This is not somebody you're going to be able to blow Blow away. Oh,
see?
Adam: Well, at least we have a different setting, you know, at least someone else's answering some questions. A little tired of the president and his
hanging chads. But the media is this kind of I guess it's been happening for a while but I only put the two together and realize that there's a new
style in news opinion shows, although they appear on news networks, specifically CNN and MSNBC. So there's these are news news outfits. And and it
goes like this. You talk to the President for some reason. These Talking Heads now believe that it's they should be telling the president what to do
and they're they're looking into the camera and talking Talking to the President. Have you seen this
John: Don Lemon? Does this john lemon
Adam: and he did a very interesting one the other night, then I just want to it's 45 seconds. But you can he's looking right in the camera. And it's
just Yeah,
John: I saw that I didn't clip it by should have that you this is a good clip.
Unknown: What is it about President Obama that really
Adam: gets under your skin?
Unknown: Is it because he's smarter than you?
better educated,
made it on his own, didn't need daddy's help. At all.
Wife is more accomplished.
Adam: This is the kind of thing you don't say to a guy's face. Because you could beat him. better looking.
Unknown: I don't know, what is it? What is it about him? And he's a black man that's accomplished. became president.
Wow.
And he punked you on the whole birth certificate thing?
What is it about him?
Just wondering.
Adam: This is a very odd thing he's doing but I believe it's very successful with the audience he has I think they like it. I think they really dig
that he's doing this.
John: I don't think it brings a new audience though. I mean, no, no, no, no, no, no, he has this. They're locking their audience down and the audience
is small. Yes.
Adam: is about half of MSNBC, which is half of Fox. But speaking of msnbc morning, Joe is now doing the same thing. In morning, Joe, and this is just
a minute, but it went on for five, six minutes is talking to the President.
Unknown: Obviously, Donald,
you didn't want to hear that again.
I know. I've been saying it a lot. And you actually tweeted something
extraordinarily cruel. He's literally
Adam: talking as if he's talking to someone on a on a video chat. It's very odd. And meek is going like like Diamond and Pearl bow. Yeah. Preach.
Yeah, you go.
Unknown: I know you meant to be extraordinarily cruel to me. by attacking me. weaken My God. Diamonds. So
you're supposed to have a working weekend.
You got it wrong. Again. You
said 50,000 deaths 60,000
deaths.
Now you're saying 100,000 deaths. What
John: was your working weekend? What did you do during your working weekend? Well,
Unknown: when you tweeted more hateful things about colleagues of ours. You tweeted conspiracy theories about Jeffrey Epstein. Really you have time
for this. You tweeted conspiracy theories about Barack Obama. Really you have time for this? You attacked George W. Bush
for simply sending out a unifying message. This President, I ask that you get checked out.
I ask that you take a rest.
I ask that you take care of yourself, maybe let Mike Pence run things for the next week. You're not well.
Adam: It's a very odd form of journalism that is taking place.
John: Well, it's obviously not journalism. It's these guys that they think so highly of themselves that they feel obliged to do this. And everybody
wants to be wants to editorialize. I mean, you can go to Lionel's nation. If you want to hear this sort of thing from Lionel, the crazy lawyer who
likes to scream at the camera. Yeah. And he's got some very good rants on there. And he's holed up in like in his basement much like Biden is in his
basement. The it but they're more entertaining than this, because it guy knows what he's doing. I had this reminded me of the clip of morning in
America, which I don't have the whole thing I do have I have the democracy now report of it. And this is that group, the Lincoln project.
Adam: This is the George Conway's
John: group, George Conway. And so at Amy, the way she structures her her commentary on the sheet needs to this morning report is great, because all
these smart Republicans hate Trump. And then of course, she uses the word lashes out and then she gives an example at the end, which is not Trump
lashing out at all. In fact, this whole lashing out thing with Trump is nonsense, but this is a I'm gonna play this clip. This is Amy talking about
that. And that includes a small clip of morning in America, and then she reads a Trump Trump tweet. I don't know if these people know that these
tweets are extremely funny. And they see him as like some negative horrible thing and I think Morning Joe, was everybody's hates these tweets. Yeah,
here we go.
Unknown: President Trump is lashing out against a new advertisement by a republican led group called the Lincoln project calling out his mismanagement
of the coronavirus pandemic. The one minute ad is titled morning in America. spin on Ronald Reagan's 1984 campaign slogan
there's morning
America
under the leadership of Donald Trump,
our country's weaker
and sicker.
Americans are asking if we have another four years length this
morning in America ad spelled mo u r and i n j and a series of angry tweets posted just after midnight, Tuesday morning. Trump attack the makers of
the ad singling out George Conway, longtime Trump critic husband of White House counselor Kellyanne Conway. Trump tweeted quote, I don't know what
Kellyanne did to her deranged loser if a husband moon face but it must have been really bad Trump tweeted.
Adam: He said that before but to hear me say it is better. It is
John: far left progressive. He's read Trump tweets. It's just dynamite.
Adam: Isn't this just pure controlled opposition? If you really look at it. I mean, that that's that's I keep thinking this is controlled opposition?
John: I don't think it is, I think is because it did control opposition really resides on msnbc. Which is more representative the democrat party as a
whole. Well, Amy may be a Democrat. She's really a Bernie bro. No, but I mean, no, I
Adam: mean, the Lincoln group, the Lincoln group is,
John: is real for sure.
Adam: That's controlled opposition, isn't it? I
John: mean, there's I but who's controlling the control?
Adam: Kellyanne Conway?
John: I don't know. Maybe he,
Adam: okay, that this cannot be a healthy relationship.
John: I don't there may be something to the theory that this is all planned and controlled. Because to him, he's insulting Kellyanne, and George in
that little tweet, in a funny kind of a way calling me a loser and you know, your husband, you don't want to hit if you work for somebody and you call
somebody calls your husband a loser. Face moonface loser of a husband. I don't know. Maybe I find it amusing. I like the tweets are funnier than that
stupid morning in America thing.
Adam: It's morning in America. And there's 1000 points of light. I was I was shocked. I will say shocked that Project Veritas comes out with the big
news with undercover video and voice altered witnesses that CBS faked a shot.
John: Oh, no. This I'm shocked. shocked.
Adam: This is so what a waste. So that and I got a minute from their from their teaser report. Well just listen to it. We've this happens five times a
day at least.
Unknown: You're telling me you're 100% certain that CBS News CBS News Corp national staged a fake event they fake the news. They think the reality and
broadcasted that to all of their audience last Friday on CBS This Morning. Only six
states have reported more cases than Michigan. But fewer than 2% of its people have been tested for the virus. In our series on the state of
Coronavirus testing. Adriana Diaz shows how Michigan is trying to improve a system that has failed some of its people. But the governor says testing
above all else will help determine when to fully reopen.
Adam: Alright, so the whole report is this bad. And I mean, what happened is they were going to do a shot of a line of cars waiting to test to be
tested for Coronavirus. And there was almost no one there. So CBS arranged a whole bunch of fake cars and patients. And of course, sadly, there were
some actual people who were waiting for about an hour because of the shenanigans who really were patients who needed to be tested.
John: Yeah, I drove past the Berkeley testing thing which is that no cars zero not even one car I was gonna drive through just ask him a few
questions. I should have brought my little camcorder. Did
Adam: you hear this but this Veritas would like the heartbeat music you know?
John: Women, that one woman who I can't remember her name, but she does a bunch of videos on YouTube. As she did the expos and showing all these the
day before shot. You know, all these people lined up. The ambulances are coming in and that next day a bunch of
Adam: locals. Yeah, there we go. It was unbelievable. We went to the site of the CBS news crew there. They were lining up cars, but they weren't cars
of patients. No. They were cars of interns. They were manipulating the media to make it look like there was a lot of people being tested. This was
false. We have an eyewitness.
I mean, come on, you're insulting me.
John: Jeez, it would have been better if it was like in all the cars there were all driven by the dead.
Adam: And that is exactly why we are non commercial. We don't have to do dumb crap to get people to watch or pay attention. I'm going to
John: show my little by donating to no agenda. Imagine all the people who could
Unknown: do. Oh, yeah, that'd be fun.
John: But one thing we have to do is thank those who helped us
Adam: get the show going. And that's a pleasure. That's the that's the highlight of the show. For me.
John: Often it is especially with Joseph Salazar, in India, India, Atlantic, India, Atlantic. Where's that in Florida? Ooh, I don't know where that
does have a call up. I want to call out. Dougie fresh as a douchebag. Shout out to claymation the corona survivor Can you please tell me the show
number? Where clips of the Johns Hopkins virus pandemic walkthrough meeting booked took place if you can get a chance. Go to the shownotes. Explain
how to do that. Adam. Yeah,
Adam: go to na shownotes.com look
John: it up.
Adam: Look it up. Yes. And look it up. Damn it. There you go.
John: Yeah, just shown us and there's a search engine you can look up. Well, you
Adam: know what I'm sorry to say the search engine has been abandoned by its developer. Oh, yeah. Yeah, being it.io. I've redirected that there is
another place that's pretty good. If you if you actually go to Bing it.io or rohner, radio.com. There's, there's a new nogen. That's it's actually no
agenda experience is just a placeholder. But there's transcripts in there that you can search very easily just know, find Ctrl F in your search, and
then you click on that link, and immediately it starts playing on that word. So it's a search, and it's a player all in one. Can't beat it. Not
really.
John: And the point is, is that we don't know when that we ran it. We don't do that. We know we're not archivists in that sense. We have the systems
we,
Adam: we provide all of our data in structured format, opml, it's available, the show notes and everything is available and people put that together
and can create great things except we our developer just lost interest I guess. And and as of January 1, it hasn't been updated. Well, poor thing.
John: Christopher Kessler's Next on the list from Marshfield, Wisconsin $124, Cassia Grizz, Gazelle, Scott Gazelle, Sky think and effort Pennsylvania
12399.
Adam: I think it's Grizzly Grizzly, aka
John: Davis, like Drake. Yes is a tough one. To run into a pronounced theater. David Drake in Midlothian, Virginia 12345 Daniel Walraven 12345 and
Eindhoven bought out from Daniel Wallace Eindhoven.
Adam: It's actually from his wife he says after hitting her in the mouth for months well thank you Daniel's wife.
John: Yeah. nonnamous in Colorado spit. I must be Colorado Springs but since Colorado 10101 Meredith Talbot 100. My fiance Brandon loves your show. He
plan to donate to become a knight but he passed away. Oh my god for 2120 Please accept just donation in his honor. Okay.
Adam: Oh, Meredith.
John: That's terrible. Well,
Adam: we need emergency karma for Meredith and all the families this horrible news and thank you very much. But Wow, sorry about that.
Unknown: You've got karma
Adam: to probably say love and light. Stuff like that. He would get a chuckle out of it.
John: They probably, sir be even our or be winner. Not sure he's in East Berlin, Pennsylvania. $100. It's got a birthday coming up.
Adam: He also has he has a call out for Butch. Hmm.
John: I see the beginning. All douchebags he's got written on man Andy
Unknown: and Jerry.
Adam: Come on guys. He says value for value. Yo,
Unknown: got it.
John: We got an F cancer call. I will put that at the end for you.
Adam: Oh a friend Ryan who also recently lost his life battle with cancer. And he says,
John: Jen yeah genosha Moser on Frankfurt I'm on Main $93 Deutschland Mm hmm. Ali breedlove and Columbia, Virginia 85 Dena Isabel got a birthday
sisters Oregon 6033 Mika Meyers and birren Bremen, Alabama 606. Me Megan Kendall in Sandy, Utah to the 85 got another birthday. A lot of birthdays
today. Yeah. Danilo. shashwat
Adam: Australia. Thanks for cork Ireland.
John: She's in Cork in Ireland
Adam: 5555 and has a call out I would like to call out Mark kremens as a douchebag he's been listening for a year and to my knowledge has not yet
donated I've been keeping an eye in the sale for his donations but haven't seen any. And that is a Dutch ism. Keeping an eye in the sale and Okay,
upset about sale. howdah
John: talking about Dutch Yep. john paul della ha, della Hey, in a bourbon. This slaving okay.
Adam: In the right this laughing Beverly, Beverly this Latin which is actually not a place he just tricked you into saying free the slaves.
John: You tricky Dutch. Stephen shevlin in Southampton he's, by the way he's in 5555 Stephen shevlin in Southampton, Massachusetts. 5520 Sir
Christopher Barron of Brown County Green Bay, Wisconsin 2510. And I'll bet you that your quarterback. Are you going to lose your quarterback? Sure
Sean desantis Night of the Northern Everglades Fort Pierce, Florida 5510. Lord Michael gates barren of the rest of Colorado, in Colorado Springs 50 to
80 Jason Dean in Mesa, Arizona 5151 Justin and he's got a birthday. Justin boots zelinsky in permission waka Mishawaka, Indiana 5123 Jason Deluce, sir
Jason deluzy on chatard, Pennsylvania 50 and these are all $50 donors from here on out name and location, starting with Jason and Baronet sir lineman
of the net, Raleigh Hawk and Anna, Illinois. Glen Graham, sir Matthew, Jana Zhu ski has been with us forever. Christopher Rivera in Austin, your buddy
in Austin, Texas, Edward mazurek and Memphis Tennessee braid bread Brady Schroeder in Milton, Georgia, and Mary huie. A great name Scott Grice in
Starkville, Mississippi, sir Jonathan Meyer in Xenia, Ohio. And last but not least, Jeff Neff. Oh, James Neff. And I was just looking for a rhyme.
James Neff in Hanover, Pennsylvania. In entry, I ln 70 threes from Hanover. So I want to thank all these folks for making the show for 1240. worth
doing. Thank you very much.
Adam: It's well worth doing. Yes, thank you to all of these producers and to the producers who came in under $50. That's a sure way to keep your name
off the list because that's where we cut off for for mentions for anonymity. But also there's many with the subscriptions, the plans that eventually
get them to knighthood and Dame hood and it's extremely important, if you can to do one of those it has to base that keeps us rolling throughout the
high times in the low times. And thank you again for all of your courage. We will be here again on Sunday. You can support us please go to John
dvorak.org. Slash and a Dan some jobs and Kent f cancer requests.
Unknown: Here we go.
jobs, jobs, jobs and jobs. Let's vote for jobs.
Karma.
Adam: The right side the jingles I can see out of that. All right, here we go. Here's your birthdays today being of course the seventh of may 2020. We
say happy birthday to David Walsh. She celebrates tomorrow. Even our says Happy birthday was smoking hot girl My wife Carrie. She turned 42 today
Dennis. denna Isabelle Happy Birthday to her husband who's turning 60 Megan Kendall to the love of her life john Kendall 35 tomorrow and finally Jason
Dean says Happy Birthday to his son Ryan. He will be turning 20 tomorrow Happy Birthday to everybody here at the best podcast in the universe
Unknown: don't want to be
Adam: titled title changes today for the parents lady Cara week apart because lady Cara of the clean with her new occupational hazard job answer
Rowley of Weybridge now becomes thoroughly of Crystal Palace Slayer of the concrete dinosaurs. And we have one two, we've got four now what do we have
three? Three things for today. So we've got our Rona
John: blade Yep, my three first sword Here you go.
Adam: Wait a minute. Yes. Okay, I got it. Let's go. Up on the podium please. Scott Porter, anonymous and David waltz. All three of you are about to
join the illustrious club known as the no agenda, knights and names of the round table because of your support and the amount of $1,000 or more and b
are very, very proud to pronounce the cane you guys as sir Scott of the High Plains, Captain Luke Knight of the Barbary Coast. And sir Dave have the
Gold Coast for you hookers and blow rent boys and Chardonnay, grandpa and manicotti rabbit meeting goat milk brown cheese aka beat and smiley faces
and toffee Baka vanilla buggy to bourbon, sparkling cider ness, horse trailer, breast milk and pavlin. ruminants woman Rosie the mutton and Mead. It's
always here. It is a roundtable favorite. And thank you for supporting the show. This is great, really is it's unexpected often. Well, but please go
to no agenda nation.com slash rings and give Eric the show all your info. So we can get that to you as soon as possible. I have one important topic
for for these remaining moments we have. And it's an A das related topic, American descendants of slavery. This came up on the mo show and of course,
it didn't hit my twitter and didn't hit your Twitter. But this is about a move in the political space or a move of a movement. And we've been tracking
that the democrats need the black vote. They lost some of it, I think, not a substantial enough amount during the previous election, that it made
people pay attention. But as you know there are a lot of African American descendants of slavery who are considering not voting for the democrat party
doesn't mean they're voting for somebody else. But that they will no longer hand over their vote without and hear the key words to look out for
tangibles. Like give us something that's really for us. Or reparations, I would say is the that is that is the big ask. And it's not being listened to
is not being discussed, Joe Biden came out with his that Biden for black America plan which believe it or not mentioned the word reparations. And but
it was in the context of doing another study to see what we should what should be done who should get it so that
John: that's not gonna fly. We need more studies.
Adam: But Diddy came out on he was doing, which is funny if you know Diddy, but he was on a live stream with Nomi campbellton kind of Rona, let's hang
out together and do a zoom video everyone can participate in and here's what he said the Blackboard
Unknown: is not gonna be for free. We're gonna have to see some promises. You know, what are we getting in return five vote, and nothing has changed
for black America. And in order for us to vote for Biden, we can't be taken for granted like we always are because we're supposed to be Democrats, or
because people are afraid and Trump is whoever is going to take care of our community. Whoever wants to make a deal. This is business at this point.
You know, we can choose politicians, you know, so we want to know very clearly, just like Trump made it clear that he wanted to build a wall. The body
needs to make it clear that he's going to change the lives and quality of life of black and brown people obviously can't get the boat. I will hold the
boat hostage if I
said it here that at first.
John: Breaking News. Breaking News.
Adam: Aditi is no stranger to the voting process. He's done a lot of a lot of campaigns over the years people do listen to him. He's no slouch I think
they should be worried about him.
John: Got a lot to be worried about?
Unknown: Yeah,
John: yeah, maybe they should be. I don't know what they're gonna do I think about this is like, what are these guys gonna do? They got this. They got
it they got the country on, you know, just beaten by this virus and shut down everything that mean that that's weakens Trump's position but then
they've come up with a candidate like Biden, although I think it's, you know, you could point out that most of the people they're going to vote for
Biden don't even know what a bumbling idiot that he is because they don't get to see those clips. Because they won't show them to them. The mainstream
media is all in for bite into democratic big wigs are all in for Biden, and they're just hoping for the best. They're hoping for a fluke. And then of
course, he'll die and the the vice president became president. So that's the first you got to really keep an eye on Did you see the I don't think any
of this is gonna happen to be honest about it. I think it's gonna be a one sided slaughter. And Biden's out.
Adam: Did you see the New York Times opinion letters to the editor? And this was Joe Biden and Tara Reid, whom to believe. And the letters to the
editor included. I mean, this is the one they published The New York Times published these letters to the editor. And you know, it was very clear that
this you know, that you got to listen to something's going on here. So we have to investigate this. Thank you for this editorial. For the record. I'm
a lifelong Democrat and will vote Democrat this fall regardless, defeating Donald Trump and saving our democracy is the most important thing. However,
we do still need a full transparent investigation. I totally agree with this editorial. I don't want an investigation. I want a coronation of Joe
Biden. What do you make a great president unlikely? What do you make a good president? Good enough? What do you make a president better than the
present occupant? Absolutely. I don't want justice whatever that way may be I want to win. The removal of Donald Trump from office and Mr. Biden is
our best chance. By the way, that's Martin Tolson who was a former reporter for The New York Times. And they published and they published it with his
name, and it says the writer is a former reporter from the New York Times.
John: Well, they probably felt obliged to do that because of the disclosure stuff they like to do. That's crazy. And so there's probably a here's the
discussion when you're in the middle, you're putting it just one person usually the actually the editor does take part in some of these letters,
because they like to slant the perspective. And so they had this discussion is Oh, this is a great letter. Look at us, he slams Trump to hold things.
Isn't that one of our old writers? Should we just pull this one and run a different one now you know, I kind of like it. All we have to do is just put
the disclaimer in there. That good letter that we want to put it in there no one's good. nobody reads us is gonna think anything about it. Whereas
anybody who is not a normal stooge for the time is it what kind of corruption is this? Why don't you just have the editor write up phony letter
yourself for himself? Sorry. Yeah, well, I got some news. I got some news. I have a well, I got a kind of a kick out of the Well, here's the well
here's that clip I wanted to play earlier in the show. This is the new york dead and the vaccine This is one I was cringing is 24 second clip. Okay.
Unknown: CBS is more or less it is going to lead us off tonight. In New York City Mola,
Laura wall deaths in New York are down significantly from their peak just a few weeks ago, we're
still losing more than 200 people a day to this virus. So many dead bodies
are being stored in makeshift morgues like those white refrigerator trucks that you see behind me there and that is why there is so much hope in this
experimental new vaccine that could be ready by this fall.
John: Give it to me Bill Gates I read and they got some guy getting shot up with it. cringing watching this clip. Oh, brother. Okay, so my ended up
unless you have some for the industry. I got two clips, I finished things off.
Adam: I just want to end with commentary. I would just like to run through one bit of information then both of your clips are good to go. Now I have
one bit of information and the clip then you're good to go. Well, that work? Fine. Okay. A bit of information. Why Michael Flynn, remember we asked
this question. Why was he so
John: we get the theories are rolling? Yes. Well, this is from
Adam: our military intelligence. Okay, who knows Flynn Personally, I can attest to that. This is Agent Orange. And he says here is why it's a one to
five point list. One.
John: I'm glad that he's chimed in, by the way.
Unknown: Yeah. One.
Adam: He knows what happened in Libya, and how Hillary Clinton moved weapons from Libya to Syria when she was running. State Department. He knows how
Ukraine played. And this is verbatim. He knows how Ukraine played a vital role in supplying moderate rebels in Tunisia and Egypt for the Arab Spring.
Three, he knows the last man pads in Libya were repurchased and the CIA gave them to Qatar who sold them to the Taliban that shot down a US chopper
with them with a whole SEAL team on them. For he knows, oops, for he knows who gave the stand down order regarding Ben Ghazi. And finally, he was
going to audit the intelligence agencies. I think that says enough.
John: That sounds right. I like the whole list. It's a good
Adam: a good list.
John: Anything to keep us from speculating is a plus. Yep.
Adam: And then this is my final story, where political correctness and over socialization has just gone too far. In my book, this is Alaska. Hated
Alaska,
Unknown: who vote by the mat su borough school district Wednesday night, did two things it removed the New York Times Learning Network from Teacher
Resources and getting more attention. It removed five books from the curriculum, the cost per sale because of words like rape and incest and sexual
references and language and things that are pretty serious problems, especially in our teenage world novels in question. I Know Why the Caged Bird
Sings catch 22 Invisible Man, Things They Carried. And that's Scott Fitzgerald's The Great Gatsby, which is one of the top 10 most read books amongst
high school students in the nation.
Adam: It's really baffling that this is taking place.
John: Well, those are seminal books. Well, they've been taken out of curriculum Catcher in the Rye, which is a very important book that kids read No,
Adam: no catch. 22 The catch 22 not Catcher in the Rye catch. 22 Catcher in the Rye, catch. 22 catch.
John: 22 is a fantastic course. It's
Adam: a great book.
John: It shows you the ludicrous nature of certain kinds of bureaucracies. Ah, that
Adam: would be the problem.
John: And then you have the Invisible Man, which is a I'm assuming it's the Invisible Man the great novel by Ralph Ellison. Yes. And yeah, no, this is
lutego they didn't go so catch 22 still okay.
Adam: No catch. 20 No,
John: I'm sorry, Gabe. I still okay.
Adam: Yeah, but Maya Angelou is not okay. And The Great Gatsby, because because of The Great Gatsby is minor.
John: I mean, it's a great book. It's a great structure, but it's always taught in English classes. For its balance, it's one of the best structured
novels ever written. But it but in terms of the rape and all the rest of it, it's like it's not what the books about Okay. Well, they got something
wrong with him up there then. Sounds like Texas. Hey, hey,
Unknown: I don't think so. You take it by the way, take that back. I'm sorry, Texas. Yes.
John: Okay, I get to two clips. I wonder am I meant to play last time last show I'm playing it now. There's the San Francisco protests over hotels.
Okey
Adam: dokey.
Unknown: In California medical students and doctors with the UC San Francisco do not harm coalition staged to die and outside the home of San
Francisco Mayor London breed Wednesday to protest her refusal to swiftly move unhoused people into hotel rooms. The dying lasted 30 minutes to
symbolize 30,000 vacant hotel rooms in the city that could be used to house the homeless during the pandemic. The protesters also hold a moment of
silence for three unhoused people in San Francisco who've died of COVID-19.
John: So that's because the hotels heard about this scheme. And they said no, no, we're not going to do that. And they breathe doesn't know how to
make them do it. They can't make them do it. They don't and they can't make them do it. So the whole things that fell apart that whole idea. Now the
last one which is the best flip. Aha is the California beaches clip.
Adam: Of course it is
Unknown: in California Governor Gavin Newson has ordered beaches in Orange County closed after crowds defied social distancing rules. California
reported 95 more Coronavirus deaths over the most recent 24 hour period.
Yes, the beaches are back.
Yeah,
John: except in Orange County. Screw republicans are so you close those beach of course.
Adam: Of course you got to close that. All right, well keep your social distance everybody. So the social surveillance can make sure that you are good
to go. And we'll take care of the social censorship and we will return here. Well, yes, we will return here on Sunday we will bring you another jam
packed show, no doubt deconstruction, whatever takes place in the next two days. And I will do it here from Austin, Texas where I am. It's the
frontier opportunity zone 33 FEMA Region number six and all the governmental maps. Remember us that divorce.org slash na in the morning, everybody.
I'm Adam Curry,
John: and from Northern Silicon Valley where? I don't know it's a nice day and people should be out. I'm John Dvorak
Adam: return Sunday right here on no agenda. Again remember us at the voracek.org slash na until then adios Mo.
Unknown: And
Adam: by the way, I should mention we have Jesse coin Nelson in the mix, and after the show on no agenda stream.com random thoughts. Where's the beef?
Adios, everybody.
Unknown: Both the mayor and the governor only had the right to enforce 30 days stay at home. They're now abusing their power.
We mean business and we are going to shut this down one way or the other.
Don't be stupid.
We will cite you.
And if we need to.
We will arrest you and we will take you to jail.
What do you
call yourself a progressive, but you show for yourself to Brooklyn.
Seriously, you
guys have a park you live in the middle of a park. You don't need to not essentially travel to Brooklyn.
This is the epitome of non essential travel.
You're getting too close to me to be socially distant.
Now y'all, can we just get real? Do we really care about our fans? Or is this just another deal? Just another way that we lost our way
to people remember we are people do you really need another life?
Adam: To show up everywhere. I hope that we never forget that I live forever.
Unknown: Mary McCoy
Adam: mopho.org
Unknown: slash n a
spaceforce