Unknown: Oh, no.
Adam: Adam Curry jauncey devora Sunday May 10 2020. This is your award winning gitmo-nation Media
Unknown: assassination Episode
Adam: 1200 40.
Unknown: This is no agenda
Adam: on muzzled and broadcasting live from opportunity zone 33 here in the frontier of Austin, Texas capital of the drone Star State in the morning,
everybody. I'm Adam
John: Curry in from Northern Silicon Valley where everybody's wearing masks. And you know, there's a smile under that mask of John Dvorak. Yes.
Adam: The right topic off the bat. I am on muzzled, I will not be muzzled, and you don't have to be muzzled. The official word is in wearing a mask in
public is not desired. This is Dr. Anthony Fauci on 60 minutes, right now in the United States, people should not be walking around with masks, you're
sure of it, because people are listening really closely to them.
John: And right now, people should not be worried there's no reason to be walking around with a mask. When you're in the middle of an outbreak.
wearing a mask might make people feel a little bit better. And it might even block a droplet. But it's not providing the perfect protection that
people think that it is. And often there are unintended consequences. People keep fiddling with the mask and they keep touching their face, then can
you get some schmutz is sort of staying inside their horse, of course, but when you think mask, you should think of healthcare providers needing them
and people who are ill.
Adam: There can be no question. No mask, and as a handy resource. I have made no masks.org. And if you go there, I shall do with myself. No masks.org
you will see a copy of that video, you will have an audio there. And you can bookmark and bookmark that as a handy little resource when someone gives
you crap. And you say oh yeah, look at Tony Fauci, bitch.
John: I like to wear you put a byline on it.
Unknown: Hey,
Adam: it's not really by design. It's otherwise you can't have a title without the byline. That's just some way this is
John: a cheap generator.
Adam: No, excuse me, this is the freedom controller not some cheap generator.
John: Thank you very much. It's your controller you should be able to have it
Adam: should be able to control it. Yes, I know. I know. I'm working on it. I'm working on it. Anyway. So there it is. That is the definitive answer.
It is from May 6. Nothing has changed since then. Fauci, in fact, is not even on the scene. He is in quarantine. How handy is that? When everybody
wants to just when everybody wants him to testify. All of a sudden, ya know, I Ts someone was exposed. So I have to self quarantine. It's just one of
those coincidental little things. It's kind of fun.
Unknown: timing.
Adam: So everyone is not walking around here in a mask. I would say about 50% of the people.
John: Yeah, well, you have you should probably sounds maybe it could be right. I mean, here it's 100%. Yeah. Except some of the homeless and they're
not walking around in messages yelling at people. Yeah, and shaking their fist. Everyone else is wearing a mask. happily. They're all happily wearing
masks.
Adam: This is this is so not a good idea. The more I think about it now that now that we have the official medical advice. I mean, you agree with me,
right? That is the guy who makes the call.
John: Correct. He is the referee. Oh, okay. Yes, he's
Adam: the referee. He's the guy that makes the call. He said no mask. It was very clear. We have a mask ordinance in Austin, which is illegal because
the state overruled it. But still they're gonna try and shame you and do all kinds of
John: Democrats. I
Adam: don't know if it's just because the democrats This is what
John: is reason around here.
Adam: It's something in the water and
John: the republicans Try not to
Adam: you think that's the delineation? It's not just people who are
John: won't be mythologized? Yep.
Adam: Yeah. Yes. Sadly, you're probably somewhat right. But but the protest is everywhere. People want to they want out, they're done. They don't want
to hear it anymore. They want to get back to work. They want to get back to life. They're just not taking it anymore. boots on the ground Pennsylvania
from one of our producers gonna
John: kill people.
Adam: People have had enough The overwhelming majority of deaths in Pennsylvania have been in nursing homes. The hospitals were never overrun. In
fact, they are furloughing people and hospitals are losing money by the billions due to canceled elective surgeries. not unique to Pennsylvania. We
were told that even with social distancing, there was a huge chance would overload the simple system, and it simply didn't happen. And yet, the
governor just extended the stay at home order until June 4, without any data to back it up.
John: 3457 are down,
Adam: man, the day that eight comes I'll be I'll be hooting and hollering seven cars Step seven car economy on
John: we have a we have a friend that works for NHS. And she says that it's same thing hospitals are empty. I suppose it must be a pocket someplace
where there's a full hospital full. And she says what's pathetic, is that people like there's one example recently there's this big empty hospital
places big is empty. And some guy had a stroke. So they brought him in, but because of all the rules his wife or nobody can see him so he's stuck in
there by himself. And he's half out of it. And he's wondering where everybody is. He's wondering if he's dead. My dad, where's my wife and my dad and
he's just pathetic. She says this is so sad. And this is going on all over the Great Britain with this these people because you can't just
Adam: go and see him. So if your assertion is correct, and I'm going to say in California I bet it is that it's political. The mask is a political
thing. That is so a
John: political group because the people who were the master responsible and the people don't wear their masks and want to kill everybody now horrible
Republican. Okay. So
Adam: you could say that both of these groups are acting rather cultish. Right, one says, We're the smart cult and you got to wear the mask and the
other says we're not a part of the cult and they have their own cult I guess.
John: You know true. I don't think that non match words are not part of a cult.
Adam: Okay, well that even strengthens this argument Truthstream media put together a cool little video it's in the show notes and a show notes calm
John: it's just a talking cat.
Adam: No, it's not the talking cat. Like as good though. Ladies and gentlemen. Do not despair. No agenda show has the talking cat coming up in just a
moment standby. They did a bit on cults and how people are initiated so initiation rituals into cults. So they, they kind of mashed up the idea of
what's going on now with the video while reading a very traditional piece of work about initiation rituals in the cult. And I just picked up this one
minute clip from it
Unknown: necessary for new members to function properly in the society they are being inducted into are all imbued at this time.
Repetition is typical, as its use helps hammer the spell home.
the wearing of masks may be required. masking has traditionally played an important role in rituals of this kind.
Enabling and hastening the suppression of ego to help facilitate a death of the old identity before the identification with and manifestation of a new
one. Disguised under a mask and hidden away the initiator is more easily able to transcend the self pushed further toward that invisible line between
the physical and spiritual realms.
Adam: I'm all in on this now um, so I this this mask thing no no this mass thing is a very bad idea. It's a very bad idea people have to wake up to
what's going on here we're so preconditioned forget just
John: how bad I think it is. Especially around here. Ya know if you see it there, but I'm sure you do. You have these morons. And I'll use the term
driving in their cars by themselves with a mascot.
Adam: Yes, john. We have
John: a windows are up.
Adam: Yes, we? Well, you don't want the ronin to fly in and hit you in the face. Do you know and also the air is off? No, no, you can't have any air
on it's just your hot box and down the road with your mask. I've seen it. Yes, I've seen it. So we make kind of a sport of it now to see okay. Did you
go in without a mask? Yeah, hell yeah. I did. The people aren't yelling yet they're not not yelling yet. But anyway, the preconditioning that producer
Justin, who's obviously a gamer or he was a gamer around 2000 said, there's so much stuff that has been in the, in the psyche. For so long. This is
the game DOS, dos x that gets some kind of combat game whenever and here's a little clip your appointment to FEMA should be finalized within the week.
I've already discussed the matter with the senator.
Unknown: I take it he was agreeable. He didn't really have a choice as he'd been infected. Oh, yes.
Adam: Most certainly when I mentioned that we could put him on the priority list for the Ambrosia vaccine. He was so willing, it was almost pathetic.
This play, the writing's intensifying to the point where we may not be able to contain it. Why contain
Unknown: it, let it spill over into the schools and churches Let the bodies pile up in the streets in the end they'll beg us to
save now.
Adam: That's going on for a while. Deus Ex actually I mispronounced it?
Unknown: Oh yeah, she
Adam: has this but how different how different does it sound from New York City? This is producer Nick who caught the giant voice recording going off
to as people were starting to kind of congregate getting too close to each other you know, wanting to say something to their government.
John: Yeah, this is reminding me I guess. You will be ticketed and Yo,
Adam: the red zone is for Park is
John: ticketed and towed. And you hear that? What kills me about that announcement at the airports? They play it inside the airport.
Adam: Only a JFK though. Don't think anywhere else. They do it Oakland. So you've even got Yeah, but Oakland is very small. So it's
John: just a bunch of Hicks. Oh golly. marlina forgot to bring the car around just go start outside parked.
Adam: So even some of the doctors are fed up with it and are doing the typical kind of stand up presser in front you know in the scrubs in front of
the the hospital doors up on the steps and scrubs. Yeah. Oh, yeah. There you go. Exactly. Exactly.
John: It's presser his press
Adam: scrubs. Damn it. I'm on a row presser in scrubs. This is Dr. barchi,
Unknown: one of the experts are wrong.
quarantining the healthy doesn't actually save lives. What if wearing a mask in public is not effective.
My name is Dr. Jeff barky. And I'm here representing 1000s of physicians across the country whose voices are being silenced. Because we don't agree
with the mainstream media and the experts who are telling us what to do never in the history of this great Republic. Have we quarantine the healthy?
never in the history of this great Republic? Have we told churchgoers that it's illegal for you to exercise your first amendment right? of freedom of
religion,
yet at the same
time, it's essential to keep pot dispensaries open than ever in the history of this country. Have we been told that you can't go to church because
it's not essential? But you can go get an abortion? Because
Never before in our country? Have we let criminals out of jail. But we've told you you can exercise your second amendment right and protect yourself
by purchasing a firearm. When liquor stores are deemed essential, but your businesses are deemed non essential. There's something wrong going on.
This booklet the declaration of independence in our US Constitution
was never designed to restrain the people. It was designed to restrain the government and
Adam: I can inform you The doctor has been demonetised.
John: Dr. is a Republican.
Adam: Well, there's that but he has he has some very valid points and he's he's making his points heard. But there's somebody's got
John: to do it.
Adam: But there's a lot of crazy stuff going on with that just even at a local level or the state level. And like in Austin and mayoral level, they
just don't want us to get out. They just want to come up with reasons to keep us in. And now we have the trade
John: at 5g as
Adam: well. Now we have the trace act on the way house House Resolution. Well, and of course it is it you can't make it up. It's House Resolution
666616. Too many. And here's the problem a lot of people have with it. It will authorize the Secretary of Health and Human Services to award grants to
eligible entities to conduct diagnostic testing for COVID-19. And related activities, such as contact tracing through mobile health unit, and, and
here comes as necessary at individuals residences, and for other purposes. So they're putting together a tracing squad. $100 billion is the proposal
for this. And it will be Yeah, exactly what it sounds like a form of a,
John: like the EU regulation like
Adam: an army. And so if if you've been identified as someone who may have been in contact, and they come to your house and test you and take
measures, so what could these measures be?
John: Well, it's out of the house and lock
Adam: you up. That's correct. And this is Dr. Robert Levin, he is the health secretary of what's his name here, a health director of Ventura County,
California. And here he is talking. And when you listen to him speak, just and I left a little more in this than I would have at the beginning.
Certainly, he's like Mr. Rogers. And he's, and I'll even have to interrupt him, he's so sickly at telling you what's going to happen. I mean, it's a
real doctor, and you just listen to this guy. And what he's talking about is quite concerning. We are beginning a program today. And it's a pilot
program, which will certainly grow into something larger and larger. And that is a community contact tracing program. We've done contact tracing all
along, that contact is a person who's been exposed to someone that we document to have the COVID infection. When we find someone who has a COVID
infection, those people are immediately isolated. But we also work with them to figure out who their contacts, we're just the way he says that, you
know, if you if you have the virus, okay, you can be asymptomatic, maybe you get tested, but the way he makes it sound is like isolated, isolated,
Unknown: immediately isolated.
Adam: Luckily, because you have been doing such a great job of cooperating and staying indoors, and staying isolated, you've been such good little
obedient servants and slaves. It used to be, there were 10 contacts, at least for every patient that we would find. Now, it looks like there are
probably only two or three or four contacts. Not surprisingly, so good of you very good human resources. By the way, the guy is not doing an
interview, he's speaking on stage. This is how he speaks to his his County, his his subjects, because most people have been staying away from others.
So that's, that's good news. But the purpose of this program is to bring on people, we're going to start with 10 people, we may bring on up to 50, or
even more just a pilot project after all, as the program grows, and as we see the needs for it. As we do more testing, we will find more and more
people who have COVID 19. And again, we'll isolate every one of them, and we will find every one of their contacts. We also realize that as we find
more contacts, some of the people we find, are going to have trouble being isolated. For instance, if they live in a home,
Unknown: where there's only one bathroom,
Adam: and there are three or four other people living there, and those people don't have COVID infection, we're not going to be able to keep the
person in that home. Every person who were isolating, for instance, needs to have their own bathroom. And so we'll be moving people like this into
other kinds of housing that we have
Unknown: available.
John: Oh, I want you to put him in those empty prison cells. No,
Adam: no, no, no, no, no, listen, don't call the prison cell anymore.
Unknown: They'll also have other needs, perhaps
Adam: Food, whatever it's gonna be, the county will be there to back them up and to support them. Yeah, I think you're right. It's a prison. So that's
exactly where you're going. And so, you know, when you hear this and you hear you see this bill that is coming our way, you gotta think the guy's
pretty happy about it. It's like, yeah, I'm gonna get funded perfect reminds me of this a little bit to think about intelligence work takes place
within a strong legal framework. We operate under the rule of law and are accountable for it. In some countries, secret intelligence is used to
control people in hours, it only exists to protect the freedoms, protect the freedoms, protect the freedoms, protect the freedoms and that's why we're
doing and citizen is to protect your freedoms Have no fear.
John: It's gross. Okay, that's
Adam: that unfortunately is seems to be where we're headed. Now we were looking for some names for me for some reason that that really hit a mark and
let me see where I have this people started coming up with all kinds of cooler names for tracking so that we could kind of sell it a bit better. So we
have social interactive safety social proximity awareness when we need something for these troops we need a name for them to social density squad.
John: I had one I forgot to write it down because somebody wrote one and i thought was quite good there's a bunch of them yeah, we should put a web
page together and you can put by Adam Curry on it
Adam: screw you
John: go to it
Adam: anyway I had a very infected I
John: oh yes you had a big eyeball was swollen up and you couldn't even barely see through it it was causing problems with the show show
Adam: actually suffered? Yes, I there were certain buttons I could not hit with accuracy my eye hand coordination and gotten thrown totally out of
whack. So after three days of you know as the eyelid was all swollen then the socket was a big boxing match. Yes. On the on the losing end of the
match. And so now my whole face is kind of swelling up and like all right, now we got this.
John: You already have a big hit.
Adam: Oh, no, I don't. It's the hair. That was my secret.
John: And by the way, Little Richard died and talking about a guy with a big head. Yeah,
Adam: Little Richard man he did a lot a lot for America.
John: You really bamboo.
Adam: Yeah, he did a lot. Anyway. So you know, being a podcaster the you know, the insurance scene is not all that easy. And a while back the keeper
and I found this new outfit from it's actually a couple of Silicon Valley guys. It's called decent that we may have talked about on the show. And that
they basically give you $500 a month per person disaster insurance. But you know, they they do chip in for some medication and stuff. And whatever it
you know, if something bad happens, you know, I'll have to figure out the $8,000 deductible. From there the insurance kicks in. And besides, I
typically go to Dr. Rom the Voodoo doctor anyway, it's not covered. So but one of their selling points is unlimited telemedicine appointments. So I
think Well, here's my chance, I'm going to have to do this, which of course, involves downloading the app, which I have a special phone for which is
goes off after the usage. downloaded the app and I have to tell
John: you Wait, hold on a second. You can't do this on your regular computer. Yes, you can.
Adam: You can. Can you can. There is a link and everything. Like I wanted to have the full experience so I could report on it on the show. This is the
new hot thing. telemedicine and up on the screen pops up Dr. Sam.
John: Robot duck?
Adam: No, no, I think he may have been. He's maybe Turkish descent, but he's in Vegas. And he owns the telemedicine company. He's also the CEO and he
had a bow tie, which tells you he's an inventor. And that that was fun. He's invented a device that you connect to your phone and then he can listen
to your heartbeat and take your temperature and god knows what else maybe stimulate stimulate you. But I have to say I had a really good experience
with this. And he says, you know, the thing is we can talk as long as you want. There's no limit. And and he told me I didn't say confidentially, but
anyway, he said that he only charges $10 per telemedicine visit to the insurers. It says you have no idea how we make it up on Volume Two, we've got
10s of 1000s of customers and the calling with pretty simple things. And for me, it was like, Okay, I see why you're calling the guy. Do you see the
problem? You know, three questions and then pop get the drops. And by the end of the afternoon, it was already starting to clear up. I was impressed.
I'm not a guy who likes to go to the doctor for anything.
John: Yeah, well, it's not it's a dangerous place.
Adam: It's a very dangerous place. That was quite Yeah, I, there's something to it. And I and these guys are trying to figure out a different business
model by making it more affordable. I don't know if they're actually making money, but it certainly is a hell of a lot cheaper than lots of other
routes I've seen
John: and your eyeballs. Okay, my
Adam: eyeball is doing quite well. Thank you got some antibiotics. And I'm rocking and rolling.
John: Well, what did he tell you what this problem was?
Adam: what my problem
John: was wrote the eyeball.
Adam: Yes, he had a name for it, which I promptly forgot. But it is essentially inflammation of the eyelid from allergies, histamine. And then and
then you rub it and then if you rub it, then he gets screwed up and you're screwed. Yeah.
John: Texas syndrome.
Adam: Yes. Indeed, Texas syndrome.
John: Yeah. Okay. I'm gonna bet you're better. Yeah,
Adam: I feel good. I have a phrase that I think we will be hearing
John: the phrase from the chaise,
Adam: no, I think Well, no, it's gonna be a phrase from the future. And I've read it a couple times. And I'm like, wow, are they really pushing this?
And maybe I'm wrong. But the recovery through prevention, which is just the most Newspeak I've ever heard, recovery through prevention, which of
course, you know, what that leads to?
John: Yeah, lucky in jail, let the pressures out. You
Adam: know, the vaccine, of course, it leads you straight to vaccines. Yes. Exactly. vaccines,
John: which play that earlier
Adam: clip? Well, I'm gonna play this one for you. And this will kind of finalize the getting back to work part. Even though everywhere, everywhere in
the world people are just giving up they're getting they're walking out of their homes. They've had it I mean, they are they just took them this long
it's Amsterdam is Rotterdam, it's the UK is is different. The UK, I think they shoot you on the spot. They're really locked down over there. Hey,
John: I have a couple of UK reports.
Adam: Okay, we'll get to it. After we listen to the only way we can get back the only way the world and get back to normal Ladies and gentlemen, we
have to listen to the guru. William gates
John: and my lifetime there, this will be the greatest economic kit, but you don't have a choice. People act like you have a choice. People don't feel
like going to the stadium when they might get infected.
Adam: You know, it's not the government who speak for yourself pansy boy
John: saying, okay, just ignore this disease. And you know, people are deeply affected by seeing these dots by knowing they could be part of the
transmission chain and old people, their parents or grandparents could be affected by this. And so you don't laugh it about me?
Adam: Well, I think this he's actually laughing because it's a tell some people have brought the hammer down on me and say, no, it's because of his
Parkinson's. Like, well, that may be
John: but Oh, okay. When his Parkinson's began about a decade ago.
Adam: Yeah. And they're gone as far as I can see.
John: I know, bill before he went, he was still giving speeches about how we make money by selling code. And I've seen and I've seen very young, yeah.
Oh, really, that laugh has always been there. And when and when when he drew the line and the and the inappropriate smile right in the middle of a
sentence. What?
Adam: Right. So what is that then if you've been around it?
John: Well, I think that the idea that it's a tell is probably the closest that gets by knowing. I mean, you could say well, it's just a nervous
laugh. But why does it show up when it shows up? Because always shows up at a tell moment.
Adam: I think he's giddy about the whole idea. He's giddy about people being afraid he's giddy about the only solution being his Guinea as
vaccinations.
John: Well, I think that's a valid interpretation. I could be my knowing they could be part of the transmission chain and an old people, their parents
or grandparents could be affected by this. And so you don't, you know, you don't get to say ignore what's going on here. There are there will be the
ability particularly in rich countries to open up if things are done well over the next few months.
Unknown: For the world at large, normal seat
Adam: only returns when we largely vaccinated. The entire global population and and so, you know, although there's a lot of work on testing a lot of
work on drugs that were involved with, you know, trying to achieve that ambitious goal which has never been done for the vaccine that rises to the top
of the list. This indoctrination from Dr. Bill is so deep that people are buying into it. I think part of this is the reason why even when cuz Fauci
is, he's compromised. He's a Trump guy. He's got Trump goo on him.
John: He's not a Trump. No, no,
Adam: no, I think Fauci is now being pushed away. And he's being seen as as a turncoat. Just like Burke's I'm telling you the you should know out
there, Fauci is really, there's questions about him, he won't go to the house first testimony. Now he's at home. Whoo. Now, no, Bill Gates is still
the ultimate guy, he Dr. Bill, he knows everything.
John: People are getting sick of Bill. And you only
Adam: have to ask someone like Sean Penn, who appeared on The View
John: of play who appeared on The View to an outlier and using that as your example. It's still
Adam: Hollywood. Its Hollywood. I just want you to hear the programming, Sean Penn. I know Sean Penn, I got remind me one of these days to tell me
sean penn story on the MGM Grand air. But for now, theory is on the view,
Unknown: as somebody who has seen government response to crises firsthand, how do you think this administration Sean has been helping and handling
COVID? And what worries you the most? Well, on the federal level,
I think that one thing that certainly should be much more robust is in the defense production act. Manufacturing, just listen to it and kits. I
believe that if we had that on the kind of level with which that act was used in the past,
Adam: for war efforts, that there'd be no question but that we could test, in fact, multiple tests
Unknown: over a series of weeks to every American, there's no question, we have a model
that's that we've been able to push out. And with that, using a combination of local governance and community organizations or NGOs, it would work on
a small municipality level
as it would in a big city for rural areas.
Adam: Yeah, no, Shawn, there's no way we're going to get multiple tests for every man, woman and child in the United States. And I gotta appreciate
the guy has local teams, he has a score, I think his name was group and and they do a lot of good things. But no, you're you're drinking the Kool Aid,
man. It's not feasible. But then again, the other one, Oh, yes.
John: Nobody did this universal vaccine, is it the whole world's gonna be vaccinated is never the whole world's never been vaccinated for anything
he's talking about. He's talking about specially when nobody in Africa even trust Bill Gates talking
Adam: about testing now. Not Vax. No, no, I'm
John: talking about backing up because you didn't let me get that little jab in there. What bill was to go back go ahead, you
Adam: jab all you want to Dr. Bill
John: is bullcrap. Well, Canada is there's gonna be more people marching in the streets against any universal vaccine, Trump, I totally subscribe to
the Trump thesis, which I kind of think where I may know where it comes from. But it's been observed before this thing is just going to go away. It's
not gonna be here next year.
Adam: The Canada is already talking about making the vaccine mandatory for all citizens
John: of Canada, this guy's will probably bend over and
Adam: hey, not all Candida avions. Not all of them.
John: They know who they are.
Adam: I have a second part of this if you just want to laugh a little more. The fear has also been that all we do the fear
John: mob. This shows you that not Bill Gates, the
Adam: Yeah, that is kind of what we do. This shows you what right what the programming does if you only listen, he's appearing on the view. You have
to think he's probably getting his input from one sided sources at this point.
John: Shawn?
Adam: Yes, yes. So you know, his fear level is also at a point that is just off the scale and unwarranted. Well,
John: I don't think you saw this. He looks nervous and scared.
Unknown: Not at all.
Well, I don't think we need to
attach a face a personality or what somebody was sending on their social media to be able to identify an active shooter. An active shooter is anything
John: that is continuing to to kill people. Our brothers and sisters and fathers and daughters and sons. This is this virus is the active shooter. And
if we were at, I think that we can wrap our head around it in that way and understand that it's principally putting in the radical people of color
elderly people, there you go, people. It's racist, randomly selecting all of us.
Adam: But you see what he's doing their keys. And the way I hear it, and I think I'm hearing what he's thinking is this is active shooter and look at
it, he almost ate, it would have been better if you said, and active shooters also target black people. That's almost what he's saying. Programming is
so deep on that man. Anyway, with the weather without the vaccine, it's all going to be okay. Especially in New York. We're going to get get back.
We're going to bring our city back. And we're going to bring in the best people to help our children when
Unknown: we are reopening schools. Let's open a better school. And let's open a smarter education system. And I'm going to thank the Bill and Melinda
Gates Foundation will be working with them on this project
is a visionary
Adam: mofo is in everywhere. He's like, Hey, we got a city down, sitting down, bring in the Scholastic services.
Unknown: Common Core that
Adam: was common. He can repurpose Common Core, but less he's a genius. I just need Cuomo was just another
Unknown: Bill Gates is a visionary. And his ideas and thoughts on technology and education. He's spoken about for years. But I think we now have a
moment in history where we can actually incorporate and advance those ideas.
Adam: Yes. So the next time windows acts like a bitch, just think Bill Gates manual. No, that's why we worship him. That's why
you can't make it up, you cannot make it up. You can't. Now I'll take you into your UK clips metadata controller, I'm going to take you into your UK
clips. Here's what we're going to do. I've got a clip from the UK. But first, some feedback on the stochastic model. And the assessment there of the
Neil Ferguson, Imperial College model.
John: And you recall me Neil Ferguson, the guy who is shacked up with his mistress when he was supposed to be Yes, sheltered in place.
Adam: Yeah, that's the one. That's the one, the guy who was overestimated quite a lot of numbers throughout
John: the run sheet that that'd be 2 million deaths, United States, we got 2,500,000
Adam: in the United Kingdom alone. Yes, that guy. And if you recall that he built these models, not on rock and roll, but on 13 year old undocumented
code, and we had the lockdown skeptics.org. And they reviewed the code, and they had some interaction as well with the college to figure out that some
questions back and forth. And one of the things that came up was, it was the stochastic part was, and I really didn't have the capability to analyze
it properly. But what you and I thought was, wait a minute, if this thing is returning random results, then something's wrong with it. And we were
partially right. And I just want to read this one paragraph from producer Richard who analyze what's going on. And he says, the model, and this is
what the article says, or the paragraph, the model and elsewhere, it's a simulation. And of course, with the simulation, you do want some random
factors being thrown in. But he says this certainly looks like a poorly written one in that in addition to the intentional pseudo randomness
underlying the simulation, there are additional hardware and configuration dependencies that cause the results to differ. I would not call these
latter random or stochastic in the statistical sense, because despite its flaws, if the code would run multiple times on the same hardware in the same
configuration with fixed random number seeds, the results would be identical, at least in single thread mode. This is how stupid This is Ferguson's
attitude about is very poor. And he says, admittedly, we're partially right about the model about it, the pseudo randomness of it. So bottom line,
this model is shaky.
John: At best, like it's, it's the you know, this is the whole thing, and I don't want to again, I'm not I'm sounding like idealogue. But this is the
same kind of thing is you have a global warming, these mediocre models and they go on and on with these models, and then they make decisions based on
their lousy output. And that's what we've have right now at this stupid thing and this month. On the Imperial College, whatever that is not Oxford.
It's not it's not Manchester. I mean, what is this place? very
Adam: influential they,
John: apparently Yeah, because the whole world's been shut down because of their their PR ad models. And this is what's going on with global warming
to which people will never listen to these people have never had a science. They've never taken a course in science, but they're all the big experts.
And so all the media people, none of them have ever they can barely get through a sociology class. But here they are talking about these computer
models and how the gold is going to it's melting the world's melting. It's not just unbelievable.
Adam: And it's not just the models, it's the actual data itself. We are hearing numbers of dead people, ranging from 37,000 to 72,000. We don't really
know what dead is. And the CDC has a history of exaggerating numbers of dead we go back to 2000 from the movie super from the documentary supersize me
Unknown: and at the time, there were headlines trumpeting everywhere that obesity was soon to overtake smoking as the number one cause of preventable
death in this country. The head of the CDC, Julie Gerberding went before Congress and issued big warnings. And there was a big uproar over the number
of deaths that were to occur. Basically, what they did was divide their survey samples between people who are obese and people who are not obese, and
then basically looked at rates of death. Now, if you are obese and you died from a snake bite, they would say that it was your obesity that was
causing your death, not the snake bite, and sound familiar was part of a little statistical Hanky Panky on their part.
Adam: In other news today, the Centers for Disease Control said it made a mistake about the scope of the obesity epidemic in the country. roughly
Unknown: a year later, another set of researchers from the CDC offered a much much lower set of estimates. According to their estimates, it was
roughly 25,000 people a year who are dying from weighing too much. Researchers say that mathematical errors exaggerated The death toll. Why did the
CDC inflate the numbers of deaths attributable to obesity
follow the
money. I think it's all about funding and bureaucratic mission. When I talked to a few CDC officials, they're constantly preoccupied about how much
money the government or Congress is going to allow for them for the next year, and they're constantly worried about getting their funding cut to
follow the money. All of this might have gone unnoticed, except for the anti tobacco people who see this as a zero sum game. So they see that if
obesity becomes a big public health issue, it's going to crowd out funding to tackle smoking as a public health issue. So they were among the first
people to point out a lot of the methodological problems in the estimates relating obesity to public health
Adam: outcomes, until they're just a bunch of lying corrupt douchebags. And they do it all for the money for their own projects for their own grants.
There's so much money and Health and Human Services is an incredible I mean, Fauci little teeny, teeny weeny division is $11 billion. And we heard
from one of our producers john you were on the email who knows people in in the business and and they hate that what they what they call the flu
people. The flu people they get all the money it's always the flu people within a we
John: also pointed out in that note that the flu numbers are probably exaggerated because we're always talking about over 60,000 60,000 dead from the
flu, the seasonal flu is killing 30 to 60,000 people. And it debt number may be exaggerated
Adam: a lot. It seemed it appears that well. RFK Jr. is all over this. He says maybe 1000 people a year die from the flu. He says it's a lie. It's
just a lie. He says but it's a big moneymaker for the that, by the way, was the first question. Adam, tell me about yourself. You're 55 Okay. When's
the last time you had your flu shot? First question out of the gate. And I say never any went Okay, next question.
John: Actually, that's funny, cuz I've had a question asked me. And, and as soon as you said my gonna get one. They don't even lecture you about it. I
made sure. It says no, they asked this question gratuitously. Oh, no. Because if they were serious about when they say, well, you should get one. No,
Adam: no, no, all they have to do is put the black check mark in the database.
John: Well, that's what I mean by gratuitous they're just doing it for the someone. The black check mark. So they've done their
Adam: job. Yes. And they're and they follow the
John: same exact same, by the way, no offense to the doctors out there. But how is that any different than would you like fries with that?
Adam: The way they ask it? Yeah. What size?
John: Because it's not as though the french fry guy at McDonald's or wherever it is. pushes it. They don't say would you like fries? Or they say no.
They say, Oh, you should they're great. No, but they're not. It's
Adam: not entirely true because then it would be McDonald's saying Excuse me, sir. When's the last time you had fries? fries? Isn't it time for a
tasty fry, aren't you You're hungry. Alright. So clearly the CDC has had issues in the past. And there's so much confusion, we cannot trust any of
this data. So who knows? It could be 1000 people, it could be 100,000 people we don't know. We don't know there's some average. But it seems to be a
heck of a lot less than we were scared into staying home for now, did this work. And you too, and I put that chart in the in the show notes of the guy
who took the data before the lockdown after the lockdown looked at all the death rates of all 50 states and charted them. And it shows statistically,
if I understand that, and I'm not a statistician that there's pretty much no difference between in the death rate between staying home or not staying
home. You saw this graph, right?
John: Yes, this graphs been going around, it was all over Twitter. And it indicated that based on the early numbers, and if he's projected outward,
distaste that said we're not locking down and the status is we're locking down there with the graph goes exactly as it would if they if they even
switched positions. Yeah. diblock down didn't do anything. In other words, that Meanwhile, we're still locked down and worried sick, because we have
again, a lot of democrat governors who are scared. If they lift a lockdown. Oh my god, I'm gonna be blamed for somebody's death. Yeah, they're gonna
point the finger at me. It's gonna be blood on my hands. But even crazier
Adam: is if you look at New York, and the numbers appear to show that over 60% of the people infected got infected while they were at home, locked
down. But that doesn't sit well with the media. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, that can't be true.
Unknown: We certainly hope so. I want to put up a quote from Governor Cuomo in New York, which which sort of had some surprising information in it. He
said, 66% of the people who were in new cases, were at home, which is shocking to us. He said, this is a surprise. Overwhelmingly, the people were at
home. We thought maybe they were taking public transportation and we've taken special precautions. But actually, no, these people were literally at
home 66% of the new cases. How does that happen? Well, generally speaking patients report and this has been well established better and safer
behaviors than reality.
They may be staying at home, they're lying.
But in fact, we know 600 people got the infection during pretty harsh sheltering conditions in the New York area. How did that happen? That means they
got the infection during the extreme measures.
Adam: Dude, this they can't even take any kind of news in any other light. Can they? These people dead liars. Oh,
John: we got an agenda. We're gonna
Adam: call it liars, liars, liars, liars. liars. Anyway, I promise to get you into the UK. I'm gonna play
Unknown: what are you gonna wear? I'm
Adam: sorry, I
John: got checkmark. I
Adam: know.
John: He's gone off the rails.
Adam: I am off the rails. I'm just gonna pull a hard left. Katie Hopkins, on Sky. Luckily, at least they can talk about the Neil Ferguson guy and his
multiple mistakes. And only in typical British fashion. Can they rip a guy down the way Katie Hopkins does in this clip.
Unknown: Unbelievable. So there's this bid scientist who's the typical science type. He looks like the sort of guy nobody would want to sit next to at
a wedding. He's called Neil Ferguson. And he's basically the guy that was the he was the one that made it such that the UK was locked down. He's
called Professor lock down. He was the one that came up with the modeling that persuaded Boris Johnson that we all had to be shut away and put under
house arrest in our homes. He said 500,000 people might die in the UK because of Coronavirus Now, what that he then did a once he had the rest of us
locked down. He got his mistress, his married lover, a woman funnily enough called Mrs. stats. So for a guy who does modeling and statistics she's
called back he had over and Professor pants down got his pecker out on a number of occasions to you know, help entertain Mrs stats whilst the rest of
us were locked out. So number one, massive hypocrisy as per usual. Number two. He is known for being absolutely crazy with these models like 500,000
deaths. we're nowhere near that number. He predicted 200 million would die from the bird flu I believe it ended up being 242 like his modeling is
about as accurate as my five year old standing up to take a pee. So why were listening to him at all I don't know. And now Professor pants down has
got his toddler out whilst the rest of us are in lockdown. So frankly regular Blitzer had enough.
Whoa, you got
John: to play in that clip really because we played a Katie Hopkins clips Two shows ago, where she's bitching about the same guy but before the
mistress story, and she used the same story about her daughter little boy trying to pee standing up. Oh, I forgot about recycling some of her gag. Oh,
boo, boo hoo.
Adam: Well, we should report that to the Sky News division is fake news. It's old news is no good. We can't have that. Alright, so here Here we are in
the UK. Welcome. It's your turn.
John: Okay, well, I don't have anything to compare to that last clip. You pre topped me. go bad. Yeah. Very fun UK restrictions garden centers, they
finally get it open. So they're gonna loosen things up by opening up the garden centers
Unknown: of any major loosening of restrictions. garden centers, though in England will be allowed to open from Wednesday. It's part of first step
measures. But with the sunlight this weekend, many people are already ignoring some of the restrictions still in place. As Rebecca Williams reports
the sun's out and you'd be forgiven for thinking lockdown is over. Despite the odd reminder, mixed messages and little information from the government
are making it feel like the country starting to move again.
Definitely needs to be lifted, roundabout now. Like a lot of the people are not really sticking to the rules anyway.
I think he should go as far as he can to reduce it. I think people have been very good so far.
But I think there's a tipping point. You feel
a bit weird. That gets contradictive the feeling of are we allowed to be outside now Are we allowed to do more than one exercise a day
it is gonna be easy, but it's already happening. So it would be very strange if he says the opposite.
It's not a holiday.
lockdown most of stuck to the rules but the police have had to come down hard on some. In the West Midlands. This man even strapped blood into a
police officers eyes he was handcuffed, raising fears of contamination. forces across the UK have been patrolling parks and streets. But there are
concerns that this weekend can place added pressure on officers. And it's got its challenges because it's a bank holiday weekend. People people need a
boost I think and it's a great opportunity to commemorate the V Day celebrations.
I knew it's confusing, but the rules are still the same.
As the week's Go on, it seems parts of the country are getting busier and busier. And the first four weeks of lockdown the police issued nearly 9000
fixed penalty notices to those flouting the rules for the highest number issued in London, the Thames Valley and also Lancashire
John: find areas that they're handing out tickets, yeah 100 pounds I think. And our friend in the UK, the NHS worker she says the real problem that
she's noticing is the what they call the British ism to the curtain Wranglers.
Adam: Curtain Wranglers
John: these are the old loads that are behind the curtain out their window and they're turning people in left and right narcs yeah narcs and they're
turning people in left to right the cops come over and give you a ticket if the curtain Wrangler called good turns you in and this is going on all
over
Adam: the UK. Do you know that we have a huge narc in Texas?
John: I mean a huge dark and dark
Adam: Okay, I'm gonna tell you what happened and you're gonna guess who it is. A guy in Texas sent secret shoppers all over Dallas to restaurants who
were opening up to find out if they were complying with reopening guidelines and published today that 96% of Dallas businesses are not complying.
Google the narc?
John: Your Mayor Mark Cuban what
Adam: Yep, Mark Cuban is a narc Cuban will continue sending out secret shoppers over the coming weeks with visits to hundreds of locations planned for
the rest of the month.
John: How is this a good idea?
Adam: Well, he has his own restaurant chains. I think he's invested in fat shack and some other pasta joint but still I mean I don't know he's just
he's someone made him Emperor and he's going around busting narking on in fact competitors
John: Wow.
Adam: Yes, yeah, I think he is quite the dick. Unless I'm missing something unless I'm missing the point behind it. You know people are struggling
man. And you know, so they're gonna cut corners, do whatever they can to get us back and you're gonna sit around narc on him. Cheese. Wow,
John: that's really a disgusting story. Okay, we'll get back to the UK. Yeah. With curtain Wranglers. Onboard to the to the newspapers, all these
little local newspapers which UK is full of the UK really is a newspaper per country, great, great country is going to be ending pretty soon we can
play this clip,
Unknown: predicting the industry could lose over a billion pounds by the end of the year, with circulation falling by around 40%. Since lockdown
started, and ad revenue down between 50 and 80%, what do you have and it's the local papers that are really suffering we,
we all want local newspapers are really important for communities and for writing local news and giving guidance to people if they start to disappear
the some already have, I think that's a real problem.
One solution being tabled is to legislate to force the tech giants to pay for news. They've
never really compensated news organizations properly for the value of their content shared through those services, and that's accelerated their
decline. And if we do nothing now, in a very short period of time, we're going to see more news organizations go out of business, and more people
increasingly reliant on the sorts of disinformation and low quality news that circulates like a virus through social media and digital users
continuing to rise. The physical paper could ultimately be saved by online success stories.
Adam: Now hold on a second, hold on a second. How does this work? How come those How come those guys are all mad at Google it shouldn't Google be
giving them their journalists like they do in America.
John: We just take it out of the line that there's once the newspapers go The only thing is gonna be low quality crappy news. And then I'm thinking to
myself do you mean like the BBC and Sky News? The broadcast element completely out of the story. What was the name of their headed
Adam: Yeah, what was the name of that outfit that the Google thing where they put in hundreds of
John: the story I
Adam: know I can't remember the name of the outfit I'll find it anyway this shoe This
John: is what is called this show they okay so then um, I couldn't get this story so I only have the teaser for it but I can explain the story if for
some reason I just kept I just couldn't get the story but there's the T two T's was UK heli heli payments
Unknown: coming up next year on Sky News giving away money to heal a sick economy how so called helicopter payments could be the cure for a global
slowdown.
Adam: Helicopter pain
John: what so this is an Ireland and so these are literally the big boy No. Yes. Drone bags of money yes.
Adam: Understand they can't just they can't just land
John: is thrown it
Adam: that I gotta hear that clip again.
Unknown: You need to get the whole story coming up next year on Sky News giving away money to heal a sick economy how so called helicopter payments
could be the cure for a global slowdown,
Adam: not just the full crap divorce.
John: So I'm telling you, they're throwing bags of money out out of the choppers and it's almost reminds me of like some old movie where the king is
throwing pennies at the peasants and they're following him on his little boys and girls that are waifs and they're all grabbing the coins and the
money off the ground and oh let's go but they haven't
Adam: they haven't actually done this yet have this has not occurred. They
John: showed a video of the chapter. throwing money but bags of money flying out the chopper. Yeah,
Adam: it's crazy. I'm trying to find this now. I want to find some pictures of it. Okay, well, the means are there. There's helicopters with the big
piggy bank underneath me. What are you working on it? Okay, perfect. heli heli payments. Who ever heard of such a ridiculous thing? That is nuts.
John: Alright, so I do have some kind of the story which was starting to appear on Thursday. Now it's getting more traction. Is this bright?
Adam: Yeah, this is so this is the guy who will be the whistleblower or he is the whistleblower. Yeah, let's This is good. I'm interested. I'm glad
you're
John: showing this. So here's here is the gigantic, like this is a four part or they're all short clips. But this Norah O'Donnell is going to
interview him today. Oh on 60 minutes. And but they took some clips for this Friday news show to tease us under the best clips. So this guy who's a
nude Nick, to say the least. And I don't want to defame him because of his sexual orientation.
Adam: What you shouldn't make it has nothing to do we're going to do that. Then why
John: you bring it up. Oh, but he is such an annoying Kind of a character, that and he's over his head, okay, he's a drama queen. All right, there
Adam: you go, that's fine.
John: And so he comes on, as you know, and he's gonna be this is going to be the democrats new Oh, he's going to be the strong man that's going to
take down Trump. And this guy can barely keep it together talking to Nora. So let's listen to that. If you're on the hook. No, it's actually only
three. So let's go with Nora interviews. Right. This is the intro
Unknown: right recently led BARDA, that's a key agency created to defend the country. And he says he was removed from his job for putting science over
politics. And he filed a whistleblower complaint earlier this week. And today, a federal agency found reasonable grounds to believe that the
administrative administration was retaliating against bright well tonight, a preview of our wide ranging conversation
Adam: buzzin
John: so this guy, you know, this agency No one's ever heard of is making a big fuss and then they're gonna use they're gonna go after another
impeachment with this character, but I think he's weak. Listen to him. He can't even keep it together in this 22 second clip part. Make it partners.
I'm sorry, it's 50 seconds. Part Two tonight.
Unknown: Another No, wait,
Adam: hold on that.
John: Interview interviews right to
Adam: okay, but we skipped over nor one. I'm sorry. At the wrong one. Okay, here we go.
Unknown: The President called you a disgruntled employee.
I am not disgruntled. I am frustrated. At a lack of leadership. I am frustrated at the lack of urgency to get a head start on developing life saving
tools. for Americans. I'm frustrated at our inability to be heard as scientist.
Those things frustrate me. As early as January emails show he was sounding the alarm. First about the critical shortage of N 95 masks. We see too many
doctors and nurses now dying.
And I was thinking that we could have done more to get this mask and this applies to them sooner. And if we had, would they still be alive today?
Ah, yeah, this
Adam: is it. This is this is the beauty. Well, yeah, Trump has blood on his hands.
John: He said you get the science meme. sooner. Yeah, he sounds like all the talking points at noon.
Adam: He sounds familiar. He sounds like this
Unknown: guy. Well, like I described earlier, there are two
fundamental classes that are just a plain fact in society. You either work for someone else, you work for yourself, and most people work for someone
else in a way that they aren't free.
Adam: didn't sound a bit like new noodle sounds like noodle
John: boy only talks even slower. I think it was like a dumb noodle bowl. It's noodle boy 2.0.
Yeah. And he's a whiner, and he's going to going into tears while he's there. He's like, but it this is so pathetic. Anyway, this part three
Unknown: is a horrible thought to think about the time that passed when we could have done something. And we didn't
break claims his persistent warnings caused tension with his bosses at the Department of Health and Human Services. It reached a breaking point when
he raised concerns over the administration's embrace of hydroxychloroquine what he called a drug unproven to treat COVID-19 patients, you believe you
were retaliated against? Because you raised concerns about hydroxychloroquine?
Yes,
I do.
And says he was surprised to learn he'd been reassigned to the NIH to develop diagnostic testing, you'd been sounding the alarm about the lack of
testing platforms. This sounded like an important job. That's an important initiative. Nora, I'm
the director of BARDA to take me out of our organization focused on drugs and vaccines and diagnostics, in the middle of a pandemic, the worst public
health crisis that our country is faced in a century and decapitate the bar organization to move me over to a very small, focused project of any scale
of any level importance.
is not responsible to that make sense?
Adam: Oh, my God, drama queen is the right question. Where's the right prescription? Oh, my goodness. So what is this bharta organization?
John: If someone is just a subgroup runs on HHS and it's
Adam: biomedical advanced research, biomedical Advanced Research and Development Authority. Oh, yeah, without those guys, we're toast. BARDA with a D.
That's what it is BARDA with a D. They got it. Yeah. rappi as website two
John: yeah this guy's this guy's gonna be their their go to guy and they're gonna do if you see him and listen to them the republicans on those
committees even though they're just going to be house you know so it's going to be led by NAD lawyer and Schiff like the republicans that are on those
committees will eat this guy alive he's gonna be a wreck
Adam: wow yeah I don't know how well he'll do
John: this interview with your without going into tears this
Adam: is this is partly died but this is part of a larger movement that the media is involved in entertainment news hollywood. I have two clips to
back it up unless you want to do more with this but about this particular topic there's blood on his hands. This shows up. This is W gmtv Chicago.
Unknown: A new study says the death toll in the US is double what it could have been if governments had responded just a few days earlier. The
earliest stay at home orders were implemented in late March orders to wear face masks began in April. Researchers with Princeton say if these orders
had come four days
earlier, the US would be seeing fewer than 1000 deaths a day instead of more than 2000 a day. They point to California which implemented stay at home
orders early and now has fewer deaths per capita than other large states.
Adam: See how that works. That's exactly how it works out. But that hasn't taken it far enough. No for that we need to go to Hollywood. And for that
we need to check in with your girl Amy on Democracy Now.
Unknown: A 56 foot billboard called the Trump gas clock has been unveiled in Time Square here in New York, a billboard which created by the Oscar
nominated filmmaker Eugene jerky.
So the Trump def clock is a billboard that hangs over time square.
Adam: By the way. This is the same little yo as, as this is blink.
Unknown: And what it shows is an estimate of the number of us COVID-19 deaths that resulted from the President and his team's failed response to the
coronavirus outbreak. thanks to Dr. Fauci and leading epidemiologists, we now know that had the mitigation guidelines been put into effect just one
week earlier, on March 9, instead of March 16 60% of us COVID-19 deaths would have been prevented. That's an incredible number. And on behalf of all
those who needlessly lost their lives, to this failed leadership and a pandemic, we need a symbol, a symbol that cries out not only for
accountability, but also for more responsible and responsive stewardship going forward.
At the time of this broadcast, the Trump death clock stands at 46,485 and growing
Adam: the arrogance of this poll right down to Amy's report and growing I am actually speechless it is
John: and of course this is the bottom of the den is like sleaze ball tactic it is and Eugene
Adam: jerky, who is a respected film directory, you know, kind of more like a Sundance kind of guy, but he has a brand new movie coming out on
Netflix, who have quite a china strategy. So maybe that has something to do with it. I don't know how you get a billboard on Time Square will I do
actually I don't know if you can even get one now if there's businesses being done, but I don't I know who owns Time Square. So this is a Chinese
thing going on with this guy. As far as I'm concerned. He's virtue signaling towards his money people and his backers and whatever else it's
sickening. And then for Amy, Dan's Yep, these pancakes.
Unknown: That death clock 46,321. and counting.
Adam: Lady, horrible, horrible, horrible.
John: That is the that is yes. That death clock thing is it's a humiliation to the country.
Adam: Speaking of humiliation,
John: China, China. Oh, yeah, China's put the death clock up there because they hate Trump. They may be behind this whole thing for all we know, they
can't, nobody's been able to prove it. And now they're doing this bullcrap. Just to get Trump out. Like Joe Biden. Well, let's
Adam: have a little listen to the president from the Oval Office. I think the words matter.
Unknown: And then we went through the worst attack we've ever had on our country. This
is where the worst attack we've ever had. This is worse than Pearl Harbor. This is worse than the World Trade Center. There's never been an attack
like this.
should have never happened.
Could have been stopped at the source.
Adam: That seems if I were in Beijing, I'd be like, what did he What did he call it an
Unknown: attack? Attack
Adam: that's very clear language to me I
John: don't know if they're gonna keep pulling this stuff like the death clock the giant entity we will say that the Chinese are behind it that
because I think your analysis is correct they're gonna hear more of that because you know they he called the Chinese flu and all this and he backed
off almost overnight because of a phone call or whatever because he does these you know he does negotiates well he's negotiating now they went the
Chinese want to keep just keep the pressure up to get him voted out. Which is meddling by the way. Yeah, in American election,
Unknown: please.
John: He's gonna he's gonna desk gonna be jacked up you watch.
Adam: Well, let's continue. Let's see what China is doing. Let me see Jimmy Kimmel. What network is he on?
John: is under Chinese control Disney network?
Adam: Yes, ABC. Let's see what he had in his opening monologue. The
Unknown: other night regarding Mike Pence, Harry is with no mask on wheeling boxes of PPS into a health care center. And doing his best to lift them
what a hero, just barely in the door. And since it was going so well, and also because he didn't realize he had a mic
on Magic Mike decided to keep it going listening closely here.
Adam: You probably can't hear it. But pence literally says to me, how about these boxes? The guy says those are empty, sir. And he says, Well, why
don't we just grab what for the for the TV cameras.
Unknown: Mike Pence pretending to carry empty boxes and peepees into a hospital
is the perfect metaphor for who he is. And what he's doing a big box and nothing. Delivering another box and nothing.
Adam: So when I saw the clip, I'm like, Oh my god, how can you How can you fail on that? That's so so blame. And I was looking at it on Twitter, and
I'm gonna give Twitter props. It right underneath the video, it said manipulated media, to like, Oh, that's interesting. I click on it. Then it says
according to some people, this was edited. It's not the way it happened. Well, it is the way it happened. Because there's this is on c span, I put a
link to it in the show notes. There's 20 minutes of pants literally lugging boxes, diving into the back of the van, schlepping them out not letting
other people really help him and they're heavy. He's putting them all down. At the very end. They're joking around. And the guy said now those are
empty. So come on, we'll just do it for the TV cameras after he's actually done that.
John: Yeah, well, Kim will apologize before we did. He did Oh, I
Adam: didn't know I apologize.
John: But he apologized in an offhanded way. The apology consisted of them saying? Well, it would turn out that the boxes he was carrying were full.
They weren't empty at all. And I'm so sorry that we made this. We This was wrong. From and I hate to say that because of the board. The administrator
was lying all the time. He has to tell us what Johnny has
Adam: to because he's got the Chinese Communist Party up his little mouse but like, Hey, be careful there. But here's what's really going on Reuters,
as far as I know, is really the first one to report on it because I think it also is going to have a name pretty soon. The name would be the economic
prosperity network
Unknown: sharpening his tone against China, President Trump said late Thursday, a trade deal between the two was now of secondary importance. The US
leader threatened Beijing with new tariffs as his administration crafted retaliatory measures over COVID-19. Trump's frustration has been growing as
10s of 1000s have died from the virus in the US. The economic contraction as a result also threatens his chances of reelection in November. Two US
officials speaking on condition of anonymity set a range of options against China. We're in the early stages of discussion. Although they added that
recommendations have not yet reached the level of Trump's top national security team or the president. One source said there's a discussion as to how
hard to hit China that could leave the US walking a tightrope in its ties with Beijing. It's currently importing crucial personal protection equipment
from China for health care workers. The multi billion dollar first phase trade deal with China was only signed in January. World stocks pulled back
further on Friday following Trump's comments. While most European markets were closed for public holiday, stocks in London slid over 2% grim data
combined with Trump's threats added to already dented sentiment.
Adam: So this thing is real and it's quite a task force. In fact, the the information coming out is this as a whole of government effort. The very
Well known phrase, of course, but in Trump's case, it might actually happen in which free trade advocates seem to be losing their struggle with the
China hawks inside the administration. Yes, it seems like the globalists are losing out this time. And I was listening to a globalist who I happen to
like where is my globalist buddy here? This is Elon Musk, oh, Ilan. And he was on Joe Rogan. Which was interesting, I think Joe does some of his best
work with with Elon Musk, that that's a very messed up interview to listen to at times.
John: But this was I found this one in pod. Musk seemed something was like something was wrong with him.
Adam: Well, I think he's still trying to figure out how to pronounce his kids own name. You know, that's, that's his problem there. It's like eight x
five, sigma tau. Find by me Ilan. But here's what he was talking about when when, because he has been pretty vocal about the shutdown appears he's
against that appears he thinks it's not a good idea. And this came up in the interview.
Unknown: I mean, you look at civilization through the ages. Most of them, you know, the rose and fell. Yeah.
And I do think like the globalization that we have,
at the sort of like the the meme sphere is, there's not enough isolation between countries or regions.
Adam: It's like, if you get up if there's a mind virus,
Unknown: that that mind virus can infect too much of the world. You know, like, I
actually
Adam: sort of sympathize with the anti globalization people because it's like, man, we don't ever want to everywhere it will be the same for sure. And
then we we need some kind of like mind viral immunity. So that's his. He's feel some sympathy with the anti globalist people.
Unknown: Wow, Ilan.
John: That was the worst. The whole interview, he just seemed it did. It was just disconnected. Well, even listen to that clip. It's like, what was he
given? I don't know what?
Adam: Well, I think what he was trying to say is that this mind virus where everyone's like, holy crap, we're all gonna die. I mean, it's not just
like something that happened accidentally, it came from somewhere and has been enhanced, a gain of function amplified by the mainstream media. And he
says, you know, how do we how do we stop that? Well, that's basically what globalism does and what it wants.
John: But well, I agree with with your you should have been on the show not go back. I
Adam: show back on the show. Yes. I have not been invited. Now you will be.
John: Let's go on to a couple other things going on in a couple of cases in the White House. Yes. He made it easy. Oh, it's Oh, this is trying to play
that Nora on new cases. This is a big deal.
Unknown: Tonight. Another White House staffer this time a top aide to the vice president has tested positive for Coronavirus Katie Miller, the press
secretary to Vice President Pence is now the second confirmed case tied to the West Wing after a valet who serves the President's meals tested
positive on Wednesday. Miller is married to Stephen Miller, one of the President's senior advisors, and tonight her test is raising questions about
whether the White House is doing enough to distance the president and vice president from others. For his part President Trump told reporters today
the whole concept of tests aren't great because they're his words and he said he's convinced the virus will just go away without a vaccine his own
advisors have said that's not true
John: says it's gonna go away by itself which is seems to be the case with all these previous events you know from bird flu to swine everywhere Yeah,
yeah, I'll buy and I'm my point people say well why would it go away it's gonna come back and say what about SARS? How come that didn't come back?
Yes. SARS we never got an immunity to SARS. MERS Yeah, we never got immunity to murder and then
Adam: you just throw in and how about peak oil? Just throw that in for no reason.
John: Really rubbish. What about Peak Oil your others so so Nora says at the end that he precedent says he's gonna be it's gonna go away. And but his
advisors say it's not how do they know? Doesn't matter? No, it's not gonna go away. What? Why does his advisors know more than he does? Because it's
it's a crapshoot. You don't know it's going to go away or it's not going to go away. There's no proof one way or the other,
Adam: but she wants Trump to go away. So that's why she has to report
John: this Wow, you're talking now you're getting this just alright. Did this go to new cases in white has just continued to report.
Unknown: Oh, But wait, there's more news that one of the Vice President's closest aides Katie Miller tested positive for the virus delayed Mr. penzeys
scheduled trip to Iowa. Miller was not onboard Air Force two, but six staffers who had recent exposure to her had to be removed.
Katie, she tested very good for a long period of time and then all of a sudden today she tested positive.
Adam: Doesn't matter what you do with Trump, you're the top You're the best. She tested me better than anybody else for negative she was just the best
negative. I mean, when it comes to testing Katie, you couldn't have a better you could not have a better person to be tested with Katie for a long
period
Unknown: of time. And then all of a sudden today she tested positive. She hasn't come into contact with me spend some time with the vice president
Miller is with the vice president nearly every day her husband, his senior presidential aide Stephen Miller, President Trump attended their wedding in
February held at Trump's Washington hotel,
Adam: despite the potential which by the way, is a great hotel. It's one of the best hotels it truly if you want to test if you want the number one
test, you got to do it the best hotel That's right. That's a we don't mess around
Unknown: Trump's Washington hotel
John: even put it in the story.
Adam: That's why I have to bring it up.
Unknown: Despite the potential exposure Mr. pence did not wear a mask while in Iowa. We also know that President Trump was in the same room as his
personal White House valet on Tuesday 25th the valet tested positive for Coronavirus. Today, the President still addressed a group of world war two
veterans at a V Day ceremony without wearing a mask.
The wind was blowing so hard in such a direction that if if the plague ever reached them, I'd be very surprised
that the president says he's now being tested every day and so far is negative. But doctors say that maybe a full sense of security,
somebody could become infected be incubating the virus and test negative every day, including yesterday, then this morning, become infectious, still
feel fine and spread it to other people before the next test shows that they are in fact infected.
John: That bastard,
Adam: I'm good. I'm glad that that report at least contained a little bit of V day, which was completely ignored by the American media. I believe you
pointed that out in the newsletter as they did, but it was also very odd to see you know, in the in the Netherlands, which was liberated on on May 5,
but on May 4, they have at eight o'clock this is actually very unique to the Netherlands 8pm. On May 4, all traffic stops. Everyone is quiet. And they
told the bell with a moment of silence two minutes, two minutes and everyone is completely silent. And and I've been in the Netherlands where it was
eight o'clock and on the highway people stopped, just stopped on the highway and then waited, some got out. And then everyone waited for two minutes
of silence and they got in there drove off. So this ceremony has been going on since the end of World War Two. And having the the troops the Yanks and
the Brits, you know coming through in their jeeps it was you know the flags. It was such a joyous occasion. None of it all just quiet. No one on the
street. There no, no parties. I mean, this is this passed by. I think it's a shame how quietly that passed by because of all this.
John: I don't think it's because of all this I think it was in spite of all this. They could have done anything. They could have made a little
presentation on the news or anything instead of all this just nonsense of doing about how Miller was married at the Trump hotel. There was very little
mention of it. By I mean Trump did this little ceremony but the media just dropped the data and want to talk anything about anything that's patriotic.
Well, no, I don't want to do it. I'd rather to me rather brag about the big science talking about how many dead are from Trump. The other thing is,
again, a Chinese influence Chinese do not want the Americans the Chinese by the web and watching CG TV, whatever it is the Chinese outlet constantly,
and their data, most of the globalists are actually coming out of China nowadays because the Chinese actually think they have the opportunity to not
only be for a globalist world, but for them to run the thing. And so a nationalist event like v day which is a nationalist event, because we beat
Hitler of all people and the nationalist event is really frowned upon. And immediate just paid Okay, we'll we will play it up. We won't even mention
it. I don't think half the people even knew it went by.
Adam: You're so right though, and I think we can't hammer it enough when we should probably reiterate, its CCP, the Chinese Communist Party. I don't
know many Chinese people I'm sure they're just like us. I'm sure that they're they're in deeper crap than we are with these a holes. Wanting to show
there's a cool video from some Chinese guy, Chinese American guy that I put in the show notes. And it's the history of China, actually, it's
John: called the I saw that it's very
Adam: great. It's called the story of how China ruined everything. And it's 30 minutes. And it's, it's pretty good. I mean, there. It's not complete.
And it's easy to skip over 5000 years here or there. But I was very impressed with that. And you'll learn something from it, it's worth is worth
watching. pompeyo is also out on the road, also, speaking out against China.
John: Like you just before I want to just mention one thing, because these clips about the infections in the White House press is giddy over this
because they're hoping to hope and Trump
Adam: gets it. Yeah, they want it. But you know,
John: we can't we can't we can't forget this one element
Adam: that we must remember this one element.
John: Trump is a germaphobe. Yeah. And he is delightfully hood of getting it based on some of the earlier reports that we've had on how you do get it.
Trump's never gonna get it unless he kisses somebody with it. Which is always possible.
Adam: Right, the pump pump out, we know for sure that this is actually context, CNBC, the financial news channel, we know for sure that this virus
originated in Wuhan, China and that the disease emanated around the world, the Chinese Communist Party covered this up, we have been working
diligently and are working diligently today to get the Chinese Communist Party to help us identify patient zero where this began, how this came to be.
And this isn't about politics. This isn't about partisanship. This is about protecting Americans tomorrow. This is an ongoing crisis are the world's
epidemiologists still don't know, the origins of this virus. The reason that we continue to ask for transparency and for a reliable partner in China
is because it matters going forward. So not only do we have this current pandemic that's taking place, but we still have to figure out how to get
therapeutics and get vaccines to market all the things that we need this information that only the Chinese Communist Party has in its possession. And
they're the only ones that can help the world resolve this today and for our American Security. But we got to make sure this doesn't happen again. So
I think this is very interesting, if true. He's saying that we can't even make the vaccine without pertinent key information that China is not handing
over. I don't know if it's true, but he's saying it and there should be questions about it. Hey, Fauci, or Hey, Bill, Dr. Bill. Doctor, Professor
bill.
John: Yeah, that's Yeah, maybe.
Adam: But But
John: well, here's the here's the attack they're not using yet. Which I think could be used. And I think it I think pompeyo could do it well, and it
would be used as leverage to Chinese cases of Corona have dropped to nothing. What do they know that we don't know? That's a
Adam: very good way. No, they just say no, Trump, Xi jingping. There's your problem that that's what would come back. Just briefly on therapeutics and
vaccines. On the therapeutic side, I have a beautiful breakdown. From our official no agenda pharmacist. Many people have noticed that New England
Journal of Medicine medicine has published a new observational study regarding hydroxychloroquine. And of course, it turns out to be completely
useless. Why would you even consider using it? But it's interesting because as our official no agenda pharmacist says, below are my favorite parts
which highlight the implicit bias. And the main bias is the patients they took out besides the fact that they had no you know, what do you call it?
Unknown: Double, double bind, no
Adam: placebo, etc. They only took and there was no treatment with zinc. Here it is. The AZT through Meissen suggestion was removed on April 12. The
hydroxychloroquine suggestion was removed April 29. The decision to prescribe either either or both medications was left to discretion of treating
team for each invalid patient. He says our pharmacist says here's the implicit bias, as the only people included in the study were those people who
needed to have moderate or severe disease treated. So they were already in the ventilator stage, which is actually as we know from other doctors who
have successfully used hydroxychloroquine is really too late. You want to use it much, much earlier, almost like Tamiflu. So it's very similar to the
VA study, no placebo One one particular group of people with a certain type of level of illness. I mean, the whole thing is, is broken down in the
show notes. It's under therapeutics, well worth a read. But a lot of people did send in that as well as a lot of people who have sent a very, it's
kind of the same letter or email. It's the debunking of the plan. demick documentary This is the one with Dr. Judy Mike ovitz who has been around for
years and is saying that Dr. Fauci should go to jail for being a criminal. And what's interesting is they all are kind of the same, these responses or
the debunking things, and it attacks her really more for business political reasons how she handled herself with publishing of studies or not really
doesn't address any of the any of the main issues. But the thing that always comes up, which I think is the mistake in this, it seems like it might be
it might be some form of coordinated response. This is literally one of those Hey, Adam, a friend of mine, has a couple of nurse friends or doctor
friends. And here's what they have to say. And then you get a foreword of the email. But it always says in there that Dr. Mike ovitz claims there's
never been an RN, a vaccine. And in every single one of these debunking responses, it's Oh, yeah. Are you kidding me? There's tons of them. There's
vaccines for all kinds of RNA viruses. Yeah, but that's the difference. There's vaccines for RNA viruses. The RNA vaccine that is being discussed,
it's
John: actually called m RNA mRNA. Hasn't?
Adam: Well, you looked into it right, that you had a thing for me to put in the shownotes.
John: Yeah, that dead paper which discusses the mRNA vaccine wishes, which is a an experimental idea. It's not Do you all the RNA vaccines are based
on the old fashioned way of you, you cultivate the the, the disease, and then you use attenuated versions are killing you grow it and then kill it,
and you do all these different things to make a vaccine just a normal way of making a vaccine. This this mRNA vaccine is a totally different animal.
It's never been proven to work. And so
Adam: yeah, so
John: the fact that this show notes, it was a good paper on it, and that's what I when somebody sent me that same exact thing. You got some put some
stooge. And I sent him a link to this to this to this paper, and I said, you read this.
Adam: The thing that I like the most is that they said, That's never That's a lie. They've been tons of RNA vaccines like, Okay, this has got to be
someone who doesn't know what they're talking about. So the debunkers are being debunked, but there's about three of them in the show notes under
debunked, you can look it up there any more clips to do in this Rona segment?
John: As we're talking about 5g debunking.
Let's listen to the talking cat. Yeah,
Adam: been waiting for almost an hour and a half.
John: Period. She talks here she talks about Fauci and, and it is just a dance I found Fauci reds very well structured.
Unknown: The scientific evidence is what needs to drive us and we appreciate the fears of the American people. But we don't want to have policy
that would have negative,
unintended consequences. That's actually fairly reasonable. But that's a quote from 2014 when he was talking about whether or not we should quarantine
for Ebola. Another interesting quote of Anthony as Fauci, MD, Director of the National Institute of Allergy and Infectious diseases that the CIA
forgot to scrub from history is when he said that there is no doubt that Donald J Trump President of the United States will be confronted with a
surprise infectious disease outbreak during his presidency. He likely said well, rubbing his hands together and then cackling to the sky for several
minutes. When questioned about concerns for the future, Trump administration, Fauci reportedly said that there was the potential for a new influenza
pandemic and outbreaks of diseases that are not yet on anyone's radar,
John: the issue of pandemic preparedness and if there's one message that I want to leave with you today, based on my experience, and you'll see that
in a moment, is that there is no question that there will be a challenge the coming administration in the arena of infectious diseases, both chronic
infectious diseases in the sense of already ongoing disease, and we have certainly a large burden of that, but also there will be a surprise outbreak.
Unknown: He has the same Dr. Fauci who according to this Wikileaks email loves Hillary Clinton.
Adam: I was a verbatim reading of something but the caps okay the cat cannot just talk the cat can read it's quite astounding. Love the cat and the
cats pretty good.
John: So that's what I have. I have oh
Adam: that's that's what you have. You would anyway and
John: I think it might be a good time when you got to
Adam: COVID Italy COVID South Korea needed break you want to do anything about South Korea or Russia get
John: cut off?
Adam: Yeah I don't know you're just talking talking at me not listening he's not not obeying me. What do you hear me?
John: Yeah, apparently hit the mute button.
Adam: I was asking is Do you not want to do the COVID Italy or Russia? I'm interested in these Oh, that
John: was the fault though. Those are the countries run does that we do that the end of the show. Okay. Well,
Adam: with that then I'd like to thank you for your courage and say in the morning to you the man who put the seat in curtain Wranglers, john shade.
John: What no morning to you. And in the morning the ships at sea and that boots on the ground, the feet in the air and the subs in the water and the
dames and knights out there.
Adam: Yes. And in the morning to our trolls. Let's do a troll count here. Well, 1820 hate trolls hanging in there. Not bad for Sunday. The troll room.
I did a little check in this morning. But the pre show after Darren Oh. And I said How y'all doing? It's mixed. It's not everyone's feeling great.
They're there. People are angry. They're tired. They're sick of it. So I'm we're feeling good.
John: Yeah, there's only so much we can do.
Adam: Well, yeah, I know. But he
John: brought the cat on and nobody has.
Adam: If you want to commiserate with your fellow trolls head over to their bridge, you can find that at no agenda. stream.com. We've got a chat there
as well. IRC chat, you can do access on the web. And of course you can listen to anything that's happening live at that moment. A lot of the shows are
live. We're also broadcast live, I believe now on 1430 5am. In Cronin in the northern part of the Netherlands. Oh, nice. Yeah, I love that. I love
just that we're on some random am frequency somewhere in the north of Holland somewhere as great and the more of that the better. If you got a little
transmitter set up, let us know is fantastic. No agenda stream.com and thanks, trolls Good to have you here helping as always, then, in the morning to
the artist for episode number 1240. The title of that was meat must flow and boy does it. And there was controversy from this over this image from
Trent drac who brought us a just a great piece COVID safe no agenda, this crazy ass look and mass, the fonts. Everything was great. And within seconds
of posting the show. The narcissists were out. That's artists who narc I'm looking at you comic strip blogger.
John: Oh, he's the he's number one narc. This
Adam: is stolen art. You must take showdown now.
John: You must change out you will get sued the stolen
Adam: art. So I'm like, oh man, did we get hoodwinked? Because we did an image search we looked for this swing. We found similar stuff. But not
exactly that. And lo and behold, there it is. On some image you follow any of this john Did you follow this going down? I
John: call it the final leg of it. Which is this is a piece of licensed art. The guy has a license. whatever he wants. I love
Adam: that he has a license. That's what that is. Now that's a no agenda producer for you right there. I'm not gonna compromise my boys. I'm not
putting the tribe in any dangerous
John: art that you could find it maybe if you searched around now with the no agenda, no stuff on it. And it's been altered like you do with licensed
start but he license a license a lot. Okay, first bring up a couple of There you go. That apparently comic strip bloggers unfamiliar with including
the piece of art that he actually did still some time ago little Santa Claus thing which could have been licensed in but he didn't license now
Adam: don't take off.
John: for commercial artists. They license certain kinds of clipart and different kinds of very specialized looking to test to be stylized. And they
will like they will take out licenses from these different places and one or two of them and then don't use this stuff judiciously as projects come
and go. And as part of the deal at this is done with video more even so even more so than it is with art. There's a number of services out there.
There's a couple of MIT Media guys. Meebo itself didn't use them but the guys had licenses and if you watch almost any of the I every time I used to
watch anybody's presentation see the spinning logo come in and flame the big ball booksplosion of flame does all these things come from one particular
site whose name I do always forget I always have to get asked Nick re about it wasn't a minute site again, but is one site just like it costs like $1
to license some of the most spectacular videos that you've ever seen? Yeah. And everybody subscribes to these services. And so we have a couple of
artists, I'm sure more than one. Most of them can listen to the show and do live art on this fly. But we do. This is an example of a licensed Pro.
Adam: Well done peaceful. I
John: hope I explained that. Yeah, absolutely. Anyway,
Adam: I just thought it was funny. The narcissists were out. That was just funny. They're so competitive. It's so competitive. It's competitive.
Should be Yeah. Well, thank you, Trent. Trent drac, for the artwork for Episode 1240. This is great, because we're one of the only podcasts if not the
only podcast that every single show we release as new album art, it shows up in your podcast players, most of them will show it. And it's exciting
when you see it in an overview and it's this is something about the show, and it's a part of what what, you know what? The package matters, packaging
matters. We learned that from Steve Jobs. We are the iPhone of podcasts, actually. You think about it. A little white box. Yes, that's so no agenda
art. generator.com is where the artists compete. But it's a fun, friendly competition. Everybody has a good time. And we laugh about it. And we love
comic strip blogger. We're just messing with him because he's a blogger. Yeah, he
John: deserves it.
Adam: You blocked him everywhere. I have to deal with the fallout when you say these things. So stop it. Just stop. No agenda Art generator.com then
John: we have our back is art I used as I probably use more comic strip blogger stuff for the newsletter I know
Adam: and you don't even follow Him, you're a heathen.
John: He's too much of a back channel or from that's certainly
Adam: part of our part of our value for value network here at the no agenda media tribe is the way the system works. Everything you've heard up up to
date, we can give you the the narrative, at least the one we hear we believe or what we're finding out from actual sources, because we're not run by
pharmaceutical companies or by China more by anybody else. For that reason. It's you, the producers. And we love to thank our executive and associate
executive producers as soon as we have quite a few.
John: So maybe we should get to it. All right, bingo boom, way more than normal. And I want to thank each and every one of them. And I don't think
it's because of Mother's Day, and maybe because you triggered some thoughts with the V day mentioned. But
Adam: I think we should say Happy Mother's Day. And we
John: will say Happy Mother's Day
Adam: to all the moms out there. And
John: yes, it was surprising because while we're at it, here's what we're really a hallmark holiday by the way
Adam: nobody hears what was surprising is typically we do a Mother's Day promotion. And the joke is that we get five people and said no agenda
producers hate their moms. And so this year, we did nothing like it's Mother's Day. And everyone's like beautiful notes to mom
John: starting with Truman with Kate who gave us $1,000 in $2.42 41 cents on top of that, Utah wait you see an instant it says last week observing all
this to stand here. X's glass shields, polka dots mass oh I see on in marketing t shirts. I thought I have done a hell of a job gratifying this
gamifying this so that's a bonus COVID is the death of truth. No agenda is the opposite of whatever that is one of the very few places where truth
exists. fucka duck thank you for this was done by a randomizer I don't know you for this podcast to YouTube, ying and yang it and it just works. It's
actually Yin. It's not Yang it's Yin. Plus a little help from us third legs that's also zoology. So ology I realized that all these is back to mac and
cheese long for long for simpler days. were no agenda was wins awards with recipes, oatmeal and console wine reviews. I'm doing my donation to a
friend who was angered by Article links being emailed about the COVID hubbub in late March so I sent the no agenda show to her her anger dissipated
and out of the blue she inquired. I think my amygdala is shrinking. Thank you for smacking Chrissy in the mouth. Dame Chrissy will enjoy being
knighted and all the accounting adornment search room and when she shut up slave it's true.
Adam: Wait, man, so this is like an instant instant naming naming
John: is a woman he hit in a mouse.
Adam: It's an instant game. Right. Do you hear me there? Did you hit the mute again? I bet you did.
John: I did
Adam: it. Stop doing that.
John: I don't even know how I did it.
Adam: I said this is an instant night instant name
John: is Damien in the mouth.
Unknown: mac and cheese live mac and cheese.
You've got karma.
John: And I'd like to alert the affiliates that we're going along. Chris dicers next from Brookline, Massachusetts. He also came in with $1,000 this
Dame hood donations from my smokin hot wife another this is an interesting coincidence number going on here. Yep. To Dame Instagram nations by men.
She's gonna be deemed diced or I think de I think dicer yet dicer She's incredible mother to our kids and I know this donation will be much more
meaningful of Mother's Day as a Mother's Day gift than any bs item I could have come up with. Diana hit me in the mouth. years ago, this is an
opposite where it normally goes. And that's just one of the many reasons I'm the luckiest man on earth.
Adam: Oh, that's so beautiful. I'm gonna give him both the karma. We feel that's right. You've got karma.
John: And we continue with this theme and
Adam: what
John: sure Maxim Rifkin with $1,000 as a birthday present to his wife, Olga, Olga Rifkin. Her birthday is on May 9 is and you're gonna intimidate her
so we have three instant games in a row without any encouragement. was on the newsletter. Good work boys.
Adam: Well done men. They love it. They love their wives and moms, don't they? The moms
John: are older would like to hear Obama you might die and don't eat me Jo Bo Jaiden also, Olga's requesting a product development, karma.
Adam: Well, we got that for you.
Unknown: You might die.
Karma.
Adam: Wow, the ladies, that'd be great. This is gonna be fun at the roundtable today. I'm looking forward to it. Sure.
John: Now we dropped him in normality sir Kevin deals the Vikon of Charlotte 330 $3.34 from huntersville North Carolina. This donation along with the
producer credit is my birthday present myself this year, I'll be turning 34 on May 12. Please add me to the birthday list this past year being 33 is
gone pretty much how and no agenda producer would expect. I'm looking forward to putting 33 behind me and this donation amount seems like a great way
to celebrate my odometer rolling over. Since this donation also completes my seventh knighthood I like to claim the title of Earl my accounting is
attached to the title upgrade will also feel like good time to expand my protectorate I'd like to claim the state of North Carolina assuming
everything checks out with the peerage committee. Please add me to the title change as sir Kevin deals Earl of North Carolina. My only Jingo request
of is not too much trouble is to have Adam play the Dylan version of the title change song. The Times are changing later in the show when we do that
changes. Since I've got the platform I like to have a couple of friendly shout outs. The first is to all the beautiful people in the no agenda local
704 Meetup group here in Charlotte and I'm looking forward to sucking in sit with all of you again hopefully very soon. Second, I'd like to give a
shout out to all the folks on the no agenda socially keep me sane. No jingle is just karma. Thank you for your courage for Kevin get dills
Adam: vi counter Charlotte thank you so much sir Kevin and of course we'll be happy to bring out the Robert Zimmerman version then we have Sir 10 t do
is that 10 t i think it is Duke of the Federal Reserve district seven gears crock pot crock pot and BuzzFeed thank you for the continued service
during the rohner lockdown I know that even Knights are struggling with the imposed restrictions, especially in the hub of Federal Reserve district
seven Chicago Keep your head up sir Joe things will get better soon enough. No karma but can I get a Bernie I have all the power gretta How dare you
and Fletcher orange combo that'd be great. All the best Sir 10 t Duke of the Federal Reserve district number seven, and he came in with $333.33 I'm
the President of the United States. I
Unknown: have all of the power How dare you got it. Thanks.
John: Guess who's up next. Maxine Waters gravel is back nice
Adam: the gravel returns
John: of Louisville 333 33. The gravel has a few enterprises that qualify for some magic Munchkin Munchkin minute minuchin money, so as to celebrate
what better way to gift a portion to the greatest show in the universe Who would have thought that the man who invoked my existence would play a part
in helping to show all hail simulation
Adam: Was that it?
John: Hold on no no All hail the simulation did this amount catapulted me into light of the move it catapulted me to barren i'd understand that may
now claim a protectorate if available. I'd like to claim the greater Bongo Bongo land and its surrounding territory. Jingle request young Jean China
not a Huntsman but the SIR Chris produced jingle Yeah, followed by China a hole and you might die goat karma for all your Corona papers please.
Cheers. MW Jean Happy Mother's Day to all to my mom and all the no agenda mums out there.
Unknown: Hello friends
just come from China the city of Chongqing
China Welcome to
Donald Trump don't trust China China
is as you might guess.
You've got
karma
Adam: sir cowl of lavender blossoms returns lavender blossoms.org it is the official What do we call it?
John: The official CBD CBD operation
Adam: in this show Dr. When we're hurting we get our lavender blossom south in the morning folks. Kay McAfee just buy me lunch no right a golden
article about you right after I write my cookbook. Did you happen to listen to McAfee on Nick the rats last podcast? No. I didn't know he was on. Oh
my gosh,
John: McAfee doing on
Adam: McAfee will do anything. He went to
John: a dinner he owes me.
Adam: Happy Mother's Day and Happy birthday, john. So it's a bit belated and that's from cow so Wayman. McAfee owes you money.
John: It owes me a dinner or dinner from what? Yeah, when he was in the heyday, when he was actually making money. It was actually working for a
living and we went out to stars in San Francisco. now defunct restaurant was very famous at the time. And I picked up the tab and he said, Ah, next
one's on me. Uh huh. That was the end of never saw him again.
Adam: Well, he's a horrible man. He's a liar.
John: No, no, but you know, maybe
Adam: come on. That's not right. Danny anyway, I will have to listen to this Nick the rat interview with McAfee. That's got to be one of the most
fabulous things to listen to no doubt. 330 309 from sir Nick, Dragon of the four domains, Waterford, Michigan. I'd like to donate for Mother's Day. I
am sure that my son Andrew loves sitting with me listening to your show. I know he's up in heaven. Oh, yes. cupping his head and shaking his head
laughing his butt off. I'm sure absolutely. I'm sure he is as well. And thank you. Thank you very much worse than nine for a wonder Barrow nets or
Nick?
John: No hard to say Joel Tucker. Meanwhile, from Largo Florida is here with $333 and he sent an email in which I isolated Oh good. What you wisely
took that next one. Uh, the next thing I do okay, he writes ITM The next thing I could do the next thing I could think to do on Mother's Day was to
become a knight and this donation brings you to the roundtable I get your pen out Oh, okay. This is good. Another one on this huge list we've got
crazy today. Now I can say to my mother see mom people are calling me sir now
Adam: but yeah, well it's true isn't up to you and nothing wrong about it. Nothing wrong about
John: leases the piers committee like you'd be knighted as sir here we go ready?
Unknown: Yep. Sure.
John: Not sure how to pronounce the LLC we've been lucky been Hello cis. Yeah. night. Night of the psycho nuts.
Adam: Psycho not?
John: p s y. Psycho na UT s like not astronauts psycho not
Adam: Oh sure. Llosa been Night of the psycho nuts. I get it. Easy. Done. Does he want something at the roundtable?
John: I'm gonna continue to read. Thursday, you are trying to come up with a name for social surveillance. I suggest social eyes is a play on words
sort of fits the criteria you're looking for. Social ace. I would like to ask you some goat karma. But as these got no special requests, I would like
to ask you some goat karma. But that has to be the greatest value for value I've ever had. I would like to ask for some goat karma. Okay, that has got
to be the greatest value. Not sure what he's meaning. Thank you so much for the infotainment. All right.
Adam: You're welcome more than
Unknown: you've got
Adam: Did you catch the note from from the kid who's graduating today?
John: No. Yes, I
Adam: did. What was his name
John: was so sweet. I wish I should have printed that note out. It was a mistake.
Adam: Because he invited us to his virtual.
John: Yeah. Robert
Adam: Robert blank, Shane? Yes, he wrote a beautiful, beautiful note about his graduation from St. John's College in Annapolis. And I just want to
read this because I feel truly as though I could not have done it without the two of you and the show and the entire no agenda community's been
listening for five years is really great. Um, so that really pleases me.
John: Yes, I was impressed by that note, honey, one of our children graduated. Yeah, sorry.
Adam: No, I was just saying honey, one of our children graduated.
John: Joel Tucker, by the way from Largo gave 333 Meanwhile, oh no Priester in ciske Holland $333. He also said it sent a note in there john and Adam
short note to confirm my donation happy to donate in proper valuation with the show brings me every other Thursday or Sunday, whatever, celebrating
our 30th anniversary on May 10. So no better moment I find a local restaurant tours able to prepare a four course meal to take away so at least we can
celebrate in style. Getting back to the last shows brainstorming how to name the monitoring another one random number again two in a row. Why not go
for so Social Security. It makes all the easy not to says it makes it all the more easy not to only use your phone and also attach a special reward
system. You are well meets Brave New World.
Adam: Okay,
John: but he bet this really Orwell rebel Iser, out,
Rebel Iser out. No, it's Orwell. Nice, brave new world. I'm sure. It's his cue. I don't know why. Toby maybe is cute. I was wondering what your
thoughts were about the latest developments in the case of Michael Flynn, and I haven't Michael. Yeah,
Adam: I have Michael Flynn stuff, too. We got lots to talk about. And well,
John: I have the new get the supercut
Adam: No, I didn't get the supercut. That's great. Well,
John: I get this just coming up. Pretty
Adam: coming up.
John: Hold on. Hold on a second. Are you sure you'd like dismiss? No. I got a big thing popped up to want to reset my machine.
Adam: No.
John: Thank you, Bill Gates.
Adam: Dr. Bill.
John: Somebody had triggered me when I was listening to earthquake clips was that the coincidences Kennedy family and specifically the RFK branch
suffered a loss recently when may MeV MeV. Kennedy drowned while kayaking. MeV As you may know, was the public health official, a co working for the
US DS Global AIDS program? What about coincidence as one would think? And another note here in the Eurozone, the erosion continues now with the red
judges have Carl soul laying an ID for the ECB stimulus program and the European Court almost instantly replying that the German Constitutional Court
lacks the legal power to judge on the European institutions role, completely ignoring the German Federal Constitution that specifically defines the
role of the Constitution visa v international treaties. They really don't give a crap. One thing is certain The longer the role of crisis lingers, the
better the odds are for EU implosion. Yeah. In the meantime, I'm now wearing a hipster ponytail, as hairdressers just feel shut and I already need to
get a haircut three months ago. If this is the worst of this lockdown, I'll take it in reality, the power grab of our civil liberties is without
precedent, and I'm wondering how long the obedience will last even in the sheeple will eventually wake up or so I hope for jingles. Oh,
Adam: and we have jingles. Yes. Uh huh.
John: I 33 and playing karma with some Jordan Peterson with kind regards. All the best to all the producers will get mo nation plus 31.
Adam: Now what?
Unknown: I know
Adam: I understand the 33 but then what did he say?
John: karma plan karma no goat. Yeah. With some Jordan Peterson I don't know what Jordan Peterson we have is wrong.
Adam: We do have don't have an ISO a Peterson. I think you're saying
John: it's wrong. Is it good?
Adam: Okay, let me see. It's wrong. I wasn't prepared for this.
John: or wrong, just wrong. Yeah.
Adam: Do you know how many how many clips we have where it's wrong is in the title. I
John: just put typing Peterson and play it. Okay. And then
Adam: the 33 thing. You don't take that very seriously. Do you just type it in and play it? But do you work in government?
Unknown: That's the magic.
The magic number.
That's wrong. Nailed it.
You've got
Adam: sir Caitlyn, the friendly fat man as a first associate Executive Producer $250 he's in Ohio. Sir calling the friendly fat man checking in from
Cincinnati. Normally my six siblings and I would get my mother some combination of flowers, chocolates or whatever. But we figured what better way to
say thanks to mom with a no agenda producer ship. So Happy Mother's Day to Colleen from Cory, Steven Caitlin, Collin, Connor, Shawn and Aiden, you
have been a shining example to all of us, and have made us who we are. Thank you for all the sacrifices and hardships you had to put up with
throughout the years. Happy Mother's Day also to my sisters, Cory and Caitlin as well as our sister in law Kate, we need a deducing for those siblings
who have never donated before and well first we'll do the dee doo dee doo. There you go. sips siblings are clean, they're cleanse but we also need to
call out Tim as a douchebag. dealer's choice Sharpton and Mike Corona thank you both for all you do to keep us folks in flyover country saying the
whole family enjoys your coverage and you have become a staple topic of conversation at our regular family dinners also mom I hope one day you can
forgive me for ruining the hamburgers and that is from sir Colin the friendly fat man we thank you for your courage sir the
Unknown: president meeting with a cola
you thought karma
John: Carrie Jason Perry in East Peter Petersburg, Pennsylvania 250 couldn't figure out how to get my message under donation but here it is. Okay,
let's let's contemplate what he just said there.
Adam: couldn't figure out how to get my message on my donation but here it is when he did it. He couldn't figure it out. He's just letting you know he
had some trouble. But it worked out.
John: I've been a listener for five years stumble upon this back by luck when searching for podcasts and never donated supposedly that means deducing
Adam: Yes, indeed.
Unknown: You've been de deuced
John: how many people we found just through that mechanism? through what probably not a lot so which my podcast keeps my amygdala shrunk and please
keep up the good work and deep dive into the lies. The M five m propagates please call out my brother in law Bob Raymond low as a douchebag several
times to hit him in the mouth even though he was definitely a note. Even though he's already a no agenda listener I guess. Please listen to that horn.
Trump aroused. Look at that juice. Don't eat me Bo Jaiden and karma of course.
Adam: Have we mentioned how sick you people are and we love you for it.
Unknown: Oh my god.
John: It was hard to get it aroused and it is hard to get it aroused but we got it. Oh my gosh.
Unknown: Can you see that?
karma
John: man that combination. Katana Texas. Oh we forgot any. Area 250 bucks he just says Keep up the good work. You can take
Adam: the Hey Ed the booty. Love you man. Thank you. Yes, we have Vincent from lantana Texas 23456 great number combo. Hey guys, we love the show
appreciate the BI weekly dose of M five m five m antibodies. We were punched in the mouth when Adam was on the Joe Rogan experience and had been
listening to you ever since there it is john proof. We got a listener from the road go
John: on. We'll get to get getting going
Adam: again Rogan experience Yeah, we have to get another one. I would like to split this donation 201 dot 23 for Sinead, the mother of my beautiful
daughter who is also my smokin hot wife. I will not say Happy Mother's Day since she is a wonderful and appreciated mother every day. And she doesn't
care for the Hallmark holidays. So it's like no agenda material to meet the rest of the donation. 3333 is for myself so that now we can both be
de-douche
Unknown: de deuced
Adam: Thank you for keeping us sane through this pandemic and if possible, can we get China is asshole and what else did he want? And that's true.
We're all gonna die and karma so Just have to line them up for a second. So China, and then Sorry, I'm spacing today. That's true. We're all gonna
die. Oh my goodness. How the hell am I gonna keep it all straight?
Unknown: I know try and don't trust China China is at home.
You've got karma.
Adam: Thank you. Welcome you too. Thank you very much. Glad you're here.
John: Sarah Gonzalez in Houston, Texas to 3333. She writes in dear john and Adam in the morning, thank you for your courage and standing up to
ignorance. In this day of social censorship. I'm trying to reverse the historical trend in sending this donation in honor of Mother's Day, and all the
moms out there trying to keep their sanity. During this insanity. I am spending most of my time these days with my kids ages eight and six, trying to
use this opportunity to teach them about things such as open debate about ideas, censorship, very good being slaves to those with hidden agendas. My
kids were the ones who we hit in the mouth in the car on the way to New Orleans. And though I still occasionally get a complaint about little girls
get a complaint about little kids Yay. Yeah. My eight year old clearly sees the calm perspective of that knowing that no agenda has brought to our
household amid the Paranoid germophobia and is constantly singing your praises
Adam: excellent.
John: Yes,
Adam: that kid that gets good Yeah, yeah. boost his profile we got to Bruce's profile
John: we definitely have a dame in the making on our hands. Oh it's a her oh great eight year olds a girl Okay good. Cuz as a dame in the making we I
really appreciate what you do. I'm happy to let you know that I'm spending Mother's Day brunch at one of my favorite restaurants that have never been
so happy to live in Texas. There you have
Adam: one is it which which restaurant isn't it?
John: Now she didn't say the reopening of business you should plug it the reopening of bizarre name named a giant it's
Adam: named the child in the restaurant
John: reopening of the businesses feels painfully slow but at least is happening on a little act of rebellion was tearing down to caution tape
surrounding the playground in the park or house a few days ago because even though the parks are open, the playgrounds are still closed rather we
wouldn't want our kids to have too much fun No, we're thankful not to get arrested or have a video of our crime posted on next door by some Korean
Wrangler curtain Wrangler and have and be happy to see a few because they saw their be seeing a few kids playing on the playground have that. So when
we returned today, thanks to our efforts, Jing anyway, should we return to the wraps it up? Please play orange for my smokin hot husband who loves to
yell this. Okay, and send out lots of jobs common to all his producers who are hurting right now and maybe a screaming goat to finish it off. Best
wishes wishes gentlemen, keep up the great work. Sara Gonzales in Houston
Adam: day mom after our own hearts. Sarah Gonzalez. Thank you for your courage Sarah.
Unknown: jobs, jobs, jobs and jobs.
Let's vote for job.
Karma.
Adam: Nikolas checks in from Cincinnati, Ohio to 3333 this is my first donation so I request a much needed dee doo dee doo was hitting the mouth of my
future brother in law about six months ago and I was called out on episode 1217. So time to donate your content and media deconstruction are just what
the doctor ordered and the treatment has successfully shrunk my amygdala. I'd like to request some small business karma for my smokin hot fiance we
created a virtual fitness website during the extra quarantine time and we using the value for value model I hope that works I want let me know this is
a fitness has been the big boom during you cannot buy any fitness equipment. You can't buy a weight a rubber band
John: Yeah. And breadmaking
Adam: breadmaking is enough. That's exactly right.
John: Yeah all the millennials are making bread
Adam: thanks for the inspiration is worked great so far. If any slaves need to get off the couch and break a sweat give it a try. And there's a
website there it's Nick fit two oh my goodness. I want to put that in the show notes. And I'll put it under actually I'll let me just mark this make
sure I do this. I will put it next to your donation so you know that thank you for your courage jingles little Gore. Yay. And there's a small business
karma. So thank you for your courage indeed and welcome to the
Unknown: you've got karma
John: Daniel Galloway from India at Georgia comes in with $229 there's no note that I can find under looking at the subject line donation or Daniel
Galloway. Let me just show you real,
Adam: real quick. I don't think I
John: do.
Adam: Doo doo doo No, I don't have anything. Sorry. I have nothing from him. Nothing.
John: Go on with Adrian. Drink, hon. What drink can drink sounds right? Yeah, Calvert in New York. $205.
Adam: She's a drunk hen.
John: 10 cents. Happy first Mother's Day to me. And Happy birthday to me and my daughter violet. Man. My husband and I love violets a popular name for
kids that for some reason a little moment here. Yeah, my husband and I love the show and listen as a family we could love a goat karma if possible. My
awesome husband Joe thinks it's hilarious. Cheers Dame Adrian. PS I hope the hope Tina the keeper and Mimi, have a great Mother's Day. Well, that's
nice. Yeah, that
Adam: is nice. And yet will there be half the keepers gotten calls and nice things and all that and how about Mimi? Have you Is she with you or she up
at the annex?
John: She is traveling at the moment. Oh, that's unnecessarily traveling. I'm gonna wrangle my
Adam: narc on that woman This is not acceptable. Yes, we have a goat karma for you absolutely love that you listen as a family happy Mother's Day
Adrian first time for everything enjoy.
Unknown: You've got
karma
Adam: barber upon which is in Norwood, Pennsylvania. And we just talked about Pennsylvania. And she says do you Adam and john, thanks for all you do.
I think I'm slowly hitting my husband in the mouth. Or he just encouraged me because I enjoy the show so much. Either way, please give my mother in
law a cancer karma for Mother's Day. That would be an F cancer karma. Of course. I'd also appreciate jobs common for everybody. And last but not least
special goat karma for my boss and friend Tom. He's a longtime listener and regularly donates would you also please play some Sharpton for my husband,
Eric, whose birthday is this Tuesday? This would crack him up. Thanks again. Barbara Pon wits. And that's interestingly, that's, uh, Eric. spelled,
like our own shill.
John: shill and by the way, you have the birthday list out?
Adam: Yeah, I do now. Who's on the list?
John: Eric put his wife on there. Now that guy's unbelievable.
Adam: Mackey? No. Oh my gosh. Danelle Mackey is what is her birthday today?
John: No, it was uh, I think it was Wednesday. Okay.
Adam: And we don't know an age right? Of course.
John: She's 19 he married young boy.
Adam: Exactly. We know how to keep the peace in the divorce act clan. She's 19 Hmm, well, she
John: looks 19
Adam: Yeah, so we do have some, some sharpen for a quick sharpen and you also wanted the F canter and the jobs karma got it all for you right here.
Good boy.
Unknown: We've jobs. jobs, jobs and jobs. Let's vote for jobs.
You've got carmax blowing away.
John: That'll take care of it. And last but not least on this very generous Mother's Day yes show. Anonymous $200.02 he's got a couple jingles on
there. Atlas Shrugged logo. Yay, ITM Jan's please keep me anonymous. I started listening during the election run up of 2016 and having missed an
episode sanks sense. As a staunch libertarian emphasis on the small L. I was overjoyed to find your podcast using the value for value system while I
had donated previously This is my first associate executive producer ship. The show is most certainly the best podcast in the universe. I was further
encouraged by Elon Musk's remark on Rogen about Corona, as he echoed much of what you two have been deconstructing in the past two months. Thanks for
the show notes. They certainly help with grad school. I bet they do. A big Mother's Day shout out to my mama Kim in South Jersey. I love you mom. She
listens regularly. And hopefully this proves that no agenda producers love their mom's dollars that this was for her Dame hood and two cents for the
penny jar.
Adam: There's one and there's the old pennies real copper. It's not that crazy new stuff. And we need atlas shrugged. Yay and a karma and We're good
to go.
Unknown: You've got karma.
Adam: There's love in the room for the moms that's for sure. Love in the room. Well, everybody, thank you, to these executive producers and associate
executive producers, you can proudly display that as your credit for Episode 1241 of the best podcast in the universe, I know that you have not only
made a lot of moms happy. We got we've upped our quota of dame's very excited about the ceremony later. But also you've kept this show going
successfully throughout. We've really had we've now witnessed everything together. We've been through a lot, we've been through a lot of things. But
now also this, I'm very proud of what we're doing very proud of the support today. And look forward to everybody showing up again on Thursday, which
you can find out more about at our donation webpage, vorak.org slash n A, and once again, you're up to speed on all things, Rona.
Unknown: Our formula is this. We go out, we hit people in the mouth
Adam: righto.
John: So that so I got this clip was for the last show, and I just wanted to play it because it's just kind of standalone. And so and I want somebody
in Australia to tell me who this woman is. So she's like a Katie Hopkins of Australia. And so she kind of rails I this is only 31 seconds of something
or went for a couple of minutes because she just kept kept laying into Joe Biden. And she's in Australia, which is I find amusing, but this place is
good. The clip is called fee make.
Unknown: Isn't it just perfect that the party of diversity has gotten rid of every woman and person of color, including the fake Native American
Elizabeth Pocahontas, Warren, and the fake Mexican Beto O'Rourke to end up with two old white millionaire men, one a socialist who had a heart attack
just five months ago. And one is so confused that he has trouble remembering where he is. And why is that Joe Biden is now the front runner to be the
Democratic presidential candidate. Yeah,
Adam: so it's good. Well
John: presented. It is pretty funny. By the way, I do have some ISOs I want to pitch
Adam: right? Yes. Good. We need to pitch pitch it or pitch away. So
John: okay, so let's start with the one which is which is the wimpy guy bright and this is wrong ISO
Adam: wrong ISO for no show wrong. Okay. Noted. Yep.
John: Yeah, here's one done more.
Adam: Oops. Oh, hold on a second. My oxygen cord disconnected. JOHN. Hold on. I gotta plug it back.
John: Yeah, they told you to stop I think from from underwater.
Adam: Yeah. Okay, I'm back. I'm back. I unplugged the cord and lost all oxygen. All right, done more. We could have done more.
Unknown: We could totally do it again.
We could have done more.
Adam: I like it because but we could have done more. Yeah, that's actually not bad. That's, I think it's a little more exciting than
Unknown: wrong.
Adam: Well, now that I hear it, wrong, that's not bad. Good wrong. Okay. It's a very it's a it's a righteous wrong.
John: Yeah, but I like to Dunmore because she's in tears.
Adam: And do you have any more?
John: Yeah, disgruntled.
Unknown: I am not disgruntled.
Adam: I think wrong. I think just wrong. is a contender. Okay, I'm surprised by wrong.
Unknown: I'm
Adam: surprised I like it's it's a righteous wrong. I like it. But we're not, you know, we're not done until we're done.
John: Let's, you want to go over to some to some international COVID Yeah,
Adam: I would like
John: I would like you're organizing your next bit.
Adam: I would like to do I got no bits man. I just did.
John: This start with I have the Italy Russia. But I have let's do USA COVID update this about the reopenings.
Unknown: state by state the country is beginning to face the reality of a slow recovery ahead from the covid 19 pandemic. Companies are considering
ways to bring workers back but the unemployment rate is staggering. Whether you are here in New York where there is still a strict lockdown order or
in an area reopening. This is a challenging time. Let's get started with today's top news. Cases of COVID Continue to slow in most of the country.
Do you have good after
two months there were more reopenings of barbershops, salons restaurants and public spaces but the rules differ state by state in New York where a
lockdown remains for much of the state Governor Andrew Cuomo said hospitalizations new cases and deaths from the virus dropped again today. But Cuomo
said three children have died from the new syndrome associated with COVID-19. And there are 73 reported cases
it's more inflammation, inflammation of the blood vessels, which can then cause problems with their heart.
Cuomo said parents need to be vigilant while New York health officials work with the CDC to investigate this new syndrome. Nationwide, there have now
been more than 77,000 deaths from COVID-19 and more than 1.2 million confirmed cases. Also today after reports at the Trump administration shelved
guidance from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention on how to reopen the country. The White House issued a statement from the director of the
CDC Robert Redfield that said the plan quote was in draft form and had not been vetted. Seriously, I'd
Adam: rather have COVID-19 than listen to that report again.
John: That was that was hate hate
Adam: that was bad. That was uninspiring
John: was not as bad as his lighting.
Adam: Was he at home?
John: Yeah, yeah. And he was not only at home but they light him somebody doesn't like him you know, cuz the lighting guys are the guys that can make
it look good or make it look horrible. He looks like Boris Karloff playing Frankenstein.
Adam: Wow. Okay.
John: Harsh. is very harsh, harsh. Okay, let's go to Italy and see what's going on just Italy or COVID Italy and it's also South Korea.
Unknown: In Italy wants to center of the global pandemic the lockdown is starting to ease. Many bars in Rome were open today for takeaway drinks, but
officials warn that social distancing must be maintained to prevent a resurgence and Coronavirus cases. In South Korea. The mayor of Seoul closed more
than 2000 nightclubs just one week after they weren't reopened. Dozens of new Coronavirus cases were connected to people who attended clubs last week.
Hmm.
John: Not much going on there. So that was pretty dull. You're right. Yeah. So let's go and take a look at de-douche is the COVID Russia and comparing
Russia to Bella rousse.
Unknown: Let's look at what's happening internationally. Russia, like most countries has scaled back its celebrations to mark the end of the second
world war in Europe because of the virus pandemic but in neighboring Belarus, one of the only countries yet to impose any social distancing measures
1000s have gathered to mark the 75th anniversary from Moscow skies data magnate has this report.
Even Russia has postponed this year's Victory Day Parade, but it's smaller neighbor to the west Belarus has not despite more than 20,000 COVID cases.
The veterans were encouraged not to come others incentivized to fill seats. good grades promise to students for example, at a time when many in
Belarus don't trust their president on this pandemic. Last summer one of the official counters have 116 deaths. The freshly dug graves at this
cemetery in the small city of stilts we suggest it's far more
Adam: miniskirt I believe.
Unknown: This reporter for Russia's channel one was expelled from Belarus and his team stripped of their accreditation after this report, which
suggested that even locals don't believe the numbers. Well, this woman telling him her mother had had COVID but that the official cause of death was
heart failure. The picture inside hospitals even in the Capitol is grim. Every piece of space is used up here. And there's that ubiquitous COVID cough
where the state is failing volunteers are stepping in
Adam: the ubiquitous COVID cough has that been identified as a specific type of cough?
John: Yeah, well that's what JC when he had he had COVID and he survived it easy enough. But he ended up with a COVID
Adam: called the cotton that lasts a while.
John: It didn't last as long you know how you get sometimes you get too cold or somebody gets into this just coughed it never goes away. And last and
last and last. You know people had I think Horowitz had it for like three four shows. I like a month he had this cough just terrible cough. The COVID
cough which is really horrible to hear it. It's like it's horrible to hear it. I mean, it's just a cringe. It didn't last long at all. Which is good.
Adam: No, that is good. That is good. Let me see if we can find it. An example of this COVID car
John: It sounds like it sounds like somebody's coffee and then you hear a goose honking
Adam: let's see like a do so here we here we have a couple of examples. The This is Does this sound like you on YouTube? That may be exactly what
we're looking for? Let's see. Why don't I hear anything? That it? No, no, no, that's you're failing
John: into a higher gear. There's a very specific thing it does. It is like really frightening to hear it. The COVID Golf.
Adam: Yes. I got an email which may fit into a good topic for us today. And I and I want to reiterate that this show john, I come to each show, we
don't talk to each other in between shows rarely, maybe an email or something. Typically Johnson me some chick on YouTube. Hey, guys, whatever. That's
usually what I get from john. So we show up and I have my stuff. He has his stuff, and I received an email that I wanted to respond to, I thought that
it would be appropriate, I see that you've got some clips to talk about it. This is from Roland. He's from Germany, German producer. In the morning,
gents, I'm not sure how voting works. But in Germany, it's like this, you get a postcard with your name on it. The city knows where you live is you
have to register when you move to it tells you when and where you can go and vote. Historically, it's been on Sundays between eight and 6pm 8am 6pm.
If you're out of town, you can't make it to the voting place. Usually a school or kindergarten in your neighborhood can send you the postcard back at
no charge. And you can ask for vote by mail papers, which you then get and send back in time done. Well, now this apparently isn't much of a thing in
the US. What is wrong? What is the problem? Why you also jacked up about it? Some analysis would be helpful, especially to the international
listeners. I think that's an appropriate question, Roland.
John: Well, I have two clips on this bingo boom. First of all, you can vote by mail and some some states. In fact, that's all you do. You don't even
there's not even this processor, you're talking about Washington State, for example, is a 100% vote by mail. There's a lot of people that believe that
it invites fraud. And allow
Adam: me to explain that as I understand the fraud part of it in the United States, and this is why it's an issue. We I I hate to say it but our
voting public is pretty dumb. So when someone knocks on your door and says, Hey, did you get your mailing voting Bally's? I don't know, man, it's
running or somewhere? Well, listen, why don't you just, you know, just, I'll take care of it. I'll hand it in just what do you want to be democrat?
Right? Okay, we'll just write this down. And I'll mail it for you don't have to worry about it. It's called harvesting. And sometimes we'll get
ballots that are just empty in the affiliate in for them. It's, it is and this is, I think it was Orange County or Calabasas somewhere in in
California where they they followed these people and showed how they do it. And this is not just the US but it but this is harvesting is a real issue.
And also, I think it's just a lame as a citizen, you go into the booth and you kick the lever. And you go there you stand in line with everybody
grousing about it. It's part
John: of the ID by the way. Well,
Adam: no, no, that's a different Well, in Texas, heaven forbid, yeah, Texas, you have to show your ID.
John: Well, here's a question. Here's an example of this is what you have to deal with. This is on PBS again. And they're having this this problem in
Connecticut because Connecticut, you can do an absentee ballot, but it's a very complicated process. And the problem with Connecticut is what the
story is about mostly is that they the Connecticut constitution says you have to show up. Yes. So it's not like Washington State is like is designing
the systems designed for vote vote by mail. And by the way, it's funny how the harvesters do such a good job. They tend to get a state loaded with
Democrats and I can just accuse the democrats but when you hear reports like this, here's the vote by mail fraud question that was asked on the PBS.
Among some people that are discussing how to do this in Connecticut.
Unknown: We just six months until November's presidential election states across the country are trying to determine how they will safely collect and
count ballots during a national health emergency. For many states, that means reevaluating in person versus absentee voting. Just yesterday,
California Governor Gavin Newsom announced that the entire state would be asked to vote by mail and the November election. But for states like
Connecticut with a long history of in person voting, the push to vote by mail remains a complicated task. NewsHour weekend's Christopher Booker has
more. The scenes for Wisconsin's recent election did not sit well with Connecticut Secretary of State Denise Merrill.
That was a turning point in my discussions with both the legislative leadership and the governor. Nobody wants to look like Milwaukee, frankly, and
that that can happen pretty easily
after democratic governor Tony Evers executive order that delayed the state's election by two months was overturned by the Supreme Court. Wisconsin
voters had to go to polling places if they wanted to cast a ballot. 52 people who worked the polls, or voted on April 7 have tested positive for
COVID-19. A situation Meryl does not want to duplicate in her state.
You know, people are just waking up to the fact that they may be asked to go either in a primary or particularly in the general election is their
concern and jeopardize their health. And I think the Milwaukee situation really galvanized people because it was all over television. And people were
home watching it,
but hoping to minimize in person voting in Connecticut will not be an easy task with voting laws dating back to the state's 1818 constitution. The
rules to vote absentee or by mail in the state, nicknamed the constitution state are restrictive.
Adam: Yeah, that's a that's a decent overview.
John: Well, that's a decent already. That was the wrong clip. But when you told me to play, vote by mail fraud question. Oh,
Adam: it was the wrong clip.
John: But that's a better clip for the intro to this clip I wouldn't have I should have actually played that clip first. So you accidentally did the
right thing.
Unknown: voter fraud is a major talking point for those against expanding vote by mail. On April 8, President Trump tweeted that Republicans should
fight very hard when it comes to statewide mail and voting. Democrats are clamoring for it tremendous potential for voter fraud. And for whatever
reason, doesn't work out well, for Republicans. voter fraud comes up quite often. Have you seen rampant voter
fraud in Connecticut?
John: Oh, absolutely not.
Unknown: I mean, for people to complain about absentee ballot fraud in Connecticut is really kind of ridiculous. Because we have so many processes in
place. First, you have to mail the application to people, they have to fill it out, mail it back to the clerk, the clerk then mails the ballot to the
person which is in a double envelope, you have to put it in an inside envelope and then in an outside envelope to protect their anonymity. And then
you mail it back to the clerk. And during all this process. The clerk has to note every step of the way. In our electronic voter registry. Secretary
Merrill says there's little evidence that there is widespread voter fraud in Connecticut, can you point to specific instances of voter fraud in
Connecticut?
I don't have them on me. But we deal with these every year, we end up having a lot of kind of quirky election issues that I don't particularly find
coincidental, but it's something we need to address.
The critics have
expanded vote by mail often cite voter fraud. Is there evidence that when you increase the access to vote by mail,
fraud increases?
No.
None.
There's no evidence
whatsoever. Nowhere it does not exist. Oh,
Adam: I'm poorly informed then.
John: Yeah, you're you don't know what you're talking about.
Adam: You need to shut up.
John: Because she said right there, that democrat woman. But she said no, no, never happened. never happens. It never happens. I know what you're
talking about. Just because you go you walk into the good like, for example, here at the house. I walk into a mailman and there's there's two or three
ballots sitting there. I could pick any with any one of them up, type a bunch of stuff. I put stuff on there, sign somebody's phony name, send it in.
I could do that anyone could do it. Oh, somebody they lose some mail. somebody steals it from a post office box. I mean, that's just minor. But the
harvest thing which you pointed out, which has always been the the big threat. And the joke of it is the democrats always hated much of this because
it would be? Well, I mean, the republicans used to hate this for the reasons that the democrats used to like it, which is in the deep south back in
the 50s. And 60s, they would just democrats would steal all the black votes just rouse
Adam: the black vote.
John: They just steal them they steal the black vote, or they buy a vote. They say you there's another way of doing it. We're harvesting you go up to
everybody you go door to door. So I'll give you five bucks for your ballot.
Adam: Is that illegal? I think it's fine.
John: It's illegal,
Adam: is it?
John: Yeah. It's illegal. It's illegal.
Adam: Is it illegal to say to someone here's five bucks write down your vote right now?
John: That's not illegal. Well, probably not.
Adam: Isn't that exactly what politics is? I'm going to give you this for your vote. Isn't that?
John: Maybe we should it's, it's, it's asking for trouble. Go. Well,
Adam: there's that.
John: But this woman when I heard that clip, were at the very end of that clip. She goes, Oh,
Unknown: no.
John: Then I know something's up.
Adam: How do we usually put that somewhere? We had a thing about that. We could see Oh, yeah. That's not it. Where is it?
John: Ah,
Adam: we had nothing to see here. I've lost so many jobs. I'm losing my touch. You are the eyeball. Nothing. It's not completely healed. I'll give you
that. But it's not that bad.
Unknown: Don't look over here. Nothing to see.
Adam: There we go. But for a long time. I couldn't find it. It's been replaced by
Unknown: what happens
John: orange.
Adam: So what is taking place now is we have this political fight, which Trump is CIA's tweeting about a lot so I guess he's worried is this you know,
the house is looking to make legislation is that I guess you can do it by state even to vote by mail, because oh Coronavirus be too dangerous for
people to show up and vote.
John: And it's lame. Is it too dangerous for them to show up at the grocery store and stand in line? Is it too dangerous to go to the hair cutter? I
mean, why is this more dangerous than these other things that people do constantly?
Adam: If there's a shop that says hair cutter, I'm not going that's a dangerous shop. It says coughs that's a different story. So there is a lot going
on in the political In fact, pretty much all of it is now political. And I have been enjoying these transcripts from the Is it the House Intelligence
Oversight Committee, these 5053 transcripts that have been released?
John: I have a clip. Can I just tell you which one our friend Kaylee? Yeah. slamming him Yummy.
Adam: Yummy, yummy. Oh, no,
John: I reading from these transcripts and saying, Well, how grainy was that they were released.
Adam: Now let's just go over this. Before we play. Before we say calian you meesh now has Flynn been exonerated? Or is that just Barr saying it has to
happen the judge hasn't done it yet. He's he actually forced exonerated exonerate dropped all charges.
John: Well, that case it's not No, no, I take it back. You gotta use this right? Because you'll get jumped on by all of these guys that are going to
write your note. It's not exoneration when the case is dropped? Was it cases dismissed, rights dismissed.
Adam: And what is interesting about the dismissal is that it comes from now overwhelming evidence from the FBI is on files that they were railroading,
Flynn.
John: Yeah, it was
Adam: really railroading him like like, like massholes like real thugs. Really not okay stuff.
John: But then he did a fat it's one of these old Russian things like Barry I used to do you know, he said, Show me a man, I'll find you a crime,
right? In addition to the burial Stalinist stick ideas, a way to do it. And that's what they were doing. And it was, but Obama was behind it. Well,
Adam: this is what's interesting. So now we have in, in this case, all of a sudden, we have 53, transcripts, declassified of all of these players, and
this is the hours and hours and hours of testimony. It's very interesting to read. I was interested in Brad parscale, the guy who's, who is now the
campaign manager, for 2020. The guy was just a web dude in Texas, in San Antonio, who did you know, like the wineries did a one pager website for
Yvonne cuz thing, whatever. And you just and they said, well, we're gonna explain 2015 exploratory throw up a page for candidate Trump, see how it
looks. And it just grew from there. And the guy just turned out to be really smart. He's never done any political campaigns, anything like that. And
he just used cars. In fact, he did everything that the political consultants in Washington DC that they advise, he did the opposite. He did all kinds
of different innovative things. And it's really interesting to read his story. Now, there's not much in the way I mean, every five or so, while you
were selecting vendors for the website, did any of them possibly have ties to Russia? I'm not kidding. Every question is like that. So did they did
they speak with an accent? I mean, this is the kind of stuff that was going on. And this has worried a lot of people. And the main, here's what's
interesting, if Flynn The case is dropped, and his his, you know, what he was accused of was lying to the FBI. And now it turns out, he was lying to
the FBI because the FBI said you better lie, or we're gonna lock your kid up. And the lie was a very minute detail of a phone conversation he had had
with the Russian ambassador Kislyak and the feds and when they were interviewing, which I believe include Peter struck, they had already heard the
call, they knew the answers to the questions they were asking. And of course, he answered something wrong or did I don't remember that or I didn't
have this time. And then they said, well, you're gonna have to plead guilty here. Otherwise, we're going to get your kid and he has a kid on the way
and it was it's really ugly. Really. It's like J. Edgar, Edgar Hoover, typestyle ugly and
Unknown: the
Adam: President Obama, all of a sudden has some coincidentally leaked audio that comes out. In fact, I have a little news report about it. Because I
think what's happening, I believe, Obama, as you pointed out, Obama is implicated in this thing. It goes all the way up to him. And he's striking back
but interesting while he's doing it.
Unknown: Former President Obama discussed the Michael Flynn case during a phone call with some former Obama administration officials. And then
portions of the audio of that call were leaked to Yahoo News. Flynn, you may remember pled guilty to lying to the FBI about his communications with
the Russian ambassador. The Justice Department announced Thursday it plans to drop the case against the former national security adviser. Obama says
he was shocked by the move. That's the kind of stuff
where you you begin to
get worried.
Basic, not just institutional norms, but
our basic understanding of rule of law.
is is
is is a risk.
President Trump praised the Justice Department's decision. He also praised Flynn calling him an innocent man. The White House says it believes the FBI
was trying to target and trap Flynn over his comments. Not surprisingly, reaction up on Capitol Hill has been split how
Adam: I don't like this report. I think it's full of crap. They also left stuff out. Here's the actual leaked call. And there's something that Obama
said here, which is factually incorrect. And I'm waiting for the news media to let us know about that.
Unknown: The news over the last 24 hours, I think has been somewhat downplayed about the Justice Department dropping charges against Michael Flynn.
And the fact that there is
no precedent that anybody can find for
someone who's been charged with perjury.
Just getting off
John: scot free. Interestingly,
Adam: he wasn't charged with perjury. That's just not true.
John: No, he didn't take an oath. perjury is very specific.
Adam: So why did Obama say that? Why is he making a big deal out of well, this has never happened before a guy perjured himself and he was like, No, I
think Obama's a little a little were a little frayed skin a little hot under the feets.
John: Yeah, did sound Do you think maybe Obama knew this was being recorded? Absolutely. And it was it was another piece of disinformation get thrown
to the pot is perjury. Nonsense. Totally. Anyway, picks it up
Adam: and see if it's even flies. Yeah. Interesting. Well, that shows he's very when Obama has to step in and do this kind of crap. He's worried.
John: Yeah, or something. That's very strange. Well, I do have the super clips. Well, what this was, this is about Flynn. And this is a bunch of clips
that came right after Flynn was first arrested, indicted, whatever they want to call it, the advertising. And all the media was banned. And and Trump
knew this was the setup. He bitched about he's a flinch and have been arrested. He's a great patriot, and on and on, and the White House and and the,
the right, the conservatives all knew something was fishy about this whole thing. And meanwhile, MSNBC and CNN and all the rest of the news media,
they had their thoughts about it, and they were mocking everybody.
Unknown: President Trump and his top aides have been routinely ignoring the truth and pushing phony conspiracy theories.
The President, it seems to be saying that this was a case of entrapment that Michael Flynn was essentially pressured into line. What is your response?
I
think that's hogwash.
You know, there are all kinds of conspiracy theories about how he was entrapped.
The FBI agents didn't do anything wrong here. So I think that's important because there are a lot of sort of conspiracy theories. They
Adam: all work together and you know, the fox news, people in the White House fuel these sorts of rumors, do they
Unknown: send these around with fax machines? They come up with these conspiracy theories and they send around fax machines, they should just knock it
off and realize that they're ridiculous conspiracy theories are going to be knocked down, stop stop with the conspiracy theories. So I think that loud
sound you heard it about 1230. Eastern was the sound of 10,000 conspiracy theories by the Trump defenders exploding
the sound you hear is a million conspiracy theories exploding.
The trumpets all over the country. Their heads were blown up.
Oh,
here's another conspiracy theory that has been blown to bits Trump talking points and right wing media conspiracies demolished for Michael Flynn. He
was
duped. It's so embarrassing to
watch all your chips
in the middle of the table. Better be damn sure you got a good hand.
The FBI broke standard protocol in the way that they came in and ambush Gen flan.
Adam: She knew better.
John: Yeah,
Adam: mad they won't be heard no one cares what they said two days ago. Do we know that all wrong cares? It's like fine. I think they're losing so
much ground the mainstream. Just people don't care. That's why people are out and about. They're not listening to your fear anymore. They're done with
you.
John: There's a lot of people that are shitting in there.
Adam: Yeah. But that's incurred Wranglers. Yeah, but they live in California.
Unknown: Imagine all the people who could do Oh Yeah, that'd
be fun.
John: There's definitely a lot in California but they're not all in California. Oh, people that we have to thank aren't all in California. But the
first one is,
Unknown: they're all there.
John: Sir. Hey, idiot. in Concord, California. comes in with 160 bucks. He does have a note I'm so credit. Sure. Hey, idiot. This is the continuation
of my animated no agenda $10 per episode pledge of support. There Alan Bose is next and he's in Langley, bc 137 88. Congratulations to Sir Jim Watson
claiming part of the overwhelming barony of dBc. And he goes on to say, Now we just need someone to claim vancouver island in the Caribbean.
Yes, sir Austin Baron of the Puget Sound in Seattle, Washington. 125. That was 137 88 for sure. Ellen. Bo's Dame Laura.
Adam: There's no way Hold on. Hold on. If you're gonna just have to say Happy Mother's Day to Dame Laura of the snowy cascades. Oh, and then she comes
in. Right out of that
John: red Jen lore of the story. cascade comes in with the same amount of money 125 we should actually move the tool. They're gonna be doing Executive
Associate executive producer dun dun. She says Happy Birthday to my best guy ever. My husband sir Austin. Oh, Baron, parrot. The Puget Sound Well,
yes, no, your two are going to be joined at the hip yes and move to associate executive producer ship you can use it on your LinkedIn you call us
Quinn Bay $111.11 he needs to deducing
Unknown: okay.
You've been de deuced
John: Brian and headlam or head dumb head dumb. in Elk Grove, California $106.61. And he's written become knighted. Yes. And he does have read
Adam: this your Adam if you do the honors of chipping in the penny and will reach knighthood. Well consider that done what a long strange trip it's
been. I was driving West through Utah at five in the morning as the sun rose over the salt lakes now is flooded with gratefulness for all that you do.
I pulled over at the nearest rest stop and sent a donation that pushed me over to knighthood. Wow. A few years ago, my Amiga was on the brink of
exploding while I was studying at Berkeley during the Trump Hillary debate. Wow. And you're alive man. Then john and Adam swooped in to save the day.
Shout out to Nick McNeil who turned me on to you guys after listening to a few episodes back on a long road trip. I was hooked. I've been a loyal
listener ever since. I would like to be knighted as sir Ryan the roamer of many lands at the roundtable. May I please have some lavender blossom CBD
rub and coconut Lacroix honored to be a member of this prestigious group. Please call my dad Kyle out as a douchebag. He's normally working in the
garage or going out fishing so maybe say his name a few times to get his attention. Dad Kyle stop being a douchebag and Thank you Ryan. I'm going to
too late order but I'm getting to get you your lavender blossom CB Robin Lacroix at the table for moments away from now.
John: Cheers sir Seth, Seth Griffin in Highland Park, Illinois. 10101 Mother's Day, by the way that if you ever noticed that everyone names Seth. Now
there's a bunch of them. There's a lot of celebrities Seth MacFarlane said, you know, Greene said so and so. But just sets they're all about the same
exact age.
Adam: Really? No.
John: So there had to be some moment at that around their birth year. That was the reason they were all called Seth. There's very few young sets and
there's almost no sets my age and or your age for that matter. Yeah. So is any set out there? Tell me who's What's the reason they wrote your called
Seth Was it a soap box or soap box soap opera character
Adam: who was the who was the Seth of the day that Brock was set. Got this raffle on us? Yes, let's find out.
John: Anyway. Sure. Seth comes in $101.01 on a Highland Park and he has a Mother's Day shout out to Kathy, who's a longtime listener, and will make a
heck of a dame. On word Matthew Schauer in Eagan, Minnesota. 100. Easy, sir. I'm happy mother's day to my mom Laurie Laurie shower. Hello, Lori. Sure
you can read this one.
Adam: Yes, sir Rob Van Dyck from the Netherlands back after some dealings with PayPal concerning my donation history. I have now much too late for my
brother's birthday present. He celebrated on the third of March three three is mine and a nine nine my dad's in 1111. That's interesting. 339 911
lemon. However, after PayPal first canceled now restarting my monthly donation of $100 I was reminded to look into my accounting again. And there was
my donations to the best podcasting universe already. finally ready for download on paypal. It's a little confusing after being knighted myself
earlier this year would now like to have my douchebag brother be knighted Okay, so he's giving his knighthood to his douchebag brother, although he
himself you must love him. Although he himself never donated insert douchebag here please. I would still like to donate a knighthood to him as to
relieve him from the douchebaggery once and for all. And after all, he is the one who hit me in the mouth years back, please Knight him sir Ed. of the
woods edge for us. No additions to the menus, but we will quietly mosey along towards the hookers and blow and maybe later on we'll have a taste of
the mutton and Mead. But I'm afraid we won't be that hungry after the hookers and blow. Guys from Holland man they know what's up. So Rob Van Dyck,
thank you very much. $100
John: What did you say there in Dutch?
Adam: mit freundlicher fruit. You know what that means? JOHN de-douche mit freundlicher fruit. John's de-douche
John: Robert de Groot and Yolanda Williams set in mierlo. Netherlands. Next on the list. They do listening for seven years to the BPI to you but I
have not donated since 2015. This makes me feel ashamed. I would have to request your forgiveness. Which I think it means the de-douche thing
Adam: I think that's what
Unknown: you've been d deuced.
John: I hit my smokin hot wife Yolanda in the mouth and now she insists to make a long do donation as always the wife is right and will be better live
our life supporting the show. Dad and we miss you in Holland I'll bet you in a better place right now though with the keeper
Adam: Adams in a better place right now. It sounds like a dead Adam. Robert he's in a better place now.
John: Captain boss 100 bucks from Franklin George's you got a mom in here listed. Who needs a jobs karma give you that the end Daniel Lange a man in
Victoria BC 9641. Cornelius Hoenig in Brooklyn New York a
Adam: six in honor of his smokin hot milk Coby k on Mother's Day we're a millennial couple love to listen to you Boomer uncle's bickering and ranting
during the long drives Upstate. We hope our nine month old son's first words will be your grumpy Oh brother.
John: So the way So do we have been called out for saying that too much? anonymous 808 boobs donation and Happy Mother's Day to my smokin hot wife the
best mom in the universe to our two human resources from grumpy green guy. PSM a longtime douchebag which I'll stay that way until I'm knighted like
that I
Adam: like that style. James Niemeyer in Tulsa Oklahoma 79 third credibly my mom Sue passed away a few years ago Love and Light always accepted. I
miss her so terribly much but she didn't raise no douchebag here 7932 represent her birthday July 9 1930. Thank you, James. I'm sure she's sir. She's
smiling that you gave your hard earned cash to those two losers.
John: Bill Johnson and grovetown ga 7186 needs to do dishing boom
Unknown: you've been de deuced
John: It's interesting. He's he's apparently his office got a bunch of paranoids in it. pushed off the whole office sad paranoia is real. We had two
large scanners delivered that are about the size of a chest freezer, and this person gets out there out of their cube and wants 20 feet to spray with
Lysol. Spray with Lysol, get Lysol.
Adam: micho resaw
John: Mitchell O'Reilly 69. I think we got a Mother's Day call out here.
Adam: Yes, Mitch the militia. Oh, hold on. Hold
John: on, Melissa. Oh,
Adam: Mitch, Mitch the meat cutter my smokin hot overworked quarantine wife Melissa. Oh, we love you and need you more than ever, babe. I'm working
insane hours, six days a week trying to feed America and she stuck to his I think his trucker and she's stuck at home trying not to go insane with
four cute kids six years old and younger. Holy crap. Give that woman a medal. she's a she's a new voluntary listener. So I graciously asked that she
be deduced and considered for the dame Dr.
Unknown: Ben de douche? Yes.
Adam: She's she will be considered for the dame drive. And thank you and you drive safe
John: barrister of Baltimore's easier to do now there's less cars on the road, but there's a lot of 100 mile an hour tickets being given up by two
maniacs? Yes. Mitchell O'Reilly. That was Mitch de barrister, a Baltimore Baltimore 69 kr in Palo Alto, California 60. He's got some story here then.
Adam: Well, he was working on the wiki you were going back and forth with him.
John: Oh, yeah. Yes. Yes. He's working on a wiki. Yeah. And you thought you wouldn't like the idea I'd like the idea. And I thought you are wiki hater
so I didn't say that specifically, but I mentioned that he should be talking to you too.
Adam: I've removed myself from the Convo
John: a good Jeffrey cinnamon Meanwhile, didn't remove himself with the Congo and donated 60 bucks for South Euclid Ohio. Request some jobs karma give
you that at the end Matt Brown in Raleigh, North Carolina. 5920. Got a mom once you read that?
Adam: Yeah, he says I've been listening for years. My first donation so deducing his donation is in memory of my wonderful mother who passed away a
few years ago from cancer. f cancer for her and anyone else who's dealing with it coming up. Yes, the true invisible enemy that will do that at the
end, Matt for sure. Harrison nobles. Southport North Carolina. Wish my wonderful mom Lynette Happy Mother's Day. She loves to listen to the show and
is a big fan of Q anon.
John: Wow. Okay. Well, uh, Roger Prater in Talladega. Alabama is 5720. home with a famous racetrack. And the Knights apparently have special knights
and Talladega. Now, he's got a he's a mastadon. Guy, probably the only person who's listened to no agenda Really? And probably the only buy Oh, he's a
blind person. Listen to no agenda. Okay. Release. No. Because Adams mentioned how blind people would be able to work with things like jazz hands
clapping. I'm so happy. I'm so glad that no agenda isn't like other conservative shows where they just do the opposite of the left. This is true, but
we're also not a conservative show. Not a conservative show.
Adam: But But Devin Prater says he has a birthday. I don't think he's on the list. Hold on a second. I turned out Yeah. 2016 always belated. So let me
just see. I want to make sure we get a stick to put him on. No, Devin. 26 on the seventh, we have we have more blind listeners than you than you'd
think. Actually. I I think well throughout the years we've had at least 20 of self identified. But it could be more at podcasts, of course. Fantastic.
It was it's great for people who are have more scent. Audible senses sensory. People who are deaf. It's Griffin. It's horrible for people who are
blind. It's great. There we go. I'm trying to just say it was horrible. That was really bad. But anyway, Roger, thank you very much. It just put you
on the list. And thank you for that it was it says Roger Prater. Oh, yeah,
Unknown: Devin
Adam: now he's done. Okay, gotcha. And Roger comes in.
John: Christopher rember, are Remer actually in circus media at circus media, Missoula, Montana fit 555 55 and he says to my mom, Christine, thank you
for being the best mom a kid could hope for No.
Adam: Bear and Bob have the dude's name Ben 5532. High Point North Carolina bear and Bob of high point I appreciate everything my mother, otter Lee
has gone through being a single mom raising two boys herself. November Charlie for Romeo golf says 7373 kilo five alpha Charlie Charlie.
John: Sure, David CPU in Massillon, Ohio 5110, double nickels on the dime happy. This is a lot of birthday mom days call out is more than ever all the
shows combined. Happy Mother's Day to my mom morona why and my wife at Pew pew pew sure Dave.
Adam: Thomas Miller Naperville, Illinois 5510 double nickels on the dyno note Christopher ruettiger. from Wyoming motifs why meeteetse myths How do
you parent was it petite meet? See, Mother's Day wishes to my smokin hot wife pickles on our first of many mother's days. Tankless pickups thanks for
all the great show, especially producer who made the lockdown 2020 mix on show 1238 fantastic Andy thank you very much Chris. Sir Patrick global Baron
of Tennessee checking in with double nickels on a dime. Happy Mother's Day to Dame Sarah for being the bestest mom and taking care of all of us.
John: That's good steward wills. Walton instead Stafford Staffordshire, UK, to defy another double nickels and a dime Happy Mother's Day to my mom
Jill 86 and still going strong in this era of cower in place. And also a smokin hot wife Michelle was put up with me while simultaneously bringing up
the two wonderful children Lucy and Alex. Love and Light.
Adam: Then we have Denise delozier Maryland Maryville, Tennessee birthday call out force for sir dancing Mike from my smokin hot wife Denise. She
suggested the great present will be a donation to the best podcasting universe for his 52nd birthday on Sunday, May 10. This will also contribute to
her ongoing drive today hood noted and done thank you both
John: Daniel Murray should do 120 and this donations have thanked his mom Jackie for all she does. I have the best mom in the world. However, I must
call her out as a douchebag Happy Mother's Day a lot my two sisters these are all douchebag call outs Stephanie. Elizabeth and my father guy. And he
needs a de-douche in the meanwhile,
Unknown: you've been de deuced
John: Sir Sir Simon Baron to the bike in Herndon, Virginia. Happy Mother's Day to my mom, Vicki who hit me in the mouth
Adam: a decade ago.
John: If it wasn't for her and no agenda, I'd probably be a total slave. Please send her comment a douchebag. Hair Governor Wolf for her.
Adam: Governor Wolf, you have been douchebag
John: voice as a governor. Hello. Sir Andrew Gardner in Leonard's town was Maryland. 50 Happy Mother's Day to my milk. Melissa. Eric boy, these are
$50 donors from now on is all $50.
Adam: Can I just say something? I don't care. What radio station what network you listen to? I did like Could you imagine PBS? Doing Mother's Day do
Mother's Day. They they do Mother's Day. Greetings on the air at NPR. I should say. Can you imagine them? Saying and this is for my milk. Mom. Can you
take it? I mean, this is what's so great about this show.
John: Just pleasure like just point he'll be around for a while. Yeah. Eric, especially with this support. Eric Boyd in Milpitas, California $50 he's
been a total douchebag since hearing Adam on the job there is you get the number two
Adam: number two.
John: I'm telling you go back go back.
Adam: I lost my job to Coronavirus fear hype this week. Me and 35 million plus other Americans are in desperate need of jobs karma. Yes, I will do
that. Your show is the only place to get it and a personal deducing please. You've been de deuced got it. Eric coming up.
John: Andrew Boyce in South Elgin, Illinois. 50 and this is a need of it uses a deducing
Adam: first time donors.
John: Lauren Calvin is smoking on wife Rockstar wife was awesome during labor. I was hitting them out two months ago and a What's her name? What's her
name? Well, okay, well, Happy Mother's Day to her. Drew mo check in El Cerrito, California. 50 David beach. 50 Pamela Schaeffler 50 would like to
donate for Mother's damage to my son Andrew is cutting his head and shaking his What? What? What? move this over? to donate for Mother's Day. I'm sure
my son Andrew love sitting with me listening to your show. I know he's always on. He's up in heaven cupping his head and shaking his Yes. laughing at
his buttons. Yes. I'm sorry. demola sir, hey, most of the Piedmont province in mooresville North Carolina, Kim burden in Greenville, Michigan for her
sweet mom or his Kim as a gender listening like Pat Benjamin Rosler. Robert decades. in Fairfax, Virginia, he's a sir by the way Sir Robert, Robert
Gannon in. No person nobody says. I think this is where a note goes happy mom's day mom and he goes to she has a monthly subscription should take care
of the accounting. Bob.
Unknown: Sir Kyle
John: Meyer in Atlanta, Georgia wraps this up. I'm going to take one quick look down the list to see if there's any mom call outs on the lesser
amounts. We just mentioned the mom. There's a mom's Yeah, there's a happy mom's day from someone.
Adam: It's all pretty much anonymous. got it covered. Yeah. And we're always happy to do it. And I am I too am surprised a little taken aback with the
the support for the moms. This has never happened on the show before.
John: Never you Oh, you I got it. I got it figured it out.
Adam: I know. Okay, what do you think? COVID? Yes, I agree. I think that during this time, is when people are looking around at their household and
going Holy crap, she does all that. That's what's going I'm telling you that's what's going on. Yeah, that's what's going on. And this
John: is this is the worst show one of the worst shows of the year is the Mother's Day show.
Adam: It's seriously absolutely the worst
John: no donation is one or two guys say my mom, no enthusiasm
Adam: at all at all. Well, thank you all very much for this and also thanks to you who came in under 50 for the anonymity also a lot of our programs.
You're right we'll be around for a while and you can support us like this. Thank you. It's very much appreciated and Happy Mother's Day. Happy
Mother's Day to all moms yes Happy Mother's Day. And their moms do a great we don't have moms so I always like to say that my mom's dead. It always it
always puts a smile on people's face on Mother's Day when they hear me say that all right here we go with our jobs and F cancer karma again. Thank you
all very much. We will be back for a another show where you can support us as well. That'll be on Thursday for that go
Unknown: to bull run.org.
Slash and a
job jobs, jobs, jobs and jobs. Let's vote for jobs.
Adam: Well, we're radioactive the Geiger counter is blast in the background that is a fact may 10 2020 here's our birthday list. We have Adrian drink
Khan and a daughter violet both celebrating today. We have Devin Prater who turned 26 on the seventh so belated birthday Happy birthday to Devin Maxim
Rifkin. Happy Birthday his wife Olga. She celebrated yesterday. Denise delozier says Happy Birthday to her husband sir dancing Mike turned 52 today's
her Kevin deals 34 on the 12th Barbara Pon Wits Happy Birthday to her husband Eric also celebrating on the 12th of Dame Laura Wilson says Happy
Birthday to her husband sir Austin Barrett of Baron of Puget Sound. He turns 54 on Tuesday. And finally, Eric the shilling your hubby loves you very
much. That's why I put you on the list. Happy birthday to Dell Maggie and Happy Birthday from everybody here the best podcast in the universe.
Unknown: Don't get around douchebag
is we all think your brothers
and sisters who gave
them nice.
And we have one
Adam: title changing today thanks to upping his supports in the show up to $101,000 for Kevin deals by count of Charlotte becomes the Earl of North
Carolina and we are very proud to have him there. And thank you very much for your courage. So then we have one two, so we have three games and four
nights on deck for today. bringing out the big blade
John: Look at this. Whoa.
Adam: I'm on stage here. Chrissy chrome and Diane dicer Olga Rifkin, Joel Tucker Ryan had Matthew shower and Ed Van Dyck all of you are about to enter
the no agenda roundtable of the knights and dames very proud to pronounce the KD Dame Chrissy Dame dicer Olga Sermo site the night of the psycho not
sir Ryan the rumor of many Lancer Matt Ensor, head of the woods at for you we've got a person blow rent boys and Chardonnay. We got lavender blossom
CBD rub and all kinds of groovy stuff like rubenesque women and Rosie geishas and sock a vodka and, and vanilla or perhaps you just want the mutton
and mead that people usually come for the hookers and blow. They stay for the mutton and Mead. Congratulations, all of you and thank you for
supporting the no agenda show please head over to no agenda nation.com slash rings Eric The show will take care of you and take good care of you make
sure that you get your ring and your sealing wax and your certificate as a P. And we actually have today
of course because of the Rhona the no agenda meetups have come to a screeching halt but not entirely because a lot of our producers just will not give
up they've done different types of meetings and I believe Boston is checking in with a report.
Unknown: This is the Boston no agenda screen meet up red 33 Red 33 We are live with the one and only the Northeast Brandon aka 33 sam
holler at your boy fuel free pop pop. Pop us
John: we're also here with JJ
Unknown: yo
jj renda plunk here.
John: And this is sir Nathan Lee Miller foster care on a good night of the wait log Blue Origin of the gold mountain top directory on stone and bear
the sword report. I can't believe I remember that. Thank you so much. pop up and corndog
Unknown: We love you and thank you for inspiring these meetings in the morning. Thank
you very much.
Adam: Yeah, allowed group they are
John: the booze is flowing. Yes.
Adam: Right and then of course no agenda meetup calm will start moving again. I did want to mention Sir scatman of Norristown, Pennsylvania has put
one on the calendar, the donut narc the thinks meetup. And that's coming up on I don't think it's until the 20th but that will be FEMA Region three.
And that will be as I said in Morristown, Pennsylvania. Morristown in Norristown. It's gotta be Morristown right, Morristown. So go to no agenda
meetup.com To find out more no agenda meetups where everything is kind of just like a potty.
Whoo, what a show what a day moms everywhere are happy. Happy, happy. Wild. Yeah.
John: So I have two things gone while What? I have two things left. Okay. I have the Kaylee slamming him each.
Adam: Oh, yes. Yeah, I was kind of excited about that. Yeah, we should
John: we do that now. And then last but not least to that last. It's not as good as your other slams in the past, but it's just a similar style. And
I'm liking the way she's doing these things. A lot of people like her. Then I got the debate and came out it looks like it came out of the basement.
Adam: Oh, okay. This is good news.
John: He did they did a special special. I don't know what a meetup personal Wait, was
Adam: this? Was this yet another technological abortion?
John: No, it was actually pretty good.
Adam: I heard that he had a really bad one
John: didn't do it. Well, and it was like Joe Biden live and he liked to live was like in quotes. It was like, you know,
Unknown: he's like
John: so so he's in the he comes out with the with a stupid mass gun looks like an idiot. And I think he's in his back in his in his basement with a
gun. I don't think he's does a bookshelf she i think is a green screen. I think they just changed the set. You have him standing. That's what I think.
I don't think he was because I don't know that he's got this background. And then if you listen carefully, I'm going to play two clips. This is the
first one is a bit of Biden. You play that? Has so here. Oops. Being here is pacing. Oh, here we go.
Unknown: It has so far cost 10s of 1000s of Americans life and millions of jobs. And make no mistake. It doesn't matter how much the market rebounds.
As long as there are millions of unemployed struggling people to get by. We won't be anywhere near bouncing back.
Adam: That sounds really dumb. We Yeah.
John: As long as millions of people struggling to get by.
Adam: It's great. That's basically what he's saying.
Unknown: As long as there are millions of unemployed struggling people to get by. We won't be anywhere near bouncing back. Yeah.
Adam: What he meant was people struggling to get by but okay.
Unknown: Second, his entire economic strategy is focused on helping the wealthy and big corporations. Just imagine, just imagine what we could be
doing now. With the $2 trillion in tax cuts, Trump delivered to his rich friends as his first priority. Imagine how much better position we be in
right now. If instead of Donald Trump cheering corporations on, they spent hundreds of billions of dollars buying back their own stock, cheese
corporations have been using that money to keep workers on their payroll. Okay.
Adam: All right. This is this is insulting to my intelligence. The Democrat Party, who were the republicans voted unanimously for this bill for the
cares Act,
John: which is not about the cares act.
Adam: What are you talking about? Then?
John: He's talking about that tax cut that went into play in 2017.
Adam: The $2 trillion.
John: Well, he's got his numbers a little mixed up.
Adam: Because that's not what it was. He does have his numbers a little mixed up.
John: Well, anyway, he goes on this next part of it, but they did produce us a little bit because they have and I noticed this in the first clip, too,
but notice it more. I heard birds in the
Adam: background.
John: That's what I'm saying. They got phony birds chirping in the background.
Adam: This is on the brown the green is no
John: way you'd have to make the birds Come on.
Adam: Hey, wait a minute. You should that Windows not open. It could be real birds. Joe Biden can't even record Joe Biden property, let alone some
birds in the background. But
John: it could be. Yeah, sure. Okay, play now. He really goes after Trump. Everything's Trump's fault. Of course,
Adam: it is. While he has blood on his hands.
Unknown: No. COVID-19 caused massive economic challenges. But this crisis hit harder and will last longer because Donald Trump spent the last three
years undermining the core pillars of our economic strength. Many small businesses closed, because stay at home or because of stay at home orders. But
a lot of them won't open again, because they don't have a cushion. Two to three years of Trump's policies that rewarded the biggest companies. Yes,
many have lost their jobs because of the crisis. Or we're seeing many proud families forced to endure epic lines for food boxes in football stadium
parking lots, because Donald Trump has spent three years tilting the playing field toward the wealthy and not the middle class. No, Trump loves to
crow about the great economy he built when the crisis hit became clear who the economy had built was built to serve not workers, not the middle class,
not families. Trump's economic agenda has three unmistakable failings, failings that have been present since day one, but are coming into sharp relief
in the current crisis. First, Donald Trump's main measure, his main measure of economic progress is the state of the stock market. It's the only
metric he values and it's the only lens through which he sees our economy. For the past three years, even as Americans have had to work harder than
ever to pay their bills. He said the economy was great, because the stock market was up. Dead. This
Adam: is pretty insulting. It really is. Yeah, I do. But I heard a different bird when I listened to Joe Biden. This is the bird I hear it it's Gosh,
man, instead of saying, here's what I'm going to do. No, this is all he's got. So the he has nothing.
John: He's got nothing. You can't just you already seen this before. You can't just run on I hate Trump know that hit? That's probably why Hillary
lost. Exactly. Above all other things. I mean, she could have won easily but just kaanchi had no no plans. It was just oh, this guy sucks. Yeah, this
guy sucks. Vote for me. What do you guys What are you offering? I don't care because this guy sucks till you vote for me and then we'll get rid of
him. Exactly.
Adam: That's exactly right. It's exactly what's happening here.
John: nothing going on. And then last on my list of clips. I do have Kaylee and she's going back and forth. As you meet she brings in some of these
quotes that were from the release papers and she was thinking is great. I'm sure she's gonna have more now.
Adam: This is Kaylee McInerney, who is the new girl on the block. She is putting up quite a fight against against the Washington press corps. I am
surprised I thought she wouldn't last a week but she's there and she's hanging in.
John: She's a tough book made up cookie. It's impressive.
Unknown: In 2015, shortly after
John: the president said at some Mexican immigrants were rapists and criminals. You
Unknown: said that that language was racist and hateful? Do you still believe that? Well, I'm
actually glad you asked that because for about the first
four weeks of the election, I was watching CNN and I was naively believing some of the headlines that I saw. And
I'm actually not
going to read the headlines. So I very quickly came around supported the president of vaccine and hired me, I was a many eight on one panels where I
proudly supported this president who I believe is one of the best presidents if not the best president this country will ever have. But I would
encourage the individual who did that analysis of my past, rather than focusing on me, he really should be focused on some of the very guests cnn
shows tab on their network he should be focused on. I mean, my over here, Jim's Jim Clapper, who said, you know, 10 days before he privately told
investigators there is no evidence of collusion, that Watergate pales in comparison to the Russia probe, I'd encourage them to look at Samantha
powers, who is privately saying I'm not in possession of any evidence of collusion, Ambassador Rice, I don't recall, intelligence or evidence of any
collusion, former Attorney General Loretta Lynch, I do not recall that being briefed to me. And for three years, two years, probably more than that.
CNN ran with the collusion narrative. And if the American people are watching right now, they're probably very confused as to some of the quotes I
read, because those individuals were saying much different things publicly than they were saying privately. And I'm very grateful that those
transcripts were released yesterday, and perhaps the K file should do an analysis of that.
Are you walking back those comments today?
This president there is no questioning that so honored to work for him and evany Next question,
thank you.
Adam: Ooh, shocking. I tell you well, you me she's got to start doing some damn error reporting. Is she only interested in making Kaley look stupid?
Is that what they're doing? What a waste of time?
John: They're not getting very far. It's like a half times Mart mean girl does that wouldn't touch her. She's probably not to be shocked. Probably one
of those women. You just don't do that too. And I want to mention she did get a little zinger in there. Which was what she said. I was hired by CNN.
On Windows. Yes. eight to one panels. Which means there's eight people eight Democrats. It's
Adam: a one rip Right. Exactly. Exactly.
John: All right, everybody.
Adam: affiliates, in case you hadn't noticed we went a little bit long but hey, we do it for the moms. We do it for the moms. Coming up after this
they happy v Day Happy VE Day as well. I'm coming up after this show on the agenda. stream.com grumpy old Ben's will be whacking tracking. Sounds
good. And of show mixes quite a few good ones. We've got Fletcher and Blaney. We've got Jason Lewis, Jesse Coyne, Nelson, and Rolando Gonzales. Oh
keyed up then I am coming to you from the capital The Lone Star State that is FEMA Region number six on the governmental maps if you're looking for it
in opportunity zone 33 in the morning, everybody. I'm Adam Curry,
John: and I'm from Northern Silicon Valley where I don't know everything seems nice is that everyone's wearing a mask and John Dvorak, no
Adam: masks.org no. masks.org and I'm sticking to it. Remember us at the vorak.org slash na until Thursday. Adios yamo photos and such.
Unknown: All these change models.
They're driving me in
my hands.
She was with
you every time you go out to the mall. Have
you ever stolen my dreams?
My childhood with your empty words, yet, I'm one of the lucky ones. People are suffering. People are dying.
A deadly and contagious virus from China
has made its way into the US
got the virus isolated myself from the beginning because I thought that well. Brexit.
Brexit was Brexit.
The UK is set to formally leave the European Union. The government will now focus on the next phase of negotiations getting a trade deal and forging a
new partnership with the remaining 27 countries.
There are three cases
of patients with Coronavirus. Prime Minister Boris Johnson has now been discharged from hospital as he continues his recovery from COVID-19.
Increasingly, families are going public with what
it means to be a transgender kid was
so cool sisters,
and you're the brother right? Were you always the brother?
John: Not always.
Unknown: What were you before? Um,
they're a sister. Because I wanted to be a boy.
A deadly and contagious virus from China has made its way into the US.
But specifically the trans community who may have been on schedule for
surgery,
John: some of them may be affected directly by COVID-19.
Unknown: That's all folks. I didn't
I didn't.
I didn't. Here we go. We go. We
sit down.
We go.
Thank you, Mr. President. That's enough. Here we go. Thank you,
Mr. President.
That's enough. We stopped him cold. There we go. I'm not gonna say anything.
Hillary Clinton is a bigot.
We shouldn't treat people that way. very weak on crime. That's one of the things I think about, hey, look, this is gonna have a huge impact on China.
So what's that
all about?
But here's the thing.
John: I didn't call you. I didn't call you. I didn't call me directly and I'll call
Unknown: somebody and give them hell.
Let's do it the way you want. Let's do it the way you want.
And we're doing well. And now we're doing better. Nobody has to tell me to do it. I've been talking about that for years. I never told you about
spaceforce Well, it's an incredible thing. It's really like trying to put out a fire. You know, long it took me to make that decision. There's no
collusion. There was no
collusion.
I want security Peter. There we go. It's a
John: disaster.
Unknown: They don't know what the hell they're doing. Here we go. angry people. It should. I've done a lot. I don't want to do it in China.
mopho.org slash n A.
John: Wrong