oh this is no agenda northern
Silicon
Valley where everybody's
wearing masks
and you know there's a smile
under that
mask I'm Jessie Dvorak yes the
right
topic off the bat I am
unmuzzled I will
not be muzzled and you don't
have to be
muzzled the official word is in
wearing
a mask in public is not desired
this is dr. Anthony Fauci on 60
minutes
right now in the United States
people
should not be walking around
with masks
you're sure of it because
people are
listening really know closely
to the
right now people should not be
worried
there's no reason to be walking
around
with a mask when you're in the
middle of
an outbreak wearing a mask
might make
people feel a little bit better
and it
might even block a droplet but
it's not
providing the perfect
protection that
people think that it is and
often there
are unintended consequences
people keep
fiddling with the mask and they
keep
touching their face then can
you get
some schmutz and sort of
staying inside
there or of course but when you
think
mask you should think of health
care
providers needing them and
people who
are ill there can be no
question no
masks and as a handy resource I
have
made no masks dot-org
and if you go there I shall do
it myself
no masks org you will see a
copy of that
video you will have an audio
there and
you can bookmark and bookmark
that as a
handy little resource when
someone gives
you crap you say oh yeah
look at tony fauci bitch
I like to wear you put a byline
on it
[Laughter]
it's not really by design that's
otherwise you can't have a
title without
the byline that's just some way
the
system is cheap generator no
excuse me
this is the freedom controller
not some
cheap generator thank you very
much your
controller you should be able
to have it
so you should be able to
control it yes
I know I know I'm working on it
I'm
working on it anyway so there
it is that
is the definitive answer it is
from
Asics nothing has changed since
then
ouchy in fact is not even on
the scene
he is in quarantine how handy
is that
when everybody wants out just
when
everybody wants him to testify
all of a sudden yeah no I
thought yes
someone was exposed so I have
to self
quarantine little things it's
kind of
fun
timing so everyone is not
walking around
here in a mask I would say
about 50
percent of the people yeah well
you have
oh you should private lands
maybe it
could be right I mean here it's
a
hundred percent yeah I accept
some of
the homeless and they're not
walking
around in messages yelling at
people
yeah and shaking their fists
everyone
else is wearing a mask happily
they're
all happily wearing masks this
is this
is so not a good idea the more
I think
about it now that now that we
have the
official medical advice I mean
you agree
with me right that is the guy
who makes
the call correct
he is the referee oh okay yes
he's the
referee he's the guy that makes
the call
he said no mask it was very
clear we
have a mask ordinance in Austin
which is
illegal because the the state
overruled
it but still they're gonna try
and shame
you and Duke on all kinds of
Democrats
I don't know if it's just
because the
Democrats this that's what is
reason
around here it's something in
the water
and MS the Republicans try not
to so you
think that's the delineation
it's not
just people who are won't be
muzzled let
sighs yep yeah yes sadly you're
probably
somewhat right but but the
protest is
everywhere people want to they
want out
they're done they don't want to
hear it
anymore they want to get back
to work
they want to get back to life
they're
just not taking it anymore that
boots on
the ground Pennsylvania from
one of our
producers gonna kill people
people have
had enough the overwhelming
majority of
deaths in Pennsylvania have
been in
nursing homes the hospitals
were never
overrun in fact they are
furloughing
people and hospitals are losing
money by
the billions due to cancelled
elective
surgeries not unique to
Pennsylvania we
were told that even with social
distancing there was a huge
chance would
overload the system and it
simply didn't
happen and yet the governor just
extended the stay-at-home order
until
June 4th without any data to
back it up
three four five man the day
that eight
comes I'll be I'll be Hootin and
Hollerin seven cars seven car
economy on
we have a we have a friend that
works
for NHS mm-hmm and she says
that it's
same thing
hospitals are empty I'm suppose
it must
be a pocket someplace where
there's a
hospital full and she says
what's
pathetic is that people look
like
there's a one example recently
there's
this big empty Hospital places
big is
empty and some guy had a stroke
so they
brought him in but because of
all the
rules his wife or nobody can
see him so
he's stuck in there by himself
when he's
half out of it and he's
wondering where
everybody is he's wondering if
he's dead
my dad where's my wife and my
dad and
he's just pathetic
she says this is so sad and
this is
going on all over the Great
Britain with
these people because you can't
just go
and see him so
if your assertion is correct
and I'm and
I'm gonna say in California I
bet it is
that it's political the mask is
a
political thing that is so it
political
grease because the people who
wear the
master responsible and the
people don't
wear the mask and want to kill
everybody
they're horrible Republicans
okay so you
could say that both of these
groups are
acting rather cultish right one
says
we're the smart cult and you
gotta wear
the mask and the other says
we're not a
part of the cult and they have
their own
cult I guess you know true I
don't think
that I think that non masks
words are
not part of a cult okay well
that even
strengthens this argument
truthstream
media put together a cool
little video
to the shownotes
in a show notes calm just a
talking cat
ladies and gentlemen do not
despair no
agenda show has the talking cat
coming
up in just a moment stand by
they did a
bit on cults and how people are
initiated so initiation rituals
into
cults are they they kind of
mashed up
the idea of what's going on now
with the
video while reading a very
traditional
piece of work about initiation
real
rituals into cults and I just
picked up
this one-minute clip from it
necessary
for new members to function
properly in
the society they are being
inducted into
are all imbued at this time
repetition is typical as its
use helps
hammer the spell home the
wearing of
masks may be required
masking has traditionally
played an
important role in rituals of
this kind
and hastening the suppression
of ego to
help facilitate a death of the
old
identity before the
identification with
and manifestation of a new one
disguised
under a mask and hidden away the
initiate is more easily able to
transcend the self pushed
further toward
that invisible line between the
physical
and spiritual realms I'm all in
on this
now I'm so no no this mask
thing is a
very bad idea the very bad idea
people
have to wake up to what's going
on here
we're so preconditioned forget
just the
one it's just how bad I think
it is
especially around here you
don't know if
you see it there but I'm sure
you do you
have these morons and I'll use
the term
driving in their cars by
themselves with
masks oh yes John we have that
the
windows are up yes we well you
don't
want the ronan to fly in and
hit you in
the face do you know and also
the air is
off no no you can't have any
air on it's
just your hotbox and down the
road with
your mask yes I've seen it
so we make kind of a sport of
it now to
see okay did you go in without
a mask
yeah hell yeah I did people
aren't
yelling yet they're not not
yelling yet
but anyway the preconditioning
producer
Justin losing obviously a gamer
or he
was a gamer around 2000 said
so much stuff that has been in
the in
the psyche for so long this is
the game
dos dos X that gets some kind
of combat
game whenever and here's a
little clip
your appointment to FEMA should
be
finalized within the week I've
already
discussed the matter with the
senator I
take it he was agreeable he
didn't
really have a choice
has he been infected yes most
certainly
when I mentioned that we could
put him
on the priority list for the
ambrosia
vaccine he was so willing it
was almost
pathetic this play the rioting
is
intensifying to the point where
we may
not be able to contain it
why contain it let it spill
over to the
schools and churches let the
bodies pile
up in the streets in the end
they'll beg
us to save them going on for a
while
Deus Ex actually I
mispronounced it oh
yeah but how differents how
different
does it sound from New York
City this is
producer Nick who caught the
giant voice
recording going off as people
were
starting to kind of congregate
getting
too close to each other you
know wanting
to say something to their
government
[Applause]
[Music]
and you are ordered to disperse
if you
fail to this person yeah this is
reminding me I guess we've got
users
from there you will be ticketed
and yeah
the red zone is for parking
[Music]
and you hear that what kills me
about
that announcement at the
airport's they
play it inside the airport only
a JFK
though I don't think anywhere
else they
do it Oakland so you've even
got yeah
but Oakland is very small so
the Oh
golly Marlene I forgot to bring
the car
around
don't start outside parked so
even some
of the doctors are fed up with
it and
are doing the typical kind of
stand-up
presser in front you know in
the scrubs
in front of the the hospital
doors up on
the steps and scrubs yeah oh
yeah there
you go exactly dr. presser his
pressures
damn it I'm on a roll presser
in scubs
this is dr. barky what did the
experts
are wrong
what up quarantine the healthy
doesn't
actually save lives
what if wearing a mask in
public is not
effective my name is dr. Jeff
Markey and
I'm here representing thousands
of
physicians across the country
whose
voices are being silenced
because we
don't agree with the mainstream
media
and the experts who are telling
us what
to do
never in the history of this
great
Republic have we quarantined
the healthy
never in the history of this
great
Republic have we told
churchgoers and
it's illegal for you to
exercise your
First Amendment right of
freedom of
religion yet at the same time
it's
essential to keep pot
dispensaries open
never in the history of this
country
have we been told that you
can't go to
church because it's not
essential but
you can go get an abortion
never be fooled another country
have we
let criminals out of jail but
we've told
you you can't exercise your
Second
Amendment right and protect
yourself by
purchasing a firearm when
liquor stores
are deemed essential but your
businesses
are getting non-essential
there's
something wrong going on this
booklet
the Declaration of Independence
and our
US Constitution was never
designed to
restrain the people it was
restrain the government I can
inform you
the doctor has been demonetised
doctor
is a republic well there's that
but he
has he has some very valid
points and
he's he's making his point
heard but
there's somebody's got to do it
but
there's a lot of crazy stuff
going on
weird they're just even at a
local level
or the state level and like an
Austin a
mayoral level they just don't
want us to
get out they just want to come
up with
reasons to keep us in and now
we have
the trait at five G up well now
the Tres act on the way House
House
Resolution D well and of course
it is
how it you can't make it up
it's House
Resolution 666 it's one six too
many and
here's the problem a lot of
people have
with it it will authorize the
Secretary
of Health and Human Services
toward
grants to eligible entities to
conduct
diagnostic testing for kovat 19
and
related activities such as
contact
tracing through mobile health
units and
and here comes as necessary at
individuals residences and for
other
purposes
so they're putting together a
tracing
squad a hundred billion dollars
is the
proposal for this and it will
be yeah
exactly what it sounds like a
form of a
like the EU regulation like an
army and
so if if you've been identified
as
someone who
may have been in contact then
to come to
your house and test you and take
measures so what could these
measures be
well let's take you out of the
house and
lock you up
that's correct and this is
doctor Robert
Levin he is the health
secretary of
what's-his-name here a health
director
of Ventura County California
and here he
is talking and when you listen
to him
speak just and I've left a
little more
in this than I would have at the
beginning certainly he's like
mr. Rogers
and he's an ally I even have to
interrupt him he's so sickly at
telling
you what's going to happen I
mean it's a
real doctor and you just listen
to this
guy and what he's talking about
is quite
concerning we are beginning a
program
today and it's a pilot program
which
will certainly grow into
something
larger and larger and that is
community
contact tracing program we've
done
contact tracing all along that
a contact
is a person who's been exposed
to
someone that we document to
have the
kovat infection when we find
someone who
has a kovat infection those
people are
immediately isolated but we
also work
with them to figure out who
their
contacts were just the way he
says that
you know it if you if you have
the virus
okay you can be asymptomatic
maybe you
get tested but the way he makes
it sound
is like immediately isolated
luckily
because you have been doing
such a great
job of cooperating and staying
indoors
and staying isolated you've
been such
good little obedient servants
and slaves
it used to be there were ten
contacts at
least for every patient that we
would
find now it looks like there are
probably only two or three or
four
contacts not surprisingly so
good
very good Human Resources by
the way the
guy is not doing an interview
he's
speaking on stage this is how
he speaks
to his his County is his
subjects
because most people have been
staying
away from others saying that's
that's a
good news but the purpose of
this
program is to bring on people
we're
going to start with ten people
we may
bring on up to fifty or even
more just a
pilot project after all as the
program
grows and as we see the needs
for it as
we do more testing we will find
more and
more people who have kovat 19
and again
will isolate every one of them
and we
will find every one of their
contacts we
also realize that as we find
more
contacts some of the people we
find are
going to have trouble being
isolated for
instance if they live in a home
where
there's only one bathroom and
there are
three or four other people
living there
and those people don't have
kovat
infection we're not going to be
able to
keep the person in that home
every
person who we're isolating for
instance
needs to have their own
bathroom and so
we'll be moving people like
this into
other kinds of housing that we
have
available empty prison cells no
no no no
no no listen you don't call the
prison
cell anymore they'll also have
other
needs perhaps food whatever
it's gonna
be if the county will be there
to back
them up and to support them
yeah I think
you're right it's a prison cell
I think
that's exactly where you're
going and so
you know when you hear this and
you hear
you see this bill that is
coming our way
you gotta think the guys pretty
happy
about it it's like yeah I'm
gonna get
fund it's perfect reminds me of
this a
little bit if you think about
takes place within a strong
legal
framework we operate under the
rule of
law and are accountable for it
in some
countries secret intelligence
is used to
control their people in powers
it only
exists to protect their
freedoms protect
their freedoms
protect their freedoms protect
their
freedoms and that's why we're
doing in
citizen is to protect your
freedoms I
have no fear yeah yeah it's
gross okay
that's that unfortunately is
seems to be
where we're headed now we were
looking
for some names for uh for some
reason
that that really hit a mark and
you see
where I have this people
started coming
up with all kinds of cooler
names for
tracking so that we could kind
of sell
it a bit better so we have
social
interactive safety social
proximity
awareness when we need
something for
these troops we need a name for
them too
social density squad I had one
I forgot
to write it down because
somebody wrote
one and I thought was quite
good first a
bunch of yeah we should put a
webpage
together and you could put by
Adam Curry
on it screw you door I could go
to it
anyway I had a very infected
eye oh yes
you had a big eyeball was
swollen up and
you could even barely see
through it it
was causing problems with this
show show
actually suffered yes there
were certain
buttons like I could not hit
with
accuracy my eye hand
coordination and
gotten thrown totally out of
whack so
after three days of you know as
the
eyelid was all swollen than the
socket
we were in a big boxing match
yes on the
losing end of the match and so
now my
whole face is kind of swelling
up and
like all right now we got this
oh it's
the hair that was my secret and
by the
way little Richard died and
talking
about a guy with a big head
yeah Little Richard man he did
a lot
he's a lot for America he
really won't
bamboo yeah he did a lot anyway
so you
know being a podcaster the you
know the
insurance scene is not all that
easy in
a while back the keeper and I
found this
new outfit from that's actually
a couple
of Silicon Valley guys and it's
called
decent and we may have talked
about on
the show and well they
basically give
you five hundred dollars a
month per
person disaster insurance but
you know
they they do chip in for some
medication
and stuff and whatever it ideal
if
something bad happens you know
I'll have
to figure out the eight
thousand dollar
deductible the insurance kicks
in and
besides I typically go to
doctor wrong
the voodoo doctor anyway it's
not
covered so but one of their
selling
points is unlimited
telemedicine appointments so I
think
well here's my chance I'm going
to have
to do this which of course yeah
good
point
involved downloading the app
which I
have a special phone for which
is goes
off after the usage downloaded
the app
and I have to tell you wait
hold on a
second you can't do this on
your regular
computer a desktop yes you can
you can't can you can't there's
a link
and everything one guy I wanted
to have
the full experience so I could
report on
it on the show this is the new
hot thing
telemedicine and up on the
screen pop
said dr. Sam robot doc now no I
think he
may have been he's maybe a
Turkish
descent but he's in Vegas and
he owns
the telemedicine company he's
also the
CEO and he had a bow tie which
tells you
he's an inventor and that was
fun he's
invented a device that you
connect to
your phone and then he can
listen to
your heartbeat and take your
temperature
and God knows what else maybe
stimulate
but I had a really good
experience with
this and he says you know the
thing is
we can talk as long as you want
there's
no limit and and he told me uh
well I
didn't say confidentially but
anyway he
said that he only charges $10
per
telemedicine visit to the
insurer's he says you have no
idea how
we make it up on volume so we
got tens
of thousands of customers and
they're
calling with prettiness simple
things
and for me was like okay I see
why
you're calling the guy do you
see the
problem you know three
questions and
then get the drops and by the
end of the
afternoon it was already
starting to
clear up I was impressed I'm
not a guy
who likes to go to the doctor
for
anything
yeah well it's not as a
dangerous place
it's a very dangerous place
it was quite yeah I there's
something to
it
and I and these guys are trying
to
figure out a different business
model by
making it more affordable I
don't know
if they're actually making
money but it
certainly is a hell of a lot
cheaper
than lots of other routes I've
seen and
your eyeballs okay and my
eyeball is
doing quite well thank you got
some
antibiotics and I'm rocking and
rolling
well did he tell you what this
problem
was what my problem will rot
the eyeball
yes he had a name for it which I
promptly forgot but it is
essentially
inflammation of the eyelid from
allergies with a histamine and
then you
rub it and then if you rub it
then he
gets screwed up and you're
screwed yeah
yeah Texas syndrome yes indeed
Texas
syndrome yeah okay I have a
phrase that
I think we will be hearing a
phrase from
the shades no I think well no
it's gonna
be a phrase from the future and
I've
read it a couple times and I'm
like wow
are they really pushing this
and maybe
I'm wrong but the recovery
through
prevention which is just the
most new
speak I've ever heard recovery
through
prevention which of course you
know what
that leads to
yeah locking in jail we let the
prisoners out now the vaccine
of course
it leads you straight to
vaccines
yes exactly vaccines which
totally that
earlier clip well I'm gonna
play this
one for you and this will kind
of
finalize the getting back to
work part
even though everywhere
everywhere in the
world people are just giving up
their
get their walking out of their
homes
they've had it am sir damn is
Rotterdam
it's no the UK isn't is
different the UK
I think they shoot you on the
spot
they're really locked down over
there
hey I have a couple UK reports
okay
we'll get to it after we listen
to the
only way we can get back the
only way
the world would get back to
normal
ladies and gentlemen we have to
listen
to the guru William Gates in my
lifetime
there this will be the greatest
economic
kit but you don't have a choice
people
act like you have a choice
people don't
feel like going to the stadium
when they
might get infected you know
it's not the
government who speak for
yourself pansy
boy saying okay just ignore
this disease
and you know people are deeply
affected
by seeing these deaths by
knowing they
could be part of the
transmission chain
and in old people their parents
that
grandparents could be affected
by this
and so you don't laugh at about
well I
think that he's actually
laughing
because it's a tell some people
have
brought the hammer down on me
and say no
it's because of his Parkinson's
like
well that may be but oh ok when
do we do
his Parkinson's began about a
decade ago
yeah and they're gone as far as
I can
see I know bill before he when
he was so
giving speeches about hobbies
make money
by selling code and I've seen
and I've
seen lucky buy for someone very
young
yeah oh really that laugh has
always
been there and went and when
would he do
the line and Andy in
appropriate smile
right in the middle of a
sentence what
the right so what is that then
if you've
been around it well I think
that the
idea that it's a tell is
probably the
closest it gets my knowing me
just I
mean you could say well it's
just a
nervous laugh but why does it
show up
when it shows up because always
shows up
at a tell moment I think he's
giddy
about the whole idea he's giddy
about
people being afraid
giddy about the only solution
being his
giddy ass vaca Nations well I
think
that's a valid interpretation I
could be
by knowing they could be part
of the
transmission chain and in old
people
their parents or grandparents
could be
affected by this and so you
don't you
know you don't get to say
ignore what's
going on here there are there
will be
the ability particularly in rich
countries to open up it things
are done
well over the next few months
few months
for the world at large normalcy
only
returns when we largely
vaccinated the
entire global population and
and so you
know although there's a lot of
work on
testing a lot of work on drugs
that were
involved with you know trying
to achieve
that ambitious goal which has
never been
done for the vaccine that rises
to the
top of the list
this indoctrination from dr.
bill is so
deep that people are buying
into it I
think part of this is the
reason why
even when cuz pouchy is he's
compromised
he's a trump guy he's got trump
goo on
him she's not a trump no no no
I think
foul Chi is now being pushed
away and
he's being seen as a turncoat
just like
Burks I'm telling you the you
should
know out there foul Chi is
really not
this questions about him he
won't go to
the house for his testimony now
he's at
home now
no no bill Gates is still the
ultimate
guy he dr. bill he knows
everything
people are getting sick a bill
and you
only have to ask someone like
Sean Penn
who appeared on the view who
appeared on
the view to an outlier and
using that as
your example it's still
Hollywood its
Hollywood I just want you to
hear the
programming Sean Penn I know
Sean Penn I
got remind me one of these days
to tell
me Sean Penn story on the MGM
grand air
but for now theory is on the
view as
somebody who has seen government
response to crises
first hand how do you think this
administration Shan has been
helping and
handling kovat and and what
worries you
the most well on federal level
I think
that one thing that certainly
should be
much more robust is in the
defense
production Act manufacturing
just listen
to it and kids I believe that
if we had
that on the kind of level with
which
that Act was used in the past
for war
efforts that there'd be no
question but
that we could test what in fact
give
multiple tests over a series of
weeks to
every American there's no
question we
have a model that's that we've
been able
to push out and with that
you're using
the combination of local
governance and
community organizations or NGOs
if it
would work on a small
municipality level
as it would in a big city or in
rural
areas yeah no Shawn there's no
way we're
going to get multiple tests for
every
man woman and child in the
United States
and and I gotta appreciate the
guy has
local teams here's a score I
think his
name was group and and they
they do a
lot of good things but no you
you're
drinking the kool-aid man it's
not
feasible but then again no yes
nobody's
did this Universal vaccine is
it the
whole world is gonna be
vaccinated is
never the whole world's never
been
vaccinated for anything
especially when
nobody in Africa even trusts
bill again
he's talking about testing now
not VAX
no no I'm talking about backing
up
because you didn't let me get
that look
jab in there well bill or
something go
back go ahead you jab all
you're one of
dr. bill it's bullcrap
well Canada is there's gonna be
more
people walk march in the
streets against
any universal vaccine Trump I
totally
subscribe to the Trump thesis
which I
kind of think where I made know
where it
comes from but it's been
observed before
this thing is just gonna go away
it's not gonna be here next year
the Canada is already talking
about
making the vaccine mandatory
for all
citizens but Canada this guy's
applied
bend over and hey hey hey not
all cand a
Navy ins not all of them they
know who
they are I have a second part
of this if
you just want to laugh a little
more the
fear has also been that all we
do the
fear but this shows you that
not Bill
Gates the yeah that is kind of
what we
do this shows you what right
what the
programming does if you only if
listen
he's appearing on the view you
have to
think he's probably getting his
input
from one-sided sources at this
point but
Sean yes yes so you know his
fear level
is also at a point that is just
off the
scale and unwarranted which
looks do you
saw this she looks nervous and
scared
not at all well I don't think
we need to
attach a face of personality or
what
somebody was sending on their
social
media to be able to identify an
active
shooter an active shooter is
anything
that is continuing to to kill
people and
our brothers and sisters and
fathers and
daughters and sons this is this
virus is
the active shooter and if we
were I
think that if we could wrap our
head
around it in that way and
understand
that it's principally putting
in the
radical people of color
elderly people young people
it's racist
in randomly selecting all of us
but you
see what he's doing there he's
the way I
hear at night I think I'm
hearing what
he's thinking is this is active
shooter
and look at it he almighty it
would have
been better if you said and
active
shooters also target black
people that's
almost what he's saying the
programming
is so deep on that man anyway
with with
or without the vaccine it's all
gonna be
okay especially New York
we're gonna get get back we're
gonna
bring our city back and we're
bring in the best people to
help our
children when we are reopening
schools
let's Oakland a better school
and let's
open a smarter education system
and I
want to thank the Bill and
Melinda Gates
Foundation will be working with
them on
this project is in everywhere
he's like
yeah we got a city down sitting
down
bring in the Scholastic
Services he can
repurpose common core but he's
a genius
I just knew that Cuomo was
jizan on Bill
Gates is a visionary ways and
his ideas
and thoughts on technology and
education
he's spoken about for years but
I think
we now have a moment in history
where we
can actually incorporate and
advance
those ideas yes so the next
time windows
acts like a bitch just think
Bill Gates
and then you'll know that's why
we
worship Him that's why you
can't make it
up you cannot make it up you
can't now
I'll take you into your UK
clips ready
control ready I'm gonna take
you into
your UK clips here's what we're
gonna do
I've got a clip from the UK but
first
some feedback on the stochastic
model
and the assessment thereof of
the Neil
Ferguson Imperial College model
here is
you me Neil Ferguson the guy
who is
shacked up with his mistress
when he was
supposed to be yes sheltered in
place is
the one that's the one the guy
who was
overestimated quite a lot of
numbers
throughout the run see that
that would
be 2 million deaths in United
States we
didn't get too many 500,000 in
the
United Kingdom alone yes that
guy and I
and you recall that he built
these
models not on rock and roll but
on 13
year-old undocumented code and
we had
the lockdown skeptics org and
they
reviewed the code and they had
some
interaction as well with the
college
defeating I had some questions
back and
forth and one of the things
came up was it was the
stochastic part
was and I really didn't have the
capability to analyze it
properly but
what you and I thought was wait
a minute
if this thing is returning
random
results then something's wrong
with it
and we were partially right and
I just
want to read this one paragraph
from
producer Richard who analyzed
what's
going on he says the model and
this is
what the article says under the
paragraph the model and
elsewhere it's a
simulation and of course with
the
simulation you do want some
random
factors being thrown in but he
says this
certainly looks like a poorly
written
one in that in addition to the
intentional pseudo randomness
underlying
the simulation there are
additional
hardware and configuration
dependencies
that cause the results to
differ I would
not call these latter random or
stochastic in the statistical
sense
because despite its flaws
if the code will run multiple
times on
the same Hardware in the same
configuration with fixed random
number
seeds the results would be
identical at
least in single thread mode
this is how
stupid this is
Ferguson's attitude about it is
very
poor and he says admittedly were
partially right about the model
about it
the pseudo randomness of it so
bottom
line this model is shaky it
sounds like
it's it's you know this is this
whole
thing and I don't want to again
I'm not
I'm just sounded like an
ideologue but
this is the same kind of thing
you see
with global warming these
mediocre
models and they go on and on
with these
models and then they make
decisions
based on their lousy output and
that's
what we've have right now with
this
stupid thing and his model in
the
Imperial College whatever that
is not
Oxford it's not it's not
Manchester I
mean what is this place very
influential
that they nearly yeah because
the whole
world's been shut down because
of their
their pride models and this is
what's
going on with global warming to
which
people will never listen to
these people
have never had a science
they've never
taken a course in science but
they're
all
all the big experts and so all
the media
people none of them have ever
they can
barely get through a sociology
class but
here they are talking about
these
computer models and how the
gold is
gonna is melting the world's
melting
it's not just Oliva balandin
snot just
the models it's the actual data
itself
we are hearing numbers of dead
people
ranging from 37,000 to 72,000
we don't
really know what dead is and
the CDC has
a history of exaggerating
numbers of
dead and go back to 2000 from
the movie
super from the documentary
Super Size Me
and at the time there were
headlines
trumpeting everywhere that
obesity was
soon to overtake smoking as the
number
one cause of preventable death
in this
country the head of the CDC
Julie Gerber
Dean went before Congress and
issued big
warnings and there was a big
uproar over
the number of deaths that were
to occur
basically what they did was
divide their
survey samples between people
who are
obese and people who are not
obese and
then basically looked at rates
of death
now if you are obese and you
died from a
snake bite they would say that
it was
your obesity that was causing
your death
not the snake bite and sound
familiar it
was part of a little statistical
hanky-panky on their part in
other news
today the Centers for Disease
Control
said it made a mistake about
the scope
of the obesity epidemic in the
country
roughly a year later another
set of
researchers from the CDC
offered a much
much lower set of estimates
according to
their estimates it was roughly
thousand people a year who were
dying
from weighing too much
researchers say
that mathematical errors
exaggerated the
death toll why did the CDC
inflate the
numbers of deaths attributable
to
obesity
follow the money I think it's
all about
funding and bureaucratic
mission when I
talked to a few CDC officials
they're
constantly preoccupied about
how much
money the government our
Congress is
gonna allow for them for the
next year
they're constantly worried
about getting
their funding cut
all of this might have gone
unnoticed
except for the anti-tobacco
people who
see this as a zero-sum game so
they see
that if obesity becomes a big
public
health issue it's gonna crowd
out
funding to tackle smoking as a
public
health issue so they were among
the
first people to tell him to
point out a
lot of the methodological
problems and
the estimates relating obesity
the
public health outcomes so
they're just a
bunch of lying corrupt
douchebags and
they do it all for the money
for their
own projects for their own
grants
there's so much money in Health
and
Human Services is an incredible
I mean foul cheese little teeny
teeny
weeny division is 11 billion
dollars and
we heard from one of our
producers John
you were on the email who knows
people
in in the business and and they
hate
that within what they call the
flu
people the flu people they get
all the
money it's always the flu
people within
we also point out in that note
that the
flu numbers are probably
exaggerated cuz
we're always talking to all
60,000
60,000 dead from the flu the
seasonal
flu is killing thirty to sixty
thousand
people and it that number may be
exaggerated Allah seemed it
appears that
well RFK jr. is all over this
he says
maybe a thousand people a year
die from
the flu he says it's a lie it's
just a
lie he says but it's a big
moneymaker
for the that by the way it was
the first
question Adam tell me about
yourself
you're 55 okay when's the last
time you
had your flu shot first
question out of
the gate and I say never and he
went
okay next question actually
that's funny
because I've had a big question
asked me
and and as soon as you say I am
I gonna
get one
they don't even lecture you
about it I
mean so I mean it's as though
they asked
this question gratuitously no
because if
they were serious about when
they say
well you should get one no no
no all
they have to do is put the black
checkmark in the database
that's what I
mean by gratuitous they're just
doing it
for someone's black check mark
so
they've done their job yes and
there and
the follow-up it's exact same
by the way
no offense of the doctors out
there but
how is that any different than
would you
like fries with that what sighs
mm-hmm
because it's not as though the
french
fry guy had McDonald's or
wherever it is
pushes it they don't say we
should like
fries or they say no they said
all you
should they're great no but for
now it's
not entirely true because the
then it
would be McDonald's saying
excuse me sir
when's the last time you had
fries time
for a tasty fry aren't you
hungry all
right
so clearly the CDC has had
issues in the
past and there's so much
confusion we
cannot trust any of this data
so who
knows it could be a thousand
people
could be a hundred thousand
people we
don't know we don't know
there's some
average but it seems to be a
heck of a
lot less than we were scared
into
staying home for now did this
work and
you too and I put that chart in
the in
the show notes of the guy who
took the
data before the lockdown after
the
lockdown looked at all the
death rates
of all 50 states and charted
them and it
shows statistically if I
understand it
and I'm not a statistician that
there's
pretty much no difference
between in the
death rate between staying home
or not
staying home you saw this graph
right
yes this graph has been going
around it
was all over Twitter and it
indicated
that based on the early numbers
and if
he's projected outward the
states that
said we're not locking down and
the
states is's were locking down
there was
the graph goes exactly as it
would if
they if they even switched
positions you
know the DES block down didn't
do
anything in other words and
meanwhile
we're still locked down and
worried sick
because we have again a lot of
Democrat
governors and who are scared
that if
they lift a lockdown oh my god
I'm gonna
be blamed for somebody else yes
yes
point the finger at me it's
gonna be
blood on my hands but even
crazier is if
you look at New York and the
numbers
appear to show that over 60% of
the
people infected got infected
while they
were
home lockdown but that doesn't
sit well
with the media oh no no no no
no that
can't be true well we certainly
hope so
I want to put up a quote from
Governor
Cuomo in New York which which
sort of
had some surprising information
in it he
said 66% of the people who were
new
cases were at home which is
shocking to
us he said this is a surprise
overwhelmingly the people were
at home
we thought maybe they were
taking public
transportation and we've taken
special
precautions but actually no
these people
were literally at home 66% of
the new
cases how does that happen well
generally speaking patients
report and
this has been well established
better
and safer behaviors than reality
so people report that they may
be
staying at home they're lying
but in
fact we know 600 people got the
infection during pretty harsh
sheltering
conditions in the New York area
how did that happen that means
they got
the infection during the extreme
measures dude this they can't
even take
any kind of news in any other
light can
they these people be dead liars
liars
liars liars liars liars anyway
I promise
to get you into the UK I'm
gonna push
one off the rail I'm off the
rails I'm
just gonna pull a hard left
Katie
Hopkins on Sky luckily at least
they can
talk about the Neil Ferguson
guy and his
multiple mistakes and only in
typical
British fashion can they rip a
guy down
the way Katie Hopkins does in
this clip
unbelievable so there's this
bearded
scientist he's the typical
science type
he looks like the sort of guy
nobody
would want to sit next to at a
wedding
he would Neil Ferguson and he's
basically the guy that was the
the he
was the one that made it such
that the
UK was locked down he's called
professor
lockdown he was the one that
came up
with the modelling that
persuaded Boris
Johnson that we all had to be
shut away
and put under house arrest in
our homes
he says 500,000 people might
die in the
UK because of coronavirus now
what they
then
did whilst he had the rest of
us locked
down he got his mistress his
married
lover a woman funnily enough
called
missus stats so for a guy who
does
modelling and statistics she's
called
back he had her over and
professor pants
down got his pecker out on a
number of
occasions to you know help
entertain
mrs. stats whilst the rest of
us were
locked out so number one massive
hypocrisy as per usual number
two he is
known for being absolutely
crazy with
these models like five hundred
thousand
deaths we're nowhere near that
number he
predicted 200 million would die
from the
bird flu I believe it ended up
in two
hundred and forty two like his
modeling
is about as accurate as my
five-year-old
standing up to take a pee so
why were
listening to him at all I don't
know and
now professor pants down as god
is
torture out whilst the rest of
us are in
lockdown so frankly regular
Brits that
had enough whoa you got butt
slam in
that clip really because we
played a
Katie Hopkins clips two shows
ago where
she's bitching about the same
guy but
before the mistress story and
she used
the same story about her little
boy
trying to pee standing up oh I
forgot
about recycling some of her gag
oh boo boo hoo well we shall
report that
to the sky news division these
fake news
is it's old news this is no
good we
can't have that alright so here
I here
we are in the UK welcome it's
your turn
ok well I don't have anything
to compare
to that last clip you pre
topped me very
funny UK restrictions garden
centres
they finally get their openers
loosen
things up by opening up the
garden
centers of any major loosening
of
restrictions garden centers
though in
England will be allowed to open
from
Wednesday it's part of first
step
measures but with the Sun out
this
weekend many people are already
ignoring
some of the restrictions still
in place
as Rebecca Williams reports
the sun's out and you'd be
forgiven for
thinking lockdown is over
despite the
odd reminder mixed messages and
little
information from the government
to
making it feel like the country
starting
to move again definitely needs
to be
lifted two roundabouts now like
a lot of
the people they're not really
sticking
to the rules anyway I think he
should go
as far as he can to reduce it
I think people be very good so
far I
think there's a tipping point
you feel a
bit weird like it's
contradicting the
feeling of are we allowed to be
outside
now I realized to do more than
one
exercise a day I think is going
to be
definitely easy because it's
already
happening so it would be very
strange if
he says the opposite doing the
lockdown
most have stuck to the rules
but police
have had to come down hard on
some in
the West Midlands this man even
spat
blood into a police officers
eye as he
was handcuffed raising fears of
contamination forces across the
UK have
been patrolling parks and
streets but
there are concerns that this
weekend
could place added pressure on
officers
it's got its challenges because
it's a
bank holiday weekend people
people need
a boost I think and it's a great
opportunity to commemorate the
VE Day
celebrations I knew it's
confusing but
the rules are still the same
so the week's go on it seems
parts of
the country are getting busier
and
busier in the first four weeks
have
locked down the police issued
nearly
nine thousand fixed penalty
notices to
those flouting the rules for
the highest
number issued in London the
tenth Valley
and also Lancashire fine there
is that
they're handing out tickets
yeah hundred
pounds I think and our friend
in the UK
the NHS worker she says the
real problem
that she's noticing is the what
they
call them to British isn't like
the
curtain Wranglers curtain
Wranglers
these are the old laws behind
the
curtain out their window and
they're
turning people in left and right
narcs yeah the narcs and
they're turning
people in left or right and the
cops
come over and give you a ticket
if the
curtain Wrangler call it good
turns you
in and this is going on all
over the UK
do you know that we have a huge
narc in
Texas let me a huge dork a narc
ok I'm
going to tell you what happened
then
you're gonna guess who it is
a guy in Texas sent secret
shoppers all
over Dallas to restaurants who
were
opening up to find out if they
complying with reopening
guidelines and
published today that 96% of
Dallas
businesses are not complying
who's the narc well your Mayor
Mark
Cuban what yeah Mark Cuban is a
narc
Cuban will continue sending out
secret
shoppers over the coming weeks
with
visits to hundreds of locations
plan for
the rest of the month
how is this a good idea well he
has his
own restaurant chains I think
he's
invested in fad shack and some
other
pasta joint but still I mean I
don't
know he's just he's someone
made him
Emperor and he's going around
busting
narking on in fact competitors
Wow
yeah I think he is quite the
dick unless
I'm missing something unless
I'm missing
the point behind it you know
people are
struggling man and you know so
they're
gonna cut corners do whatever
they can
to get us back you're gonna sit
around
arc on them
geez wow that's a really a
disgusting
story okay well you getting
back to the
UK yeah with curtain Wranglers
on twere
to the other thing the
newspapers all
these little local newspapers
which UK
is full of the UK really is a
newspaper
country's a great great country
for
press families gonna be ending
pretty
soon during play this clip
predicting
the industry could lose over a
billion
pounds by the end of the year
with
circulation falling by around
forty
percent since lockdown started
and ad
revenue down between 50 and 80
percents
do you have and it's the local
papers
that are really suffering we
all want
local newspapers they're really
important for communities and
providing
local news and giving guidance
to people
if they start to disappear as
some
already have I think that's a
real
problem
one solution being tabled is to
legislate to force the tech
giants to
pay for news they've never
really
compensated news organizations
properly
for the value of their content
shared
through those services and
that's
accelerated their decline and
if we do
nothing now in a very short
period of
time we're going to see more
news
organizations go out of business
and more people increasingly
reliant on
the sorts of disinformation and
low-quality news that
circulates like a
virus through social media and
with
digital users continuing to
rise the
physical paper could ultimately
be saved
by online success stories these
persons
can use hold on a second hold
on a
second how does this work how
come those
how come those guys are all mad
at
Google issued in Google be
giving them
their journalists like they do
in
America we just talk about the
line that
there's did once the newspapers
go the
only thing is gonna be
low-quality
crappy news and then I'm
thinking to
myself you mean like the BBC
and Sky
News the broadcast element
kablooey out
of the story what was the name
they're
headed yeah what was the name
of that
outfit that the the Google
thing where
they're putting hundreds of the
story
yeah I know I can't remember
the name of
the outfit no I'll find it
anyway this
is what it's called so they
okay so the
only way I couldn't get this
story so I
only have the teaser for it but
I can
explain the story I'd for some
reason I
just kept I just couldn't get
the story
but there's the teeth of the
teasers UK
heli heli payments coming up
next here
on Sky News giving away money
to heal
the sick economy how so-called
helicopter payments could be
the cure
for a global slowdown a
helicopter paid
what so this is it Ireland and
so these
did these chocolate
no helicopters the big boy no
yes and
then thrown bags I don't
understand they
can't just they can't just land
what's
going on just throwing it that
I gotta
hear that clip again you need
to get the
whole story coming up next here
on Sky
News giving away money to heal
this sick
economy how so-called helicopter
payments could be the cure for
a global
flow day full of crap Dvorak
drunk bags
of money out of the choppers
and it's
almost it reminds me of like
some old
movie where the king is
throwing pennies
at the peasants they're
following him
unused little boys and girls
are there
Waifs and they're all grabbing
the coins
and the money off the ground
and now
let's go but they haven't they
haven't
actually done this yet have
this is not
a card they showed a video of
the
chopper throwing money but bags
of money
flying out of the chopper yeah
I'm
trying to find this now I want
to find
some pictures of it okay well
the memes
are there there's helicopters
with a big
piggy bank underneath are you
working on
it okay perfect heli heli
payments who
ever heard of such a ridiculous
thing
that is nuts
all right so I do have some
kind of the
story which was starting to
appear on
Thursday and now it's getting
more
traction is this bright yeah
this is so
this is the guy who will be the
whistleblower or he is the
whistleblower
this is good I'm interested I'm
glad
you're so so here here is the I
got ik
like this is a four parter
they're all
short clips but this Norah
O'Donnell is
going to interview him today so
on 60
minutes
mm-hmm but they took some clips
for this
Friday a new show to tease us
and
they're the best clips so this
guy who
is a nudnik to say the least
and I don't want to defame him
because
of your
sexual orientation well you
shouldn't
that makes it has nothing today
we're
gonna do that then why you
bring it up
oh but he is such an annoying
kind of a
character that and he's over
he's okay
he's a drama queen all right
there you
go that's fine and so he comes
on is it
you know and he's gonna be this
is gonna
be the Democrats new oh he's
gonna be
the strong man that's gonna
take down
Trump and this guy can barely
keep it
together talking to Nora so
let's listen
to the clip this is nor on the
hook no
it's actually only three so
let's go at
Nora interviews bright does the
intro
quite recently led Barta that's
a key
agency created to defend the
country
against troops and he says he
was
removed from his job for
putting science
over politics and he filed a
whistleblower complaint earlier
this
week and today a federal agency
found
reasonable grounds to believe
that the
administrative administration
was
retaliating against bright well
tonight
a preview of our wide-ranging
conversation buzzing so this
guy you
know this agency nobody's ever
heard of
is making a big fuss and they
they're
gonna use they're gonna grow
after
another impeachment with this
character
but I think he's weak listen to
him he
can't even keep it together in
this
twenty two second clip part no
no to
make it part noise from size 50
seconds
part two tonight another no
wait hold on
we had interviews bright too
okay but we skipped over nor it
uh-huh
I'm sorry I had the wrong one
okay here
we go the president called you a
disgruntled employee I am NOT
disgruntled I am frustrated at
a lack of
leadership I am frustrated and
urgency to get a head start on
developing life-saving tools for
Americans I'm frustrated at our
inability to be heard as
scientists
those things frustrate me as
early as
January email show he was
sounding the
alarm first about the critical
shortage
of n95 masks we see
to many doctors and nurses now
dying and
I was thinking that we could
have done
more to get this mask and their
supplies
to them sooner and if we had
would they
still be alive today this is
the beauty
oh yeah
Trump has blood on his hands he
saw all
the talking points at Nancy's
he sounds
familiar he sounds like this
guy either
work for someone else are you
work for
yourself and most people work
for
someone else in a way that they
aren't
free noodle boy only talks even
slower
dumb noodle boy its noodle boy
2.0 yeah
and he's a whiner and he's in
cunt you
going into tears why he's there
he's
like you see but it this is so
pathetic
anyway this part three that's a
horrible
thought to think about the time
that
passed where we could have done
something
and we didn't bright claims his
persistent warnings caused
tension with
his bosses at the Department of
Health
and Human Services it reached a
breaking
point when he raised concerns
over the
administration's embrace of
hydroxychloroquine what he
called a drug
unproven to treat kovat 19
patients you
believe you were retaliated
against
because you raised concerns
about
hydroxychloroquine yes I did
and says he
was surprised to learn he'd been
reassigned to the NIH to develop
diagnostic testing you'd been
sounding
the alarm about the lack of
testing
platforms this sounded like an
important
job that's an important
initiative nor
I'm the director of Barda to
take me out
of our organization focus on
drugs and
vaccines and diagnostics in the
middle
of a pandemic the worst public
health
crisis that our country is
faced in a
sense
three and decapitate the Barda
organization to move me over to
a very
small focused project of any
scale of
any level importance it's not
responsible didn't make sense
oh my god drama queen is the
right
question or is the right
description oh
my goodness so what is this
Barda
organization if someone is just
a
subgroup who runs on HHS and
it's
biomedical Advanced Research
biomedical
Advanced Research and
Development
Authority oh yeah without those
guys
we're toast
Barda with addy that's where it
is Barda
with addy they got a crappy-ass
website
- yeah this guy's this guy's
gonna be
their their go-to guy and
they're gonna
do if you will see them and
listen to
them the Republicans on those
committees
even though they're just gonna
be housed
you know so it's gonna be led
by Nadler
and shit the Republicans that
are on
those committees will eat this
guy alive
he's gonna be a wreck Wow yeah
I don't
know how well he'll do without
going
into tears this is this is
portly died
but this is part of a larger
movement
that the media is involved in
Entertainment News Hollywood I
have two
clips to back it up unless you
want to
do more but this could but
about this
particular topic there's blood
on his
hands this shows up
this is WGN TV Chicago
a new study says the death toll
in the
u.s. is double what it could
have been
if governments had responded
just a few
days earlier the earliest
stay-at-home
orders were implemented in late
March
orders to wear face masks began
in April
researchers with Princeton say
if these
orders had come four days
earlier the US
would be seeing fewer than a
thousand
deaths a day instead of more
than 2,000
a day they point to California
which
implemented stay-at-home orders
early
and now has fewer deaths per
capita than
other large states see how that
works
that's exactly how it works so
but that
hasn't taken it far enough no
for that
we need to go to Hollywood and
we need to check in with your
girl Amy
on Democracy Now 56 foot
billboard
called the Trump Dethklok has
been
unveiled in Times Square here
in New
York the Billboard was created
by the
oscar-nominated filmmaker
Eugene Jarecki
so the drunk Dethklok is a
billboard
that hangs over Times Square by
the way
this is the same will yo as as
this is
Brent guy and what it shows is
an
estimate of the number of u.s.
kovat 19
deaths that resulted from the
president
and his team's failed response
to the
corona virus outbreak thanks to
doctor
foul Chi and leading
epidemiologists we
now know that had the mitigation
guidelines been put into effect
just one
week earlier on March 9th
instead of March 16th 60% of
u.s. kovat
19 deaths would have been
prevented
that's an incredible number and
on
behalf of all those who live
needlessly
lost their lives to this failed
leadership in a pandemic we
need a
symbol a symbol that cries out
not only
for accountability but also for
more
responsible and responsive
stewardship
going forward at the time of
this
broadcast the Trump Dethklok
stands at
46,000 485 and growing the
arrogance of
this hole right down to Amy's
report and
growing I am actually
speechless it is
and of course this is the
bottom of the
days like sleaze ball tactic it
is and
Eugene
Jarecki who is a respected film
director
you know kind of more like a
Sundance
kind of guy but he has a brand
new movie
coming out on Netflix who have
quite a
China strategy so maybe that has
something to do with it
I don't know how you get a
billboard on
Times Square will I do actually
I don't
know if you can even get one
now if
there's business is being done
but I
don't I know who owns Time
Square so
this is a Chinese thing going
on with
this guy as far as I'm
concerned he's
virtue signaling towards his
money
people and his backers and
whatever else
it's sickening and then for Amy
this
pencast the Dethklok 46,000 321
and
Counting lady horrible horrible
horrible
that is the that is yes that
Dethklok
thing is it's a humiliation to
the
country but speaking of
humiliation and
it's China China oh yeah
China's put the Dethklok up
there
because they hate Trump they
may be
behind this whole thing for all
we know
they can't nobody's been able
to prove
it and now they're doing this
bullcrap
just to get Trump out something
like Joe
Biden well let's have a little
listen to
the president from the Oval
Office I
think the words matter you know
what you
the worst attack we've ever had
on our
country this is really the
worst attack
we've ever had this is worse
than Pearl
Harbor this is worse than the
World
Trade Center there's never been
an
attack like this and it should
have
never happened
could have been stopped at the
source
that seems if I were in Beijing
I'd be
like what did he what did he
call an
attack an attack that's very
clear
language to me I don't know if
they're
gonna keep pulling this stuff
like the
Dethklok the china and yeah we
will say
that the chinese are behind it
that
because i think your analysis
is correct
they're gonna hear more of that
because
you know they we call it the
Chinese flu
and all this and he backed off
almost
overnight because of a phone
call or
whatever because he does these
you know
he does ago she eights well he's
negotiating now no he went the
Chinese
want to keep just keep the
pressure up
to get him voted out which is
meddling
by the way yeah an American
election
hopefully he's gonna please
gonna that's
gonna be jacked up you watch
well let's
continue let's see what the
China is
doing jimmy kimmel what network
is he on
he's on the Chinese control
Disney that
yes ABC let's see what he had
in his
opening monologue the other
night
regarding Mike Pence Harry is
with no
masks on wheeling boxes of PP
ease into
a health care center and doing
his best
to lift them what a hero it
just barely
in the door and since it was
going so
well and also because he didn't
realize
he had a mic on Magic Mike
decided to
keep it going listening closely
here
you probably can't hear it but
pence
literally says to how about
these boxes
the guy says those are empty
sir and he
says well why don't we just
grab what
for the for the TV cameras Mike
Pence
pretending to carry empty boxes
of pee
pees into a hospital is the
perfect
metaphor for who he is and what
he's
doing a big box of nothing
delivering
another box of nothing so when
I saw the
clip I'm like oh my god how can
you how
can you fail on that that's so
so lame
and I was looking at it on
Twitter and
I'm gonna give Twitter props
it's right
underneath the video it said
manipulated
media I'm like that's
interesting I
click on it then it says
according to
some people this was edited
it's not the
way it happened well it is the
way it
happened because there's this
is on
c-span I put a link to it in
the show
notes there's 20 minutes of
pense
literally lugging boxes diving
into the
back of the van
slapping him out not letting
other
people really help him and
they're heavy
he's putting them all down at
the very
end they're joking around and
the guy
says now those are empty so
come on
we'll just do it for the TV
cameras
after he's actually done that
yeah well Kimmel apologized
because he
did oh I didn't know I
apologize so but
he apologized in an offhanded
way the
apology consisted of him saying
well it
would turn out that the boxes
he was
carrying were full they weren't
empty at
all and I'm so sorry that we
made this
we this was wrong from and I
hate to say
that because of it for the
administration was lying all
the time
johnny has to because he's got
the
Chinese Communist Party up his
little
mouse but like hey hey hey you
be
careful there but here's what's
really
going on Reuters subs fara nod
know is
really the first one to report
on it
because I think at all it also
is going
to have a name pretty soon the
name
would be the economic
prosperity Network
sharpening his tone against
China
President
Trump said late Thursday a
trade deal
between the two was now of
secondary
importance the u.s. leader
threatened
Beijing with new tariffs as his
administration crafted
retaliatory
measures over COBIT 19 Trump's
frustration has been growing as
tens of
thousands have died from the
virus in
the u.s. the economic
contraction as a
result also threatens his
chances of
re-election in November two US
officials
speaking on condition of
anonymity said
a range of options against
China were in
the early stages of discussion
although
they added that recommendations
have not
yet reached the level of trumps
top
national security team or the
president
one source said there's a
discussion as
to how hard to hit China that
could
leave the u.s. walking a
tightrope in
its ties with Beijing it's
currently
importing crucial personal
protection
equipment from China for health
care
workers a multi-billion dollar
first
phase trade deal with China was
only
signed in January world stocks
pulled
back further on Friday
following Trump's
comments while most European
markets
were closed for a public
holiday stocks
in London slid over two percent
grim
data combined with Trump's
threats added
to already dented sentiment so
this
thing is real it's quite a task
force in
fact the the information coming
out is
this is a whole-of-government
effort the
very well-known phrase of
course but in
Trump's case it might actually
happen in
which free trade advocates seem
to be
losing their struggle with the
China
Hawks inside the administration
yes it
seems like the globalist are
losing out
this time and I was listening
to a
globalist who I happen to like
where is
my globalist buddy here
this is Elon Musk Oh a LAN and
he was on
Joe Rogan which was a
interesting I
think Joe does some of his best
work
with with Elon Musk that that's
a very
messed up interview to listen
to at
times well this was I found
this one in
pod musk seemed something was
like
something was wrong with him
well I
think he's still trying to
figure out
how to pronounce his kids own
name you
know that's that's his problem
there
it's like a ex5 Sigma Tau fine
by me
Elon but here's what he was
talking
about when when because he's
been pretty
vocal about the shutdown and
appears
he's against that it appears he
thinks
it's not a good idea and this
came up in
the interview I mean you look at
civilization through the ages
most of
them you know they rose and
fell yeah
and I do think like the
globalization
that we have at these sort of
like the
the mean sphere is there's
there's not
enough isolation between
countries or
regions it's like if you get up
if
there's a mind virus that that
mind
virus can infect to much of the
world
you know I'm like I actually
sort of
sympathize with the
anti-globalization
people because it's like man we
don't
ever want to everywhere it'll
be the
same for sure and then we we
need some
kind of like mind viral
immunity so
that's his he's feel some
sympathy with
the anti-globalist people Wow
you're on
that was the worst the whole
interview
he just seemed it did it was
just
disconnected well even
listening to that
clip it's like what was he
given I don't
know it's well I think what he
was
trying to say is that this mind
virus
where everyone's like holy crap
we're
all gonna die I mean it's not
just like
something that happened
accidentally it
came from somewhere and has been
enhanced a gain-of-function
amplified by
the mainstream media
and he says no HUD how do we
how do we
stop that well that's basically
what
globalism does and what it
wants but
well I agree with with you your
you
should have been on the show
back on the
show yes I have not been
invited well
you will be that's going to be
a couple
other things going on we can
take a
couple of cases in the white
house yes
this is Mayo
and so this is to try to play
that Norah
on new cases this is a big deal
tonight
another White House staffer
this time a
top aide to the vice president
has
tested positive for coronavirus
Katie
Miller the press secretary to
vice
president pence is now the
second
confirmed case tied to the West
Wing
after a valet who serves the
president's
meals tested positive on
Wednesday
Miller is married to Stephen
Miller one
of the president's senior
advisors and
tonight her test is raising
questions
about whether the White House
is doing
enough to distance the
president and
vice president from others for
his part
president Trump told reporters
today the
whole concept of tests aren't
great
those are his words and he said
he's
convinced the virus will just
go away
without a vaccine his own
advisors have
said that's not true this is
gonna go
away by itself which seems to
be the
case with all these previous
events you
know from bird flu to swine
everywhere
yeah my point people say well
why would
it go away it's gonna come back
I said
what about SARS how come that
didn't
come back
SARS we never got an immunity
to SARS so
we've got MERS yeah we never got
immunity tumor and then he's
just
throwing and how about peak oil
throw that in for no reason so
so Nora
says at the end that he
president says
he's gonna be it's gonna go
away and but
his advisors say it's not yeah
how do
they know doesn't matter
no it's not gonna go away what
why does
his advisors know more than he
does cuz
it's it's a crapshoot you don't
know
it's gonna go away or it's not
gonna go
away there's no proof one way
or the
other
but she wants Trump to go away
so that's
why she has to report this oh
you're
talking now just alright did
this go to
new cases and white houses a
continue to
report oh but wait there's more
news
that one of the vice
president's closest
aides Katie Miller tested
positive for
the virus delayed mr. Pence is
scheduled
trip to Iowa Miller was not
onboard Air
Force two but six staffers who
had
recent exposure to her had to
be removed
Katie she tested very good for
a long
period of time and then all of
a sudden
today she tested positive
doesn't matter
what you do with Trump you're
the top
you're the best tested me
better than
anybody else for negative she
was just
the best negative I mean when
it comes
to testing Katie you couldn't
have a
better one you tell me you
could not
have a better person to be
tested it was
Katie a long period of time and
then all
of a sudden today she tested
positive
she hasn't come into contact
with me
spend some time with the vice
president
Miller is with the vice
president nearly
every day her husband is senior
presidential aide Stephen Miller
president Trump attended their
wedding
in February held at Trump's
Washington
hotel despite the potential
which by the
way is a great hotel it's one
of the
best hotels it truly if you
want to test
you want the number one test
you're
gonna do it the best hotel
that's where
that's a we don't mess around
Trump even
put it in the story to bring it
up
despite the potential exposure
mr. pence
did not wear a mask while in
Iowa we
also know that President Trump
was in
the same room as his personal
White
House fillet on Tuesday before
the valet
tested positive for coronavirus
today
the president still addressed a
group of
world war ii veterans at a VE
Day
ceremony without wearing a mask
the wind
was blowing so hard in such a
direction
that if if the plague ever
reached them
might be very surprised the
president
says he's now being tested
every day and
so far as negative but doctors
say that
may be a false sense of security
somebody could become infected
be
incubating the virus and test
negative
every day including yesterday
then this
morning become infectious still
feel
fine and spread it to other
people
before the next
shows that they are in fact
infected
that bastard
I'm glad that that report at
least
contained
a little bit of VE Day which was
completely ignored by the
American media
I believe you pointed that out
in the
newsletter
but it was also very odd to see
you know
in the in the Netherlands which
was
liberated on on May 5th but a
May 4th
they have at 8 o'clock this is
actually
very unique to the Netherlands
8 p.m. on
May 4th all traffic stops
everyone is
quiet and they told the Bell
with ever
they have a moment of silence
two
minutes two minutes and
everyone is
completely silent and it and
I've been
in the Netherlands where it was
o'clock and the highway people
stopped
just stopped on the highway and
then
waited some got out and then
everyone
waited for the two minutes of
silence
and they got in there drove off
so the
this ceremony has been going on
since
the end of World War two and
having the
the troops the Yanks and the
Brits you
know coming through and their
jeeps it
was you know the flags it was
such a
joyous occasion none of it all
just
quiet no one on the street if
there no
no parties I mean this is this
passed by
that I think it's a shame how
quietly
that passed by because of all
this I
don't think it's because of all
think it was in spite of all
this they
could have done anything they
could have
made a little presentation on
the news
or anything instead of all this
just
nonsense of doing about how
Miller was
married at the Trump Hotel
there was
very little mention of it by I
mean
Trump did this little ceremony
but the
media just dropped the day
doesn't want
to talk anything about anything
that's
patriotic well no I don't want
to do it
they'd rather do it that made
rather
brag about the big sign talking
about
how many dead or some Trump the
other
thing is again a Chinese
influence the
Chinese do not want the
Americas the
Chinese by the way I've been
watching CG
TV whatever it is the Chinese
outlet but
constantly and their date the
most of
the globalists are actually
coming out
of China
now it is because the Chinese I
actually
think they have the opportunity
oh yeah
do not only be for a globalist
world but
for them to run the thing and
so a
nationalist event like VE Day
which is a
nationalist event because we
beat Hitler
of all people yeah and the
nationalist
event is to be frowned upon and
the
media just paid ok we'll we
will play it
up we won't even mention it I
don't
think half the people even knew
it went
by
you're so right though and I
think we
can't hammer it enough when we
should
probably reiterate it's CCP
Chinese
Communist Party I don't know
many
Chinese people I'm sure they're
just
like us I'm sure that they're
there in
deeper crap than we are with
these
a-holes running the show
there's a cool
video from some Chinese guy
Chinese
American guy that I put in the
show
notes and it's the history of
China
actually it's Kali I saw that
it's very
full great it's called the
story of how
China ruined everything
and it's 30 minutes and it's
it's pretty
good I mean there's it's not
complete
and it's easy to skip over 5000
years
here or there but I was very
impressed
with that and you'll learn
something
from it's worth is worth
watching
Pompeyo is also out on the road
also
speaking out against China help
really
wait just before I want to just
mention
one thing cuz these clips about
them
infections in the White House
that
depresses giddy over this
because
they're hope and true hope and
some gets
it yeah they want it but we
can't we
can't forget this one element
that we
must remember this one element
Trump is
a germaphobe yeah and he is the
likelihood of him getting it
based on
some of the earlier reports
that we've
had on how you do get it
Trump's never gonna get it
unless he
kisses somebody with it which
is always
possible yeah right we know for
sure
that this is actually context
CNBC's the
financial news channel we know
for sure
that this virus originated
Wuhan China and that the disease
emanated around the world the
Chinese
Communist Party covered this up
we have
been working diligently and are
working
diligently today to get the
Chinese
Communist Party to help us
identify
patient zero where this began
how this
came to be and this isn't about
politics
this isn't about partisanship
this about
protecting Americans tomorrow
this is an
ongoing crisis are the world's
epidemiologists still don't
know the
original of this virus the
reason that
we continue to ask for
transparency and
for a reliable partner in China
is
because it matters going
forward so not
only do we have this current
pandemic
that's taking place that we
still have
to figure out how to get
therapeutics
and get vaccines to mark and
all the
things that we need this
information
that only the Chinese Communist
Party
has in its possession and
they're the
only ones that can help the
world
resolve this today and for our
Americans
security but we got to make
sure this
doesn't happen again
so I think this is very
interesting if
true he's saying that we can't
even make
the vaccine without pertinent
key
information that china is not
handing
over I don't know if it's true
but he's
saying it and there should be
questions
about it hey foul cheat or hey
Bill dr.
bill doctor professor bill yeah
yeah
maybe but but well here's the
tack
they're not using yet which I
think
could be used and I think I
think Pompeo
could do it well and it would
be uses
leverage the Chinese cases of
Corona
have dropped to nothing what do
they
know that we don't know they
just say no
Trump Xi Jinping
there's your problem that
that's what
would come back just briefly on
therapeutics and vaccines on the
therapeutic side I have a
beautiful
breakdown from our official No
Agenda
pharmacists many people have
noticed
that the New England Journal of
Medicine
medicine has published a new
observational study regarding
hydroxychloroquine and of
course it
turns out to be completely
useless why
would you even consider using it
but it's interesting because as
our
official No Agenda pharmacist
says below
are my favorite parts which
highlight
the implicit bias and the main
bias is
the patient's they took Oh
besides the
fact that they had no you know
what do
you call it double double by no
placebo
etc they only took and there
was no
treatment with zinc here it is
the AZ throw Meissen suggestion
was
removed on April 12 the
hydroxychloroquine suggestion
was
removed April 29th the decision
to
prescribe either either or both
medications was left the
discretion of
treating team for each interval
patient
he says our pharmacist says
here's the
implicit bias as the only people
included in the study were
those people
who needed to have moderate or
severe
disease treated so they were
already in
the ventilator stage which is
actually
as we know from other doctors
who have
successfully used
hydroxychloroquine is
really too late you want to use
it much
much earlier almost like
Tamiflu so it's
very similar to the VA study no
placebo
one one particular group of
people with
a certain type of level of
illness I
mean the whole thing is is
broken down
in the shownotes is under
therapeutics
well worth a read but a lot of
people
did send in that as well as a
lot of
people who have sent a very
it's kind of
the same letter or email it's
the
debunking of the plan Demick
documentary
this is the one with dr. Judy
Mike Ovitz
who has been around for years
and is
saying the doctor foul she
should go to
jail for being a criminal and
what's
interesting is they all are
kind of the
same these responses or the
debunking
--zz and it attacks her really
more for
business political reasons how
she
handled herself with publishing
of
studies or not Roy doesn't
address any
of the many of the main issues
but the
thing that
always comes up which i think
is the
mistake in this it seems like
it might
be might be some form of
coordinated
response this is literally one
of those
hey Adam a friend of mine has a
couple
of nurse friends or doctor
friends and
here's what they have to say
and then
you get a four word of the
email but it
always says in there that dr.
Mike Ovitz
claims there's never been an RN
a
vaccine and in every single one
of these
debunking responses it's oh
yeah are you
kidding me there's tons of them
this vaccines for all kinds of
RNA
viruses yeah but that's the
difference
there's vaccines for RNA
viruses the RNA
vaccine that is being discussed
that
actually felt M R an mRNA has
well you
looked into it right you had a
thing for
me to put in the show notes
yeah that
debt paper which discusses the
mRNA
vaccine which is a which is a an
experimental idea it's not do
get all
the RNA vaccines are based on
the
old-fashioned way view you
cultivate the
the the disease and then you've
used
attenuated versions or killing
right you
put you grow it and then kill
it and you
do all these different things
to make a
vaccine is just a normal way of
making a
vaccine this is this mRNA
vaccine is a
totally different animal it's
never been
proven to work and so like yeah
so to
the fact that this was a good
paper on
it and that's what I when
somebody sent
me that same exact thing you
got some
put some stooge to this in this
paper
and I said here read this the
the thing
that I like the most is that
they said
there's never that's a lie
they've been tons of RNA
vaccines like
okay this has got to be someone
who
doesn't know what they're
talking about
so the debunkers are being
debunked but
there's about three of them in
the
shownotes under the bronx you
can look
it up there any more clips to
do in this
Rona segment I want to guess is
we're
talking about Bochy debunking
our
let's listen to the talking cat
yeah
been waiting for almost an hour
and a
half period she talks here she
talks
about pouch II and again and it
just add
anti foul foul Chi rats very
well
structured the scientific
evidence is
what needs to drive us and we
appreciate
the fears of the American
people but we
don't want to have policy that
would
have negative unintended
consequences
that's actually fairly
reasonable but
that's a quote from 2014 when
he was
talking about whether or not we
should
quarantine for Ebola
another interesting quote of
Anthony a
slouchy and the director of the
National
Institute of Allergy and
Infectious
Diseases
that the CIA forgot to scrub
from
history is when he said that
there is no
doubt that Donald J Trump
President of
the United States will be
confronted
with a surprise infectious
disease
outbreak during his presidency
he likely
said well rubbing his hands
together and
then cackling to the sky for
several
minutes when questioned about
concerns
for the future trump
administration foul
she reportedly said that there
was the
potential for a new influenza
pandemic
and outbreaks of diseases that
are not
yet on anyone's radar the issue
of
pandemic preparedness and if
there's one
message that I want to leave
with you
today based on my experience
and you'll
see that in a moment is that
there is no
question that there will be a
challenge
to the coming administration in
the
arena of infectious diseases
both
chronic infectious diseases in
the sense
of already ongoing disease and
we have
certainly a large burden of
that but
also there will be a surprise
outbreak
he has the same doctor found
you who
according to this WikiLeaks
email loves
Hillary Clinton I was a
verbatim reading
of something but the cat's okay
the cat
cannot just talk the cat can
read it's
quite astounding love the cat
and the
cats pretty good
anyway so that's what I have my
head
that's what you have you want
you got to
Cove in Italy Kovac South Korea
needed
break you want to do anything
about
South Korea or Russia I get cut
off yeah
I don't know you're just
talking and
talking at me you're not
listening he's
not not obeying me what do you
hear me
yeah I just barely hit the mute
button
asking is do you not want to do
the KO
vid Italy or Russia I'm
interested in
these that was the fun oh those
are the
country to run down so we do
that the
end with that then I'd like to
thank you
for your courage and say in the
morning
to you the man who put the C in
curtain
Wranglers John Wayne Oh morning
to you
and in the morning the ships at
sea and
that boots on the ground the
feet in the
air and the subs in the water
and the
dames and the nights out there
yes and
in the morning to our trolls
let's do a
troll count here whoa 18 20
hate trolls
hanging in there not bad for a
Sunday
the troll room I did a little
check in
this morning bed the pre-show
after
Darren oh and I said how y'all
doing
it's mixed it's not everyone's
feeling
great they're there people are
angry
they're tired they're sick of
it some
are feeling good yeah it was
always so
much we can do well if you want
to
commiserate with your fellow
trolls head
over to their bridge you can
find that
at no agender stream comm we've
got a
chat there as well IRC chat
that you can
access on the web and of course
you can
listen to anything that's
happening live
at that moment a lot of the
shows are
live we're also broadcast live
I believe
now on 1435 AM enthroning in in
the
northern part of the
Netherlands nice I
love that I love just that
we're on some
random a.m. frequency somewhere
in the
North Pole that's great the
more of that
the better if you got a little
transmitter set up let us know
is
fantastic no Jenna stream calm
and
thanks trolls good to have you
here
helping as always then in in
the morning
to the artiste for episode
number one
four zero the title of that was
meat
must flow and boy does it and
there was
controversy from this over this
image
from Trent Drac who brought us
a just a
great piece kovat safe no
agenda this
crazy-ass looking mass the fonts
everything was great and within
seconds
of posting the show the NAR
kissed were
out and that's artists who narc
I'm
looking at you calm extra
blogger he's
dumb he's number one art this
is stolen
art you must take showdown now
you'll
get sued stolen art so I'm like
oh man
did we get good wink because we
did an
image search we looked for this
wing we
found similar stuff but not
exactly that
and lo and behold there it is
on some
image did you follow any of
this John
did you follow her this going
down I
thought the final leg of it
which is
this is a piece of licensed art
the guy
has a license now that's a no
agenda
producer for you right there
I'm not
gonna compromise my boys
putting the
tribes art that you could find
maybe if
you searched around not with
the no
agenda other stuff on it and
it's been
altered like you do with
licensed art
but he license he likes a lot
okay this
first bring up a couple of
there you go
that parent League comic strip
bloggers
unfamiliar with including the
piece art
that he actually did still some
time ago
a little Santa Claus thing
which could
have been licensed any but he
didn't
like now don't think for
commercial
artists they licensed certain
kinds of
clipart and different kinds of
very
specialized looking to tends to
be
stylized and they will like
there would
take out licenses from these
different
places and in one or two of
them and
then they'll use the stuff
judiciously
as projects come and go and
it's part of
the deal and this is done with
video
more even so even more so than
it is
with art there's a number so
there's a couple named Evo the
guy's
meteo itself didn't use them
but the
guys had licenses and if you
watch
almost any of the every time I
said
watch anybody's presentation
see the
spinning logo come in and flame
the the
big ball but explosion of
flames as all
these things come from one
particular
site whose name I could always
forget I
always have to ask Nick we
about it
what's the name of that site
again but
it is one site just like its
cost like a
dollar to dice and some of the
most
spectacular videos that you've
ever seen
yeah and and everybody
subscribes to
these services and so we have a
couple
of artists I'm sure more than
one Muslim
can listen to the show and do
live art
on this fly but we do it this
is a
example of a licensed pro well
done
people oh I hope I explained
that yeah
absolutely
anyway I just thought it was
funny the
NARC aswer out that was just
funny
they're so competitive it's so
competitive if it's competitive
it
should be yeah
well thank you Trent Trent drak
for the
artwork for episode 1240 this
is great
because we're one of the only
podcast if
not the only podcast that every
single
show we release has new album
art it
shows up in your podcast
players most of
them will show it and it's
exciting when
you see it in an overview and
it's this
is something about the show and
it's a
part of what what you know what
the
package matters Packaging
matters we
learned that from Steve Jobs we
are the
iPhone of podcasts actually you
think
about it your little white box
yes
that's so no agenda art
generator calm
is where the artists compete
but it's a
fun friendly competition
everybody has a
good time and we laugh about it
and we
love comic strip blog or just
messin
with him because ladies comics
your
blogger he deserves it you
blocked him
everywhere I have to deal with
the
fallout when you say these
things so
stop it just stop
no agenda art generator calm
then we
have more values art I uses I
probably
use more comic strip blogger
stuff for
the newsletter
no and you don't even follow
him you're
a heathen these are too much of
a back
channel or from that's the only
problem
part of our like part of our
value for
value network here at the no
agenda
media tribe is the way the
system works
everything you've heard up to
date we
can give you the narrative at
least the
one we hear we believe or what
we're
finding out from actual sources
because
we're not run by pharmaceutical
companies or by China or by
anybody else
for that reason it's you the
producers
and we love to thank our
executive and
associate executive producers
as soon as
we have quite a few maybe we
should get
to it
All Right bingo boom way more
than
normal and I want to thank each
and
every one of them and I don't
think it's
because a mother's day and
maybe because
we triggered some thoughts or
the ve-day
mention but well I you look you
should
say happy Mother's Day and and
we will
say happy Mother's Day to all
the moms
out there and yes it was
surprising
because while we're at it
here's what's
not really a Hallmark holiday
by the way
nobody here's what we're
surprising is
typically we do a Mother's Day
promotion
and the joke is that you know
we get
five people and said no agenda
producers
hate their moms and so this
year we did
nothing like it's Mother's Day
and
everyone's like beautiful notes
to mom
starting with stretc rooming
with you
who gave us a thousand dollars
in two
dollars and forty two forty one
cents on
top of that little Utah wait to
see it
instantize he says last week
observing
all this to stand here X's
glass shields
polka-dots masks oh I see only
marketing
t-shirts I thought I have done
a hell of
a job gratifying this game of
finding
this so this is that's the
bonus kovat
is the death of truth no agenda
is the
opposite of whatever that is
one of the
very few places where truth
exists fuck
a duck thank you for this is
this was
just done by a randomizer I
don't thank
you for this podcast a to you
you too
yin and yang it and it just
works it's
actually yen it's not Yin it's
yen plus
a little help from us third
legs and
it's also zoology
zoology I realize that all
these is back
to mac and cheese long for long
for
simpler days where no agenda
was wins
awards and with recipes oatmeal
and
coffee or wine reviews I'm
donating my
donation to a friend who was
angered by
article links being emailed
about the
cove ad hubbub in Lake March so
I sent
to no agenda show to her her
anger
dissipated and out of the blue
she
inquired I think my amygdala
shrinking
thank you for smacking Chrissie
in the
mouth Dame Chrissy will enjoy
being
knighted and all the
accompanying
adornments search room and when
she shut
up slave it's true women so
this is like
an instant instant aiming
deeming it's a
woman he hid in the mouth it's
an insta
Dame right do you hear me there
did you
hit the mute again yeah but you
did I
did stop doing that I don't
even know
how I did it I said this is an
instan
ight insta Dame today me in the
mouth
[Music]
there is nothing like this
like mac and cheese
you've got karma and I'd like
to alert
the affiliates yeah we're going
along
Chris die stirs next from
Brookline
Massachusetts he also came in
with
$1,000 this Dame Hood donations
from my
smokin hot wife another this is
an
interesting coincidence number
going on
here yep - Dame installations
by men
she's gonna be Dame die store I
think D
I think it's die store yet die
stir
she's incredible mother to our
kids and
I know this donation will be
much more
meaningful of Mother's Day as a
Mother's
Day gift than any BS item I
could have
come up with Diana hit me in
the mouth
years ago this is an opposite
way it
normally goes and that's just
one of the
many reasons I'm the luckiest
man on
earth oh oh that's so beautiful
I'm
gonna give them both the Karma
the B
field that's right you've got
Karma and
we continue with this theme and
what sir
Maxima Rifkin with $1,000 as a
birthday
present to his wife Olga Olga
Rifkin her
birthday is on May 9th and
you're gonna
insta dame her so we have three
mr.
Dame's in a row without any
encouragement it was in the
newsletter
good work boys well done men
they loved
it they loved their wives and
moms don't
they the the moms Mary's the
older would
like to hear Obama you might
die and
don't eat me Joe
beau Jayden also goes
requesting a
product development Karma
well we got that for you you
might die
[Music]
you forgot karma Wow the ladies
that'd
be great it's gonna be fun at
the
roundtable today I'm looking
forward to
it sir now we dropped him a
normality
sir Kevin deals the vikon of
Charlotte
three and $33 and 34 cents from
Huntersville North Carolina
this donation along with the
producer
credit is my birthday present
myself
this year I'll be turning 34 in
may 12
please add me to the birthday
list this
past year being 33 has gone
pretty much
how I no agenda producer would
expect
I'm looking forward to putting
33 behind
me in this donation amount
seems like a
great way to celebrate my
odometer
rolling over
since this donation also
completes my
seventh night hood I'd like to
claim the
title of Earl my accountings
attach the
title upgrade will also feel
like good
time to expand my Protectorate
I'd like
to claim the state of North
Carolina
assuming everything checks out
with the
peerage committee please add me
to the
title change as sort Kevin
deals Earl of
North Carolina
my only jingle request if it's
not too
much trouble is to have Adam
play the
Dylan version of the title
change song
the times we're changing later
in the
show when we do that little
dude since
I've got the platform I like to
have a
couple of friendly shout outs
the first
two all the beautiful people in
the no
agenda local 704 meetup group
here in
Charlotte and I'm looking
forward to
sucking in soot with all of you
again
hopefully very soon second I'd
like to
give a shout out to all the
folks on the
no agenda social you keep me
sane no
jingle is just karma thank you
for your
courage sir Kevin get Dill's
vite count
of charlotte thank you so much
sir Kevin
of course will be happy to
bring out the
Robert Zimmerman version then
we have
sir ten T do is that ten T I
think it is
Duke of the Federal Reserve
District
seven dears crock pot crackpot
and
BuzzFeed thank you for the
continued
service during the Rona
lockdown I know
that even knights are
struggling with
the imposed restrictions
especially in
the hub of Federal Reserve
District
seven Chicago keep your head up
sir Jo
foe things will get better soon
enough
no karma but can I get a Bernie
I have
all the power
Greta how dare you and Fletch
your
orange combo that'd be great
all the
best certainty Duke of the
Federal
Reserve District number seven
and he
came in with three hundred and
$33.33
the president the United States
I have
all of the power how dare you I
got it
thanks yes who's up next Maxine
Waters
gravel is back nice the gravel
returns
of Louisville 33333 the gravel
has a few
enterprises that qualify for
some magic
munchkin munchkin Mooney
minuchin money
so as to celebrate what better
way to
the gift a portion to the
greatest show
in the universe who would have
thought
that the man who invoked my
existence
would play a part in helping
the show
all hail simulation was that it
hold on
no now all hail the simulation
is just a
mount catapults me delighted to
move it
now the catapults me to Baron
I'd
understand that may now claim a
protectorate if available I'd
like to
claim the Greater Bongo Bongo
land
surrounding territories jingle
request
John King China not a Huntsman
but the
Sir Chris produced jingle yeah
followed
by China a whole and you might
die goat
Karma for all your Corona
papers please
cheers mwg happy Mother's Day
to all to
my mom and all the no agenda
mums out
there hello friends the show
just come
from China the city of
Chongqing China
welcomes you don't trust China
Chinese
how you might duck
you've got a circle of lavender
blossoms
returns lavender blossoms org
it is the
official what do we call it the
official
CBD CBD operation to show tribe
when
we're hurting we get our
lavender
blossom south in the morning
folks Kay
McAfee just buy me lunch and
they'll
write a golden article about
you right
after I write my cookbook did
you happen
listen to McAfee on Nick the
rats last
podcast no I didn't know he was
on oh my
gosh McAfee doing on McAfee
will do
anything wait dinner he owes me
a happy
Mother's Day and happy birthday
John so
it's a bit belated and that's
from Cal
so wait a minute McAfee owes
you money
no it was made dinner Oh dinner
from
what yeah when he was in the
heyday when
he was actually making money he
was
actually working for a living
and we
went out to Stars in San
Francisco now
defunct restaurant was very
famous at
the time and I picked up the
tab and he
said ah next one's on me uh-huh
that was the end of never saw
him again
well he's a horrible man he's a
liar no
no but you know maybe come on
it's not
right anyway I will have to
listen to
this Nick the rat interview
with McAfee
that's got to be one of the most
fabulous things to listen to no
doubt
three 3309 from Cernik who
dragon of the
four domains Waterford Michigan
I'd like to donate for Mother's
Day I am
sure that my son Andrew loves
sitting
with me listening to your show
I know
he's up in heaven oh yes
cupping his head and shaking
his head
laughing his butt off well I
thought
sure absolutely I'm sure he is
as well
thank you thank you very much
what was
the 9 for I wonder baronet
surnicc know
hard to say Joel tuckered
meanwhile from
the largo florida is here with
$333 and
he sent an email in which they
isolated oh good whyyou wisely
took that
next one uh the next thing I
could okay
he writes ITM the next thing I
could do
the next thing I could think to
do on
Mother's Day was to become a
knight and
this donation brings you to the
round
table ah get your pen out okay
this is
good
it's another one on this huge
list we've
got crazy today now I can say
to my
mother see mom people are
calling me sir
now the peers committee like
you'd be
knighted as Sir here we go
ready yep sir
not sure how to pronounce a LOC
white
bin loki bin hello see ya
night-night of the Psychonauts
psycho
naughty as psy psycho you're in
a UTS
like not astronauts I cannot Oh
sir
Llosa bin night of the
Psychonauts i get
it easy done does he want
something at
the round table I'm gonna
continue to
read Thursday you were trying
to come up
with a name for social
surveillance I
suggest social eyes or the play
on words
sort of fits the criteria you
are
looking for social haze I would
like to
ask for some goat Karma but is
he's got
no special requests I would
like to ask
for some goat Karma but that
has to be
the greatest value for value
I've ever
had I would like to ask for
some goat
Karma okay that has got to be
the
greatest value fidelity of
everyone not
sure what he's meaning thank
you so much
for the infotainment all right
you're
welcome more than welcome
you've got
from the kid who's graduating
today No
yes I did
boss's name I'm so sweet which
is good I
should have printed that no
doubt it was
a mistake because he invited us
to his
virtual yeah Robert Robert
blank Shane
yes he wrote a beautiful
beautiful note
about his graduation from st.
John's
College in Annapolis and I just
want to
read it to sorry I feel truly
as though
I could not have done it
without the two
of you and the show and the
entire No
Agenda community has been
listening for
five years that's really great
I'm sure that really pleases me
yes I
was impressed by that note
honey uh
sorry I was just saying honey
one of our
children graduated Joel Tucker
by the
way from Largo gave 333 and
meanwhile oh
no priests are in Sisk Holland
$333 he
also said it sent a note in
your John
and I'm short note to confirm my
donation happy to donate in
proper
valuation what the show brings
me every
other Thursday or Sunday
whatever
celebrating our 30th
anniversary on May
10th
so no better moment I found the
local
restaurant tours able to
prepare a
four-course meal to take away
so at
least we can celebrate in style
getting
back to the last shows
brainstorm on how
to name the monitoring another
one the
random number again two in a
row when I
go for so social security
it makes all be easy not to he
says it
makes it all the more easy not
to only
use your phone and also attach
a special
reward system mm-hmm
you are well meets brave new
world okay
but you but it's really or well
the
ruble eyes are out ruble eyes
are out
no it's Orwell meets brave new
world I'm
sure says Q I don't know why oh
oh but
maybe it's cute I was wondering
what
your thoughts were about the
latest
developments in the case of
Michael
Flynn and I haven't Michael
yeah I have
Michael Flynn stuff - we got
lots to
talk about and well I have to
get the
supercut no I didn't get the
supercut
that's great well they get this
just
coming up ready coming up hold
on hold
on a second are you sure you'd
like this
Miz
no I got a big thing popped up
and
wonder reset my machine no
thank you
Bill Gates dr. bill someday had
triggered me when I was
listening to RFK
clips was that the coincidence
of this
Kennedy family and specifically
the RFK
branch suffered a loss recently
when may
mmmm Kennedy drowned while
kayaking meth
as you may know was the public
health
official Mao working for the
USDA's
global aids program
what about coincidences one
would think
on another note here in the
eurozone the
erosion continues now with the
red
judges of Carl Sewell laying an
AED for
the ECB stimulus program and the
European Court almost instantly
replying
that the German Constitutional
Court
lacks the legal power to judge
on the
European institutions role
completely
ignoring the German Federal
Constitution
that specifically defines the
role of
the Constitution visa vie
international
treaties they really don't
wanna clap
one thing is certain the longer
the
rhone of crisis lingers the
better the
odds are for EU implosion you
know in
the meantime I'm now wearing a
hipster
ponytail as hairdressers are
still shut
and I already need to get a
haircut
three months ago yeah if this
is the
worst of this lockdown I'll
take it in
reality the power grab of our
civil
liberties is without precedent
and I'm
wondering how long the
obedience will
last even in the sheeple will
eventually
wake up or
so I hope for jingles oh man we
hate and
we have jingles uh-huh a 33 and
playing
karma with some Jordan Peterson
with
kind regards all the best to
all the
producers from Gitmo nation
plus 31 now
what I know I understand the 33
but then
What did he say
karma plan karma no goat yeah
with some
Jordan Peterson I don't know
what Jordan
Peterson we have is wrong we do
have
don't we have an ISO a Peterson
I think
you're saying it's wrong is it
good okay
let me see it's wrong I wasn't
prepared
for this you're wrong just
wrong yeah do
you know how many how many
clips we have
where it's wrong is in the title
anything just put type in
Peterson and
play it okay and then the 33
thing you
don't take that very seriously
do you
just type it in and play it
what are you working sides
government's
away
[Music]
that's wrong nailed it you've
got Sir
Colin the friendly fat man as a
first
associate executive producer
$250 he's
in Ohio so called the friendly
fat man
checking in from Cincinnati
normally my
six siblings and I would get my
mother
some combination of flowers
chocolates
or whatever but we figured what
better
way to say thanks to mom with a
No
Agenda producer ship so happy
Mother's
Day to Colleen from Cory
Stephen Caitlyn
Colin Connor Sean and Aidan you
have
been a shining example to all
of us and
have made us who we are thank
you for
all the sacrifices and
hardships you had
to put up with throughout the
years
happy Mother's Day also to my
sisters
Corey and Caitlin as well as our
sister-in-law Kate we need a
deducing
for those siblings who have
never
donated before and well first
we'll do
the deed in their clans but we
also need
to call out Tim as a douche bag
dealer's
choice Sharpton in my Corona
thank you
both for all you do to keep us
folks in
flyover country sane the whole
family
enjoys your coverage and you
have become
a staple topic of conversation
at our
regular family dinners also mom
I hope
one day you can forgive me for
ruining
the hamburgers and that is from
Sir
Colin the friendly fat man we
thank you
for your courage sir the
president
meeting with the cola cute
[Music]
you thought well Harry
Jason Perry in East Peter
Petersburg
Pennsylvania 250 couldn't
figure out how
to get my message on the
donation but
here it is okay let's let's
contemplate
what he just said there
couldn't figure
out how to get my message on my
donation
but here it is what he did it he
couldn't figure it out he's
just letting
you know he had some trouble
but it
worked out I've been a listener
for five
years number look upon this
back by luck
when searching for podcasts and
never
donated supposedly that means a
douche D
douching yes you've been
deduced how
many people we found you
through that
that mechanism through was
probably not
a lot so which mere podcast
keeps my
amygdala shrunken please keep
up the
good work and deep dive into
the lies
the m5m propagates please call
out my
brother-in-law Bob Raymond
Loewy as a
douche bag several times to hit
him in
the mouth even though he was
definitely
a note even though he's already
an
original listener I guess
please play
listen to that horn
Trump aroused look at that
juice don't
eat me bulge I didn't and karma
of
course have we mentioned how
sick you
people are and we love you for
it
it was hard to get it aroused
and it is
hard to get it aroused but we
got it
around 250 bucks he just says
keep up
the good work you can take this
love you
man thank you yes we have
Vincent from
Lantana Texas two three four
five six
great number combo hey guys we
love the
show appreciate the bye weekly
dose of
m5 and to m5m antibodies we
were punched
in the mouth when Adam was on
the Joe
Rogan experience and have been
listening
to you ever since
there it is John proof we got a
listener
from the road johann we'll get
you get
Rogan experience yeah we have
to get
another one I would like to
split this
donation to Oh 1.23 for Sinead
the
mother of my beautiful daughter
who was
also my smokin hot wife I will
not say
happy Mother's Day since she is
a
wonderful and appreciated
mother every
day and she doesn't care for the
Hallmark holidays sounds like
no agenda
material to me the rest of the
donation
3333 is for myself so that now
we can
both be deduced thank you for
keeping us
sane through this plan Demick
and if
possible can we get China is
asshole and
what else do they want and
that's true
we're all gonna die in karma so
I just
have to line them up for a
second so
China and then sorry I'm
spacing today
that's true we're all gonna die
oh my
goodness how they
you've got karma thank you
welcome you
too thank you very much this is
Sara
Gonzales in Houston Texas to
3333 she
writes in Dear John and Adam in
the
morning and thank you for your
courage
and standing up to ignorance in
this day
of social censorship I'm trying
to
reverse the historical trend
and sending
this donation in honor of
Mother's Day
and all the moms out there
trying to
keep their sanity during this
insanity I
am spending most of my time
these days
with my kids ages eight and six
trying
to use this opportunity to
teach them
about things such as open
debate about
ideas very good iing slaves to
those
with hidden agendas my kids
were the
ones who we hit in the mouth in
the car
on the way to New Orleans and
though I
still occasionally get a
complaint about
little girl and get a complaint
about
little kids yay yeah my
eight-year-old
clearly sees the calm
perspective of
that knowing that no agenda has
brought
to our household amid the
paranoid
germophobia and is constantly
singing
your praises
yes profile we got a Bruce's
profile
we definitely have a demon to
making on
our hands oh it's a her oh
great eight
euros a girl okay good because
there's a
dame in the making we I really
appreciate what you two do I'm
happy to
let you know that I'm spending
Mother's
Day brunch at one of my favorite
restaurants and never been so
happy to
live in Texas there yeah that's
one is
it which which restaurant isn't
it now
she didn't say the reopening of
business
she should plug it the
reopening of
business I'm it's named the
child in the
restaurant the reopening of the
businesses feels painfully slow
but at
least is happening on a little
act of
rebellion was tearing down two
caution
tape surrounding the playground
in the
park or a house a few days ago
because
even though the parks are open
the
playgrounds are still closed
brother we wouldn't what our
kids to
have too much fun oh we're a
thankful
not to get arrested or have a
video of
our crime posted on next door
Wrangler curtain Wrangler and
have and
be happy to see a few cuz they
saw there
be seeing a few kids playing on
the
playground have that so when we
returned
today thanks to our efforts
Jing anyway
should we return to it and she
wraps it
up please play orange for my
smoking-hot
husband who loves to yell this
okay and
send lots of jobs karma to all
those
producers who are hurting right
now and
maybe a screaming goat to
finish it off
best wishes wishes gentlemen
keep up the
great work
Sarah Gonzalez in Houston day
mom after
our own heart Sarah Gonzalez
thank you
for your courage sir jobs jobs
and jobs
let's vote for job Nicolas
grass checks
in from Cincinnati Ohio to 3333
this is
my first donation so I request
a much
needed decision I was hit in
the mouth
of my future brother-in-law
about six
months ago and I was called out
on
episode 1217 so time to donate
your
content and media
deconstruction are
just what the doctor ordered
and the
treatment has successfully
shrunk my
amygdala I'd like to request
some small
business karma for my
smoking-hot fiance
we created a virtual Fitness
website
during the extra quarantine
time and
we're using the value for value
model I
hope that works I want to let
me know
this is a Fitness has been the
big boom
during you cannot buy any
fitness
equipment you can't buy a
weight a
rubber band
yeah bread-making that's
exactly right
yeah all the Millennials are
making
bread thanks for the
inspiration has
worked great so far if any
slaves need
to get off the couch and break
a sweat
give it a try and there's a
website
there it's nick fit too oh my
goodness
I'm gonna put that in the show
notes and
I'll put it under actually I'll
let me
just mark this and make sure I
do this I
will put it next to your
donation so you
know that thank you for your
courage
jingles little girl yay and
there's a
small business
so thank you for your courage
indeed and
welcome to the bottom you've
got karma
[Music]
Daniel Galloway from Marietta
Georgia
comes in with $229 there's no
note that
I can find under looking under
the
subject line donation or Daniel
or
Galloway let me just show you
real real
quick I don't think I sorry I
have
nothing from him nothing
adrin drink on
what drink on drink sounds
right yeah in
Calverton New York $205 she's a
drunk
hen it ten cents happy first
Mother's
Day to me whoo and happy
birthday to me
and my daughter Violet man my
husband
and I love you violets a
popular name
for kids now for some reason a
little
moment here yeah my husband and
I love
the show and listen as a family
we could
love a goat Carm if possible my
awesome
husband Joe thinks it's
hilarious
cheers Dame Adrienne PS I hope
the hope
Tina the keeper and Mimi have a
great
Mother's Day well that's nice
that is
nice and yet the keepers gotten
calls
and nice things and all that
and how
about me me of you is she with
you or
she up at the annex she is
traveling at
the moment
oh that's necessarily traveling
I'm
gonna wrangle my narc on that
woman this
is not acceptable yes we have a
goat
karma for you absolutely love
that you
listen as a family happy
Mother's Day
Adrienne first time for
everything enjoy
you've got Barbara pon wits is
in
Norwood Pennsylvania and we
just talked
about Pennsylvania and she says
do you
Adam and John thanks for all
you do I
think I'm slowly hitting my
husband in
the mouth or he just encouraged
me
because I enjoy the suit of the
show so
much
either way please give my
mother-in-law
a cancer karma for Mother's Day
that
would be an F cancer karma of
course I'd
also appreciate jobs karma for
everybody
and last but not least special
goat
karma for my boss and friend
Tom he's a
longtime listener and regularly
donates
would you also please play some
sharpen
for my husband Eric whose
birthday is
this Tuesday this would crack
him up
thanks again barber upon wits
and that's
interestingly that's Eric
spelled like
our own shill and they are
chillin by
the way do you have the
birthday list
out yeah I do now who's on the
Eric put
his wife on there Janelle that
guy is
unbelievable Mackey no oh my
gosh
Danelle Mackey is when is her
birthday
today no it was I think it was
Wednesday
okay and we don't know an age
right of
course she's 19 years younger
[Music]
exactly we know how to keep the
peace in
the dvork clan she's 19
mm-hmm she
looks 19 yes so we do have some
some
sharpton for you quick Sharpton
and you
also wanted the eff cancer in
the jobs
karma got it all for you right
here big
annoy we've uh jobs jobs and
jobs let's
vote for job
you've got Carmack should blow
it away
that'll take care of it and
last but not
least on this very generous
Mother's Day
a show anonymous $200 in two
cents he's
got a couple jingles on there
Atlas
Shrugged logo yay I TM gents
please keep
me anonymous I started
listening during
the election run-up of 2016 and
haven't
missed an episode
thanks since as a staunch
libertarian
emphasis on the small L I was
overjoyed
to find your podcast using the
valley
for value system while I had
donated
previously this is my first
associate
executive producer ship the
show is most
certainly the best podcast in
the
universe I was further
encouraged by
Elon Musk's remark on Rogen
about corona
as he echoed much of what you
two have
been deconstructing in the past
two
months
thanks for the show notes they
certainly
help with grad school but they
do a big
Mother's Day shoutout to my
mama Kim in
South Jersey I love you mom she
listens
regularly and hopefully this
proves that
no agenda producers love their
moms $30
of this was for her Dame hood
and two
cents for the penny jar oops
there's one
and there's the old pennies
real copper
it's not that crazy new stuff
and we
need to Atlas Shrugged EE and a
karma
and we're good girls
[Applause]
by I'm ready
you've got karma Wow
there's love in the room for
the moms
that's for sure
that's how you do it love in
the room
well everybody thank you to
these
executive producers and
associate
executive producers you can
proudly
display that as your credit for
episode
1240 one of the best podcasts
in the
universe and know that you have
not only
made a lot of moms happy we got
we've
upped our quota of Dame's very
excited
about the ceremony later but
also you've
kept this show going
successfully
throughout we've really had
we've now
witnessed everything together
we've been
through a lot we've been
through a lot
of things but now also this I'm
very
proud of what we're doing very
proud of
the support today and look
forward to
everybody showing up again on
Thursday
which you can find out more
about at our
donation webpage vollrath org
slash n/a
and once again you're up to
speed on all
things Rona
our formula is this we go out
we hit
people in the mouth
[Music]
right Oh so that so I got this
Clippers
for the last Jonas wanted to
play it
because it's just kind of
stand-alone
and it's a and I want somebody
in
Australia to tell me who this
woman is
she's like a Katie Hopkins of
Australia
mm-hmm and so she kind of rails
I this
is only 31 seconds of something
I went
for a couple of minutes because
she just
kept laying into Joe Biden and
she's in
Australia which is I find
amusing but
this place is good the clip is
called
fie make isn't it just perfect
the party of diversity has got
rid of
every woman and person of color
including the fake Native
American
Elizabeth
Pocahontas Warren and the fake
Mexican
better O'Rourke to end up with
two old
white millionaire men one a
socialist so
had a heart attack just five
months ago
and one is so confused that he
has
trouble remembering where he is
and why
is there Joe Biden is now the
frontrunner to be the Democrats
presidential candidate it is
pretty
funny by the way do you have
some ISOs I
want to pitch right yes good we
need a
pitch pitch it will pitch away
so okay
so I got let's start with the
one which
is which is the wimpy guy
bright and
this is wrong I so wrong I so
for end of
show wrong okay noted yep
uh yeah here's one done more
oops
oh my oxygen cord disconnected
John hold
on I got a plug I told you to
stop
anything from from underwater
yeah okay
I'm back I'm back I unplugged
the cord
and and it lost all oxygen
alright done
more we could have done more
we could've definitely that one
again we
could have done more I like it
because
but we could have done more
yeah that's
actually not bad that that's
yeah I
think it's a little more
exciting than
wrong
well now that I hear it wrong
that's not
bad good wrong okay it's a very
it's a
it's it's a righteous wrong
yeah but I
like the Denver because he's in
tears
and do you have any more
yeah disgruntled I am NOT
disgruntled I
think wrong I think just wrong
is a contender okay I'm
surprised by
wrong I'm surprised I like it -
it's a
right just wrong I like it but
we're not
you know we're not done until
we're done
let's yes you want to go over
to some to
some international likova yeah
yeah I
would like I would like your
organising
your next bit I would like to
do I got
no bits man I just start with
the Italy
Russia but I have let's do USA
kovat
update there's about the
reopening
state-by-state the country is
beginning
to face the reality of a slow
recovery
ahead from the Koba 19 pandemic
companies are considering ways
to bring
workers back but the
unemployment rate
is staggering whether you are
here in
New York where there is still a
strict
lockdown order or in an area
reopening
this is a challenging time
let's get
started with today's top news
cases of
Kovach 19 continue to slow in
most of
the country do you view it
after two
months there were more
reopening zuv
barbershops salons restaurants
and
public spaces but the rules
differ
state-by-state in New York
where a
lockdown remains for much of
the state
Governor Andrew Cuomo said
hospitalizations new cases and
deaths
from the virus dropped again
today but
Cuomo said three children have
died from
a new syndrome associated with
Kovac 19
and there are 73 reported cases
it's
inflammation of the blood
vessels which
can then cause problems with
their
fortune Cuomo said parents need
to be
vigilant while New York health
officials
work with the CDC to
investigate this
new syndrome nationwide there
have now
been more than 77 thousand
deaths from
coke at 19 and more than 1.2
million
confirmed cases also today
after reports
at the Trump administration
shelve the guidance from the
Centers for
Disease Control and Prevention
on how to
reopen the country the White
House
issued a statement from the
director of
the CDC Robert Redfield that
said the
plan quote was in draft form
and had not
been vetted you seriously I'd
rather
have Kovac 19 than listen to
that report
again that was bad that was
uninspiring
was not as bad as his lighting
yeah was
he at home yeah yeah he was now
at home
but they light him somebody
doesn't like
him you know cuz the lighting
guys are
the guys that can make you look
good or
you look horrible he looks like
Boris
Karloff playing Frankenstein
Wow okay
Marsh is very harsh Marsh
okay let's go to Italy and see
what's
going on just Italy or is Ovid
Italy and
it's also to South Korea in
Italy once
the center of the global
pandemic the
lockdown is starting to ease
many bars
in Rome were open today for
takeaway
drinks but officials warn the
social
distancing must be maintained
to prevent
a resurgence in coronavirus
cases in
South Korea the mayor of Seoul
closed
more than 2,000 nightclubs just
one week
after they were reopened dozens
of new
coronavirus cases were
connected to
people who attended clubs last
week hmm
not much going on there so that
was
pretty dull you're right yeah
so let's
go and take a look at that this
is the
cove in russia and comparing
russia to
belarus let's look at what's
happening
internationally Russia like most
countries has scaled back its
celebrations to mark the end of
the
second world war in Europe
because of
the virus pandemic but in
neighboring
Belarus one of the only
countries yet to
impose any social distancing
measures
thousands have gathered to mark
the 75th
anniversary from Moscow skies
down a
magnet has this report
even Russia has postponed this
year's
Victory Day parade but it's
smaller
neighbor to the west Belarus
has not
despite more than 20,000 covet
cases the
veterans were encouraged not to
come
others incentivized to fill
seats good
grades promised to students for
example
at a time when many in Belarus
don't
trust their president on this
pandemic
most newcomer one the official
count is
of a hundred and sixteen deaths
the
freshly dug graves at this
Cemetery in
the small city of stones B
suggests it's
far more fear of my doom this
reporter
for Russia's Channel one was
expelled
from Belarus and his team
stripped of
their accreditations after this
report
which suggested that even
locals don't
believe the numbers Anna Lilla
through
this woman telling him
her mother had had kovat but
that the
official cause of death was
heart
failure the picture inside
hospitals
even in the capital is grim
every piece
of space is used up here and
there's
that ubiquitous co vidcom where
the
state is failing volunteers are
stepping
in the ubiquitous covered COFF
has that
been identified as a specific
type of
cough yeah well that's what JC
when he
had Kovac and these survived it
easily
enough but he ended up with
that Kovac
caught the cotton that lasts a
while I
did last as long you know how
you get
sometimes you get to coal or
somebody
gets into this just coughed
that never
goes away gonna last and last
and last
you know people that I think
horowitz
had it for like three four
shows I like
a month he had this cough this
terrible
call the covet cough which is
really
horrible to hear it it's like
it's
horrible to hear it I mean it's
just a
cringe oh it didn't last long
at all
which is good no that is good
that is
good let me see if we can find
an
example of this Co good cause
it's it
sounds like it sounds like it's
somebody's coffee and then you
hear a
goose honking here we have a
couple of
examples the the
is does this sound like you on
YouTube
that may be exactly what we're
looking
for let's see and why don't I
hear
anything
is that it no no really no
that's your
fake to a higher gear there's a
very
specific thing it does it is
like really
frightening to hear it
the ghovat caught yes I got an
email
which may fit into a good topic
for us
today and I and I want to
reiterate that
this show John I come to each
show we
don't talk to each other in
between
shows rarely maybe an email or
something
typically John sending me some
chick on
YouTube whose hey guys whatever
that's usually what I get from
John so
we show up and I have my stuff
he has
his stuff and I received an
email that I
wanted to respond to I thought
that it
would be appropriate I see that
you've
got some clips to talk about it
this is
from Roland he's from Germany
German
producer in the morning gents
I'm not
sure how voting works but in
Germany
it's like this you get a
postcard with
your name on it the city knows
where you
live is you have to register
when you
move to it tells you when and
where you
can go and vote historically
it's been
on Sundays between 8:00 and 6p
at 8 a.m.
6 p.m. if you're out of town
and you
can't make it to the voting
place
usually a school or
kindergarten in your
neighborhood can send you the
postcard
back at no charge you can ask
for
vote-by-mail papers which you
then get
and send back in time done well
now this
apparently isn't much of a
thing in the
US what is wrong what is the
problem why
are you all so jacked up about
it some
analysis would be helpful
especially to
the international listeners I
think
that's an appropriate question
Roland
well I have two clips on this
bingo boom
first of all you can't vote by
mail in
some some states in fact that's
all you
do
you don't even there's not even
this
processor you're talking about
Washington State for example
there's a
100% vote by mail ah there's a
lot of
people that believe that it
invites
fraud and allow me to explain
the as I
understand the fraud part of it
in the
United States and this is why
it's an
issue
we I I hate to say it but our
voting
public is pretty dumb so when
someone
knocks on your door and says
hey did you
get your mail-in voting bally's
that I
don't know man it's around here
somewhere
well listen why don't you just
you know
just I'll take care of it I'm
gonna hand
it in just what do you want to
be
Democrat right okay we just
write this
down and I'll mail it for you
don't have
to worry about it
it's called harvesting and
sometimes
they'll get ballots that are
just empty
and they'll fill it in for them
it's
theirs and this is I think was
Orange
County
there are Calabasas somewhere
in in
California where they followed
these
people and showed how they do
it and
this is not just the US but its
but this
is harvesting is a real issue
and also I
think it's just lame as a
citizen you go
into the booth and you kick the
lever
and you go there you stand the
line with
everybody grousing about it
it's part of
your ID by the way well no
that's
different well in Texas but for
a bid
yeah Texas you have to show
your ID well
here's a question here's a good
example
if this is what you have to
deal with
this is on PBS again and
they're having
this this problem in
Connecticut because
Connecticut you can do an
absentee
ballot but it's a very
complicated
process and the problem with
Connecticut
is what the story's about
mostly is that
they the Connecticut
Constitution says
you have to show up yes so it's
not like
Washington state it's like it's
designing the systems designed
for vote
vote by mail and by the way
it's funny
how the harvesters do such a
good job
they tend to get a state loaded
with
Democrats I'm not gonna just
accuse the
Democrats but when you hear
reports like
this here's the vote by mail
fraud
question that was asked on the
PBS
amongst some people that are
discussing
how to do this in Connecticut
we just
six months until November's
presidential
election states across the
country are
trying to determine how they
will safely
collect and count ballots
during a
national health emergency for
many
states that means reevaluating
in person
versus absentee voting just
yesterday
California governor Gavin Newsom
announced that the entire state
would be
asked to vote by mail in the
November
Action bought four states like
Connecticut with a long history
of
in-person voting the push to
vote by
mail remains a complicated task
Newshour
weekend's Christopher Booker
has more
the scenes from Wisconsin's
recent
election did not sit well with
Connecticut's Secretary of
State Denis
Merrill that was a turning
point in my
discussions with both the
legislative
leadership and the governor
nobody wants
to look like Milwaukee frankly
and that
that can happen pretty easily
after Democratic governor Tony
Evers
executive order that delayed
the state's
election by two months was
overturned by
the Supreme Court Wisconsin
voters had
to go to polling places if they
wanted
to cast a ballot 52 people who
worked
the polls or voted on April 7th
have
tested positive for kovat 19 the
situation Merril does not want
to
duplicate in her state you know
people
are just waking up to the fact
that they
may be asked to vote either in
a primary
or particularly in the general
election
is their concern and jeopardize
their
health and I think the Milwaukee
situation really galvanized
people
because it was all over
television and
people were home watching it
but hoping
to minimize in-person voting in
Connecticut will not be an easy
task
with voting laws dating back to
the
state's 1818 Constitution the
rules to
vote absentee or by mail in the
state
nicknamed the Constitution
state are
restrictive yeah that's a decent
overview well that's a decent
order that
was the wrong clip the one you
told me
to play vote by mail fraud
question oh
it was the wrong clip but
that's a
better clip for the intro to
this clip I
would have had it I should have
actually
played that clip first so you
accidentally did the right
thing voter
fraud is a major talking point
for those
against expanding vote by mail
on April
8th President Trump tweeted that
Republicans should fight very
hard when
it comes to statewide mail and
voting
Democrats are clamoring for it
tremendous potential for voter
fraud and
for whatever reason doesn't
work out
well for Republicans voter
fraud comes
up quite often have you seen
rampant
voter fraud in Connecticut oh
absolutely
not
I mean for people to complain
about
absentee ballot fraud in
Connecticut is
really
kind of ridiculous because we
have so
many processes in place first
you have
to mail the application to
people they
have to fill it out mail it
back to the
clerk the clerk then mails the
ballot to
the person which is in a double
envelope
you have to put it in an inside
and then in an outside envelope
to
protect their anonymity and
then you
mail it back to the clerk and
during all
this process the clerk has to
note every
step of the way in our
electronic voter
registry secretary Merrill says
there's
little evidence that there is
widespread
voter fraud in Connecticut can
you point
to specific instances of voter
fraud in
Connecticut I don't have them
on me but
we deal with these every year
we end up
having a lot of kind of quirky
election
issues that I don't
particularly find
coincidental but it's something
we need
to address the critics of
expanded
vote-by-mail often cite voter
fraud is
there evidence that when you
increase
the access to vote by mail fraud
increases none there's no
evidence none
whatsoever no where it does not
exist
oh I'm poorly informed then
yeah you
don't know what you're talking
about I
need to shut up right because
she said
right there that Democrat woman
no no never happened ever
happens I know
what you're talking about
by the way just because you go
you walk
into the good like for example
here at
the house I walk in that mail
has been
there's two or three ballots
sitting
there I could pick any with any
one of
them up we had type a bunch of
stuff I'd
put stuff on their sign
somebody's phony
name send it in I could do that
anyone
could do it or somebody they'd
lose some
mail somebody steals from a
post office
box
I mean that's just minor but the
harvesting which you pointed
out which
has always been that the big
threat and
the joke of it is the Democrats
always
hated much of this because it
would be
well I mean the Republicans
used to hate
this for the reasons that the
Democrats
used to like it which is in the
deep
south back in the 50s and 60s
they would
just the Democrats would steal
all the
black votes just rouse the
black votes
they just steal them they steal
the
black vote or they buy a vote
they say
there's another way of doing it
before
harvesting you go up to
everybody you go
door-to-door so I'll give you
five bucks
for your ballot is that illegal
I I
think it's a farce it's illegal
is it
yeah what is illegal raise the
league is
it illegal to say to someone
here's five
bucks
write down your vote right now
that's
not illegal well probably not
it's not
exactly what politics is I'm
gonna give
you this for your vote isn't
that okay
we should the ditch it's it's
asking for
trouble go well there's that
yeah but
this woman when I heard that
clip we're
at the very end of that clip
she goes oh
then I know something's up how
do we
usually put that somewhere we
had a
thing about that that we could
see oh
yeah that's not it where is it
ah we had
nothing to see here I've lost
so many
I'm losing my touch
you are just a eyeball nothing
it's not
completely healed I'll give you
that but
it's not that bad for a long
time I know
that's why I couldn't find it
you know
it's been replaced by so you
know what
it's taking place now is we
have this
political fight which trump is
ch
tweeting about a lot so I guess
he's
worried is this you know the
the house
is looking to make legislation
and I
guess you can do it by state
even to
vote by mail because all
coronavirus be
too dangerous for people to
show up and
vote same is the to danger for
them to
show up at the grocery store
and stand
in line is it too dangerous to
go to the
haircutter I mean why is this
more
dangerous than these other
things that
people do constantly if there's
a shop
that says haircutter I'm not
going
that's a dangerous shop it says
coops
that's a different story so
there is a
lot going on in the political
in fact
pretty much all of it is now
political
and I have been enjoying
these transcripts from the is
that the
house intelligence Oversight
Committee
these 50:53 transcripts that
have been
released yeah I have a clip our
friend
Kaylee yeah
slamming yum yummy yummy yummy
SHhhh
oh no I reading from these
transcripts
and saying well how great it
was that
they were released now let's
just go
over this before we play before
we play
Kaylee and Yumi she now has
Flynn been
exonerated or is that just bar
saying it
has to happen the judge hasn't
done it
yet he's he actually exonerate
exonerate
dropped all charges well in
case it's
not no no I take it back
you gotta use this right
because you're
getting jumped on by all these
guys that
are gonna write your note it's
not
exoneration when the cases drop
was it
cases dismissed rights
dismissed and
what is interesting about the
dismissal
as that it comes from now
overwhelming
evidence from the FBI's own
files that
they were railroading Flint yeah
absolutely railroading him like
like
real assholes like real thugs
really not
okay stuff but then he fight
it's one of
these old Russian things like
Barry I
used to do you know said show
me a man
I'll find you a crime right in
addition
to this very old stalinistic
idea as a
way to do it and that's what
they were
doing and it was but an Obama
was behind
it well this is what's
interesting so
now we have in in this case all
of a
sudden we have 53 transcripts
Declassified of all of these
players and
this is the hours and hours and
hours of
testimony it's very interesting
to read
I was interested in Brad parse
Cal the
guy who's who is now the
campaign
manager the for 2020 the guy
was just a
web dude in Texas in San
Antonio who
didn't you know like the
wineries did a
one-pager website for Ivanka's
thing
and you just and they said well
we're
gonna explode 2015 I
exploratory you
throw up a page for Canada
trompe to see
how it looks and it just grew
from there
and the guy just turned out to
be really
smart he's never done any
political
campaigns anything like that
and he just
used calm in fact he did
everything that
the political consultants in
Washington
DC
he what they advised he did the
opposite
did all kinds of different
innovative
things and it's really
interesting to
read his story now there's not
much in
the way I mean every five so uh
while
you were selecting a vendor's
for the
website did any of them
possibly have
ties to Russia like that
so did they did they have speak
with an
accent I mean this is the kind
of stuff
that was going on and this has
worried a
lot of people and the main
here's what's
interesting
if flynn the case is dropped
and his his
you know what he was accused of
was
lying to the FBI and now it
turns out he
was lying to the FBI because
the FBI
said you better lie are we
gonna lock
your kid up and the lie was a
very menu
detail of a phone conversation
he had
had with the Russian ambassador
kiss
lyac and the feds when they were
interviewing which I believe
include
Peter struck they had already
heard the
call they knew the answers to
the
questions they were asking and
of course
he answered something wrong
word said I
don't remember that or I didn't
have
this time and then they said
well you're
gonna have to plead guilty here
otherwise we're gonna get your
kid and
he has a kid on the way and it
was it's
really ugly really it's like J
ed ver
edgar Hoover type style ugly
and the
President Obama all of a sudden
has some
coincidentally leaked audio
that comes out in fact I have a
little
news report about it because I
think
what's happening is I believe
Obama as
you pointed out Obama is
implicated in
this thing it goes all the way
up to him
and he's striking back but
interesting
way he's doing it
former President Obama
discussed the
Michael Flint case during a
phone call
with some former Obama
administration
officials and then portions of
the audio
of that call were leaked to
Yahoo News
Flynn you may remember pled
guilty 'aa
lying to the FBI about his
communications with the Russia
ambassador the Justice
Department
announced Thursday it plans to
drop the
case against the former national
security advisor Obama says he
was
shocked by the move where you
Norm's but our basic
understanding of
rule of law is is it risk
President
Trump praised the Justice
Department's
decision he also praised Flynn
calling
him an innocent man the White
House says
it believes the FBI was trying
to target
and trap Flynn over his
comments not
surprisingly reaction up on
Capitol Hill
has been split how I don't like
this
report I think it's full of
crap they
also left stuff out here's the
actual
leaked call and there's
something that
Obama said here which is
factually
incorrect and I'm waiting for
the news
media to let us know about that
over the last 24 hours I think
has been
somewhat downplayed about the
Justice
Department dropping charges
against
Michael Flynn and the fact that
there is
no precedent then anybody can
find for
someone who's been charged with
perjury
just getting off scot-free
interestingly
he wasn't charged with perjury
that's
just not true
no he didn't take it Oh mercury
is very
specific so why did Obama say
that why
is he making a big deal out of
well this
has never happened before a guy
perjured
himself when he was no I think
Obama's a
little a little we're a little
afraid
it's getting a little hot under
the
feets yeah I did sound you
think maybe
Obama knew this was being
recorded how
he leaps it was another piece of
disinformation get thrown to
the pot
this perjury nonsense told you
I see if
anyone picks up the tree pit
flies yeah
interesting well that shows
he's very
when Obama has to step in and
do this
kind of crap he's worried yeah
or
something that's very strange
well I do
have the super clips was this
is about
the Flynn and this is a bunch
of clips
that can't be right after Flynn
was
first arrested indicted
whatever they
want to call it the advertising
and all
the media was and and Trump
knew this
was a setup he bitched about he
said
Clint shouldn't have been
arrested he's
a great Patriot and on and on
and the
White House and and the the
right the
Conservatives all knew
something was
fishy about this whole thing and
meanwhile MSNBC and CNN and all
the rest
of the news media they had their
thoughts about it and they were
mocking
everybody President Trump and
his top
aides have been routinely
ignoring the
truth and pushing phony
conspiracy
theories the president it seems
to be
saying that this was a case of
entrapment that Michael Flynn
was
essentially pressured into lying
what is your response I think
that's
hogwash you know there are all
kinds of
conspiracy theories about how
he was
entrapped the FBI agents didn't
do
anything wrong here so I think
that's
important because there are a
lot of
sort of conspiracy theories
they all
work together and you know the
Fox News
people in the White House fuel
these
sort of rumors do they send
these around
with fax machines they come up
with
these conspiracy theories and
they send
around the facts
they should just knock it off
and
realize that their ridiculous
conspiracy
theories are gonna be knocked
down stop
stop with the conspiracy
theories so I
think that loud sound you heard
it about
12:30 Eastern was the sound of
conspiracy theories by the Trump
defenders exploding the sound
you hear
is a million conspiracy theories
exploding think I could call
them the
trumpets all over the country
their
heads were blown up here's
another
conspiracy theory that has been
blown to
bits Trump talking points and
right-wing
media conspiracies demolished
poor
Michael Flynn
he was Duke it's so
embarrassing you
know watch all your chips to
the middle
of the table better be damn
sure you got
a good hand yeah the FBI broke
standard
protocol in the way that they
came in an
ambush general Flynn she knew
better
yeah don't be no one cares what
they
said two days ago think we know
they're
all wrong cares it's like fine
I think
they're losing so much ground
the
mainstream does people don't
care that's
right people are out and about
they're
not listening to your fear
anymore
they're done with you
there's a lot of people that
are sitting
in there yeah yeah but that's
in curtain
regulars yeah but they live in
California imagine all the
people who
could do Dyson oh yeah that'd
be fine
[Music]
there's definitely a lot in
California
but they're not all in
California the
people that we have to thank
aren't all
in California but the first one
is
they're all there sir hey idiot
in Concord California comes in
with 160
bucks he does have in no time I
so
credit sir hey idiot this is a
continuation of my animated no
agenda
$10 per episode pledge of
support there
Ellen boses next and he's in
Langley BC
137 88i congratulations to sir
Jim
Watson claiming part of the
overwhelming
barony of DBC and he's it goes
on to say
now we just need someone to
claim
Vancouver Island and the
Caribbean yes
sir Austin Baron of the Puget
Sound in
Seattle Washington 125 that was
137 88
first or Alan Bose Dame Laura
of the
snow wait hold on hold on this
if you're
gonna just have to say happy
mother's
day to day me Laura
of the snowy Cascades and then
she comes
in right ahead of that red gel
or of the
story Cascades comes in with
the same
amount of money 125 we should
actually
move the tool yeah they're
gonna be
doing executive executive
producer done
done she says happy birthday
John my
best guy ever my husband sir
Austin no
bearing apparent for the Puget
Sound yes
no you two are gonna be joined
at the
hip yes and move to associate
executive
producer shipping news it on
your
Linkedin collar circle
Quinn Bay 111 dollars and 11
cents he
needs the D douching okay
you've been
deduced
head lemn or head the madam in
Elk Grove
California 106 dollars and 61
cents and
he's even become knighted yes
yeah he
does have I'll read this you
Adam if you
do the honors of chipping in a
penny I
will reach knighthood well
consider that
done what a long strange trip
it's been
I was driving West's through
Utah at
five in the morning as the Sun
rose over
the Salt Lake's and I was
flooded with
gratefulness for all that you
do I
pulled over at the nearest rest
stop and
sent the donation that pushed
me over
tonight hood Wow few years ago
my
amygdala was on the brink of
exploding
while I was studying at
Berkeley during
the Trump Hillary debates Wow
and you're
a live man then Jon and Adam
swooped in
to save the day shout out to
Nick
MacNeil who turned me on to you
guys
after listening to a few
episodes back
on a long road trip I was
hooked I've
been a loyal listener ever
since I would
like to be knighted as Sir Ryan
the
roamer of many lands at the
round table
may I please have some lavender
blossoms
CBD rub and coconut Lacroix I'm
honored
to be a member of this
prestigious group
please call my dad Kyle out as
a douche
bag he's normally working in
the garage
going out fishing so maybe say
his name
a few times to get his
attention dad
Kyle stop being a douche bag
and Thank
You Ryan I'm going to it's a
late order
but I'm gonna get you your
lavender
blossom CB rub and Lucroy at
the table
we're moments away from now sir
Sir Seth
Seth Griffin in Highland Park
Illinois
101 oh one Mother's Day by the
way that
if you ever noticed does
everyone named
Seth now there's a bunch of him
there's
a lot of celebrities Seth
MacFarlane
Seth you know Green said stolen
so
buncha sets they're all about
the same
exact age really no so there
had to be
some moment that he browned
there
birthday year that was the
reason they
were all called Seth there's
very few
young Seth's and there's almost
no
Seth's my age and/or your age
for that
matter no and so is any Seth
out there
Tom
whose what's the reason they
were all
good you're called Seth who was
it a
soap box or soap box soap opera
Carrie
who was the who was the Seth of
the day
that brought was sat there goes
rats
upon us yes let's find out
anyway sure
Seth comes in $101 in once
inside a
Highland Park and he has a
Mother's Day
shout-out to Kathy who's a
longtime
listener and will make a heck
of a dame
onward Matthew shower in Eagan
Minnesota
100 Iza sir I'm happy Mother's
Day to my
mom Laurie Laurie shower hello
Laurie
sir you can read this one yes
sir Rob
Van Dyke from the Netherlands
on Dyke
after some dealings with PayPal
concerning my donation history
I am now
much too late for my brother's
birthday
present he celebrated on the
3rd of
March 3 3 is mine and I'm 9 9
my dad's
an 11 11 that's interesting
three three
nine nine eleven lemon
however after PayPal first
cancelled now
restarting my monthly donation
of $100 I
was reminded to look into my
accounting
again and there it was my
donations to
the best podcast in universe
already
finally ready for download on
PayPal
it's a little confusing you
have to be
ignited myself earlier this
year would
now like to have my huge bag
brother
benighted
okay so it's giving his
knighthood to
his douchebag brother although
he
himself and he must love him
them
although he himself never
donated insert
douche bag here please I would
still
like to donate a knighthood to
him as to
relieve him from the
douchebaggery once
and for all and after all he is
the one
who hit me in the mouth years
back
please Knight him sir edy of
the woods
edge for us no additions to the
menus
but we will quietly mosey along
towards
the hookers and blow and maybe
later on
we'll have a taste of the
mutton and
Mead but I'm afraid we won't be
that
hungry after the hookers and
blow
guys from Holland man they know
what's
up sir Rob Van Dyck thank you
very much
$400 Frey what did you say
there in
Dutch met footing look root you
know
that means John's a douche met
friends
like a cruise with trans douche
Robert
de Groot and Yolanda Wilson in
mere lo
Netherlands next on the list I
do
listening for seven years to
the BPI to
you but I have not donated
since 2015
this makes me feel ashamed I
would be
have to request your
forgiveness which I
think he means Addie douching I
think
that's what you've been deduced
my wife
Yolanda in the mouth and now she
insisted make a long do
donation as
always the wife is right and we
better
live our life supporting the
show dad
and we miss you in Holland I'll
bet you
in a better place right now
though Adams
he's in a
better place now
captain boss a hundred bucks
from
Franklin George's you got a mom
in here
listed no we needs a jobs come
her give
you that the end Daniel Lang a
man in
Victoria BC 96 41 Cornelius
Hoenig in
Brooklyn New York 86 in honor
of his
smokin hot milf Kobe K on
Mother's Day
we're a millennial couple love
to listen
to you boomer uncles bickering
and
ranting during the long drives
upstate
we hope our nine month-old
son's first
words will be your grumpy
oh brother so do we so do we
I've been called out for saying
that too
much anonymous 800 a taboo
bestow nation
and happy Mother's Day to my
smoking-hot
wife the best mom in the
universe to our
to human resources from grumpy
green guy
PS I'm a longtime douche bag
which I'll
stay that way until I'm
knighted and
like that I like that style
James Niemeyer in Tulsa
Oklahoma 79th
regrettably my mom sue passed
away a few
years ago love and light always
except
that I miss her so terribly
much but she
didn't ray
no douchebag hears 7932
represent her
birthday July 9th 1930 thank
you James
I'm sure she sir she's smiling
that you
gave your hard earned cash to
those two
losers Bill Johnson in
Grovetown Georgia
71 eighty-six needs ado
douching you've
been deduced it's interesting
he's he's
parently his office got a bunch
of
paranoids and it pushed off the
whole
facade paranoids Rio we had two
large
scanners delivered that are
about the
size of a chest freezer and
this person
gets out there out of their
cube and
wants 20 feet to spray it with
Lysol
spray it with Lysol get Lysol
Mitchell
Russell Mitchell O'Reilly 69 I
think we
got a Mother's Day call out
here yes
yeah meets the meet Mitch the
meat
cutter my smoking hot overworked
quarantined wife Melissa oh we
love you
and need you more than ever
babe I'm
working insane hours six days a
week
trying to feed America and
she's stuck
up that he's I think his
trucker and
she's stuck at home trying not
to go
insane with four cute kids six
years old
and younger holy crap give that
woman a
medal she's a she's a new
voluntary
listener so I graciously asked
that she
be deduced and considered for
the Dame
Drive
you've been deduced yes
that she's she will be
considered for
the Dame Drive and thank you
and you
drive safe
barrister of Bolton was easier
to do now
there's less cars on the road
but
there's a lot of 100 mile an
hour
tickets being given up by two
maniacs
yes Mitchell O'Reilly that was
Mitch the
barrister of Baltimore
Baltimore 69 okay
are invalid Palo Alto
California 60 he's
got some story here then well
he was
working on the wiki you were
going back
and forth with him oh yeah yes
yes he's
working on a wiki yeah and I
and you I
guess I thought you wouldn't
like the
idea I'd like the idea and I
thought you
are wiki hater so I didn't say
that
specifically but I mentioned
that he
should be talking to you too
I've removed myself from the
convo good
Jefferies intamin meanwhile
didn't
remove himself with the convo
and
donated 60 bucks from South
Euclid Ohio
request some jobs karma give
you that at
the end Matt Brown in Raleigh
North
Carolina 59 20 got a mom won't
you read
that's yeah I says I've been
listening
for years my first donation
Saudi
douching is my wonderful mother
who
passed away a few years ago
from cancer
F cancer for her anyone else
who's
dealing with it coming up yes
the true
and visible enemy that will do
that the
end Matt for sure Harrison
Nobles
Southport North Carolina wish my
wonderful mom Lynette happy
Mother's Day
she loves to listen to the show
as a big
fan of Q and on
Wow okay well Roger pratter in
Talladega
Alabama 57:20 home of the famous
racetrack and the Knights
apparently
have special nights in
Talladega now
he's got he's a de Mastodon guy
probably
the only person who's listens
to Noah
Jenna really I'm probably the
only boys
a blind person listen to no
Jenna okay
really snow because Adams
mentioned how
blind people would be able to
work with
things like jazz hands clapping
I'm so
happy so glad that no agenda
isn't like
other conservative shows where
they just
do the opposite of the left
this is true
well we're also not a
conservative
shiranai conservative show but
but Devin
Prater says he has a birthday I
don't
think he's on the list hold on
a second
it turns out yeah 2016 always
belated so
let me just see I want to make
sure we
get to know Devin 26 on the
seventh we
have we have more blind
listeners than
you'd than you think actually I
think
well throughout the years we've
had at
least twenty you have
self-identified
but it could be more at
podcasts are of
course fantastic it's great for
people
who are have more sense
audible senses sensory people
who are
deaf it's Griffin it's horrible
for
people who are blind it's great
there we go I'm trying to just
say it or
if I was really bad but anyway
Rogers thank you very much and
just put
you on the list
and thank you seven thought it
was
Reggie it says Roger Prater no
he's
definitely okay gotcha
and what Roger comes in what
forever
ARIMA actually in circus media
circus
media Missoula Montana fit
55555 and he
says to my mom Christine thank
you for
being the best mom a kid could
hope for
Oh Baron Bob of the dudes named
Ben 55
32 hype
north carolina baron bob of
highpoint I
appreciate everything my mother
uh Tilly
has gone through being a single
mom
raising two boys herself
November
Charlie for Romeo golf says
7373 s kilo
5 alpha charlie charlie
sir david seep you in Massillon
Ohio a
5110 double nickels on the dime
happy
this is a lot of birthday mom
days call
out this is more than ever all
the
effort every year surprise the
show it's
combined mind Happy Mother's
Day to my
mom more I wonder why and my
wife Amy
pewpewpew sure Dave to Thomas
Miller
Naperville Illinois 5510 double
nickels
on the dyno note Christopher
Rutger from
Wyoming Matisse and white
Meeteetse
Matisse how do you print was it
petits
MIT meet see Mother's Day
wishes to my
smokin hot wife pickles on her
first of
many mother's days thankless
pickles thanks for all the
great show
especially the producer who
made the
lockdown 20/20 mixin show one
two three
eight fantastic indeed thank
you very
much Chris Sir Patrick Lobo
Baron of
Tennessee checking in with
double
nickels on the dime happy
Mother's Day
to Dame Sarah for being the
bestest mom
and taking care of all of us
it's good steward Will's Walton
and stat
Stafford Staffordshire UK did
you fight
another double nickel sundered
I'm happy
Mother's Day to my mom Jill 86
and still
going strong in this era of
Cour in
place and also a smokin hot wife
Michelle it was put up with me
while
simultaneously bringing up to
two
wonderful children Lucy and
Alex love
and light
then we have Denise DeLozier
Marilyn
Maryville Tennessee birthday
call-out
force for sir dancing Mike from
my
smokin hot wife Denise she
suggested a
great present would be a
donation to the
best podcast in universe for
his 52nd
birthday on Sunday May 10th
this will
also contribute to her ongoing
drive
today mahad noted and done
thank you
both huh daniel marie 5120 and
this
donations to thank his mom
Jackie for
all she does I have the best
mom in the
world however I must call her
out as a
douche bag happy Mother's Day a
lot of
my two sisters these are all
douche bag
call-outs Stephanie and he
needs to de
douching in the meanwhile Erin
of the
bike and Herndon Virginia uh
happy
Mother's Day to my mom Vicki
who hit me
in the mouth a decade ago if it
wasn't
for her no agenda I'd probably
be a
total slave please send her
Carmen a
douche bag hair Governor wolf
for her
governor wolf you have been
douche
bugged Florida Governor Sir
Andrew
Gardner in Leonard's town is
Maryland 50
happy Mother's Day to my milf
Melissa
Eric boy these are $50 donors
from now
on use all $50 can I just say
something
I don't care what radio station
what
network you listen to I like
can you a
man
PBS doing mothers they do
Mother's Day
they they do mother days
greetings on
the air at the NPR I should say
can you
imagine them saying and this is
for my
MILF mom can you I mean this is
what's
so great about this show
this pledge you like just point
yeah
I'll be around for a while yeah
Eric especially with this
support Eric
boy did Milpitas California
$50.00 he's
been a total douche bag since
hearing
Adam on the Joe Deborah's you
get the
number two number two I'm
telling you go
back go back
I lost my job to coronavirus
fear height
this week me and 35 million
plus other
Americans are in desperate need
of jobs
karma yes I will do that your
show is
the only place to get it and a
personal
deducing please Andrew Boyce in
south
elgin illinois 50 and this is
need of it
uses addy douching first time
donor wife
was awesome during labor i was
hitting
the mouth of months ago and
what's her
name what's her name
well okay well happy mother's
day to her
drew mo Jack in El Cerrito
California 15
David Beach 58 Pamela
Schaeffler 50 I
would like to donate for
Mother's Day
I'm sure my son Andrew is
cupping his
head and shaking his what what
what you
move this over for Mother's Day
I'm sure
my son Andrew loves sitting
with me
listening to your show I know
he's
always all he's up in heaven
cupping his
head and shaking his yes
laughing at his
buddies yes I'm sorry
spamela sir he moose of the
Piedmont
province in Mooresville North
Carolina
Kym burden in Greensville
Michigan for
her sweet mom or his Kim is and
genderless names like Benjamin
Roth
Fleur Robert deccan a in Fairfax
Virginia
he's a sir by the way Sir
Robert Robert
Gannon in no parts of no basis
I think
this is where a note goes happy
mom's
day
a mom he goes she's a monthly
subscription she'll take care
of the
accounting love Bob sir Kyle
Meyer in
Atlanta Georgia wraps this up
I'm gonna
take one quick look down the
list see if
there's any mom call-outs on
the lesser
amounts we just mentioned the
mom
there's a moms yeah this is a
happy moms
day from someone no it's all
pretty much
innominate yeah and we're
always happy
to do it and I am I too am a
little
taken aback with the the
support for the
moms this has never happened on
the show
before never
uou I got it I got it figured
it out I
know okay what do you think
Kovach yes I
agree I think that during this
time is
when people are looking around
at their
household and going holy crap
she does
all that that's what's going
I'm telling
you that's what's going on yeah
that's
what's going on and it's likely
because
this is the worst show of one
of the
worst shows of the years the
Mother's
Day show absolutely the world no
donation at all at all well
thank you
all very much for this and also
thanks
to you came in under 50 for the
anonymity also a lot on our
programs
you're right we'll be around
for a while
you can support us like this
thank you
it's very much appreciated and
happy
Mother's Day happy Mother's Day
to all
the moms yes happy Mother's Day
and their moms do a great we
don't have
moms so I always like to say
that's it
my mom's dead it always it
always puts a
smile on people's face on
Mother's Day
when they hear me say that all
right
here we go with our jobs and f
cancer
karma again thank you all very
much we
will be back for another show
where you
can support us as well that'll
be on
Thursday for that go to Lauren
org slash
and
[Applause]
jobs jobs and jobs let's vote
for jobs
you've got
[Music]
well we're radioactive the
Geiger
counter is blasted in the
background
that is a May 10 20 20 here's
our
birthday enlist we have
Adrienne drink
on and a daughter Violet both
celebrating today we have Devon
Prater
who turned 26 on the seventh so
belated
birthday happy birthday to
Devon Maksim
Rifkin happy birthday his wife
Olga she
celebrated yesterday
Denise Dalhousie IRS's happy
birthday
new husband sir dancing Mike
turned 52
today through Kevin Dill's 34
on the
12th Barbara pond wits happy
birthday to
her husband Eric also
celebrating on the
12th Dame Laura Wilson's his
happy
birthday to her husband's to
Austin
Barrett of Baron of Puget Sound
he turns 54 on Tuesday and
finally Eric
the shill your hubby loves you
very much
that's why he put you on the
list happy
birthday to Dale Mackie and
happy
birthday from everybody here at
the best
podcast in the universe
[Music]
don't gather round douchebag
would you
say Ashley
is we are
brothers and sisters who
[Music]
J
and we have one title change
today
thanks to upping his supports
in the
show up to him one another
$1,000 for
Kevin Dill's Vike out of
Charlotte
becomes the Earl of North
Carolina and
we are very proud to have him
there and
thank you very much for your
courage so
then we have one two three and
four
today very proud and vanilla or
perhaps
you just want the mutton in
media people
usually come for the hookers
and blow
they stay for the mutton and
Mead
congratulations all of you and
thank you
for supporting the No Agenda
show please
head over to no agenda
nation.com slash
rings Eric the shill we'll take
care of
you and then take good care of
you and
make sure that you get your
ring in your
sealing waxing your certificate
ASAP
and we actually have today of
course
because the Rona the No Agenda
meetups
have come to a screeching halt
but not
entirely because a lot of
producers just
will not give up they've done
different
types of meetings and I believe
Boston
is checking in with their
report we are
live with you know the one and
only
Negro the Northeast Brandon aka
like Paula wretched boy feel
free to pop
us we're also here with JJ yo
JJ reddick
lunk here and this is her
Nathan Lee
Miller foster a chaotic good
night at
the White Lodge the Blue Orchid
of the
cold hard mountaintop directory
lstoneham bear the sword
reports I can't
believe I remember that thank
you so
much dog we love you and thank
you for
inspiring these meetings a loud
group
they are booze is flowing
that's right
and then of course no agenda
meetups
calm we'll start moving again I
did want
to mention sir Scott Matt of
Norristown
Pennsylvania has put one on the
calendar
the doughnut narc the thinks
meet up and
that's coming up on nothing
it's until
the 20th but that will be FEMA
Region
three and that will be as I
said in
Morristown Pennsylvania
Morristown in
Norristown it's got to be
Morristown
right Morristown so go to no
agenda
meetups dot-com to find out
more no
agenda meetups where everything
is kind
of just like a potty
[Music]
sometimes you wanna go hang out
with all
the nights and days you'd be
me check it all hell I even
gonna be
with everybody
there is a party whoo what a
show what a
day moms everywhere are happy
happy
happy happy wild yeah so I have
two
things gone wild what I have
two things
left okay I have the Kaylie
slamming him
each oh yes yeah I was kind of
excited
about that yeah well should we
do that
now and at last but let's do
that last
it's not as good as her other
slams in
the past but it's just a
similar style
and I'm liking the way she's
doing these
things a lot of people like her
then I
get to bite and came out and it
looks
like it came out of the
basement oh okay
this is goodnight a special
special I
don't know why the meet out
personal way
it was this was this yet another
technological abortion no it was
actually pretty good
I heard that he won didn't do
it well
and it was like Joe Biden live
and his
lunch life was like in quotes
it was
like you know so he's he comes
out with
with a stupid mask on looks
like an
idiot and I think he's in his
back in
his in his basement with a guy
and I
don't think he's there's a book
she'll
see I'm I think it's a green
screen I
think they just changed the set
you have
them standing that's what I
think I
don't think he was because I
don't know
that he's got this background
and then
if you listen carefully I'm
gonna play
two clips this is the first
one's a bit
of Biden you play that oops
being here is pacing oh my
sorry it just
affects there we go it has so
far cost
tens of thousand Americans
lives and
millions of the jobs and make
no mistake
it doesn't matter how much the
market
rebounds as long as there are
millions
of unemployed struggling people
to get
by we won't be anywhere near
bouncing
back
[Applause]
haha that sounded really dumb
we yeah as
long as millions of people
struggling to
get by it's great that's
basically what
he's saying as long as there are
millions of unemployed
struggling people
to get by we won't be anywhere
near
bouncing back yeah what he
meant was
people struggling to get by but
okay
second his entire economic
strategy is
focused on helping the wealthy
and big
corporations just imagine just
imagine
what we could be doing now with
the 2
trillion dollars in tax cuts
Trump
delivered to his rich friends
as this
first priority amazes how much
better a
position we be in right now
struck if instead of Donald
Trump
cheering corporations on that
spend
hundreds of billions of dollars
buying
back their own stock these
corporations
have I'm guessing that money to
keep
workers on their payroll okay
all right
this is this is insulting to my
intelligence the Democrat Party
who with
the Republicans voted
unanimously for
this bill for the cares Act
which he's
not tell about the cares Act
what's he
talking about then he's talking
about
that tax cut that went into
play in 2017
the two trillion dollars well
he's got
his numbers a little mixed up
cuz that's
not what it was he does have
his numbers
little mixed up well anyway he
goes on
visit next part of it but it
doing just
that they did produce us a
little bit
because they have and I you
notice this
in the first clip too but
notice it more
I heard birds in the background
that's
what I'm saying
they got phony birds chirping
in the
background is on the brother
greens
there's no way you'd have to
mic the
birds and come on hey wait a
minute you
sure the windows not open it
could be
the real birds Joe Biden they
can't even
record Joe Biden property let
alone some
birds in the background but it
could be
yes sure okay
please done now he really goes
after
Trump everything's Trump's
fault of
course it is well he has blood
on his
hands
you know Koba 19 caused massive
economic
challenges but this crisis hit
harder
and will last longer because
Donald
spent the last three years
undermining
the core pillars of our economic
strength many small businesses
closed
because stayed home or because
of
stay-at-home orders but a lot
of them
won't open again because they
don't have
a cushion due to three years of
Trump's
policies that rewarded the
biggest
companies yes many have lost
their jobs
because of the crisis or we're
seeing
many proud families forced to
endure
epic lines for food boxes in
football
stadium parking lots because
Donald
Trump has spent three years
tilting the
playing field toward the
wealthy and not
the middle-class
you know Trump love to crow
about the
great economy he villains but
when the
crisis hit became clear who the
economy
had built this was built to
serve not
workers not the middle class not
families Trump's economic
agenda has
three unmistakable failings
failings
that have been present since
day one but
are coming into sharp relief in
the
current crisis first Donald
Trump's main
measures main measure of
economic
progress is the state of the
stock
market it's the only metric he
values
and it's the only lens through
which he
sees our economy for the past
three
years even as Americans have
had to work
harder than ever to pay their
bills
he said the economy was great
because
the stock market was up hey
this is
pretty insulting it really is
yeah I do
but I heard a different bird
when I
listened to Joe Biden this is
the berta
here it's it's gosh man instead
of
saying here's what I'm going to
do no
this is all he's got so that he
has
nothing that's got nothing you
can't
just lean this before you can't
just run
on I hate Trump no that's
probably why
Hillary lost exactly above all
other
things I mean she could have
won easily
but just con she had no plans
it was
just all this guy sucks yeah
this guy
sucks vote for me what are you
guys what
are you offering i al care
because this
guy sucks
you vote for me and then we get
rid of
him that's exactly right
is exactly what's happening
here nothing
going on and then last on my
list of
clips I do have Kaylee and this
is going
back and forth with you me she
brings in
some of these quotes that were
from the
released papers and she was
thinking
that's great I'm sure she's
gonna have
more about their real this is
Kaylee
mackaninee who is the new girl
on the
block she is putting up quite a
fight
against against the Washington
press
corps I I am sorry I thought she
wouldn't last a week but she is
there
and she's hanging in she's a
tough
made-up cookie it simply glad
you asked
that because for about first
four weeks
of the election I was watching
CNN and I
was naively believing some of
the
headlines that I saw I'm
actually not
going to read the headlines so
I very
quickly came around supported
the
president in fact CNN hired me
I was on
many eight on one panels where
I proudly
supported this president who I
believe
is one of the best presidents
it's not
the best president this country
will
ever have but I would encourage
the
individual who did that
analysis of my
past rather than focusing on me
he
really should be focused on
some of the
very guests CNN chose to have
on their
network he should be focused on
I mean
my over here Jim Jim clapper
who said
you know ten days before he
privately
told investigators there was no
evidence
of collusion that Watergate
pales in
comparison to the Russia probe
I'd
encourage them to look at
Samantha
Power's who was privately
saying I'm not
in possession of any evidence of
collusion ambassador rice I
don't recall
intelligence or evidence of any
collusion former attorney
general
Loretta Lynch I do not recall
that being
briefed to me and for three
years two
years probably more than that
CNN ran
with the collusion narrative
and if the
American people are watching
right now
they're probably very confused
as to
some of the
I read those individuals were
saying
much different things publicly
than they
were saying privately and I'm
very
grateful that those transcripts
were
released yesterday and perhaps
the Kay
file should do an analysis of
that
president there is no
questioning that
so honored to work for him and
ebony
next question
shocking I tell you well you
misha's got
to start doing some damn Arab
reporting
is she only interested in
making Caylee
look stupid is that what
they're doing
what a waste of time they're
not getting
very far it's like a huff x
mark mean
girl does that wouldn't touch
her she's
probably not to be touched
probably one
of those women you just don't
do that to
and I wanted message she did
allo singer
in there which was was she said
I was
hired by CNN oh yes eight to
one panels
there's eight people eight
Democrats at
the one exactly exactly I feel
like it's
the case you hadn't noticed
went a
little bit long but hey we do
it for the
moms we do it for the moms
coming up
after this day happy VE Day
happy VE Day
as well coming up after this
show on the
on no agenda stream dot-com
grumpy old
Benz will be whacking a
tracking sounds
good
end of show mixes quite a few
good ones
we've got Fletcher and Blaney
we've got
Jason Lewis Jesse coy Nelson
and Rolando
Gonzales all keyed up then I am
coming
to you from the couple of the
drone of
Star State it is FEMA region
number six
on the governmental maps if
you're
looking for tin opportunity
zone 33 in
the morning everybody
I'm Adam curry and from other
Silicon
Valley where I don't know
everything
seems nice except everyone's
wearing a
mask I'm Jesse Dvorak no masks
org no
masks org and I'm sticking to it
remember us at Dvorak org slash
in a
until Thursday adios everybody
yo mofos
and such
[Music]
where
no anger
I wake up in the morning
back saying
they're driving me insane
my hand
[Music]
we're gone that is fine
work for the GUP No
no ain't gonna work for the
governor no
the girly hands you a nickel
she was damn
me ass shoes with the grin
a good time
every time we go out to door
for the Geffner no more
how dare you you have stolen my
dreams
my childhood with your empty
words yet
I'm one of the lucky ones
people are
suffering people are dying
a deadly and contagious virus
from China
has made its way into the u.s.
[Music]
got the virus isolated myself
from the
beginning because I thought
that's well
[Music]
directed
directed the UK set to formally
leave
the European Union the
government will
now focus on the next phase of
negotiations getting a trade
deal and
forging a new partnership with
the
remaining 27 countries there
are three
cases or patients we have
coronavirus
[Music]
the Prime Minister Boris
Johnson has now
been discharged from hospital
as he
continues his recovery from
kovat 19
increasingly families are going
public
with what it means to be a
transgender
kid so two sisters and you're
the
brother right were you always
president I'm not always what
were you
before I'm their sister because
I wanted
to be a boy a deadly and
contagious
virus from China has made its
way into
the u.s.
[Music]
but specifically the trans
community who
may have been on schedule for
surgery
some of them may be affected
directly by
coping 19 that's all folks
I didn't cause I didn't call
you I
didn't I didn't there we go sit
down
there we go
Thank You mr. president that's
enough
here we go Thank You mr.
president
that's enough we stopped him
cold there
we go I'm not gonna say anything
Hillary Clinton is a bigot do
we go we
go we shouldn't treat people
that way
yes one of the things I think
about Hey
look this is gonna have a huge
impact on
China she looks at all of that
but
here's the thing I didn't I
didn't I
didn't call me directly and
I'll call
Sonny and get mail okay let's
do it the
way you want let's do it the
way you
want we're doing well and now
we're
doing better nobody has to tell
me to do
it I've been talking about that
for
years I never told you about
spaceforce
wants an incredible thing Julie
like
trying to put out a fire till
we get our
log it does better make that
decision
there's no collusion there was
no
collusion I want security Peter
there we
go it's a disaster they don't
know what
the hell they're doing
there we go angry people it
should end
I've done a lot I don't want to
do it in
China Dvorak
org slash in a wrong