so dollars in attorneys say
Trump sucks
Adam curry this is no agenda
curry from
northern Silicon Valley where
we're all
wondering whatever happened to
the ice
bucket challenge I'm John Cena
Barret so
I doubt everybody's wondering
what
happened to that no they're not
no one's
wondering about that yes that
was for
ALS the money went to ALS oh
well I
don't know man you should dive
into it I
want a full report I want a
full report
Sunday I want to know all about
it
hey I had hair cut right here
good it's
okay with me
I'm so happy I had a haircut
it's so
nice but what an experience
that you
like long hair no well I did
I mean well no actually I've
never liked
it it just looked good on me at
the time
back in the day remember I have
a small
head in order to work well on
TV you
need a big head so if you don't
have a
big head
it's not that small by the way
it's not
as big as Pat Sajak's or Vanna
White or
Little Richard have you ever
seen the
size of that guy's head he had
a big
head what Little Richard was
anything
but little it was pretty good
it was
pretty big so I learned a
little bit
about about returning back to
work and
what it means when the governor
on a
Friday afternoon says hey guess
what you
guys with hair salons you can
open up on
Monday
you don't think about it as a
customer
obviously and like oh that's
fine great
so I immediately this was yeah
I think
it was Friday I saw the news I
immediately started texting
Johanna my
hair stylist to the Stars of
Austin and
and she said oh my god we
weren't ready
for this we had no idea we
thought the
18th is the last we heard is
the 18th
that would just you know we
would be
able to take a look and we'll
figure out
a timeline but all of sudden
they you
know they threw it on him in
two days
this was not a smart idea I've
heard
about this around the country
there's
different errors and there's
always day
hair salons and I was thinking
to myself
I'm thinking to myself self so
how hard
is it to boot a hair salon you
got you
know you're standing you need
your
scissors you need a cut in your
little
buzzing things you need a
bucket of goo
for the color this is know what
this is
exactly what hard can it be
this is what
I thought or at least the
impression I
had it's a lot first of all
what happens
is without you knowing and who
go bad or
some in the meantime wow man I
hope the
next person who cuts your hair
stick
scissors in your eye
you're horrible three four five
six
seven seven cars on the Zephyr
ladies
and gentlemen were still in a
state of
depression yep
No so the first thing that
happens is
without any knowledge that this
would
take it was a scissors in my
ass not
nice so I'm warning you really
because
you know you get my hairdresser
hair
cutter he he doesn't listen to
the show
nobody listens to the show in
that dead
business I can I just tell you
what what
the experience was so it so you
understand why I think you're
wrong
about all you needed some goop
and his
scissors and some shampoo okay
so
imagine your year it's a Friday
night
you don't even know what day it
is
anymore in the lockdown and all
of a
sudden some someone of
importance says
oh yeah Monday you can go back
to the
hairdresser what do you think
happens it
gets warm up with order in the
caught
off guard and there's a lot has
to
happen there
there you know we have very
strict city
ordinances despite what the
governor has
ordered the City of Austin is
going yeah
we'll get into that in a moment
so you
have to have policies it has to
be
published you have to let
everybody
knows everyone has to wait in
the car
before they come in you have to
clean
off all surfaces there's a lot
of
different things that have to
take place
and then the fear it's not like
the
whole hair salon wanted to come
back
there were other hair cutters
and like
no I'm terrified so can you
open up with
half a shop you know there's a
lot of
questions
III do didn't think about it
but then
when you get into it it's
really weird
to have your hair cut with a
mask on and
even even Johanna is like
looking at me
like now I know this sucks so
bad but
but it'sit's requirement not
legally but
it's a requirement based on
shaming this
let me play these clips and
you'll
understand we kind of started
on this
but when the governor of Texas
said okay
here's what here's what can
happen we
can open up there's no
requirement for
masks in public or or even
indoors I
mean it can be up to the
proprietor or
if they want to force people to
wear
underwear on the head but Adler
said oh
no no no we're just gonna tell
everyone
they need to wear masks I think
we had
the clip on the last show and
even
though I can't find you or send
you to
jail knowing that you've killed
somebody
should be enough if you don't
wear a
mask outside all the time in
90-degree
heat so now the Texas Attorney
General
has sent a warning to Austin
and its
mayor at a time when some
Austin staples
like Shady Grove have closed
their doors
for good
Texas Attorney General Ken
Paxton sent a
warning letter in part to Mayor
Steve
Adler and Travis County judge
Sarah
Eckhart saying that the local
health
orders issued last Friday were
confusing
and unlawful because the order
doesn't
clearly differentiate between
recommendations and requirements
Kelsey Ericksen roofers with
the Texas
Restaurant Association they
also sent a
letter to mayor Adler asking
him to
change section 11 of the local
order it
encourages restaurants with the
capacity
of 75 or less to keep a log of
all
customers and employees who
came in
including the dates and times
they were
there and where they sat TRA
says if
small businesses are doing this
so
should the big ones
city and county attorneys are
now
reviewing Paxton's letter but
in a
statement to CBS austin a
travis county
spokesperson said in part our
initial
thought as we disagree with the
Attorney
General
mayor Adler also sent us a
statement
saying in part up to this point
we have
avoided the naked
politicization of the
virus crisis I will not fry the
AG down
that road the city's order
complements
incorporates and does not
conflict with
the governor's orders Adler
also brought
it up during his daily virtual
address
so Adler is trying to do a
Cuomo every
single day from his office
there above
the W Hotel in downtown Austin
it's I
really this guy's being he's
not yeah I
don't think he's left his home
at all
he's the guy that's pussy he's
the one
that's sitting inside and
requiring
small businesses in particular
restaurants we had this happen
when we
went to the first open first
restaurant
opening you've got it write
down your
name you got to sign a piece of
paper
and of course people are going
to revolt
against that and it's not even a
requirement by law but you
heard it it's
the shaming that's where all of
this is
headed
one more clip of the response
from Adler
regarding the defiant Austin
Texas your
state is opening up but your
city is not
yet why not
well we're opening up to these
the governor has has put it in
his order
so we're compliant with the
state but
the messaging that we're trying
to send
to our community is to take this
cautiously and slowly because
no one
knows what the impact of this
is going
to be and it's going to take us
three
weeks maybe four weeks to get
the the
data on hospitalizations that
we need to
see to see whether or not our
toe dip
here is putting us on a path to
another
surge so it's more what other
surged
there was never a surge in
Texas to
start with but he feels that
there's a
surge surge so it's more of a
messaging
element than anything else we
have a lot
of community members that know
that
while these things are opening
it
doesn't mean we have to go and
doesn't mean that we that we
have to
open the governor has allowed
those
things to happen but we are
urging our
community to take this
cautiously and
and slowly so that we can
measure the
impact before we end up with
another
surge another she said twice
isn't
checked just to make sure maybe
I missed
the wording somewhere there's
not even a
headline with surge in Texas
Travis
County or Austin this is about
shaming
and I was surprised because I
kind of
scoffed when you said it but my
hairdresser she said oh my god
I never
Intel she says I never expected
to see
it was kind of funny this level
of
social shaming from liberals
I'm like
what okay
and she said literally it's
very clear
if you wear a mask you're
Democrat if
you don't you're a Republican
it's
exactly what you said about
California
history and and even she
recognizes it's
only to make you feel good
these are the
masks are the like the ribbons
after
9/11 you know and that is
community
there's also a community aspect
to it
I've noticed this when you go
around
without a mask in a but with
people
mixed
no masks you can start to see
the
connection you can see that the
no mask
people or the you see a lot of
macho
guys motorcyclists it's kind of
like
that Larry David episode
worried or the
trump hat start to see then you
can see
these old guys are just aren't
gonna do
it you know Murray just gave me
a great
idea
oh here's what you need read
make
America great again
masks yeah hello this is the
perfect for
the mask no are you kidding me
I think I
think Republicans will wear the
mask
where you have to wear the mask
to get
into the store to Whole Foods
for
example yeah yeah big good mask
he had
great American make America
great again
or a meg Meg masks it's a mega
man where
are they they must have already
been
made well it just came up in
another
thing when I'm watching
television and
I'm seeing actors I'm seeing
commercials
they don't represent the
American public
anymore I demand that every
single
commercial the actors wear
masks in the
commercial I'm looking at masks
all day
and I come home and all I see
is faces
ooh
ugly if I put a mask on that
mask you
know what I hate to be this
sexist
everyone thinks I am I don't
like that
so they're what you run into
this
situation but again I just
happened the
other day it's like there's
some leggy
girl or is it group somebody
with great
legs let's just make it be
honest about
all right and she's got the
mask on and
then you starting to you wonder
you're
wondering what what does the
face matte
and match the rest of the body
match the
lake or is it this old woman
with great
lace does he you see that
everyone
survived you would run into
that in
Florida this this is also a
godsend for
older women because they can
have a
scarf or something like Nancy
Pelosi you
have a nice you know scarf
you have around your neck you
can pull
up if you need a mask situation
but in
the meantime a women love
hiding there
you know if they are unhappy
with their
neck that a lot of older women
aren't
yeah so that it can work as a
fashion
statement for them well the
topic of
these mats they do have an Amy
Goodman
clip well before you do that
hit'em Isis
well I'm sorry well I have to
apologize
first you can't just like why I
made a
mistake
I made a mistake on the last
show I made
a big deal about the foul Qi
clip which
was listed as may 6 out it was
March 6
and and he was clearly saying
no masks
whatsoever it's not necessary
it's even
dumb and right and people got
mad at me
John you got two letters okay
dude I get
my letters and your let's be
serious I
get my letters and your letters
so stop
with me I want to play the
original then
I want to get to Amy because I
have a
Judy and Judy will lead to Amy
that
makes a lot so Amy is about the
masks
this is about the mass this is
foul John
the mouse Judy I saw this too
this
breakdown of foul Chi the thing
was
labeled it would when the when
that clip
went out and it was criticizing
you for
playing this clip and giving a
wrong
date there's two things one it
was
mislabeled that I saw this I
saw these
these clips they had a Mis
label on them
they were labeled May and the
second
thing is this is just proving
that foul
she was a debt into the whole
thing
early on and now they're
blaming Trump
with with quotes which I have
on certain
clips I have a clip saying oh
and Trump
wouldn't listen to foul she
thought she
was not into this until later
so here is
the original this is from March
and even
though it's an outdated opinion
I don't
see how the science of what
he's saying
changes right right now in the
United
States people should not be
walking
around with
asks you're sure of it because
people
are listening really know
closely to
this right now people should
not be why
there's no reason to be walking
around
with a mask when you're in the
middle of
an outbreak wearing a mask
might make
people feel a little bit better
it might
even block a droplet but it's
not
providing the perfect
protection that
people think that it is and
often there
are unintended consequences
people keep
fiddling with the mask and they
keep
touching their face then can
you get
some schmutz sort of staying
inside
there or of course but when you
think
mask you should think of health
care
providers needing them and
people who
are ill so very clear it sounds
to me
like he's talking
scientifically this
just makes no sense by the way
have some
hair that's cut off your head
fall in
between your mask and your face
see how
that feels is very very is a
shitty
experience so now we have April
3rd so
that's still a month ago here's
Judy on
PBS asking Pope Falchi about
the masks
again masks oh by the way
that's my eye
so candidate masks we are told
that the
Trump administration is on the
verge of
urging Americans to wear masks
when they
go out tell us about the
thinking on
that because just a few days
ago we were
told that the thinking was that
was not
necessary
it's a great question Judy into
thinking
yeah I could there's no way to
edit
anything in after that great
question
that the thinking was it was not
necessary it's a great question
Judy and
the thinking is really now
influenced by
information that's coming in
and the
information is that more and
more
accumulation of data indicate
that
people who are without symptoms
at all
can transmit the virus but
importantly
they can do it merely by
speaking now
this I I want to see this
report I don't
know what he's referring to but
now you
can transfer it it's before it
was a
droplet maybe highly unlikely
now just
the force of your voice
so there's yeah there was I
just want to
mention that I picked up on this
a couple recent clips I may
even have
one of them I'm not sure
because I
didn't think I didn't think it
was it
was a trend but yeah they're
saying that
talking yeah just this goes
back to your
theory about the mass being
just a
gentle slave muscle it's a
muzzle weasel
you're talking shot
thank you it's a good point
just by
talking you're you're very
dangerous
yeah
muzzle they can do it merely by
speaking
so there's been a recent study
that came
out that said even the force
from your
voice of speaking there is a
degree of
aerosolization namely the virus
can come
out not very far but a few feet
and down
so even though the perfect
solution to
this is if everyone at all
times it's
day six feet separated so in
all the
years in 35 years of of
infectious
diseases and viruses now all of
a sudden
this one is different than all
the rest
we're just the force of your
voice can
go out a few feet and down and
it can
kill people
it's just I'm surprised
sometimes
because the genius virus has
never
spoken to an Arab at a Lebanese
fish
market no well they spit on you
stay six
feet separated from another
person but
as you correctly mentioned this
is not
always feasible there are times
when you
have to do necessary functions
you have
to get food you have to get
drugs from
the pharmacy and you might
inadvertently
be in a situation where you're
close
enough where that kind of
transmission
can take place but and
importantly I
think what people don't fully
appreciate
is that putting a mask on
yourself is
more to prevent you from
infecting
someone else
all right so but it's still not
a legal
requirement it's not something
you have
to do by law and why well
because
unfortunately we can't throw
people in
jail and the same question
about masks
that I was asking about staying
at home
if these are things that that
save lives
keep people
healthy why not require them to
do this
you know Judy I understand
where you're
coming from but it becomes
difficult
when you say required by what
by penalty
by putting people in jail I
mean that
becomes a you know something
that really
could be counterproductive in
the
society that we live in and in
America
perhaps you might be able to do
that in
China he says he doesn't say
well if you
want that kind of crazy you got
to go to
China that's where they force
the people
to do stuff no he's saying you
got to be
China if you want that just
wink-wink
nudge-nudge you might be able
to do that
in China but I think it would be
difficult to do it here so what
we're
relying on is two people to
really
understand the importance of
this yes
and the importance indeed I saw
after
the the hair hairdresser on the
way home
I'm like I'm hungry I'm gonna
get me a
sausage biscuit yeah and a hash
brown at
McDonald's in the drive-through
and this
was my experience because the
order-taker
who already you know they have
the
headset with the microphone
she had a mask on she had a
mascot I
like could I have a sausage
biscuit it
what yeah I'll have a dr.
pepper oh my
goodness so of this I so masks
friend of
show I think it's boring but I
don't
have anything to get people
this so I
don't relish this you you have
you have
you have no standing if you
have nothing
to compete with none can't tell
me my
shits boards okay all right
let's say
what do you got with a no I
this is back
to the idea this is the
original idea
and I think this is more
important than
the a lot of this especially
throwing
people in jail part although I
do like
the bit you should
bit of the person we're gonna
marry and
by the way they're isolated
anyway there
are over by themselves the
people that
are on the McDonald's
microphone but
okay this is a me are talking
about a
big con fad going on and there
was Trump
had one of these two with the
governor
of Nebraska and the governor of
Colorado
and and just that you went
pulled the
camera back at two sides of the
room the
Colorado governor's wearing a
mask and
his assistant was there all
wearing
masks on one side and the other
side the
the Republicans from Nebraska
weren't
and Amy notices this elsewhere
and it's
it's becoming a thing
Republican Rand
Paul of Kentucky the first is
this the
one confab is that what you
want cuz I
have to know what the one is
right the
top it says Amy Rapp mass
affection
because you mentioned confab
that's why
here we go well we're gonna
start today
in Washington DC as president
Trump
claims the u.s. is prayer to
prepare to
transition to greatness and the
Kovach
19 death toll surpasses eighty
one
thousand two of the nation's top
scientists told a Senate
committee
Tuesday that needless death
would result
if states reopened too soon the
stark
warning from the nation's top
infectious
disease expert dr. Anthony
Fauci and dr.
Robert Redfield the director of
the
Centers for Disease Control and
Prevention came just a day
after NBC
News published an unreleased
White House
report showing a surge of
coronavirus
cases and US communities okay
now we
have to watch out for this word
because
now they're just throwing it in
anywhere
they want and what is what is
the
definition of a surge is it a
number if
you have one case in your
county and
then you have to a sudden
powerful
forward or upward movement
especially by
a crowd or by natural force
that's to be a more than
including
Nashville Tennessee in Des
Moines Iowa
Central City Kentucky topped
the list
the report based on a May 7th
internal
memo directly contradicts
Trump's claim
Monday that the number of kovat
19 cases
is rapidly declining around the
country
in a surreal scene
dr. pouchy dr. cereal and food
and drugs
commissioner dr. Stephen Hahn
all joined
the Senate Health Committee
remotely
while they quarantine after
being
exposed to the virus or to a
staffer at
the White House who tested
positive
Republican senator Lamar
Alexander from
Tennessee was also in
quarantine after
his staffer tested positive he
presided
over the hearing from his home
of the
Senators who joined the hearing
in
person
most Democrats wore masks or
balaclavas
most Republicans did not wear
masks can
Senator Susan Collins of Maine
began the
hearing without a mask but put
one on
during Republican senator dr.
Rand Paul
of Kentucky the first senator
known to
test positive for the virus did
not wear
a mask this is so important for
her oh
yeah well the mask didn't wear
a mask
and he was exploding here you
know had
tested positive and they make
it you're
right it's just a shaming all
that this
is to get this is all about
Trump yes
and do you know why or when
when it will
be safe to go outside without a
mask
because I know when there's
going to be
an exact moment that we will
all feel
safe do you have any idea what
that is
nobody bet you do
it's when the soccer mom says
so oh yeah
yeah they should this revealing
didn't
Twitter I think I did I don't
remember
that I just I want to read
something
from Washington Post a buried
lead I
feel and this was one of this
thing come
out Monday
during a taskforce meeting
Wednesday a
heated discussion broke out
between
deborah birx that's the
ambassador
lieutenant colonel general the
physician
who oversees the administrations
coronavirus response and Robert
Redfield
the director of the Centers for
Disease
Control and Prevention Burks
and others
were frustrated with the CDC's
antiquated system for tracking
virus
data which they worried was
inflating
some statistics such as
mortality rate
and case count by as much as 25%
according to four people
present for the
discussion or later briefed on
it which
of course I can't believe this
either
because we can all believe it
in any
case but I'm just reading it to
senior
administration officials said
the
discussion was not heated quote
there is
nothing from the CDC that I can
trust
Burke said according to the -
two of the
people Redfield defended his
agency but
there was general agreement
that the CDC
is in need of a digital upgrade
Oh
that'll fix the problem what do
you need
to do an abacus counting we're
relying
on this data of who dies of
what and
although shootable we've got
more
digital I actually have a
couple of
clips regarding this one foul
she is the
one that's saying well I think
the
numbers are probably a lot
lower than
they really are
I'm sorry he's saying exactly
the
opposite I have he had a hold
testimony
where he said it's probably
double what
it is yes what I said no you
said you
said the opposite he said the
numbers
are much lower say you said
much lower
no I I would move I would ask
you to go
back but foul she says that the
numbers
are I probably put it poorly
you did
pouchy has been saying that the
numbers
are higher than we're reporting
he says
he says he believes it's double
and
other people like you said of
our saying
the opposite including Burke's
who is
foul cheese Burke's well listen
to this
one I got a good one here this
one is
do-do-do-do-do-do papa
like if I find it I've got my
clips are
still not well organized
Rick bright now-no Trump Trump
Trump
this is fun
I'm love hearing you struggles
okay we
got time no one's going anywhere
yeah I can play a little
interlude music
if you'd like while you look
for that oh
well let's do the big concert
but I want
to go back to the Kami clip
first you've
missed a little put his little
gotcha in
there as she had okay she made
the point
if she made a point in that
clip of
saying that the report the
Democrats are
not only wearing masks but they
were
wearing a balaclava sorry I
heard it I
lost even with a lot of love
AHS black
lava whatever high over your
italic lava
yeah what is what what are they
you know
what these things are they're
just like
like a Muslim thing this brings
us back
to sir Imus and his claim that
we're
being turned into above a
Sharia State I
forgot about that yeah yeah
balaclava
there's well a balaclava to me
just
looks like just some kind of
kerchief
well if you look it up it's
there are
the full face once and cover
your whole
ass right right the ones that
could be
printed with that's interesting
because
I don't think a single person
was
wearing an actual balaclava
you're right
that's not true at the meeting
with
Trump and the Colorado Governor
his
health director was well a
balaclava the
definition is a close-fitting
garment
covering the whole head and
neck except
for parts of the face so what
he would
have to go over your face over
your head
and you have the eyes in the
mouth open
it's also seen in
any clubs in Amsterdam this
outfit funny
I found your a clip it's a desk
exaggerated over desig Zaheer's
now this
is a classic role we have to
point out
Illinois zone state health
director who
had a recent second this is
your buddy
Laura Ingraham and I have a few
clips
from her but she I believe she
actually
says Illinois's troll we have
to point
out Illinois own state health
director
who at a recent press
conference just
casually admitted this if you
were in
hospice and had already been
given you
know a few weeks to live and
then you
also were found to have kovat
that would
be counted as a Cova death even
if you
died of a clear alternate cause
but you
had kovat at the same time it's
still
listed as a Cova death
yeah well this story of course
has been
told a thousand times on a
thousand
YouTube videos by a thousand
doctors
this is the consistent story
everyone
knows is very consistent fact
those two
doctors that were taken down
they was
that word same thing would
taken down by
YouTube mm-hmm discussed this
in great
detail but it just keeps coming
up yes
and except out she right now
she says
the opposite is true
yeah foul she says it's
probably double
then he said that in testimony
and
that's when everyone went
apeshit once
again and I have the I have a
you have
rent Ron Paul I got a right on
over on
Paul's book I got a Rand Paul
cliff we
have the Rand Paul clip that's
Rand Paul
I put Ron Paul because it was
late okay
is it the same as mine cuz I
already got
acute up let me see is it is it
the
testimony that you have or I
don't have
the testimony no I have him
discussing I
believe with Judy or one of the
yeah oh
oh oh how about this why don't
I play
what he said in the Senate Rand
Paul and
then we'll go to what he said
at Judy
how's that sound
if it's good if it's related
yeah
it's about the the schools and
about
getting back to life no I think
he's
just didn't he is just moaning
hold on
let's listen to this with
regard to
going back to school
none thing that was left out of
that
discussion and she probably
mentioned
that Rand Paul I think he's a
physician
is the ophthalmologist what
he's a
physician believe he's an
ophthalmologist yes but he's
still a
doctor is the doctors the
doctors an MD
is mortality I mean shouldn't
we at
least be discussed part of this
weighs
more MD than Ted Ross that's
for sure
going back to school
one thing that was left out of
that
discussion is mortality I mean
shouldn't
we at least be discussing what
the
mortality of children is this
is for
doctor Falchi as well you know
the
mortality between 0 and 18 in
New York
data approaches zero it's not
gonna be
absolutely zero but it almost
approaches
zero between 18 and 45 the
mortality in
New York was 10 out of a hundred
thousand so really we do need
to be
thinking about that we need to
observe
with an open mind what went on
in Sweden
where the kids kept going to
school the
mortality per capita in Sweden
is
actually less than France less
than
Italy less in Spain less than
Belgium
less than the Netherlands about
the same
as Switzerland
god bless the Swedes man god
bless you
thank you for - which Eleni
mentioned
anybody did Sweden these as
Sweden's the
one that stayed open and I say
God bless
Sweden god bless them for doing
that
otherwise we'd have no other
proof but
basically I don't think there's
anybody
arguing that what happened in
Sweden is
an unacceptable result I think
people
are intrigued by it and we
should be I
don't think any of us are
certain when
we do all these modeling's
there's been
more people wrong with
modelling than
right we're opening up a lot of
economies around the around the
US and I
hope that people who are
predicting doom
and gloom and saying oh we
can't do this
is going to be surged to admit
that they
were wrong if there isn't a
surge
because I think that's what's
going to
happen in rural States we never
really
reached any sort of pandemic
levels in
Kentucky and other states we
have less
deaths in Kentucky that we have
in us in
an average flu season it's not
to say
this isn't deadly but really
outside of
New England we've had a real
Tivoli benign course for this
virus
nationwide and I think the
one-size-fits-all that we're
gonna have
a national strategy and
nobody's gonna
go to school is kind of
ridiculous we
really ought to be doing at
school
district by school district and
the
power needs to be dispersed
because
people make wrong predictions
and really
the history of this when we
look back
will be a wrong prediction
after wrong
prediction after wrong
prediction
starting with Ferguson in
England so I
think we ought to have a little
bit of
humility in our belief that we
know
what's best for the economy and
as much
as I respect you dr. Falchi I
don't
think you're the end whole I
don't think
you're the one person that gets
to make
a decision we can listen to
your advice
but there are people on the
other side
saying there's not going to be
a surge
and that we can safely open the
economy
and the facts will to bear this
out but
if we keep kids out of school
for
another year what's gonna
happen is the
poor and underprivileged kids
who don't
have a parent that's able to
teach them
at home are not gonna learn for
a full
year and I think we got to look
at the
Swedish model and we got to
look at
letting our kids get back to
school I
think it's a huge mistake if we
don't
open the schools in the fall so
foul she
is is obviously being worshipped
certainly by elements in the
media and
politicians and he's
untouchable no
matter how many times he
contradicts
himself or said it was no big
deal and I
think you got some clips coming
up
there's one thing I wanted to
mention
about fout she when now when
when we
were looking well when the
Vatican was
looking for a new pope I
predicted this
Pope by name and I want to tell
you and
I think I explained how I did
that but I
did it by looking for - well
really for
looking for one thing I knew
was gonna
be some priest from South
America and I
knew it had to be a New World
Order guy
because I am a firm believer
that the
last real Pope was Pope John
Paul the
first to by the way was
eliminated after
exactly 33 days on on his papal
throne
one of those magic numbers that
were
always wary of yeah he was he
that was
possessed you what the
godfather 3 movie
was about yeah fascination of a
pope
right well I think he was he
was the
real deal and then they had to
get some
of these New World Order guys
and then I saw that the Frances
that he
is a Jesuit now I only know one
Jesuit I
mean really no not well not
really
really no but I know him well
enough and
that's the Padre from twit and
looking
at his psychological profile
which i
think is representative of the
of the
Jesuit model is that of well
unwanted
submission to control and
there's also a
lot of historical stuff about
the
Jesuits and Freemasonry and
before you
know it you're down the rabbit
hole of
Illuminati but it turns out
foul she's
also a Jesuit and then it kind
of comes
together
you've got the Pope he's
sitting there
in the Vatican with his
billion-dollar
empire and here's foutch II
sitting
there at NIH with this
billion-dollar
empire telling people what to
do I think
he has a bit of a god complex
and it's
being played into if not a much
deeper
agenda yes an interesting point
I didn't
know he was a Jesuit no I'd
only found
out myself just a couple days
ago Mike
oh that's interesting I really
don't hey
if you're a Jesuit sitting at
home and
you're mad at me then let me
know what's
going lately I'm sure we have a
number
of Jesuits listen to the show
because
they have to exactly yeah but
now she
mentioned Sweden I want to
bring up a
laura ingraham ham clip because
this is
I when she did this she's doing
this new
sisters gimmicky things they do
it she's
got this traitors frauds and
winners or
something I don't know what it
is and
she's like I Domingo finger
kind of
thing she does okay so she but
this
would when she did this little
little
little bit these are all short
I thought
to myself besides thinking
about Sweden
I said this isn't being covered
very
well she's absolutely correct
and this
is the ingre ham florida and
georgia
clip and now onto the frauds
what
start with Pennsylvania Health
Secretary
Rachel Levine who weeks ago
ordered
nursing homes to admit kovat
positive
patients
well while thousands of
residents saw
their loved ones and family
members die
Levine quietly extracted her
own mother
out of harm's way
reportedly moving her from a
nursing
home to a hotel
my mother requested and my
sister and I
as her children complied to
move her to
another location during the
kovat 19
outbreak my mother is 95 years
old she
is very intelligent and more
than
competent to make her own
decision I'd
rather have her mother be health
secretary of Pennsylvania
frankly well
this well that wasn't the ingre
ham
Florida and Georgia clip was it
thought
it was I thought that was ingre
ham on
pennsylvania health secretary
clip on I
apologize
it's the I all right now we try
that
again with the correct no well
yeah I
want to go back to the Florida
trip but
since you played that clip yeah
there's
something to say about it I
wanted I
want to play it again because I
want you
to listen to this woman who is
the
pennsylvania health secretary
and she's
a very strange-looking person
she's a
kind of a squat fat woman with
a long
gray scraggly hair and she's
talks and
sounds and then if you listen
to that
clip I don't believe it if you
look back
on it you'd think it was a
woman at all
it sounds just like a guy
mm-hmm dies at
a transgender person who is the
health
secretary in Pennsylvania an
old old
transgender I don't know let's
just say
the voice of this woman is just
just a
head shaker oh okay this is
Rachel
Levine oh yeah I know she's a
she's a
she's obviously a transsexual
okay that
makes sense with a voice yeah
play play
it again listen to do okay with
I don't
even need to play it again
let's start
with Pennsylvania Health
Secretary
Rachel Levine who weeks ago
ordered
nursing homes to admit kovat
positive
patients well while
the residents saw their loved
ones and
family members die
Levine quietly extracted her
own mother
out of harm's way reportedly
moving her
from a nursing home to a hotel
my mother requested and my
sister and I
as her children complied to
move her to
another location obviously yeah
well
okay that's an observation I
don't know
if it's off-putting
all right now here here she is
talking
about this is the story that I
did
nobody's gonna want to cover
apparently
if it's and if it's true but
this is the
Florida in Georgia clip no you
don't
want to talk about those
elderly homes
for a minute you want to go
straight
through the Florida and Georgia
well I all I was interested in
is the
business act that they would
that this
ninety five year old woman was
moved out
of the home when they moved all
the
covert people and it's just
kind of well
no this is this talk about this
is it's
a sick situation I don't
understand
what's very this is very
important to
stop this is the this is the
problem so
first of all it's not discussed
because
if it's brought up and really
you delve
into it you will find that
Governor
Cuomo made a mistake yes and at
the end
of March ordered sick people
kovat 19
patients to be put temporarily
in
nursing homes and homes for the
elderly
and allowed for kovat 19
positive staff
to continue working in nursing
homes
that means he lent him to be
president
but okay so let me just let me
just
break this down for a second
this is
obviously now that we have the
numbers
and it turns out that over
sixty percent
of all infections took place in
the home
and over fifty percent in New
York of
the deaths are in nursing homes
so I'm
sure that Cuomo or whoever made
this
decision is not an evil bastard
and it
was a mistake if someone was not
thinking probably because they
were
completely obsessed and
preoccupied with
the surge and the hospital
system and
this killed people and it has
to be
admitted if someone has to say
you know
what we made a really big
mistake here
and we learned
but the in the United States in
particular but look at Italy
every other
country it's people over 75 and
mainly
those who are in in this case
state-run
care said we don't give a shit
about the
elderly in the United States we
don't
care about them let me get this
straight
would your advocating is that
somebody
admitted to making a mistake
you have to because people are
in
artesia society like this
somebody's
gonna make it you're gonna make
a
statement like that if it if so
if no
one makes the statement then
what will
happen is there will be
lawsuits is
gonna be a horrible that may
happen
anyway
but we all for the death toll
in general
we have all these people dead
whether
it's legitimate count or not
it's
important for us to understand
it's not
children and it's mainly people
the
majority of people who died
were elderly
in Khitan in nursing care
facilities who
by the way shared it with kovat
positive patients and staff
that would
help people understand this put
forth
how does this put forth the
bite in
Democrat agenda no I'm not I'm
speaking
as a human being I'm not
speaking as a
media analyst I'm speaking as
someone
who says that this will not fly
you have
to admit the mistake and
because we know
it already the information is
out there
and no one's gonna take anything
seriously and and I'm sorry
Cuomo or each team made a
horrible
mistake and we have to
acknowledge it
and move on and mark it down as
something we won't do in the
future
right next to don't open up the
Hair
Salons 48 hours before they
know I mean
come on this is this is a
learning
moment I'm sorry people died
this
doesn't help the Trump clock
that's
gotta go well that's really
this is
really sick then
oh so what so what you're
saying is in
order to get a Trump I can now
deduce
this just what you are implying
is Trump
is hated so much we have to up
the
people dead who do we have um
fuck it
how about those old people send
some
kovat over there that's what
you're
saying yeah
well if that's true then god
save the
Republic well it's gonna need
saving the
way these guys are operating
now you're
being facetious you don't
really think
that's true
oh not completely facetious I'm
skeptical Wow I know nobody
pologize and
that's not gonna happen but
it's also
good to know that most people
really are
not at a huge risk of dying it's
interesting I had this is you
and we
talked about it on the show and
and
Sunday after the show I wish
you'd take
it a picture and posted it it
was ugly
Sunday after the show I get
email after
email after text message doo
doo doo
dude this is this is this how
it starts
for some people infected I I
got Agent
Orange who was down for 10 days
he says
oh it started with me with an
infected
eyelid and then the runny nose
and then
the cough and then I was out
for 10 days
and and one after the other I'm
like oh
my god how what poetic justice
to give
me the rona so of course the
eye passes
but then last night what it's
like after
dinners like 7:15 7:30 and
we're outside
drinking a coffee and all of a
sudden my
nose starts running like crazy
like
crazy the power of suggestion
ladies in
general well and you know what
I did
against that for the power
suggestion ID
I thought to myself what would
jcd do so
I immediately went and grabbed
fifty
fifty thousand mega mega Bork's
of
vitamin D Tamara that shit down
it's
gone I am NOT dripping from the
nose so
I don't know what
but I feel good could have been
they
might have been right it's a
good thing
you jumped on the d3i
it WWJ CD came we came right
right you
got a doctor
you are not a doctor but I was
very
happy very happy it is there I
think I
had to say I had a similar not
a eyeball
thing followed by that but I
thought I
could was catching something
during the
era that JC buzzkill jr. had he
did have
it
and apparently Jesse had a
diversion
where you lost your sense of
smell yes
I've heard that heard this too
during
that little period I was
catching
something and it was like that
this is a
dis and it was weird too it
wasn't like
the normal kind of like oh I
think I'm
getting a cold I'm getting the
flu or
something and I just said I'm
just
taking the DI / - take some d3
and it
was going that was the end of
that and
it was all over we'll see the
it down
the road if you have antibodies
anyway
let's go - ok I think we're
over with
that load segment let's talk
with about
the Florida and Georgia thing
which is
what I wanted to discuss him it
initially yeah that was the
initial idea
the two states that opened up
first
Florida and Georgia both are
continuing
to see declines and kovat
infections
while shocking the liberal
haters but
not to you because we told you
that the
virus was probably weakening
and that
people would innovate to stay
safe
innovate wow she's mean I don't
know
what she means you know
innovating is
six feet apart or who knows
whatever how
in the case nobody is
discussing the the
you know it that went Georgian
more than
Florida yes they they were they
busted
wide open so what's going on
everything's fine and everybody
jumped
all over him said the Republican
governor cuz you know Stacey
Abrams
wouldn't have done this no lost
up in
the Bay State yeah I mean the
basement
you'd be still yeah a Stacey
Abrams
would never make a mistake like
that but
otherwise I guess it's just
fabulous
then well well the whole this
is just as
getting more enjoy the promises
now
this is a new world order I you
knowed
amazing Polly found some
documents
saying this whole thing was a
test
[Music]
mazing paulien is amazing so
amazing
Polly does this thing and it's
and by
the way if you got the last
news there's
a link in there still up it
won't be up
forever no because the people
see this
and they there's nothing in
there that's
inaccurate she's just taking
from
professional documents you know
and
showing them and but they find
ways to
go oh no no this is bad it's a
bad
influence on the done the
youngins or
something I don't know why they
take her
down well the beauty of it all
is that
in certainly in the United
States not so
in other countries but in the
United
States it is all voluntary I
mean we
have a court case after court
cases
being struck down against
people are
being arrested etc so it is
really up to
us and and that's it's actually
much
bigger and much more
frightening to me
that we have this social
control of
shaming shaming yeah it truly
is shaming
let me just just because we're
still on
opening up and stuff I have two
clips
about California because it's
very
confusing
is California open is a closed
mayor
Garcetti the Garcetti of Los
Angeles
County has extended these stay
at home
order through August but what
does that
mean but it's not would they
stay at
home orders they know you're
top health
officials said yes they expect
us to
extend the orders for another
three
months but explain exactly what
that
means sure I think we have to
all
recognize that we're not moving
to earn
cope at 19 we're learning to
live with
it
it's important not to overreact
but it's
important to take this serious
because
it is as dangerous today as it
was the
first day that it arrived in
our cities
in our country so quite frankly
there's
no so-called open state or open
country
that doesn't continue to have
health
orders telling us to cover our
faces
physically distance and to tell
people
that your safest working from
and
staying at home that's all that
the
County Health Director was
saying and we
can't expect that to disappear
in a
matter of weeks or even a few
months
the same time we're learning a
lot of
really important lessons about
how to
safely reopen sectors and
places and we
have to assess each of those
steps give
three or four weeks time to see
is there
any additional spread are we
endangering
more people and how can we keep
our most
vulnerable safe so we are
learning to
live with it at the same moment
that we
are also learning the lessons
of how to
do this so I believe that that
he also
recognizes he has absolutely no
power to
tell people or to keep people
at home
they're just using new world
order terms
now stay at home order doesn't
mean you
have to stay at home because
they can't
actually enforce it it's a
trick it's a
mind-control well we're
learning to deal
with it stay at home you know
it's
learning to deal with it we're
learning
here know you're mind
controlling people
into feeling unsafe and afraid
of other
people and so the restaurants
like Texas
open up with spread out and I
think it's
25% capacity max for the next
foreseeable whatever and then in
California I will say here's
some of
your innovation all right what
do we got
here we've got oh look at look
at this
look closely at this that's a
restaurant
that's using mannequins to fill
out the
half-empty dining room what's
the story
behind this one ash because it
looks so
crappy they're putting
mannequins at the
other table so the restaurant
looks more
fun and full instead of actual
people
smoke and mirrors out there
la-la-land
Wow yeah yeah so it's what's
got that
kind of money those things
aren't cheap
those good mannequins who's got
it you
can't you can't run a
restaurant at 25%
capacity you can't run it at 50
literacy
you can't run it you can't it's
crazy
what you don't the shaming
thing let's
get back to the shaming okay
this is
interesting it's just like the
whole
thing it's like there and it's
the
Democrats that are the shamers
cuz the
Democrats to the streamers
let's just be
honest about it
no no but even Johanna was she
recognized that and setage is
I'd never
expected this kind of shaming
from
liberals shame shame shame on
you
yeah which of course ventually
show
tries to become shame on you
for voting
for Trump shame on you for
being a
republic yes if you vote for
Trump
you're voting for the virus you
vote for
Democrats strategy all over
that meme
vote for Trump is a vote for
the virus
gentlemen that was $100,000
idea and two
points of all the media Buy
damn it damn it damn it damn it
should
have known better
so what is going to what's
weird because
the testing is now has been
kind of it's
not really in the conversation
at the
moment it's going to glide well
now it
not not the way it was but it's
going to
come roaring back because China
just
made their move I think I think
this is
a move against Trump and Shi
Jing P says
the CCP will be testing 14
million
people in Wuhan in ten days time
fourteen million drop has been
showing
this chart
oh yeah not that this is an
information
war and China is saying huh
look at you
with your stupid orange man
over there
we're going to test fourteen
million
people in Wuhan
in ten days which means you've
got about
15 the FF that's 900 tests a
minute for
24 hours a day for 10 days so I
don't
know what kind of army and if
they're
gonna go into people's homes
and rouse
to them or how they're gonna
get that
done in 10 days stick a probe
up them
but but the whole but this
whole thing
is isn't it I don't think it's
true it
may well be but I'd be
surprised it's to
make China look like they're
that
they're the boss they're doing
it the
best way this is the way to go
world
health world health
organization we know
what's up Trump bad bad bad bad
it's not
going to end with this testing
which is
it's like the ultimate we
cannot go back
to work we cannot fully
function until
we test everybody every day
five times a
day and we had a vaccine huh
the irony
that the testing is the obvious
which is
that the more you test the more
cases
you uncover because most people
don't
have symptoms and never will
yeah so you
have and so that makes the
numbers go up
and then that numbers go up and
makes
you need for more testing which
means
the numbers go up even more and
then we
got to stay at home longer cuz
there's
more numbers as sewers to surge
more cases what are we gonna do
we're
all gonna die I'd like to do a
quick
review of the three trillion
dollar
package that the Democrat Party
announced to be discussed be
we're
always introduced into the
house because
I read it it wasn't hard to do
because I
well okay I want you can you do
that
after I give to play two clips
namely
Amy's take on it yeah
definitely Trump's
a rebuttal yeah definitely okay
where
are we well I guess it's just
not my day
but this
let's try the big confab maybe
that's
the one that's got the stuff
about the
bill Republican Rand Paul of
Kentucky
the first senator knows no no
no that's
can't be it
loser relief bill promoted by
DN n DN is
that it DNA yeah that's
apparently it on
Capitol Hill House Democratic
leaders
have unveiled
don't be so damn creative with
your
titles because it's messing up
the
workflow to war loser relief
bill
promoted by DN odd I mean
that's a title
man that is a damn title right
there on
Capitol Hill House Democratic
leaders
have unveiled a massive
eighteen hundred
page coronavirus relief package
worth
three trillion dollars the
so-called
heroes Act would fund expanded
unemployment benefits through
January
2021 send most US adults another
one-time twelve hundred dollar
stimulus
check and provide one trillion
dollars
and assistance to hard-hit
state local
and tribal governments it would
also
expand snap food benefits fund
hazard
pay for frontline workers
increased
funding for kovat nineteen
testing and
provide twenty five dollars in
funding
to the u.s. postal service the
bill
would not expand Medicare to
cover
millions of newly uninsured
Americans
nor does it provide for rent and
mortgage relief or recurring
cash
payments in US households the
bill would
expand the paycheck protection
program
to bail out corporate lobbyists
firms
climate activists say the bill
fails to
close loopholes for big
polluters
Greenpeace USA tweeted quote
fossil fuel
CEOs will be rejoicing that
Congress has
once again left the door wide
open for
handouts to struggling
mismanaged oil
and gas corporations this was a
slanted
report as if this bill was a
corrupt
bill to protect polluters you
know it is
a crap I just want to respond
to Monday
Trump's response this is just
one thing
before it before I forget
the lobbyist thing IIIi I just
need to I
just need to because that was I
was I
said listen to how she reported
that
because it was it was really
lame what
she did there hold on provide
for rent
and mortgage relief or
recurring cash
payments to US households the
bill would
expand the Paycheck protection
program
to bail out corporate lobbyists
firms
okay so to say that because it
doesn't I
read this thing to my knowledge
nowhere in the bill does it say
oh
here's a special provision for
corporate
lobbying firms that is not
reporting
what Amy did there that is
editorializing because there is
a a joke
now going around in DC that the
lobbying
group that represents lobbyists
has said
they need payroll Protection
Act money
otherwise they can't help
Washington
write very bills they're voting
on so
it's a circular thing that they
want
they want money from the bill
they
helped right so they can
continue to
write bills but there's nothing
in that
bill that says it's going to
help
lobbying firms but you yeah so
I don't
know why because it's really a
slam
against Pelosi I'm not sure why
why she
would I would think she would
be all in
but maybe that's how you make
it seem
balanced she twist the story in
such a
way that as though that the
Republicans
had some input in this doll
their fault
well believe me the the
Republican Party
I see on the hill it had no
hand in this
all right well here's what
Trump this is
Trump on the Pelosi bill
it suggests that depends and
certainly
not the package size so today
basically
if you look at that package
what they
want more than anything else is
it's a
voting package they want to be
able to
make sure that Republicans
can't win an
election by putting it all
sorts of
mailing ballots now that's the
problem
with mail-in ballots are they
going to
dump a whole pile of ballots on
your
desk just before the election
so the
problem with the mail-in
ballots is
subject to tremendous corruption
tremendous corruption cheating
so I'm
against it and if you look at
the bill
that Nancy Pelosi is putting in
it has a
lot to do with elections and
then we're
not gonna we're not gonna lose
elections
because of that I don't find
that to be
true
I don't think Trump's truthful
either I
mean I went through this bill I
reviewed
several different reviews of
the bill
because there's a lot of
legalese is it
what this is it's really and
it's
typical it's an omnibus bill so
if they
take a whole bunch of stuff
that's been
waiting around has been sitting
you know
it's been in the process been in
committee it's you know it's
different
people's important little bills
it's like sweeping up the mess
and yes
and they put it all together
into this
huge bill and therefore it's
disjointed
the only way it flows together
is by
continuously saying we're going
to get
to an example 25 billion
dollars to the
United States Postal Service to
help
combat the corona virus in
kovat 19 you
understand how they do it so
it's just 1
billion dollars to the No
Agenda show to
help combat coronavirus in
kovin 19 if
only so a lot of existing bills
wrapped
into one
almost every Inspector General
gets a
little extra an extra budget
usually it
from a million to several
million so
that they can accurately have
oversight
and investigate any misdoings
with the
money which is meant to
investigate and
to support and combat the to
combat
coronavirus and covert 19 a
hundred
million dollars and by the way
these
numbers you realize like out a
million
here 500 million here truly
nothing we
were talking trillions a
thousand
billion
so much money so a hundred
million to
violence against women and other
domestic abuse victims community
oriented policing which I I
love it
sounds like something I want a
part of
300 million there are state
bailouts to
compensate for revenue
shortfall five
hundred and forty billion
sounds about
right that's where that's what
New York
California and an Illinois need
so
that's in there twenty five
billion as I
said to the United States
Postal Service
couple of billion for some work
programs
every single Department gets a
top-up
you know at you need some money
thirty
million extra for you to combat
coronavirus and Cova nineteen
godly the
Ryan White hiv/aids boy
for covert nineteen I don't
know why
exactly but they turn around
and give
half a billion to the niaD or
NIAID
which is foul cheese group he
gets five
hundred million dollars dude
you know to
combat coronavirus seven
billion for
states child care services
ninety
billion for schools
then there's the Student Loan
Forgiveness up to ten thousand
dollars
and of course there's a twelve
another
second stimulus check of twelve
hundred
dollars and extension of
unemployment
benefits infrastructure oh boy
they put
it in there fifteen billion
dollars for
highways which is like no
that's nothing
but they did add another 15
billion
reserved for overrun because
that's how
the government works you know
it might
be double that one hundred
billion
dollars one hundred billion
dollars for
rental assistance I don't know
what Judy
read but it's right there in the
document a hundred billion
dollars for
what that would Amy Amy
11 billion assistance for the
homeless
well what was she reading
everything
you're saying here is an envier
had
nothing to do with her
interpretation I
don't know I'm I'm just telling
you what
I saw eleven billion for the
homeless
assistance which interestingly
interestingly was not worded as
people
experiencing homelessness it
was just
homeless assistance and then
they shored
up the language around relief
funds so
the stimulus of the SBA loans
who can
have it who can't and I think
this is
the big point that you know if
you
listen to Tucker Carlson which
I did not
clip give the money to illegals
so it's
not a good enough you don't
need to clip
no sounds just like it nowhere
in this
document does it say that but
remember
this is the heroes Act so the
heroes Act
wants to honor the heroes and
the heroes
try to give again that's called
the
heroes act right and the heroes
include
people who are what is the term
what
kind of workers do we have
right now we
have what we have essential and
non-essential yeah so grocery
store
checkout clerks and write
heroes and as
we have discussed many times in
the past
in the United States if you are
living
here illegally you're
undocumented if
you have a job construction
domestic
work restaurant kitchen you can
obtain
from the IRS at ein a tax payer
information number and you can
pay taxes
every single month or every two
weeks
and you it's completely legit
so you're
not committing tax fraud even
though you
here illegally and don't have
all your
other papers in order and of
course
there's no payroll to a bunch
of things
that don't work but this has
been
accepted behavior for decades
as long as
you pay your taxes in America
it's okay
so what they specified in this
bill is
how anybody should be eligible
for
relief funds retro actively as
long as
they have a taxpayer
identification
number so you don't have to be
here
legally and in addition to that
essential workers cannot be
deported
they need to be protected these
heroes
because they work in kitchens
they work
and clean up etc and that's
quite a lot
of people a lot of heroes who
are here
illegally and work in those
jobs and are
thus considered essential while
illegal
and that is it's an amnesty
because once
you know if it's like hey during
coronavirus you can't deport
people who
work in kitchens or work in
cleaning
services or etc it's quite
broad the
podcasters are also essential
personnel
literally stated podcasting so
that
casting is actually mentioned
in the
bill yes yeah no no no no no
not this
one in the one in the original
from the
federal government under media
services
under media services the
original bill
or the original recommendation
because
now there's no bill that's sure
that
yeah I am because I put it in
the show
notes I remember these things
well I'd
like to see it Oh God
right after I have you saying
it's just
that seems unusual okay I've
only said
put in one document and that
was the Los
Angeles County Health
Department's yeah
I'll get it for you so anyway
that is of
course a non-starter because
it's a
sneaky way of providing some
form of
amnesty and until coronavirus
is over
which it never will be then
these people
could not be deported or could
not be
you know dealt with as illegals
but
that's an interesting trick
it's a well
the Tucker's right but then but
it's not
entirely truth he says it so
then there
are payroll tax cuts for
corporations
who have employees working
during the
pandemic and then all of a
sudden a
whole telecom section no price
gouging
rules there will be much money
for free
Wi-Fi at and around schools and
libraries emergency broadband
for those
who cannot afford it and if you
can't
afford any kind of phone or any
kind of
device we've got the new Obama
phone and
it's a they call it the enhanced
lifeline
with 4G LTE yeah you got a 4G
LTE Trump
exactly
Corona phone and all of a
sudden in
there this is how it's so
obvious that
this is just a bill stuck
together by
other bills there's a heading
that says
don't break the t band and I'm
like what
what is this it's clearly a
slogan yes
it is the repeal of the t band
auction
for telephony that's very
important for
coronavirus obviously and
whatever
lobbyists from the
telecommunications
industry who put that in there
with the
existing headline don't break
the t band
that that was really the for me
that's
pretty sloppy to build I was
like okay
this is horrible it's sloppy I
mean of
course Trump already said it's
DOA and
the Republicans aren't gonna
vote for a
new I know so they gotta have
the reeds
do it but what if this is this
bad right
off the bat and they're gonna
massage a
little bit could could it get
worse cuz
eventually something's gonna
get passed
well let's listen to Pelosi on
Tapper
just you can get when get into
her head
she's wearing her little
kerchief around
her reptilian neck I can say
that
because I don't like lavage
she's
wearing a balk loes not a balk
Lavazza
crew chief chief and the fact
is that in
all four the bills that have
passed
before they've all been
bipartisan and
we've all in our caucus have
agreed that
everything is coronavirus
centric and
also in a timely way that
relates to the
virus it's too deadly to our
lives to
our livelihood to our democracy
for us
to use it for any other purpose
so when
the money for state and local
is to lay
the cost of the defray the cost
of the
outlets they've made for
coronavirus and
the revenue lost because of the
corona
virus testing testing with
three pillars
I honor are here this is very
interesting listen to how she
doesn't
she doesn't really care about
anything
but power and yes did you
notice that
she was about to say yes that's
why I
think testing that's why I
stopped it
she's about to say a number of
thing
here which he just listened to
what
she's really saying and you
tell me if
she's concerned about the virus
or about
her position and party and a
and well
man bad the coronavirus testing
testing
the three pillars okay the
three pillars
I thought it's gonna be testing
testing
testing but the three pillars
oh no it's
very different honor our heroes
by
supporting our state and local
entities
honor our heroes so that they
don't lose
their jobs these heroes don't
lose their
jobs open up how about opening
up the
hospitals for other things
Nancy instead
of Oh honor them what does it
mean how
do I honor our heroes so they
don't lose
their jobs what can I do with my
honoring them how will that how
will
that possibly help these heroes
don't
lose their jobs open up
government by
testing tracing treatment etc
testing
wait a minute so the most
important
question we have this is the
most
powerful woman in American
politics how
do we open up our states I want
to know
opening up my state here in
Texas what
do I need to do again Nancy
don't lose
their job open up government by
testing
tracing a treatment etc testing
tracing
treatment etc
yep that's worse than Trump's
plan it's
not maybe it's just me and the
third is
putting money in the pockets of
American
people all of the time - and
Centrex to
the coronavirus we would be an
endless
amount of money if we put our
wish list
for the future in there but
that is not
what the case is and sometimes
I get a
little heat for my own folks
who say why
can we do this in this bill and
that in
the bus because that's not what
the bill
is about this bill is for this
purpose
and it's a big price but it's a
big
problem and as chairman of the
Fed said
think big because the interest
rates
will never be lower and so we
are
they've used the interest rates
now here
here it is this is where she
goes into
full on partisan mode she said
well the
secretary said interest rate
too low
will never be lower and so we
are
they've used the interest rates
to give
confidence that credit will be
available
because the interest rates are
low we
want those same interest rates
and they
use it to bolster the stock
market we
want to use it to bolster the
American
people oh so true Nancy this
woman is
horrible and it leads me to
another
horrible individual and only
because you
were talking about the Irish
helicopter
money with yes yeah sorry did
you find
this story - throwing money out
knife
I found another helicopter from
the
mooch Anthony are they doing
too much or
too little well I think they
need more
helicopter money to be handed I
mean I
we did that analysis it's about
three
thousand dollars a person and
fifteen
hundred dollars for a child and
they're
offering of twelve hundred and
five
hundred respectfully so yes I
think they
need to put up more helicopter
money
they just injected or they're
gonna pass
state orders fifty billion
dollar
additional small business
stimulus and I
predict that they will send more
helicopter money out to the
average
American this will be a Main
Street and
Wall Street recovery program
helicopter
money helicopter money
helicopter money
I guess that should be
a show title one day a mangies
helicopter money was using the
term but
maybe he has a helicopter and
wants to
throw some cash out I don't
think I
don't think I've ever that I've
heard
the term but I it's like
helicopter
parents the parents aren't
actually
flying in a helicopter above
the kid
well I did because I had a
helicopter
but that's hovering around I
actually
did that okay so we've done the
bailouts
excuse me well beside before
you go on
because Pelosi did say
something there
mm-hmm on the interest rates
will never
get lower let's play another
Trump clip
from his when his little
meeting there
and Trump on negative interest
rates
that he wasn't interested in the
bringing interest rates
negative and
that you saw a need for
additional
stimulus from Congress I know
that you
said we could wait to see on
stimulus
that you you want negative
rates lalala
believer and negative rates
only if
other countries that are
competitors
with Germany feared allied
they're
friends of ours but there's
still
competitors on trade and other
things so
Germany Japan others have
negative rates
that I think if they do we're
the most
prime of the world you know
where it's
based many countries based on
the dollar
the dollar is by far the
strongest most
powerful currency in the world
we've
made it more powerful we've
made it
stronger and certainly if
they're gonna
have the advantage of negative
rates we
should too
I feel strongly we should have
negative
rates negative rates is
basically where
they pay you interest if you
borrow
money this is a new one I've
been
looking for something like that
all my
life that's a pretty good one
but
certainly if other countries
are going
to be paying for putting out
money I
mean they think of it they're
borrowing
money or instead of paying
interest they
getting paid
it's the craziest thing but you
know
what other countries are doing
it look
at Germany look at Japan look
at others
and with the most Prime in the
world
right now and we have this we
have the
currency and we have we have
the power
of the dollar Wow Wow just step
the hell
back and take this one so Trump
is all
in on the negative interest
rates well
there you go anyone he wants it
Oh
doesn't want it Paulo she's
full of shit
when she says it won't go any
lower the
right the end is near oh my god
so well
of course from his perspective
we're not
competitive with our rate so we
we have
to go to negative interest
rates whoo
that's gonna be fun and all of
this a
mere day or two before the
Bitcoin
happening oh my goodness what
is gonna
happen in the world you know
bitcoins
gonna go to $400,000 in the
next month
or two so I'm just saying huh
yeah
according to Max you know you
getting
cash a coin and it quit the
show me
meanwhile what and give up show
business
yeah I know
meanwhile the European Union is
in such
disarray over over Germany
because
Germany I think the European
Union is
now kind of realizing that
Germany
actually runs the show and
there's the
new German Republic the new
German
Empire they finally figured
this out we
even though the Brits have been
telling
him this forever it's yes and
they're
very some Peretz some Brits
have noticed
it but yeah we've noticed it
yeah very
very dismayed over how things
are going
financially in the European
Union hmm
well what's the French figure
it out
then war yeah yeah you're not
kidding
just a little update you have
been
working a lot on my on my
computer setup
that would pretty much all
command line
now so I also took the time to
there
well
you know what in act of the
future I
have decided that computers are
first of
all they're just getting lower
throughput into from you to the
machine
and back I mean that's is why
we have
pads and touch and please don't
actually
do anything you can't get the
computer
do anything unless you unless
you go to
a system that lets you program
your apps
and string them together
yourself it
doesn't matter I wanted to get
rid of
the contactless thermometer
spam because
I what okay I keep receiving
emails
which is spam for contactless
thermometers you know the ones
which you
cannot find if you want to go
buy one at
the at the skew you know a CVS
or
anywhere I mean all
thermometers are
sold out so this spam is all
over the
place and it keeps getting
through the
spam filter I've never gotten
one of
these things ever well I'll
never get
one ever again because the word
thermometer is the one and only
word
band now but I figured out what
they're
doing they reverse engineer
Bayesian
logic in the body of the message
so the subject line they
literally say
contactless thermometer you
need it now
or something like that and then
in the
body of the message they've
they have
these sentences strung together
which
will always include my first
name and
maybe a topic of interest to me
which I
think they probably got from
you maybe
is on a forum or from Twitter or
something and they scrape stuff
and
through that they literally go
against
the Bayesian logic that would
determine
that to be spam by putting these
elements in and the spam
detector just
can't stop it it's you know who
those
guys should be advertising for
real
products because they know what
they're
doing it's very interesting
well I'm
drove you to go command line no
I'm told
I'm totally command line it's
actually
I'm hjkl that's where I live
okay I live in H you know what
hjkl is
no I don't know what hjkl is
the HJ Kel
and K and L keys on the
keyboard are the
universal keys for navigation
on command
line so H is left J is down k
is up L is
right and this is an old word
star o
what it's the VI works that way
but also
if you go to the if you go to
Twitter
just the web Twitter and you go
to just
what doesn't matter what it is
hit the J
key it'll go down hit the K key
it'll go
up hit the L key it'll like
that that
tweet hit the the T key it'll
do a
retweet so this is this has been
something that that's that
efficient
data engineers have been doing
for a
long time they do for a living
to have
to sit the keyboard they got to
get
things done and as it turns out
this is
what I do for a living I sit at
the
keyboard all day managing data
managing
emails managing RSS feeds
stories managing clips
exactly exactly why I did it
I'd like to
talk about the brain what do
you think
no no I think we should do a
quick thing
on China and then we'll take a
break
Dutch way to China afterwards I
like
China well it sounds like
you've got
some China well then we'll take
a break
got really got no China that's
the
reason oh so you just don't
want me to
do China maybe I get no no you
know what
never mind we will go into a
break all
right you have a China clip
yeah we're
gonna do that after the break
but before
we do that I do need to play
this clip
you've got to ask yourself what
level
has John McAfee sunk to if he's
doing
interviews on the Nick the rat
show
clearly clearly unawares of
the knick the rats show is hey
wait a
minute hold on stop hey wait so
you get
a phone - hi would you like to
do my
show what's it cause - Nick the
rat show
and he's oblivious to the name
of the
show itself so much so that he
doesn't
figure out what's going on I
mean even
listen to an old show John is
gonna
sewer junks in a sewer during a
show
john mcafee it does an
interview with
anybody any buddy regardless of
who you
are where you are audience
sighs it
doesn't matter which is one of
the
reasons why I have no interest
in
speaking with him because he's
already
been everywhere but I think
that Nick
the rat deserves a
Congressional Medal
Medal of Honor for asking the
following
question time for one more
question okay
one more question last question
is uh
the do you know John C Dvorak
used to
write for PC Mac I'm sorry this
is not
safe for work and I'm not in
the habit
of bleeping it out but it's not
safe for
work you have been warned is he
parent
Lee you owe him a lunch
nonsense that
mother fucker owes me way more
than a
goddamn lunch every time he
brings you
up he's like John McAfee he
owned he
owes me a lunch and but I was
wondering
fuck that shit he owes me a good
articles thank you so much
interview
ends of course after that after
that
fabulous question of course but
you know
I've heard this because Nick
sent me a
copy of course and I thought to
myself
first of all is dinner yeah I
know I
know this is this is that was
irksome
yep and McAfee is full of crap
well what
is this you owe him a good
article what
it what kind of nuisance side
gigs you
running Dvorak I'm not running
anything
that he just throws that in he
doesn't
need what okay I'll give you a
good
article here I'll mail it to
you I think
I think you should do an
article about
how McAfee is overexposed on
low-level
podcasts not including Nick the
rat by
the way
I have not written about john
mcafee
since he was doing he says he
created
the entire virus environment in
con
computers it was pretty much
more
abundant ill he popularized it
he made
he popularized it for all
practical
purpose of course he did it was
abandoned he was a Superbrand
McAfee was
I mean he first he created the
idea of
virus and then he created
viruses to
sell virus software didn't he
is that
how it worked well we don't
know that he
created but some suspicious he
retired
rich because he sold off his
whole
company that he spent all his
money yeah
but literally on hookers and
blow which
is kind of but he a boss he I
guess he
when he says I do I
automatically cuz
I'm thinking he feels that he's
done so
many spectacular things not to
say that
he hasn't because he's
definitely been a
newsworthy guy and I should
have written
something about it yes that's
true
that's what I think he's
thinking but
hey you know Mac if he gets
plenty of
ink I just doesn't I don't know
what
good it's doing I would like I
would
just like anybody just someone
who's
never done a podcast just to
contact
McAfee and say I want you to do
a bug
hit just make up a crazy name
and see if
he shows up well you could
actually I
bet you could do this and then
you could
actually get an interview say I
am going
to inaugurate a new podcast
call me
whatever you want to call it
called the
John McAfee John I really don't
care
but I think what he would Joey
would do
it I am very proud of our very
own Nick
the rat you can hear Nick the
rat
Wednesday evenings he broadcast
live
from the sewer and of course
you can
often hear his show on No
Agenda stream
calm where we have all these
crazy
people including ourselves and
trolls
and all kinds of fun and
without I'd
like to thank you for your
courage and
say in the morning to you the
man who
put the C in the China clip
block John C
Dvorak well in the morning you
mr. Adam
curry also in the morning to
all the
ships to see boots on the
ground feet in
the air subs in the water and
all the
day miss tonight's up in the
morning to
the trolls mentioned them just
a moment
ago let's do a quick troll
count see how
we're doing
we're low today 1550 usual like
16 1700
leveling off it is while people
are
going back to work I think or
have other
things it's you know Thursday
people
have other things to do now
yeah they
shouldn't be listen to old wives
seriously you must have to get
a live
stream and get the internet
while your
drew while you're driving you
can
probably put it on your car
because kind
of a fun saying true the trolls
hang out
at no agenda stream calm that
we have a
chat there which is 24/7 is IRC
you can
log in all kinds of different
ways even
on the go you can talk to the
trolls
troll away and we also as
simultaneously
listen to 24 hours a day seven
days a
week
of the no agenda stream podcast
from all
around the globe all talk no
commercials
completely devoid and free of
commercial
interests therefore probably
stunningly
fun to be a reminder that you
can get an
invite for no agenda social
calm our
node of the federation of the
true
social network of the internet
the
federated mastodons servers
we'd love to
see you there and of course you
don't
have to sign up you can also
just follow
any of the people at No Agenda
no sign
up just show up no agenda
social calm
and you can follow me no agenda
social
calm also begin the morning to
our
artist for episode number or
rule to
1241 we titled that one Curtin
Wranglers
and it was good to see
caesium-137 back
back again and with a typical
caesium-137 classic piece of
art so well
put together the Chinese
McDonald's
french fries the fries are
hypodermic
needles we've got a little what
was the
goofy oh the Microsoft Bob yeah
my
yourself Bob from the
background and a
unique font it was it was a
beautiful
piece did we did we look at
other things
we look at yes we did we looked
at its
competitor as a competitor to
it that we
looked at and this was the one
that had
back
scenes with a big sea anenome
get the
ugly mcdonald's and that was
done but
where the that was done by
nicked a rat
actually coincidentally that he
came in
later I think we'd already
chose I'm
looking now let's see what
maybe he may
have but but the thing is Nick
and then
Twitter said that that I know
he came in
earlier actually then cesium
cesium came
in late right I see it no yeah
and so he
says well I Nick who had me
smeared on
his show says on Twitter that I
was
proud I not you as though I'm
picking
the art is just not true
believe me we
both picked the art and we
argue about
it he says that I specifically
was
afraid of the clown and then
it's
created the threat of John's
afraid of
clowns memes oh boy that must
have kept
you busy for an afternoon no I
just
blocked I saw the threat of
comic strip
blogger of being blocked by you
that was
pretty funny
which one exactly
he was just complaining that
you that
you blocked him and he and his
is even
though you literally said why
you
blocked him he say yeah it's
because I
doesn't want me to ask if his
mother is
polish as Porter's passport
like twice my mother is polish
your
mother's not even with us she's
dead
she's sorry but she did lately
she got
to eight ninety which is kind
of a go
that's not bad it's not bad not
bad it's
not bad it's not great it's not
like
that woman in Pennsylvania the
transgender woman has got the
mom 95 and
according to her is genius even
that's
95 anyway I just wanted yeah
and would
you explain it very well he's a
back-channel because and it
spit and
then and it's true because he
had he
sent me a message back channel
DM asked
of Iraq about as my reporters
Pat hot
meanwhile he's asking you the
same thing
and you're blocking him for it
so it's
like I hate don't like that
don't do
that that's what that's
when my daughter used to do
that daddy
can I have this and then you
know me
meanwhile already has gone to
mom and
gotten some kind of you know
did tricky
yeah it's a double dipping hold
it now
not that we don't love him
she's man I
that's good work save this oh
my god
someone sent me oh I think I I
probably
wanted I not someone said the
old comic
strip blogger jingle but I don't
remember what I did with it
well you'll
find it let's start let me let
me read
off so here it is here it is
okay this
should be it comic strip it's
not like
we don't have jingles form and
stuff wow
it's pretty official
well let's talk about something
that's
more official which is
Christopher Barry
coming in with $1,000 and from
Williamsville New York I'm
sorry I just
like to thank
cesium-137 one more time no
agenda art
generator calm and is this an
instant
knighting for Christopher Barry
Oh looks
like it since it's in blue code
blue
I think we have
our instant light sound ITM
Jensi rice a
long time Lister five hundred
cents to
five hundred first-time donor
like to be
known as sir end or not wave
bender of
spark okay
he needs a D douching right
hold on
getting the douche up and the
douche
sausage you've been deduced he
says we
both rock and he'd like a
little goat
karma you might die with the
simultaneous two to the head oh
I think
we can do that you might die
you've got
all right did he have any Vizio
name-brand or not did nothing
for the
round table though right no
orders nope
doesn't seem so okay good
Harvey Smith
harvey Smith's next on the list
at 345
dollars and 67 cents from
Cambridge
Massachusetts
seems the US government has
stimulated
me into making this value for
value
purchase yes you got a check in
the mail
and we recommend everybody take
some of
that free money and send it our
way
no jingles with some great
general-purpose go car would be
lovely
thanks for all you do
you've got followed by Jeff
Anderson of
Carmel Indiana $333 ITM John
and Adam
thank you for a great show has
changed
how I view everything I used to
be a
rabid Republican beholden to
the daily
infotainment cycle and I until
a high
school friend mentioned your
show this
is a good yeah by the way thank
you
mother
yes a lot of Republicans were
dead
listen to the show we have
Democrats and
Republican Republican is a good
a good
describing Republicans and they
tend to
listen to Alex Jones it's Fox
and then
that was that Hannity Hannity
Hannity we
had one for a second last night
it's all
they the New York toilet paper
times
which I thought he
he says it over and over I have
said
this before he has got to be
the hardest
working guy in show business it
shows
its mediocre he took over where
James
Brown left off the only thing
is I the
whole show the Washington
toilet-paper
times but I thought what's
funny is the
either the Washington compost
that one I
hadn't heard I thought that was
funny oh
yeah he's I think mark I think
mark well
anyway it's tiresome if you do
it if you
do it over and over again it's
like what
do you do i compost he's bad is
another
one anyway he goes on he says
until a
high school friend mentioned
your show
since that time have been
happily taken
my truth vaccine twice weekly
will
forever be free from any future
amygdala
swelling that's true I would
like to
call out David Brantley who hit
me in
the mouth as a douche bag Andrew
Williams as a douche bag I do
not
believe they have ever donated
no I
would also like to be deduced
you've got
it you've been deduced I want
to mention
a little just a little
housekeeping here
to the donors that like to
douche people
and deduce themselves I believe
cosmically it's quite likely
that ad
douching after calling out
people for
being a douche bag doesn't
deduce you
but possibly D douches the
douche bags
do we have any empirical
evidence for
just anecdotal I just totally
anecdotal
hmm and I get from sources I
got it from
sources or syllogism Illya with
the
matter and intelligence sources
agree so
I the intelligence community the
intelligence community they all
agree on
this according to sources yes
so put
your D douching up front up
front just
for your own safety
what can I hurt anyway Nugent
no jingoes
no karma yet as I do not
believe I have
earned them you
well Jeff thank you Jeff thank
you very
much thank you for your courage
Jonathan Fodor ik in
Westminister
California another 333 which 0
0 first
off I want to thank you for the
priceless information it has
been
essential for my mental health
can I
please get a D douching I would
like to
call it my smoking hot babe
Liana for
being a douchebag
as well as my friend Brandon
douchebag
ok I have another piece of
housekeeping
here ok I'm noticing a trend
for men and
women both to use this exact
same term
smoking hot right I am I'm just
requesting personally that
somebody
dream up another term
indicating a
similar concept though because
I'm kind
of tired of it I don't know
about you
patience pay people supporting
the show
you're doing it wrong I
recently had the
abbot antibody test done
Oh from admin Lazarus right
right right
unfortunately I tested negative
I was
really hoping to boost my No
Agenda
antibodies match your fraud it
looks
like I'll be a fraud for now
this brings
me to the question by the way
there was
a report it might have it on my
clipless
that there's like 40% of these
things
are faulty faulty faulty I have
one data
point that's fun from our
official No
Agenda pharmacist the he sent
me a
report it's a it's a
pharmaceutical
industry report the serology
testing do
you know how big that business
is or
will be billions 65 billion Wow
billion for for swabbing
swabbing and
testing beautiful it's probably
a lot of
blood tests counting in yeah
well
whatever
there's no serology serology
Oh miss you know serology and
got the
includes blood testing kill
ma'am wrong
who cares there's a lot of
money someone
gets the antibodies and tests
and tests
positive does this positive
test get
added to the daily confirmed
new corona
virus I hope would hope so I was
supposed to isn't it
that would obviously be a major
discrepancy but considering how
problematic the date has been I
would
not be surprised hopefully you
guys can
shed some light thanks again
boys can I
get a comment a dealer's choice
sergej from the land of scruffa
butters
uh what kind of dealer's choice
I hadn't
really thought about something
you got
something you want to play I'm
good well
we have to do something I
barked it down
specifically to ask you oh yeah
there
was one I had in mind it I
can't think
of it oh never mind I got a
[Music]
yeah
you've got Carla flat-footed I
wrote it
- you told me earlier I could
have been
thinking about it I'll say it
wisely
so I script from now on she
being a
pronounced this lies lies lies
Allah is
in Calverton New York yes three
oh three
oh three oh here we go
tonight's number ITN
destination for my
smoking smoking hot wife day
Matt Drew
Adrienne and her daughter
Violet another
girl named violet we have a lot
of in
fact yes we have a couple of
even they
went to the Oakland meet if
there was a
little baby named violet that's
a nice
name on May 13th she donated
last week
to herself so please D do Shmi
you if
you turn 303 on its end it
spells mom I
like that mom mom my mom I'm on
my mom
my mom 303 is the mom donation
it's a
good one yeah what's up with
your mom
303 in college smokin hot it's
ankle
Joseph going down an associate
executive
producer starting with Lucas ty
Hema
Hema tayo its writers I'm sorry
I'm
thinking that's okay Lucas
time' in
august the ish ditched books
deeds booze
faced who stays just boost
faced who
stayed close enough
whatever 256 is obviously in
holland
yearly podcast feat for 2020
yes thank
you
happy enjoying the show show
since 2009
cast work you have just been
with us for
a long time so nice actually
thank you a Jordan Olson and
Nebraska
Bellevue to be exact two
hundred thirty
three dollars and 33 cents
por la maana
what am i some IRA my right on
this
effort due to the wish calm flu
and I
figured I would put that money
to good
use I'd like to call out my
buddies dad
max
for being a douche bag douche
bag blink
blink drip-drip can I get some
I got
ants followed by a goat caramel
well we
can't do the whole thing but we
always
do like to play the little
intro and the
first bit of dance song I got a
handsome
[Music]
ashle Lesage in wykisha
wisconsin to
3333 from ash the thrash la
sage i TM
gents from the great state of
Wisconsin
where our Supreme Court has
just struck
down or unconstitutional stay
at home or
yes right which is an article
that we
could have been discussing on
the show
they did strike it down with
cuz it's
illegal yes what we talked
about we
mentioned this happened we
mention it
yeah it's funny
woohoo in other states I was
rightfully
called out as a douchebag last
week and
I'm in desperate need of a D
douching
you've been deduced by Matthew
my cousin
Matthew a rock wall rock wall or
whatever hit me in the mouth
about a
year ago and a year and a half
ago and I
haven't missed an episode since
he's a
very intelligent young man but
has
always had different insights
that I
don't get from the news or talk
radio I
could not express how grateful
I am for
all the work you guys do to
provide us
with this podcast times are
tough we put
a lot of work into this podcast
yes
times are tough as an elder
millennial
with a shrunken amygdala but I'm
thankful I get relief for a few
hours
twice a week now I continued to
do my
due diligence and return the
value for
value that you've been
providing me I'm
also happy to report that we've
been
recruiting new listeners and
our circle
of friends and family faster
than the
spread of Cova 19 yes
keep up the incredible work and
thank
you for your courage can I get
a goat
camera for the Tristan Onion
Mart tens
who is finally able to have his
back
surgery today an a that's true
for Mike
the shark because we use it in
our daily
conversations and it's
hilarious trust
me it'll get old eventually
tonight
we've we've even gotten over it
I was
going to say about this that's
true I
was going to say
yeah about this show actively
for every
show and this is kind of the
secret of
the value for value model there
are
hundreds of people producing
every
single episode and just listen
to who
was being thanked that besides
these
financial producers who were
supporting
us we have void 0 and BEM Rose
and Darin
oh and we got Nick the rad and
we got
CSB and we got Paul curse or
Paul cat or
for the art generator and they
can go on
and on and on and on hundreds
of people
per episode that's why it's the
best one
in the universe people it's
true you've
got Neil ID in st. Petersburg
Florida
200 only mentioning because
john and
anna always talk about his name
pronunciation yeah we got
trouble with
it this donation is dedicated
to the
birthday of my smoking-hot wife
Amanda
yes thank thank you for the
show which
supports our mental health
brings us
closer together and strengthens
our
relationship Adam yes thanks for
inspiring me to finally getting
a ham
radio license well thank you
very much
see how that works
happy birthday Amanda in jnk
Neil ko4
ACM 73 yes 73 kilo 5 alpha
Charlie
Charlie now was of course
influenced by
John to get my hem ticket and
of course
I did the real deal I'm a
general and
Johnny I was like it's a walkie
talkie
guy 2 meter 70 centimeter I did
the real
test man you did like the
little entry
test there but ok yes we are we
are hams
and proud of it no agenda hams
calm
check it out yet another group
of
fantastic people supporting the
show you
know I do have a call signing
when all
hell breaks loose and I have
save the day yeah and I could
pretty
much use any gear I want oh
yeah you're
just gonna try and figure out
how to
configure it to work with the
repeater
and that happened then after
the hello
one question during the entire
rona
crisis have you once turned on
the radio
your handheld to see if you
could reach
anything or even listen for one
one
minute this is what hams were
born for
man we're in the middle of this
is the
apocalypse this is the
apocalypse and
all you can do is is joke
around we need
to take your ticket back they
got a
renewing in in November I may
upgrade it
to extra now here we have ham
radio guys
ham radio is the public service
network
of last resort when the
apocalypse comes
we're the guys who are going to
save the
world right right
well we're it dear producer
Adam and
John we're the hams they're
gonna save
the world eyes okay so you know
and we
need more people to get their
license
Tom Turner meanwhile in Salt
Lake City
Utah Tom if you got your
license you
have 200 bucks here for us
Thanks hello
ingredients for the moderate to
low risk
and low alcohol content content
state of
Utah been listening to Adam
since he was
on Rogue another one and this
is my
first donation what I liked
about the
Rogan people and there's been
about I
think you probably picked up a
mouse a
lot of listeners 5-nothing mm
Oh a lot a
lot okay and they got into the
donating
mode faster than listeners from
other
sources I agree I agree that
you're
right as they come in pretty
and they
come in at the executive
associate
executive producer level pretty
quickly
there may be some $5 these
subscribers
but so I'm impressed with
Brogan's
Rogen's audience and that says
to me do
the show again well first of all
we're not calling them
audiences we call
the media tribes now and
there's huge
overlap between his tribe and
our tribe
and and people who produced
this show
listened to his show so and I'd
love to
go back Joe is I mean I I was
trying to
get Joe over here he's
complaining he's
like as I told him that we went
to
Lonesome Dove and I sent him
the menu
it's like how we were thinking
about
renting a plane we can't eat
anything we
can't go anywhere we're all
bummed out
about I'm like go broke and
rent the
plane come by ask him well I'm
sure I'll
be invited back on eventually
you should
be one of those guys on standby
but hold
on a second hold on I don't
want to be
the guy on standby you just
want to get
on if you could be honest
excuse me all
right never mind this is not
twit is the
Joe Rogan trick you get on the
overnight
charges have been unsuccessful
what overnights show the oldie
of what
used to be you know that
overnight show
it's called overnight it takes
the name
of it Oh somebody knows the
name in the
chat room huh
it's the one that talks about
you know
flying saucers at red Oh
coast to coast coast to coast
that's the
listening yeah we can bet you
so I want
to get see I don't want to be
on that
shows twos anyway yeah I do I
want to be
on coast-to-coast okay well
someone
please set that up and as John
at Dvorak
org do not repeat do not email
me and do
not email coast to coast am and
pretend
you're me or John and fill out
a form
and put our email addresses no
maybe he
continues on his note I'll be
working
diligently towards knighthoods
I'm
wishing to beat my
overachieving limey
father-in-law who's actually
very close
to receiving a real knighthood
from
Queen I love the show and
deliberating
possible knighthood names such
as Sir
Thomas of the Church of the
Jesus Christ
of the Latter day Saints please
okay Sir
Tom the underachieving son in
law that
overachieving limey father in
law the
thoughts sounds like all that
all
winners to me
Garland's thanks for the
incredible show
and take and take care all
right take
care of yourself Tom thank you
very much
tom
of course he's from st. the
Salt Lake
City so we have a lot of LDS
producers
as well we take them all we'll
take your
rabid Republicans will take
your lib
tards will take your your Lib
Joe's
we'll take your dev Joe's Lib
devs we'll
take anything yeah I'll tell
you the lip
tarts and the lip Joe's don't
look don't
like to show it shit shakes up
their
worldview and they don't like
it it
makes them uncomfortable
uncomfortable
yeah well we're pretty
comfortable
knowing that we have at least
some tribe
out there who is supporting the
work and
happy with it and I love seeing
the
trolls the trolls are very
active today
in the in the troll room before
before
could you have to mention
something it's
raining yeah it's raining we're
in the
middle of May in California the
desert
that is raining they in snow in
New
Yorker earlier this week very
strange
well it's HAARP it's all part
of the
program thank you to our
executive
producers and associate
producers for this episode 1242
it is
highly appreciated and we'll be
thanking
more people in our second
segment but
these are the ones that really
can go
immediately put these titles to
good use
they are true entertainment
titles if
you're looking for a statue or
maybe
just work put it on your
LinkedIn
apparently people have success
with that
and we will be here for another
program
on Sunday please support us at
the
following web site address
Dvorak org
slash and where we are
our formula is this we go out
for here
people in the mouth
premature born a second kid
[Music]
should probably also mention
that the
younger producers secular
producers can
can incorporate this credit
into their
pickup lines now when they
reopen the
bars at last
absolutely and I just
remembered I would
like to give a special jobs
karma to our
very own sir Jean Duke of the
south as
the Rona has taken away all of
his
clients and he didn't ask for
this but
I'm gonna give it to jobs jobs
jobs and
jobs
that's the job cuz you know
what when
someone is like hey man I gotta
find
that client like who do I know
how can I
think of anything I'm like I've
got the
most powerful weapon at my
disposal the
jobs karma why am i messing
around
thinking about who I can call
yeah so
that's hopefully hopefully hold
ghostbusters jobs karma will do
will do
its business mesh is something
that
happened there Guardian printed
this
article I don't know why cuz
there Woody
Allen's on the outs but this is
a
guardian article and it says
Woody
Allen's a rainy day in New York
tops
global box office so they've
been
rolling at this movie that was
paid for
by Amazon Amazon Studios kicked
woody
out after you know Dylan Farrow
made a
fuss again even though this has
been
done in court and one of
Woody's other
kids says bullcrap but he's
been accused
of being a molester and so they
do won't
let his movie so they won't
even show
he's been outed stuff not out
it what's
the word cancelled so badly
that they
won't even release this movie
in the
United States and I saw this
movie it
wasn't it on Amazon
no no Amazon refused to put it
on I
thought they had it on briefly
where did
you see it I got it with a
screener
interwebs yeah I got a screener
uh-huh
and I watched this movie so
after it
came out I think this is maybe
one of
his best New York he's got a
series of
new movies he's not about New
York I
think this is one of his best
ones hmm I
think his award-worthy I mean
it's a
get some it's a plot neurotics
in new
york again but it brings is a
little bit
more about celebrity and the
shallowness
of new york and it's just a it
but it's
but it's an ode to new york i
think is
one of his best new york movies
ever
and unfortunately the american
public
will never get to see it the
theater of
course who cares nowadays note
all the
theaters it was the renewed
interest in
in in canceling him was it
there was a
ronin pharaohs me to work or
what was
the it was some of Ronan Farrow
and
Dylan came out again and
started making
a fuss they made a big fuss and
they did
it using canceled culture
techniques
they started hounding Amazon
because
Amazon had picked his contract
right
right right
so they started how and and
dammuz on
you know did he also supposed
to do some
TV work for them and he did this
horrible really a bad piece of
work and
he gave it to them it's just
junk and I
think Amazon so hypocritical
you know I
mean I'm not a huge Woody Allen
fan of
his movies I've seen you know
somewhat
of course there's some seminal
ones that
we can you know how could you
ever live
without it just seeing some of
these
great movies but you're really
into it
and I'm like a movie yeah which
was that
was the first one well the fur
actually
this first movie was was it
kind of an
overdub asunder first of all he
was take
the money and the real for real
first
we'll just take the money and
run that's
a sight or it gives a gut the
note to
the teller he's gonna rob a
bank and it
ended teller says I've got a
gun what's
a gub to give me your money
I've got a
gun I got a gun no it doesn't
say gub he
says yeah it does here it says
gun
everything you always want to
know about
sex
I saw probably when I was nine
yeah
anyway okay well I'm glad thank
you for
that Woody Allen update
relevant to no
one I really appreciate it's
really
great average he's relevant no
what sir China China let's talk
about
China for a second China ten
inch an
inch in it I have my one China
clip yeah
you wanna do your one China
let's do this clip because this
clip is
kind of like I don't know what
they did
they don't know quite what did
how to
handle this clip because they
the
Chinese influence news media
I'm sure
they have mixed feelings but
they gotta
run the story and like I say bi
Chinese
hackers I like how you say
influence you
you can just say control but the
influence is just warm and
fuzzy yes CBS
CBS is on a tear here we go
tonight the
FBI and federal cybersecurity
agents are
warning that hackers linked to
the
Chinese government are trying
to steal
research on coronavirus
vaccines and
therapies the FBI says the
potential
theft could jeopardize the
treatment of
patients here in the u.s.
here's CBS
chief justice and homeland
security
correspondent Jeff Pegues well
the
corona virus was sweeping
across parts
of China in January my god Jeff
isn't
stop one second I want to
mention
something in this particular
thing
especially when he's reporting
from home
I am now wondering as we all
you like to
make fun of Jeff in it
come on is really a great
reporter but
he's got this funny voice I
think he's
got the same condition that JFK
giora
when Robert Kennedy jr. has oh
oh when
you hear reporting from home
that's when
you're gonna hear it and I've
never
looked into it but I'll bet you
he's got
the same condition because he's
got
these qualities well I don't
know why
you have to take my joy away
that he's
just has to poop dirty
correspondent
Jeff McGee's
well the corona virus was
sweeping
across parts of China in
January US
officials say Chinese hackers
were
already focused on the United
States
trying to steal research from
universities and pharmaceutical
companies that were working on
a cure
john Demers is the assistant
attorney
general for national security
the
chinese per year
have targeted biomedical
research and
there's nothing more important
than
kovin 19 research right now in
that
field the hacking charges
ratcheted up
tensions over the virus between
the US
and China or should have been
stopped at
the source which was China but
it's not
just China Iran is also on the
attack
researchers at the
cybersecurity company
recorded future say the Iranian
state
targeted an executive at Gilead
Sciences
the manufacturer of the
promising
coronavirus treatment drug when
des
aveer but Demers said China is
desperate
to be first with a vaccine you
called
this a holy grail of
information that
these foreign actors are going
after
there's nothing more important
right now
than these treatments and
perhaps most
significantly for China for a
geopolitical value to be able
to say
that they were the first to
develop a
vaccine tonight in the
statement Chinese
officials said the accusations
were
without evidence but US
officials say
anyone working on a vaccine
should be on
hyper alert margarett well when
I heard
him speak kind of in the
interview I
heard it what the the condition
is
called spasmodic dysphonia
that's what
Robert Kennedy jr. has could be
could be
that he has some of that or it
comes
more like he just overworked
his voice I
did you blow your voice shot
but good
sound interesting
well CBS is doing all kinds of
reports
about China and this was 60
minutes
this past Sunday it's just kind
of
interesting how they their
version of
the timeline of Corona and
China and Rob
told us to direct questions
about the
origin of the virus to the
Director of
National Intelligence the
Chinese
Communist Party has also
blocked the
truth in the earliest days the
doctor in
Wuhan who discovered the
outbreak was
silenced by local officials he
later
died
covet 19 in February the
Chinese did
allow a visit by an
international team
of experts including American
scientists
we are coordinating with the
Chinese
government and working closely
together
on the corona virus outbreak in
China
initially president Trump
praised China
but in the following weeks
testing in
the u.s. failed to catch up to
the need
vital equipment was short
bodies filled
refrigerated trailers and
science was
continuously challenged don't
dump dump
dump dump dump dump dump dump
dump and then I see the
disinfectant in
a minute and is there way we
can do
something like that injection
as the
u.s. led the one and illness
and death
the White House moved the focus
to the
Chinese government that's where
this
began last Sunday Secretary of
State
Mike Pompeo attempted to
resurrect a
debunked theory that the virus
was
man-made in China a debunked
theory this
has got to stop reporters
journalists
just saying something is a
debunked
theory is not journalism
let's eat at least the mighty
CBS 60
minutes
Pompeyo was trying to revisit he
debunked the conspiracy
theories never
been debunked of course it
hasn't been
debunked but talking about why
is he
saying it's debunked CB vs.
evidence
that is debunk just because
somebody
else said it wasn't the case
because
it's uni and we still you know
here's
what's not resolved people keep
saying
this they say there's no bats
being sold
at that at that wet market and
other
people say well then it came
from bats
being sold at the wet market
and other
people say they don't sell bats
at that
wet market is a seafood place
as our
President himself says covering
up the
spread of the corona virus
everybody
knows what's going on there did
you see
the altercation with the Asian
American
reporter
it's perpetual which one is
this this is
a new one this was this was a
new
reporter and she's one of the
activists
the activist reporters that are
now
showing up to these conferences
men and
women are good-looking they're
young the
good-looking the guys are you
know
they're kind of hunky the girls
are
really cute and this and and of
course
if they have anyone who's
either of
collar journalists of color but
if you
can get an asian-american to
ask a
question about China that's
even better
but this I think she jumped the
shark on
this one you'll hear why
problem okay
yeah go ahead please
said many times that the u.s.
is doing
far better than any other
country when
it comes to testing yes why
does that
matter why is this a global
competition
to you if everyday Americans
are still
losing their lives and we're
still
seeing more cases every day so
it's like
a typical unimportant
unimpressive
question that is only meant to
attack
the president's demeanor or how
he talks
about something and and this is
she's
wasting our time with this but
then this
happens well they're losing
their lives
everywhere in the world
then maybe that's a question
you should
ask China
don't ask me has China that
question
okay when you ask them that
question you
may get a very unusual answer
yes behind
you and here's what's really
interesting
she came back after he said
well why
don't you go ask China about
that which
he's very consistently say
China knows
everybody knows is China but
remember
she's Asian Americans so she
gets to ask
this follow-up question what
sir why are
you saying that to me
specifically I'm telling you
I'm not
saying it specifically to
anybody I'm
saying it to anybody they would
ask a
nasty question like please go
ahead do
you really think she expected
the
President to say well clearly
you got
splitty eyes you're a gook what
do you
want I mean what the hell are
these
people doing is that really
what she
thought is that really why she
why do
you say that to me is because I
look
Chinese
this is infantile why you
notice the
White House can ban these
people I don't
know why they let him in well
then
you're banning a woman of color
well
it's it did what I would have
said the
Carll ABC he's the one who
heads up the
correspondents that get to go
to that
thing in the first place of
course he's
the guy that's bringing all the
the
activists journalists in yeah
and then
and then another good-looking
journalist
from CNN okay anybody else
please go
ahead in the back please it's
okay
you're intimated I had two
questions
this direction next place but
you didn't
you call it on me
I did and you didn't respond
and now I'm
calling on sorry just a young
lady in
the back please I just want to
let my
colleague okay the cast ladies
and
gentlemen thank you very much
appreciate
it
thank you very much what looks
clearly
clearly some kind of attitude or
something and he's like I not
you
anymore and oh but then we just
like
that's not fair yeah you called
on me
it's my time it's my turn of
course that
question I want to question a
bunch of
kids I'm probably what's her
name the
Kaylee she also walks out I
mean at some
point are you just dare to be
harrangue
by the media they're unit
there's not
these are not legitimate
questions well
they're legitimate questions if
your
National Enquirer or you know
or not
even there no it's this these
are these
are just questions to harass the
president and he's not he
doesn't have
to even show up
ball bomb I think went over a
year
without doing a press
conference at one
point I mean Trump is doing a
favor I
mean if they're gonna ask actual
questions but I didn't hear any
questions that were just like
no I use
showing a chart you know it's
not what
kind of a question is that what
I'm
showing the truck because I
think it's
interesting and you know and I
wanted to
show it I'd beid what can you
can answer
it yourself why you showing a
chart well
we are in in a modern kinetic
war which
means there's no bullets but
the the
kinetics come from money and
regulation
and maybe viral warfare but the
Trump
administration is now talking
to as many
chip makers as possible about
building
fabs in the US which some are
of course
going to do Apple is moving a
significant amount of their
iPhone
production from China to India
it was
kind of interesting to see Van
Jones he
had to some backpedaling to do
he was
supposed to speak at some
conference and
he tweeted I guess he found out
by
himself that oh my god I'm glad
this got
canceled because I I couldn't
have ever
even done it and I found out it
was they
were
sponsored by wal way and that my
takeaway is that's exactly
what's going
on there's so much because Van
Jones
wasn't just gonna go speak just
to be a
nice guy he's getting paid all
these
people II don't speak for free
generally
I mean some people do but their
speeches
are worthless yeah but but I
guess the
understood even yeah professor
in
Arkansas University his money
because he
thought wait a minute
okay somebody book okay the way
it's
usually done somebody books you
to begin
with right you don't just show
up to
speak right so somebody calls
you up and
say I'm gonna do it that we're
doing a
conference blah blah blah blah
blah
we're gonna pay you so much
money in his
case he probably makes pretty
good money
a 10 grand minimum and okay
I'll do that
in this because and then you
tend to
because you have to give a
speech to
this audience the next thing
you do and
I would say all speakers do
this you
check out the event so you go
to their
web page and see who's gonna be
there
and what was a who the audience
is cuz
you got to adjust your speech
to the
people if it's a woman's a
bunch all
women you got to think about
this so you
go to the thing and you go to
the web
page and the web page really
tells you
the sponsor at the start of
this show
two hours ago you said I don't
know why
people think I'm a misogynist
but really
you got to be careful if it's a
conference with all women oh
yeah so you
go yeah cuz of the you do I'm
not an
idiot so you go to the website
you check
it out and you're on the
website the
most important thing you see on
there's
who's sponsoring the thing and
the wall
way people would be front and
center
well this is no surprise he's
full of
shit this guy well you walked
right into
it because this was a
conference of the
NABJ which makes it even worse
National
Association of blowjob artists
clothes
no black journalists and so the
National
Association of Black Journalists
are sponsored by the Chinese
just want
you to understand that and so
he tweeted
I accepted invite this is
verbatim I
accepted invite two peas already
speaking Chinese I accept am i
all today
I accepted the invite to
participate in
NABJ webinar a webinar warning
black
community about kovat
misinformation
I said yes without knowing the
sponsor
glad NABJ canceled I would not
have
participated i'll keep raising
alarm
about pandemics impact on
vulnerable
people though and he as a
posted and
says so he cancels after they
canceled
correct and oh now that he
decides to
virtue signal yeah but if i am
not
buying it but what he's doing
is he's
busting the the National
Association of
Black Journalists that they're
in bed
with the Chinese he's busting
it because
they cancelled his money-making
event
okay now thank you
it always comes down to the
money a
professor at the University of
Arkansas
arrested for undisclosed ties
to China
Arkansas man Arkansas at least
went to
Arkansas another one of these
thousand
talents program did not
disclose the the
money the deals that he had
there they
charge and arrest these guys
now this is
this is not some slap on the
wrist
well good yeah I think so too
and I
think we should talk about
Flint this is
what Flynn oh yeah I got I got
Flint
eclipsed well it's time to do
it now
because we are in a very
interesting
situation where really the news
wants to
focus on death and destruction
and
Corona and scary things we have
all
kinds of documentation coming
out that
seems and appears to backup
pretty much
everything that has been said
about the
Muller investigation the Russia
collusion investigation about
the spying
on the president the president
is now
also tweeting Trump gate that
what it is
Obama gate I'm sorry Obama gate
my god
that jingles are showing up
Obama Gate
tag Obama gate it's what's
trending it's
what's trending she has a very
distinctive voices very good
you can you
can it's me she just from a
professional
point of view from listening to
your
doing voices yeah I mean I
don't device
about just listening to voice
she's
borderline professional voice
over she
has a couple of anomalies that
once
they're corrected they're very
minor she
has got the voice of that's
worth a lot
of money whoa that's quite the
endorsement I mean the way I
hear it she
would fit perfect in our in our
mornings
ooh
don't you think she would fit
perfectly
she would she would do a zoo
what did she what is she what
does she
need to be corrected do you
want to
correct her Live Well their
sake there's
an inconsistent there's an
inconsistency
in hers in her sweet sexiness
and this
is and I can only express it
this way
it's it's not mean it's like
when you
try to do you're one of your
voices and
it feels like an imitation of
somebody
you can't maintain it you can
do a bit
yeah a little bit you know yeah
you can
do a little short thing it
sounds like
Christopher Walken or someone
but you
can't really do a maintain and
she she
is at that point where she can
do it but
there's a maintenance issue and
so she
did apparently there's a meal
to hang in
there longer with this sexiness
all
right I'm a maintenance issue
okay
maintenance it mate is my
maintenance I
mean maintaining the all
maintaining the
level of voice I got you yeah
okay
that's very interesting what I
would
suggest everybody reads and I
put it in
the show notes in a show notes
calm and
yes I'd like to reiterate
search dot na
show notes calm and being it
dot IO are
no longer work the developer
who made
the search engine is as
abandoned it the
beginning of the year everyone
multiple
people have tried to reach out
to him
the the site doesn't even work
now you
could still go to na show notes
calm
draw back all the show notes
yeah
there's a drawback all the show
notes
are there everything is in
structured
XML data so if anyone wants to
build a
new search engine please feel
free would
be happy to resurrect search
any show
knows calm anyway so we're back
to back
to the yeah well really I don't
fit
exists I have three clips okay
I just
want to give a little
background her and
then want your clips we really
need a
daily Flynn podcast because
this is
truly about the deep state
and it's it's going to if we
didn't
already have a wedge in in this
country
is going to get a lot more
interesting
and I was like why I just want
to say
that Sidney Powell who is
Flynn's Mike
General Michael Flynn and how
this all
fits together hopefully your
clips will
start to explain it
Sidney Powell is his new lawyer
and
she's the one that has pretty
much
successfully brought all this
to light
she has a complete timeline of
everything that's taken place
and I will
sum it up as follows
the Obama administration and the
Democrat Party with Hillary
Clinton were
keeping tabs on Trump that's
why they
had this research that was done
and paid
for by Clinton and a law firm
and this
was all known that this was
they even
worked with Russians to get it
because
they just needed something
really think
it was going to win and and
just to make
sure everyone got in the game
we figured
out how to use some phony
baloney
information from multiple
people to go
through the FISA the Foreign
Service for
surveillance act court to be
able to
wiretap and listen in while not
actually
get previously recorded
conversations
from multiple people one of
them being
general Flynn and just so
everyone
understands why this is a big
deal we
have a constitution in America
you can't
do that we have a Fourth
Amendment Fifth
Amendment there's a number of
other
amendments this would violate
but after
9/11 we all as a country said
you know
if we had only know more about
these
terms than we could have caught
them and
all these people wouldn't have
died so
the Patriot Act which was
written a long
time before that but it showed
up and in
that there was a new deal you
could
listen in on American citizens
which is
unconstitutional in at the
heart but we
made a special law that you
could do
that if you got a warrant from
a secret
court secret but you could
trust it
don't worry it's secret because
it will
be of the high
a bar that it will be so
difficult to
get a warrant to spy on an
American
citizen it's I mean we might as
well not
even have the court at all
and of course you have to be
very
truthful and confident in the
evidence
you show to that court to
obtain this
warrant none of that happened
in this
case and spying was done here's
where it
all went wrong in my opinion
Trump won the Obama
administration and
all the people who were
involved with
this everyone who had
quote-unquote
unmasked a flynn call with the
Russian
ambassador they were in on it
including
Joe Biden and that's documented
and they
had a discussion on it on
January 5th
just right before the
transition and
Obama said oh man we got to do
it by the
book but everyone sat in that
room and
then they knew that if they
handed over
all of the information they had
what
you're supposed to do from one
President
to the next and the transition
one
administration to the next if
they if
they truly were honest and gave
it all
then Trump would know
immediately he had
been spied on and who had been
doing it
so they suppressed that and
they doubled
down trying to implicate Trump
in a
Russian spying scheme with
Flynn kind of
the point of the speak of the
spear
which served two purposes one
we had to
get Flynn out of there because
Flynn
would be the one to investigate
and
figure it out and and two we
needed a
fall guy
to really stick the knife into
Trump and
that's now starting to unravel
because
they didn't get Trump out in
time they
weren't able to impeach him and
I
presume the president's just
been
sitting on this and now it's
time to
release it and I think every
day we'll
get a new piece and this latest
piece
that we received is a list of
39 people
39 or 29 things
listen 20 lot around 30 people
who all
requested unmasking unmasking of
these of these phone calls and
if you
want I have a two-minute clip
of NSA
director Admiral Mike Rogers
explaining
how that works as an older clip
because
he's the guy once you play that
and then
I'll play these three this
about bite
and mostly yeah but it also
brings in
Trump and Trump they do be the
last clip
and Trump previews what's
coming or
predicts right there we go on
so here is
how the process works of someone
obtaining the call that they're
interested in the of an
American citizen
would be redacted and now we
have to
know who that person is so we
can
understand what the call is
about so the
respect to unmasking the
following
criteria is apply first for the
National
Security Agency we define in
writing who
has the authority to unmask a
u.s.
person identity that is 20
individuals
in 12 different positions I am
one of
the 20 in one of those 12
positions the
director secondly we outline in
writing
what are the criteria that will
be
applied to a request to unmask
in a
report and again part of our
process
under 702 to protect the
identity of US
persons as part of our
minimization
procedures when we think we
need to
reference a u.s. person in a
report we
will not use a name we will not
use an
identity we say u.s. person one
u.s.
person to u.s. person three
that report
is then promulgated some of the
recipients of that report will
sometimes
come back to us and say I'm
trying to
understand what I am reading
could you
help me understand who is
person one or
who is person two etc we apply
two
criteria in response to their
request
number one you must make the
right
question writing number two the
request
must be made on the basis of
your
official duties not the fact
that you
just find this report really
interesting
and you're just curious it has
to
tangibly tied to your job and
then
finally I said two but there's
a third
criterion and that is the basis
of the
request must be that you need
this
identity to understand the
intelligence
you're reading we apply those
three
criterion we do it in writing
and one of those 20 individuals
then
agrees or disagrees and if we
unmask we
go back to that entity who
requested it
not every individual will
receive the
report but that one entity who
asked for
us we then provide them the US
identity
and we also remind them the
classification of this report
in the
sensitive sensitivity of that
identity
remains in place by revealing
this u.s.
person to you we are doing it
to help
you understand the intelligence
not not
so that you can use that
knowledge
indiscriminately it must remain
appropriately protected and so
the 29
people got to see this yeah and
even
though you'd notice Roger says
there's
20 people qualified to ask yeah
that was
all I'm a little unclear
whether that
means it's I thought it was 20
people
can approve someone who can who
can look
at it but that's it's a little
unclear
to me what is interesting
though is the
response from the New York
Times and the
New York Times who they cannot
deny the
the paperwork that is coming
out over
this their headline is Trump
White House
rewrites history this time
about Flynn
and their article shows a
different
picture by omission so they're
leaving a
lot of things out and
background and
it's quite sad they're in
trouble it's
quite sad to see them I think
they're in
trouble because not only cannot
just
anybody go looking at these
names but to
leak that name to the press
which
happened repeatedly and I think
there's
some documentary evidence of
that that's
a that's a jailable offense
remembered
um but it's gonna get get
introduced
guys are well sadly I have I
have
thought in a wringer yeah sadly
I have
thoughts on who but let's
listen to your
your joke clips and let's get
into the
see how this will affect our
future
there is a kind of a follow
kind of a
cascade effect from Joe Biden
going on
Good Morning America and so
this is
we've just before the list
comes out Joe
goes on this is kind of edited
down but
this is biting on it says CMA
but GM a
contradiction here we go I know
nothing
about those moves to
investigate Michael
Flynn number one number two no
I thought
you asked me whether or not
always
having to kill that clip I'm
sorry
that's the clip I have to do
play that
clip later play clips from GMA
1 sorry I
know nothing about those moves
to
investigate Michael Flynn
number one
number two this is all about
diversion
this is the game this guy plays
all the
time the country is in crisis
were in an
economic crisis a health crisis
but if
they you were reported to be in
a
January 5th 2017 meeting where
you and
the president were briefed on
the FBI's
planned a question Oh Michael
Michael
Flynn over those conversations
he had
with the Russian ambassador his
lyac now
I thought you asked me whether
or not I
had anything to do with him
being
prosecuted okay I'm sorry I was
aware
that there was that there that
asked for
an investigation but that's all
I know
about it I saw this and I have
an
observation well wait okay what
give me
your observation first but I
then I have
an interesting point to make my
observation is when this
question was
being asked and the follow-up
Jo had an
IFB and he was wiggling it in
his ear
and he cocks his head to the
left and I
guarantee you someone was
saying and you
can see his face tilt again in
recognition and then he comes
back with
the oh no like I was talking
about this
he was being souffle is that
the real
I'm I now that you bring that
up I would
say you're probably right
because he
asked it was asked one question
he says
I thought you talked about
prosecuting
yeah which was the second part
when you
take the first part from this
earlier
part of the conversation and
then you
put the second part which is
what I have
here in this contradiction clip
when you
take those two together this is
what you
really got he never said
anything or
even thought anything about your
question being about
prosecution list
to this clip I know nothing
about those
moves to investigate Michael
Flynn
number one number two now I
thought you
asked me whether or not I had
anything
to do with him being prosecuted
there it
is yeah yeah but he switched
midstream
I'm telling you switched yeah
you're
probably right because he's so
dumb that
he never thought that that he's
already
made the mistake no I thought
you said
something else oh yeah you said
that you
wanted orange juice I didn't
know you
said milk at Tina Tina and I
were
watching last night and I said
did you
see that and I rolled it back
and she
saw it too it says look he's
getting
instructions he you know the
the the
holding your left hand or what
did I FB
is the is the intercom and
you're the
depending on how it's set up
it could have been Joe's people
talking
to him it could be the the TV
network
talking to him it could be you
know just
same thing exactly and you've
seen it
before where the newsreader
goes hold on
hold on I'm getting important
information one moment so he
makes one
of those moves with his hand
he's
cocking his head and he's
getting
information he's being told
what to say
this is gonna be great I hope
there's a
debate with Trump but sadly I
think
something else is gonna happen
well I ain't ready for it but
someone
has to go down for this spying
and
Biden's name turns up on the
list as and
Weah wydad in he's lying here
clearly
because he knew all about it he
heard
the call well but hold on
why is Biden being highlighted
besides
it being Joe I think it's time
to
finally take him down so
Hillary can
come in well I'm not gonna of
course I
still have never pulled my
Hillary
prediction so I'm gonna stick
with it
but let's go on with this
theory of
yours in mind and this is Ron
Paul says
Ron people but it's not rand
paul and
he's talking about the biting
unmasking
questions that have Rennell
addressed
the acting intelligence
official senator
where does that stand is Rick
Rennell
going to testify to your
committee if
you've got confirmation of that
no but I
did send a letter last evening
to
Director of National
Intelligence Rick
Cornell and asked him if he
would
declassify this and we got this
information today and released
it and I
think this is astonishing that
Vice
President Biden and really all
of
President Obama's inner circle
individually were requesting the
unmasking of a political
opponent and
you know you remember there was
a whole
to do about trying to impeach
the
president saying that we're
using the
power of government to go after
a
political opponent this is this
is a
smoking gun if there ever was
one that
Vice President Biden was using
the power
of government abusing that
power to go
after a political opponent
essentially
unmasking someone is the
equivalent of
illegally wiretapping them the
government had permission to
listen to
the Russian ambassador but to
protect
Americans we mask their
identity but you
got the whole President Obama's
inner
circle clambering around
listening to
the private conversation I
think he
illegally and I think with ill
bill
ill-begotten motives do you
know senator
whether these unmasking
requests then in
each and all of these cases
occurred
after the election I mean
obviously the
assessment was prior to the
election
that Hillary Clinton was going
to win
obviously that didn't happen so
did a
lot of this that transpire
after the
election itself yes the
document that we
got listed all the names and
listed the
date that they did the
unmasking so vice
president unmasked general
Flynn to
listen to his conversation
which i think
is reprehensible but so did
James Comey
so did James clapper so did
John Brennan
so did Samantha Power's and so
did
President Obama's chief of
staff and a
dozen other people so think
about this
it's illegal to listen to
people's
private conversations you could
listen
to if you have a national
security
matter a foreigner but it's
thus the
foreigners saying we're going
to blow up
the Capitol and will you help
me you
don't get to listen to the other
person's conversation if
they're just
talking
yeah Rand Paul Graham answers
the
question but the guess that
conversation
took place after the election
there's no
other reason to do it but now
we have
the president chiming in on
this and he
talks about it at that meeting
of the
two governors and here he is on
a met an
unmasking and he puts a little
predictive thing at the end
here which
makes you wonder what's coming
next is a
massive massive thing it's I
just got a
listing it's who can believe a
thing
like this
and I watched Biden yesterday
on Good
Morning America being
interviewed by one
of your colleagues Stewart
Stephanopoulos and he said you
know
nothing about anything he has
no ideas
he knows nothing about anything
it's
nothing at all and then it gets
released
today that he was a big young
masker so
how do you know nothing of
you're one of
the unmasked errs it's one of
the very
big stories and I suspect
you'll have if
it's possible even bigger
stories coming
out yeah it's he's been holding
on to
this he's been wait I think
he's gonna
hold on Obama and until after
the
election does he want Obama
down I know
he does because this is Trump
when that
that White House one press
Correspondents Dinner
that's when Obama dressed him
down
that's that's a publicly
ridiculed him
that's called dressing him down
is it
not oh I thought he was that
that that
somebody with transsexual sorry
you are
on a roll today hate for women
confused
about transsexuals for women I
don't
know what to do with you man
I'm telling
you I love the smokin hot
ladies all
kinds of issues with you today
so where we're at now is Bill
Barr the
Department the Attorney General
said hey
to the judge I think is that in
Washington DC we're dropping
all charges
against Flynn clearly he was
railroaded
we
have evidence we have
handwritten
evidence of what the of what
the FBI
agents were doing you know you
know some
of the names like struck I mean
come on
it's very clear and the judge
said no
man I don't know about that I
think we
should bring in another we need
to have
some voices chime in here so
one he's
got a retired judge who's gonna
come in
and tell everybody Flynn should
be drawn
and quartered yeah and at the
same time
but I kind of like this doesn't
happen
often but I lost my train of
thought the
whole point was no I remember
the two
thousand names they got the two
thousand
name list for the lawyers who
were
always writing everything
prosecutor
lawyers yeah attorneys say
Trump sucks
yes that's exactly what they
did again
they sent out a message to the
email
list you have the list where
you had the
list you have all the hey
mister list I
have it yes it's always if you
go back
no hit the story because I
failed a
couple these guys to see if
they were
religious or alive and they
weren't and
they're all part of a Trump
hating crowd
hold on let's do this let's
look at how
many stories we've had about
the 2000
prosecutors so February 17th
bill Barr
resignation more than 2000
former
prosecutors okay let's see well
so we
have that's all February let's
go back a
little bit further because this
is being
used over and over again hasn't
it yeah
by the media loves it so it was
those
guys who wanted bar to reside
there was
a another example though he
wanted all
kinds of stuff yeah I don't
know how you
search for it mm prosecutors is
the
search I'm doing and it's
popping up
everywhere but it's I have to
go back
further wait I can do tools
let's do anything let's do last
year see
past year
that's past you anyway it's
it's the
same group and they are em
they're like
oh hey I got an email from the
group
what are we to sign it okay so
that's
where we're at and that's gonna
be very
interesting to see what happens
but
someone's got to go down and it
would be
great if it was Comey it would
be it
would be great if they close
the FBI but
Brennan I think Brennan could
be in
trouble
but ma'am branch according to
everybody's in trouble but he's
not in
trouble and I'd like to know if
anybody
can confirm that his security
clearance
was pulled I never heard that
it was
confirmed I don't know you're
talking
new stories from three years ago
okay all right did now did you
have more
on the no that's all I got I
just got
the bite and stuff and I think
you're
probably right this may be the
one it
may not be the one because you
still
have the same old the John
Cooper's out
there these guys who are you
know old
PACs democrat party and they're
the ones
who pushed Obama past Sanders
because
they're not putting up with
didn't you
know losing all that banking
background
well that bankers money and the
bankers
all said in the band the
Democrats are
more of a holder to the bankers
and the
Republicans are from what I can
tell
seems and the oops hold on 1 2
3 4 5 5
oh my god that is effor no
that's the
coastal coming down from
Seattle but the
coastal is always a little bit
I thought
it was six last time now it's
five now
it's five it just wouldn't
normally 12
that thing isn't bad you know
what that
means
what negative interest rates it
probably
has something to do with these
three
states cuz this effort goes to
Chicago
and this comes from Seattle it
goes down
as Los Angeles's
and these states are all
Democrats and
all God you know don't get on a
train
anyway where was I I was going
while I
was gonna switch gears if we're
done
with Flynn I want to do a quick
thing on
Bill Gates and then thank some
more
people okay on show number 780
of this
No Agenda show best podcast the
universe
from December 10th 2015
this is what we discovered and
trumpets
and yet Bill Gates knows what's
going on
oh man apparently at the time
trump was
all over Bill Gates and we have
to do
something we have to go see
Bill Gates
and a lot of different people
that
really understand what's
happening
apparently it was all in on
Bill Gates I
don't think so so much anymore
and here
is the the obligatory once a
show clip
of Bill Gates telling us what's
going to
happen what's needs to happen
and it's
gonna be an RNAi vaccine and
sure people
will die but it's the only way
to go
there's an approach called the
RNA
vaccine that people like
Madonna her
back and others are using by
the way
these are the companies that
either he
personally but certainly the
Gates
Foundation has put money into
moderna
would be the number one it's
why he
mentions it that in 2015 we
died enta
fide that is very promising for
pandemics and for other
applications as
well and so if everything goes
perfectly
with the RNAi approach we could
actually
be at the 18 months we don't
want to
create unrealistic expectations
the
efficacy of vaccines and older
people is
always a huge challenge you
know it
turns out the flu vaccine isn't
that
effective and old early people
most the
benefit comes from younger
people not
spreading it because they're
vaccinated
this is an interesting little
tidbit and
I I just kind of like
highlighting that
since we know that the previous
flu shot
the 2017-2018 increased the
likelihood
of the person who received the
shot of
developing a respiratory virus
by a very
infect infection by 36% and so
if you've
got old people in nursing homes
who I'm
sure are pretty much told
you're getting
this this vaccine even Bill
Gates knows
they're not very effective on
older
people because of the state of
their
immune system
and also in order to make it
effective
they got to jack it up which is
is that
think that's what you use the
adjuvant
for the Hamburger Helper of
vaccines and
that could make that viral
infection
even worse possibly and that
that
benefits on a community basis
the
elderly here we clearly need a
vaccine
that works in the upper age
range
because their most at risk of
that and
doing that so that you amp it
up so it
works in older people and yet
you don't
have side effects you know if
we have in
a one in 10,000
side effects that's you know
way more
700,000 you know people who
will suffer
from that so really
understanding the
safety at gigantic scale across
all age
ranges you know pregnant male
female
undernourished existing
comorbidities
it's very very hard and that
actual
decision of okay let's go and
give this
vaccine to the entire world
governments
will have to be involved
because there
will be some risk and
indemnification
needed before that can be
decided on
here's the question
with all this moderna and all
this work
on the r and a vaccine which is
in no
means a vaccine in the
traditional sense
because it's changing RN a
versus
building immunity by
introducing a
toned-down and or dead version
of the
violated attenuated well here's
my
question with all this focus
from Bill
Gates clearly on this RNA
vaccine what
if it doesn't work are we in
parallel
doing the old growing it in an
egg thing
I don't hear anyone talking
about it
because now we I mean we are
not buddy
coronavirus apparently does is
not isn't
that's why they said I'm a new
pouchy
said himself in one of these
little
ditties there may never be a
vaccine for
coronaviruses to one of those
it's like
aids is one of those things
well like
it's like
like all these things like like
Ebola
yes all these things why Bala
they do
have something but it changes
just
enough that it can't really be
a vaccine
is ineffective and what they
mean
generally speaking by changes
enough not
so much with with AIDS but with
these
corona viruses that they think
they do
generate and the next thing you
know
they're not effect they don't
really
have the impact anymore Laura
Ingraham
mentioned it the French guy who
talks
about this together when you
know the
Nobel Prize in medicine that
guy who
thinks his nuts because these
goes
against the grain who says this
bullcrap
this thing isn't gonna last you
know
more than a year because it's
going to
just turn into dust can't
reproduce and
live your are not on the right
program
today man what do you think
that is and
that is what Trump thinks too
yeah so
this whole thing is that's
whether it's
such a rush to get a vaccine
out so they
can at least have something to
sell
right well then we just get
back to the
chlorine or oxy chloroquine
let's play
one last clip from Laura this
is ingre
Amano CQ now I told you about
seven
weeks ago that
hydroxychloroquine was
likely saving lives and now
another
study confirms that conclusion
and it
was conducted by NYU's Grossman
School
of Medicine where researchers
looked at
932 kovat patients who are on
hydroxychloroquine along with
zinc in
his it's room Ison they
concluded that
the triple combo that they
awell with
that they were 44 percent less
likely to
die from the corona virus good
news
take that FDA yeah I like the
I'd like
the practical results more than
just
these damn studies that are
rigged and
you've got you know certain
AIDS groups
whether it's positive or
negative I like
hearing this from Texas what
happened to
this nursing home was one of
the first
big tests of its kind in Texas
I thought the risk of seeing
15% of that
nursing home die was just not an
acceptable risk a third of
patients said
this place in Galveston County
got the
corona virus so dr. Robin
Armstrong used
hydroxychloroquine pills to
treat 39 of
them so the pace
so done well you said most of
the
patients have done well
somebody's
listening to this might say way
he
qualified it with most have
there been
some who have not done well
with it well
I would say I would say all the
patients
have done well on Sunday these
finish their five days of
treatment and
dr. Armstrong said no one
experienced
any side-effects but the 65
year old
anti-malarial drug has suddenly
become
controversial President Trump
said it
was promising for kovat 19
patients
Armstrong admits he supports the
president but Democrats
correctly
cautioned that this drug remains
unproven for the coronavirus
well let's
say that the president didn't
bring this
drug up well we would be having
this
conversation now I wonder sir
that is
about the best question I've
had so far
and I don't think so I don't
think this
would even be a conversation
honestly no
I think the news reporting
would be
hopeful results good news
senior saved elder's it's not a
death
sentence I mean all of this
could have
no but no and when all is said
and done
and ten years from now when we
look back
we're gonna see that there was
a lot of
stuff that could have been done
that the
actual hate of the president
not even
the pregnant heat of a man a
man with
orange hair resulted in death
yeah these
Democrats are murderers and
Democrats
Democrats the idiots it's an if
the
media as many Republicans that
hate
Trump too but this is political
if they
do everything you keep hearing
about
hydroxychloroquine is totally
political
the Democrats doctors and the
rest of
them oh no it's no good
and the Republicans yeah it's
good it
works we've done it I mean come
on when
is this gonna end it's gonna
end in the
election in November no agenda
imagine
all the people who could do
gossip oh
yeah that'd be fine
[Music]
Jamie got a few people are
fighting for
sure starting with James
Niemeyer in
Tulsa Oklahoma 124 dollars and
20 cents
and he says he found a show on
snitcher
what is snitcher isn't that
stitcher o
stitcher
I don't like stitcher I never
used it
stitcher makes a copy of our
show and
then they have different
formats and
quality and they put an ad in
front of
it that's really the if you
really want
people ripping us off then you
should
use that well we have an open
source
policy did you just get it some
other
way
nest door Molina in one he got
it he
came in with a hundred twenty
four
dollars and 20 cents that was
highly
appreciated
Nestor Molina and Walker in
Michigan he
he's at $100 then we have sorry
Christopher revolt revolt one
of his
revolt or revolt I would just
say revolt
I'm rhyme mister revolt WCCC
100 Chris
revolt with you everybody it's
a great
name I love it that would be a
good yeah
jock name shock me jock named
jock named
Christina Thomason drums
Pennsylvania
100 sir how now brown cow in
rora
Arlington Virginia 85 one of our
Arlington fans we love those
guys
Forrest Tucker and Eagle River
our cat
Arkans Arkansas yeah Arkansas
no no no
Alaska Alaska that's a lot last
yeah I'm
sorry helps us with it with a
little
prompt there aka dummies he
writes you
know how you can remember a are
ar-15
it's you know the South
Arkansas a que
somos Russia a are 16 Alaska's
near
Russia so it's ak-47 there you
go wow
that works yeah it does Cody
Wilson
works to enough so they could
send us
$66 from Rosanna Victoria
Australia and
he needs to call out Pippa
McNamara as a
douchebag to Colin Wilson as a
douchebag
meanwhile Tara recent Urbana
Illinois 65
33 David Forbes and shikou P
Minnesota
600 six sir not appearing on
this
podcast in Richland Washington
5678 J Jase Jase Hahn line hand
line on
hey hey line
Halon I don't know handsome
maybe Hanlon
and lose Hanlon
5588 Norcross Georgia David
Russell and
Aurora Colorado 55 10 and he's
gonna be
a night yeah
sir he's got the accounting and
he's on
the list sir buck of 2112 in
Charleston
beautiful city 55 bucks and
he's got on
South Carolina yeah he's got he
wants to
boy I haven't if he says he
wish his smoking-hot wife named
Jennifer
we know her from animated no
agenda and
the voice that she's working on
a happy
birthday weekend Oh she'd be
fun yes he
says the Jennifer's the best
wife in the
world and you guys stay away
from her
I'm the luckiest man in the
world I tell
her all the time that but she
doesn't
believe the people around you
all the
time I'm not liking that so
much G the
man security guy comes in the
front $51
an 11 cents as mr. show since
Adam on
Rogan huh right on
that's it that's sick there's
no agenda
is exactly the podcast he
needed to add
to his rotation nice there you
go but
yes he listened he said he also
hit his
dad in the mouth not shortly
after and
started listening he started
listening
now too
wow man this Rogen appearance
has got us
seven new people
at least Skyler Sanders in
Oklahoma I'm
sorry I'm sorry
he asked for deducing we missed
it
you've been deduced and the
security guy
well some business partners are
helping
out Skyler Sanders in Oakland
California
51:11 says that he started
listening
about a month ago at the behest
of one
of his business partners cool i
also a
show producer so he will be he
will be
he be called out for a birthday
today
for his wife who is also a
registered
nurse very good
he says he's a business owner
in Oakland
with insight information do you
have
lead into a boiling scandal by
city
officials that will partially
they'll be
partially precedent for Martin
Elon Musk
Tesla's lawsuit against Alameda
County
oh he should probably have a
watch now
read it reach out to you and
your
special note yeah we do have a
1 Elon
Musk clip they're talking about
this
Thomas JA tenon in Vinita
there's a lot
of double a's in this know 50
dollars
and 33 cents she takes me
tonight hood
all right TJ you got it hey and
the
following peeler $50 known
donors name
and location story was Robert
Kerr back
in essexville Michigan Cassidy
Eastwood
in Oklahoma City Brandon savoir
I'm sure
is sure sir Brandon in Port
Orchard
Washington store alignment of
the net
and Anna Anna Illinois or as
some people
would pronounce it Ella noise
Kimberly
Redmond in Toronto Ontario
Tyler Boyd
parts unknown store labrat of
the Hill
Country over there in Universal
City
Texas a lot of booze makers in
that area
Clayton Clayton Dunivant in
Greenfield
Wisconsin sure big papa moose
of the
Ogallala Aquifer in liberal
Kansas
Michael bralette odessa florida
rosen
touch coughed in london UK and
last but
not least our favorite Dame
Patricia
Worthington there in Miami she's
actually a Baroness in Miami
Florida and
that concludes our producers and
well-wishers for show
12:42 then we appreciate the
production
help from everybody also those
who
helped produce under $50
usually for
anonymity if it's right around
the 50
but there's several programs we
have
that are sustaining for us and
recurring
for you we have 33 33 11 11s we
got $5 a
show $5 a month it's all
explained at
Dvorak dot org slash na and
thank you
very much was once again
the hundreds of people have come
together to bring you this
episode of
the best podcast the universe
known as
the No Agenda show as requested
a couple
Karma's jobs jobs jobs and jobs
Devorah org slash na
[Music]
and we got a couple of
birthdays to
celebrate today is the 14th of
May 20
2007 ezel says happy birthday
to his
smokin hot wife Dame Adrienne
and his
daughter violence and that will
be for
those yesterday's or one daily
Tim W
says happy birthday to his
daughter and
as she turns 16 sir Andy of
Terrigal
Beach happy birthday to his
dementia B
mother Carol who turns 78 today
and she
still reads the newspaper
without her
glasses meal ID says happy
birthday to
his smokin hot wife Amanda sir
Park of
2112 happy birthday to you
guests at his
smokin hot wife Dame Jennifer
and Skylar
Sanderson's happy birthday to
his wife
we say happy birthday for
everybody here
at the best podcast in the
universe
[Music]
we have one two three four we
have one
two three four
Wow four knights and a dame
satellite
talks and I was like the
beginning of a
song sorry I tripped over the
wire you
need this yes that's and I got
a pick
mine up now you have supported
the No
Agenda show in the amount of
$1,000 or
more some of you taken a long
time mama
bear I'm looking at you and
we're very
happy to pronounce the Kate all
of you
as sir and or not we've been
drove the
spark
sergej from the land of scuffle
butters
sir Russell sake Bachman
Billabong gets
and bourbon sparkling cider has
four
ginger ale and herbals breast
milk and
tabla and of course mutton and
Mead it's
all here at the table for you
thank you
for your support we love
honoring you
here at the round table and on
your way
out head over to no agenda
nation.com /
ring so Eric the shield can get
that off
to you as soon as we get them
in we got
another batch on the way soon
I'm
reliably informed thank you
again and
remember we'll be back on
Sunday Dvorak
org slash any let's see if we
had
anything else interesting well
I got a
promise to do the test of the
Tesla
store so here's an Elon Musk
update from
Democracy Now okay in Northern
California billionaire Tesla
CEO Elon
Musk has restarted work at
Tesla's huge
electric vehicle factory in
Fremont
daring government officials to
arrest
him for violating a coronavirus
lockdown
on Tuesday President Trump
tweeted
California should let Tesla and
Elon
Musk open the plant now it can
be done
fast and safely the president
tweeted
Elon Musk tweeted back Thank
You musk
has repeatedly downplayed the
threat of
the corona virus and cold
government
imposed quarantined fashion
Los Angeles County's top public
health
officials said Tuesday stay at
home
orders will be extended for the
next
three months at least 1300
deaths in LA
have been linked to kovat 19
California
State University's president
Tuesday
announced plans to cancel most
in-person
classes during the fall
semester yeah
you know I can't just not good
a quick
trip around the world I've got
I have
Corona in Brazil and Africa
which is an
interesting little report not
so in
Brazil which is emerging as a
serious
epicenter even though President
jarba
Sanaa rose supporters still
cheer him on
he's provoked outrage as a Cova
denier
who still won't social distance
on this
weekend he went for a
provocative spin
on a jet ski as the number of
coronavirus deaths past 10,000
local
authorities put a Kovach
message on
Rio's famous Christ the
Redeemer statue
have a heart wear a mask 10,000
dead and
we have 80 pushing 90,000 yeah
and we
shut down the country in Brazil
didn't
and our population is 350
theirs is 250
so their part their numbers
should be
hired I mean it looks like an
experiment
they don't want to do because
Boston our
Boston our bowls an arrow is is
a bright
wing or supposedly a kind of a
piece of
business oriented guy they've
left press
down there hates him they cause
basically oh I'm a fascist and
so you
got the same kind of politics
going on
with Brazil you know what I
want their
numbers aren't really being I
don't
think their numbers are high
enough - no
they're not no they're not but
you know
just just throw in surge and
dead and
whatever so you have to see the
Statue
with with that big to see the
person that's a beautiful
statue what I
think we should do he
America is we should put a big
mask on
the Statue of Liberty yes I
think that's
exactly what I was thinking was
there a
mask
let's go to Africa in Africa and
Southeast Asia the virus does
appear to
be spreading more slowly maybe
because
the population tends on average
to be
younger Wow that's all you got
you don't
have anything about
antimalarials okay
but no one is sure and it's
quite
possible that the worst is yet
to come
yeah Serge it's quite possible
worse is
yet to come they can't stand it
Boris Johnson goofed up during
Prime
Minister's question time Thank
You mr.
Speaker I thank the Prime
Minister for
his update on progress of
testing and
tracing this invisible killer
but can
you confirm the people of West
dr. ship
that the new systems that we
are putting
in place will in for some time
be able
to detect local flare-ups mr.
sandy mr.
speaker the intention is that
the
decoded alert system in time
will be
sufficiently sensitive and
flexible as
to detect local flare-ups so
that for
instance if a the code is
detected in
the water supply of a certain
time or
well then then steps can be
taken on
this path so people immediately
went
what Congress did coronavirus
can be in
the water supply please
well what he meant of course he
meant in
the sewage system
uh-huh maybe that's not saying
much for
the water supply in England no
kidding
may I have one last clip
and this is just a wacky clip
that the
mainstream won't pick up on in
the man
that Bernie Bernie bros won't
pick up on
but Bernie it along with neil
honda omar
these two communists have
decided that
they think that the all the
just why the
banks don't want this guy by
the way and
they're never good he's never
gonna be a
candidate you should realize
this if you
listen to this insanity vermont
independence senator bernie
sanders a
Minnesota Democratic Congress
member
Ileana Omar have joined more
than
3-hundred lawmakers around the
world
calling for the cancellation of
the
cornea you had to start it over
but I
just what 300 lawmakers she
says 300
lawmakers around the world this
includes
like the Communists in
Venezuela and the
Socialists here and the
Socialists there
should this is 300 lawmakers
around the
world aren't anyone in their
right mind
but go on not play it again
Vermont
independence senator Bernie
Sanders a
Minnesota Democratic Congress
member
Ileana Omar have joined more
than
3-hundred lawmakers around the
world
calling for the cancellation of
poor
nations debts as they struggle
with the
kovat 19 crisis this comes as
the United
Nations warns as many as a half
a
billion people could fall into
poverty
due to the pandemic in a letter
to the
leadership of the World Bank
and the
International Monetary Fund
Tuesday
senator Sanders writes quote in
the face
of a horrific pandemic in a
worldwide
recession we cannot allow poor
countries
to get educate money that
should be
going towards protecting the
health and
safety of their people to pay
off
unsustainable debts
we cannot allow these countries
to be
deprived of the resources they
need to
purchase food medicine
protective gear
and medical equipment sanderson
cancel
everyone else's debt except ours
yeah cancel all the debts
around the
world which is you got yourself
in this
situation and you want to just
have it
canceled you hoped that it gets
canada
he also wants to cancel all
student loan
debt and you me he just wants
to cancel
everything so i don't know if he
understands the nomar the rest
of it
even know how the system works
we're not a socialist society
we're not
China were not we're a
capitalist
country it's just bullshit I
mean I get
funded to be offensive
it's all so short-sighted look
at what
President Trump is saying his
idea I
like his idea is let's get
negative
interest rates and then
ultimately when
you take out a loan for school
you'll
get paid for it
it's real simple I don't
understand why
people don't understand this is
great I
can't wait for negative
interest rate
waiting for it all my life and
says
everybody's been waiting for
that
well CNN is and needs to be my
last clip
CNN just like when the Malaysian
airliner was lost you know they
they
went on for over a year every
single day
and that items and special
shows so now
CNN is doing what they do best
they've
got to do their gut do their
special
show so let's check out a promo
for one
of them taking on coronavirus in
hard-hit communities of color
joined on
lemonade Van Jones with dr.
Regina
Benjamin and Robert Smith Plus
messages
of hope from Mario Lopez samuel
l.jackson and more the color of
kobane
live tomorrow at 10:00 on CNN
the color
of CO vid with say inspiring
messages
the hopeful messages even one
black
person who watches CNN romrio
local
messages of hope from
podcasters you
love from around the world
yeah that's there's that and
then we
have this little ditty just as
fun join
Anderson Cooper and dr. Sanjay
Gupta
former acting CDC director
Richard
Besser former Health and Human
Services
Secretary Kathleen Sebelius an
activist
Greta tune Berg for coronavirus
affection fears live Thursday
at 8:00
I'm glad you got that I can't
wait it's
tonight
Greta - and Berg what the hell
does she
have to do with coronavirus
will she
have it so what did that so
you're an
expert cuz you caught you
caught a cold
so now you're a doctor
oh and Van Jones isn't is an
expert on
coronavirus come on man it's
you got to
enjoy the little things this is
fun you
know it's gonna be a turd it's
just it's
really fun man come on
well I got one I got one then
let's
listen to some other another
idiocy this
is Rick bright he's gonna
testify in
front of Congress he's well on
his of
ayala gist but somehow he's
become
magically become an
epidemiologist
tomorrow on Capitol Hill
Rick bright the
administration's former
top vaccine researcher who is
pushed out
of his position will testify
that if the
response is not ramped up work
2020 will
be the darkest winter in modern
history
yes it'll be a cold and lonely
Christmas
without you I don't believe any
of it
anymore
I really don't it's quite the
beach I
don't believe any of it anymore
and we
just hire some it is a little
tiresome
it's amazing we can put a show
together
I mean it's I have to struggle
well
that's a very good point
because we both
I know that we both were
digging deep
and hard for for material for
today if
you don't want to bore people
you know
you got to come up with new
stuff and
here you go
the c-span is still a beautiful
thing
yeah got some stuff from them
coming up if you want to hear
the foler
Nick the rat interview with
John McAfee
that'll be a no agenda stream
calm I
like how these guys think
very smart here at the no
agenda stream
and we have a couple of end of
show
mixes we've got Rolando
Gonzalez which I
promise to play from the last
show we've
got Jason Lewis and Jesse Coyne
Nelson
and we would love to see you
back with
us again to produce another
episode of
the best podcast in the
universe on
Sunday until then I'm coming to
you from
the opportunities own 33 here
in Austin
Texas FEMA region number six
and the
governmental maps in the morning
everybody
I'm Adam curry and from
northern to
Silicon Valley where we're all
wondering
whatever happened to hands up
don't
shoot I'm John C Dvorak we
return on
Sunday right here on no agenda
remember
us at Dvorak dot org slash na
until then
adios mofos ends you know the
Nursery
Rhyme that goes
hickory dickory dock the mouse
ran up
that Trump Dethklok has over
Times
Square and what it shows is an
estimate
of the number of us pulpit 19
deaths
that resulted from the
president and his
team's failed response to the
corona
virus outbreak yes who's here
on Sesame
Street today from Dethklok and
the
masses right over here thanks
to doctor
foul Qing and leading
epidemiologists we
now know that how the mitigation
guidelines been put into effect
just one
week earlier on March 9 instead
of March
16th 60 percent of us covet 19
deaths
would have been prevented
don't run ready to run up the
Trump
dethklok's and the clock is
ready to
strike one the Trump death
clock stands
at forty six thousand four
hundred
eighty five and growing
[Music]
lavender
to drive with
travels
[Music]
oh man
Podcast
driving here that's dirty
[Music]
in sections of 10
no it's
[Music]
[Applause]
we're gonna die
show it
[Music]
here
because I
we're in a mass
[Music]
cocaine
don't you know it
[Music]
you
you are ways act surprised
say how are you nice mask
you tell me
this should never have happened
this
should never have happened
this virus should not have
spread all
over the world they allowed
this to go
into our country this should
never have
happened more than a dozen
children in
the New York City area have
ended up in
intensive care with severe
symptoms
possibly linked to corona virus
the
finding has not been peer
reviewed a
rate of infection is rising
heart rate
and their heart rate is very
high there
is now a more powerful mutant
strain of
the virus to compute the rate of
infection is rising like
bringing a
camera into focus these
techniques
[Music]
for a org slash and masks