John: 1000 attorneys say Trump sucks.
Unknown: Adam Curry,
John Dvorak.
Adam: It's Thursday, May 14 2020. This is your award winning keto nation media assassination Episode 1200 42. This is no agenda freshly cut hair don't
care and broadcasting live from opportunity zone 33 Austin, Texas capital of the drone stars in the morning, everybody.
John: I'm Adam Curry from Northern Silicon Valley, where we're all wondering Whatever happened to the Ice Bucket Challenge of John Dvorak?
Adam: Doubt everybody's wondering what happened to that? Yes, they are. No, that's not true. No, they're not. No one's wondering about that.
John: The money they gave me money got it at some people. Yes.
Adam: That was for ALS. The money went to ALS. Oh, well, I don't know. Man. You should dive into it. I want a full report. I want a full report
Sunday. I want to know all about it.
Unknown: Hey, I had a haircut.
John: And a haircut. It's okay with me.
Adam: I'm so happy I had a haircut. It's so nice. But what an experience that
John: you like long here.
Adam: No. Well, I did. I mean, well, no, actually, I've never liked it. It just looked good on me at the time back in the day. Remember, I have a
small head in order to work well on TV, you need a big head. So if you don't have a big head is not that small, by the way. It's not as big as Pat's
Ajax. Or Vanna White.
John: Or Little Richard Have you ever seen the size of that guy's head? He had a big head what
Adam: Little Richard was anything but little. He was pretty big. It was pretty big. So learn a little bit about about returning back to work and what
it means when the governor on a Friday afternoon says hey, guess what? You guys with hair salons you can open up on Monday. You don't think about it
as a customer obviously like oh, that's fine. Great. So I immediately This was I think it was Friday I saw the news I immediately started texting
johannah my hairstylist to the stars of Austin and and she said oh my god we weren't ready for this we had no idea we thought the 18th is the last we
heard is the 18th it would you know we would be able to take look and figure out a timeline but all of a sudden they you know they threw it on him in
two days it This was not a smart idea.
John: I've heard about this around the country there's different areas and there's always the hair salons and I was thinking to myself I'm thinking to
myself self self How hard is it to boot a hair salon you got you know you're standing you need your scissors you need to cut it you know a little
buzzing things. You need a bucket of goo for the cooking. So this is no What is it? This
Adam: is exactly what can it be this is what I thought or at least the impression I had this a lot first of all what happens is without you
John: knowing and poo go bad or something in the meantime,
Adam: wow man, I hope the next person who cuts your hair sticks scissors in your eye. You're a horrible person 345677 cars on these Zephyr Ladies and
gentlemen, we're still in a state of depression. Yep. No. So the first thing that happens is without any knowledge of this would take
John: me with a stick I just scissors in my head is not nice. So I'm
Adam: warning you really because
John: you know you get my hairdresser. Care cutter. He He doesn't listen to the show. Nobody listens to the show in that debt business. Like Can I
Adam: just tell you what the what the experience was? So you understand why I think you are wrong about all you need is some glutinous scissors and
some shampoo. Okay, so imagine you're you're it's a Friday night, you don't even know what day it is anymore in the lockdown. And all of a sudden some
someone important says, Oh, yeah, Monday, you can go back to the hairdresser. What do you think happens? They get swept up in order and they're caught
off guard. And there's a lot has to happen. There's, there's, you know, we have very strict city ordinances despite what the governor has ordered. The
city of Austin is going down. We'll get into that in a moment. So you have to have policies and has to be published. You have to let everybody knows
everyone has to wait in the car before they come in. You have to clean off all surfaces. There's a lot of different things that have to take place.
And then the fear. It's not like the whole hair salon wanted to come back. There were other hair cutters. They're like, No, I'm terrified. So can you
open up with half a shop? You know, there's a lot of questions. I didn't think about it, but then when you get into it, it's really weird to have your
hair cut with a mask on and Even even Johanna's, like looking at me like, now I know this sucks so bad, but it's a requirement. not legally, but it's
a requirement. Based on shaming this, let me play these clips, you'll understand we kind of started on this, but when the governor of texas said,
Okay, here's what here's what's gonna happen we can open up. There's no requirement for masks in public or eight or even indoors. I mean, it can be up
to the proprietor if they want to force people to wear underwear on their head. But Adler said, Oh, no, no, no, no, we're just gonna tell everyone
they need to wear a mask. I think we had the clip on the last show. And even though I can't find you or send you to jail, knowing that you've killed
somebody should be enough if you don't wear a mask outside all the time and 90 degree heat. So now the Texas attorney general has sent a warning to
Austin and its
Unknown: Mayor at a time when some Austin staples like Shady Grove have closed their doors for good. Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton sent a warning
letter in part to Mayor Steve Adler and Travis County Judge Sarah Eckart saying that the local health orders issued last Friday were confusing and
unlawful because the order doesn't clearly differentiate between recommendations and requirements.
Restaurants fully
support contact Tracy
Kelsey Erickson Stratford is with the Texas Restaurant Association. They also sent a letter to Mayor Adler asking him to change section 11 of the
local order. It encourages restaurants with the capacity of 75 or less to keep a log of all customers and employees who came in including the dates
and times they were there and where they sat. Tra says if small businesses are doing this, so should the big ones.
Small businesses options are to do this or to be publicly shamed. That's not an option.
We really are treating this like a requirement.
city and county attorneys are now reviewing pakhtuns letter but in a statement to CBS Austin, a Travis County spokesperson said in part our initial
thought is we disagree with the Attorney General Mayor Adler also sent us a statement saying in part up to this point, we have avoided the naked
politicization of the virus crisis. I will not follow the ag down that road. The city's order complements, incorporates and does not conflict with the
governor's orders. Adler also brought it up during his daily virtual address.
We asked
restaurants to do that voluntarily and I guess the
voluntary act.
Adam: So Adler's trying to do a Cuomo every single day from his office there above the W Hotel in downtown Austin. It's I really this guy's been he's
not here, I don't think he's left his home at all. He's the guy this pussy. He's the one that's sitting inside and requiring small businesses in
particular restaurants. We had this happen when we went to the first open, first restaurant opening, you've got to write down your name, you got to
sign a piece of paper. And of course, people are going to revolt against that. And it's not even a requirement by law. But you heard it. It's the
shaming. That's where all of this is headed. One more clip of the response from Adler. Regarding the defiant Austin, Texas,
Unknown: your state is opening up but your city is not yet. Why not? Well, we're opening up to the extent that the governor has has has put it in his
order. So we're compliant with the state. But the messaging that we're trying to send to our community is to take this cautiously and slowly, because
no one knows what the impact of this is going to be in. It's going to take us three weeks, maybe four weeks to get the the data on hospitalizations
that we need to see, to see whether or not our toe dip here is putting us on a path to another surge. So it's more
Adam: what other serves there was never a surge in Texas to start with. But he feels that there's a surge surge.
So it's more of a messaging element than anything else. We have a lot of community members that know that while these things are
Unknown: opening. It doesn't mean we have to go. And it doesn't mean that we that we have to
open. The governor has allowed those things to happen. But we are urging our community to take this cautiously and slowly so that we can measure the
impact before we end up with another surge. Another surge
John: he said twice a
Adam: week and I checked just to make sure maybe I missed the wording somewhere. There's not even a headline was surge in Texas, Travis County or
Austin. This is about shaming. And I was surprised because I kind of scoffed when you said it. But my hairdresser. She said oh my god, I never Intel.
She's definitely liberal. She says I never expected to see it was kind of funny. This level of social shaming from liberals.
Unknown: I'm like what
what okay.
Adam: And she said literally it's very clear if you wear a mask you're a democrat if you don't you're a Republican. It's exactly what you said about
California.
Unknown: exactly what it is.
Adam: And and even she recognizes it's only to make you feel good these are the masks are the like the ribbons after 911
John: you know, whatever forget what's in that is community. There's also a community aspect to it. I've noticed this when you go around without a
mask in a fight with people mix, some masks, no masks, you can start to see the connection you can see that the no mass people or the you see a lot of
macho guys motorcyclists. It's kind of like that Larry David episode where he wore the trump hat. You just start to see it. And you can see these old
guys are just trying to get to do it. You know, Marie
Adam: just gave me a great idea. Oh, here's what you need. Read. Make America Great Again. Masks. Yeah. Hello. This is the perfect
John: perfect funny idea. But there's the mask.
Adam: No. Are you kidding me? I think I think Republicans will wear the mask.
John: Or you have to wear the mask to get into the store Whole Foods for example. Yeah. bicted mask. Yeah, great. America. Make America Great Again,
are mega
Adam: mega masks. It's a Mega Man. Where
John: are they? They must have already been Microsoft. Well, we have.
Adam: Well, it just came up. And another thing. When I'm watching television, and I'm seeing actors, I'm seeing commercials. They don't represent the
American public anymore. I demand that every single commercial the actors wear masks in the commercial. I'm looking at masks all day. And I come home
and all I see is faces Ooh, ugly if I put a mask on that.
John: Put a mask on it. You know what? I hate? I don't want to be the sexist everyone thinks I am. I don't like that. So there you run into this
situation. And again, I just happened the other day. It's like there's some leggy girl or is it somebody with great legs? This is make it be honest
about all right. And she's got the mask on and then you start seeing you wonder
Adam: you're wondering what what is does the face mat match the rest of the
John: great body match the lake or is it an older woman with great legs disease see that everyone would run into that in Florida.
Adam: This is also a godsend for older women because they can have a scar for something like Nancy Pelosi you have a nice you know a scarf that you
have around your neck. You can pull up if you need a mask situation but in the meantime, a women loves hiding their you know if they are unhappy with
their neck that a lot of older women are and so that it's it can work as a fashion statement for them.
John: Well, on the topic of these mess, I do have an Amy Goodman clip well before you do that epitomizes Well, I'm sorry.
Adam: Well, I have to apologize first. You can't just like well, I made a mistake. I made a mistake on the last show. I made a big deal about the
Fauci clip which was listed as may 6 turns out it was March 6, and and he was clearly saying no mask whatsoever. It's not necessary. It's even dumb.
And right and people got mad at me john may This is why we can't listen anymore coming so obsessed with
John: Rob you got two letters.
Adam: Okay, dude, I get my letters and your mood
John: and your let's be serious. I
Adam: get my letters and your letters so stop with me. I want to play the original then I want to get to Amy cuz I have a Judy and Judy will lead to
Amy that makes a lot I don't
John: know Amy's about the masks. I know. I know
Adam: this is about the mask. This is Fauci on the mask, Judy.
John: I saw this that this breakdown of Fauci The thing was labeled. It would when the when the clip went out, and it was criticizing you for playing
this clip and giving a wrong date. There's two things one, it was mislabeled. I saw this. I saw these these clips. They had a mis label on them. They
were labeled May. And the second thing is this is proving that Fauci was a debt into the whole thing early on, and now they're blaming Trump with
quotes, which I have on certain clips, I have a clip saying, oh, and Trump wouldn't listen to Fauci, Fauci was not into this until later.
Adam: So here is the original. This is from March, and even though it's an outdated opinion, I don't see how the science of what he's saying changes.
Unknown: Right now in the United States. People should not be walking around with masks. You're sure that because people are listening really cool. To
the right now people should not be worried there's no reason to be walking around with a mask. When you're in the middle of an outbreak, wearing a
mask might make people feel a little bit better. And it might even block a droplet. But it's not providing the perfect protection that people think
that it is. And often, there are unintended consequences. People keep fiddling with the mask and they keep touching their face, then can you get some
schmutz is sort of staying inside their horse, of course, but when you think mask, you should think of healthcare providers needing them and people
who are ill.
Adam: So very clear, it sounds to me like he's talking scientifically, this just makes no sense. By the way, have some hair that's cut off your head
fall in, in between your mask and your face. See how that feels is very, very shitty experience. So now we have April 3, so that's still a month ago.
Here's Judy on PBS asking Pope Fauci about the masks again, masks. Oh, by the way, that's my ISO candidate
Unknown: masks, we are told that the Trump administration is on the verge of urging Americans to wear masks when they go out. Tell us about the
thinking on that. Because just a few days ago, we were told that the thinking was that was not necessary.
John: It's a great question, Judy. And the thinking is I could
Adam: there's no way to edit anything after that great question,
Unknown: that the thinking was that was not necessary?
It's a great question, Judy. And the thinking is really now influenced by information that's coming in. And the information is that more and more
accumulation of data indicate that people who are without symptoms at all can transmit the virus. But importantly, they can do it merely by speaking.
Adam: Now this, I'd I want to see this report. I don't know what he's referring to. But now you can transfer it before it was a droplet may be highly
unlikely now, just the force of your voice.
Unknown: So there's a shot? Yeah,
John: there was I just want to mention that I picked up on this and a couple recent clips. I may even have one of them. I'm not sure. Because I didn't
think I didn't think it was it was a trend. But yet they're saying that talking? Yeah, just talking just goes back to your theory about the mass being
just a muscle, a muscle,
Adam: it's a muscle, we, you're talking up? Thank you. It's a good point, just by talking you're you're very dangerous. Yeah,
John: muscle, they can do it merely by speaking. So there's been a recent study that came out that said, even the force from your voice of speaking,
there is a degree of aerosolization. Namely, the virus can come out not very far, a few feet and down. So even though the perfect solution to this is
if everyone at all times could stay six feet separated.
Adam: So in all the years in 35 years of, of infectious diseases and viruses. Now all of a sudden, this one is different than all the rest, were just
the force of your voice can go out a few feet and down, and it can kill people. It's just I'm surprised. I'm just surprised times it's a genius virus
John: has ever spoken to an acrobat 11 East fishmarket? No, well, they spit on you stay six feet separated from another person. But as you correctly
mentioned, this is not always feasible. There are times when you have to do necessary functions, you have to get food, you have to get drugs from the
pharmacy. And you might inadvertently be in a situation where you're close enough where that kind of transmission can take place. And importantly, I
think what people don't fully appreciate, is that putting a mask on yourself is more to prevent you from infecting someone else. Alright, so
Adam: but it's still not a legal requirement. It's not something you have to do by law. And why? Well, because unfortunately, we can't throw people in
jail.
Unknown: And the same question about masks that I was asking about staying at home, if these are things that that save lives, keep people healthy, why
not require them to do this?
John: You know, Judy, I understand where you're coming from. But it becomes difficult when you say required by what by penalty by putting people in
jail. I mean, that becomes you know, something that really can be counterproductive in the society that we live in, in America, perhaps you might be
able to do that in China. Difficult to do it here. So
Adam: notice how he says he doesn't say, Well, if you want that kind of crazy, you got to go to China. That's where they force the people to do stuff.
No, he's saying, you got to be China. If you want that. It's just wink wink nudge nudge.
Unknown: You might be able to do that in China. But I think it would be difficult to do it here. So what we're relying on is two people to really
understand the importance of this.
Adam: Yes. And the importance indeed so after the the hair hairdresser on the way home I'm like, I'm hungry. I'm going to get me a sausage biscuit and
to hash brown at McDonald's in the drive thru. And this was my experience because the order taker who already you know, they have the headset with a
microphone, so she had a mask on she had a mask on I like Could I have a sausage biscuit at what Yeah, I'll have a Dr. Pepper. I just gave up. I said,
I don't know what you're saying. Give me hashbrown
John: Hendry
Adam: Oh my goodness.
John: So that was a good good bit
Adam: but what do you think of this of this isoh masks printer show?
John: I think is boring but I don't have anything to get people with this. Why don't
Adam: you have you ever given no standing if you have nothing to compete with? had nothing to tell me my kids boards you guys okay. All right. Let's
see what do you got? What am
John: I this is back to the idea. This is the original idea and I think this is more important than the lot of this especially Trump people in jail
part. Although I do like the bit you should bit of the person wearing a mask and by the way, they're isolated anyway, they're over by themselves the
people that are on the McDonald's microphone, but okay. This is a me talking about a big con fab going on. And there was Trump he had one of these two
with the governor of Nebraska and the governor of Colorado and and just you when they pulled the camera back at two sides of the room that Colorado
Governor's wearing a mask and his assistant was wearing masks on one side and the other side did to demo the republicans from Nebraska word and Amy
notices this elsewhere. And it's it's becoming a thing.
Unknown: Republican Rand Paul of Kentucky
Adam: The fruit is this the one concepts that we want? Because I've
John: tuned What did was read up it says Amy wrap mastics
Adam: because you mentioned concept that's why it's Alright, here we go.
Unknown: Well, we're gonna start today in Washington DC. As President Trump claims the US is prayer to prepare to transition to greatness. And the
COVID-19 death toll surpasses 81,002 of the nation's top scientists told a Senate committee Tuesday that needless death would result if states
reopened too soon. The Stark warning from the nation's top infectious disease expert Dr. Anthony Fauci and Dr. Robert Redfield, the director of the
Centers for Disease Control and Prevention came just a day after NBC News published an unreleased White House report showing a surge of Coronavirus
cases, US communities,
Adam: okay, now we have to watch out for this word because now they're just throwing it in anywhere they want. And what is what is the definition of a
surge
John: isn't a number if you have one case in your county and then you have to
Adam: a sudden powerful forward or upward movement especially by a crowd or by natural force. That's to be more than putting
Unknown: Nashville Tennessee and Des Moines Iowa Central City Kentucky topped the list. The report based on a may 7 internal memo directly contradicts
Trump's claim Monday that the number of COVID-19 cases is rapidly declining around the country. In a surreal scene, Dr. Fauci Dr. Redfield and food
and drugs Commissioner Dr. Steven Hahn all join the Senate Health Committee remotely while they quarantine after being exposed to the virus, or to a
staffer at the White House who tested positive. Republican senator lamar alexander from Tennessee was also in quarantine. After his staffer tested
positive, he presided over the hearing from his home of the senators who joined the hearing in person. Most democrats wore masks or balaclavas. Most
republicans did not wearing masks. Senator susan collins of Maine began the hearing without a mask but put one on during republican senator Dr. Rand
Paul of Kentucky. The first senator known to test positive for the virus did not wear a mask
John: is so important for her.
Adam: Oh, yeah, well, the mask,
John: didn't wear a mask and he was exploiting he, you know, had tested positive and they make it You're right. It's just dis shaming all the time.
This is to get this is all about Trump.
Adam: Yes. And do you know why or when? When it will be safe to go outside without a masti I because I know when there's going to be an exact moment
that we will all feel safe. Do you have any idea what that is? No, but I bet you do. It's when the soccer mom says so. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
John: This should this be on the Twitter? I
Adam: think I did. I don't remember that.
John: Oh, somebody.
Adam: I just don't want to read something from Washington Post a buried lead. I feel and this was one of those things come out.
Unknown: Monday.
Adam: During a taskforce meeting Wednesday, a heated discussion broke out between Deborah Burks. That's the ambassador Lieutenant Colonel General, the
physician who oversees the administration's Coronavirus response and Robert Redfield, the director of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.
Burks and others were frustrated with the CDC antiquated system for tracking virus data, which they worried was inflating some statistics such as
mortality rate and case count by as much as 25%. According to four people present for the discussion or later briefed on it, which of course, I can't
believe this either, because we cannot believe it in any case, but I'm just reading it to senior administration officials said the discussion was not
heated. Quote, there is nothing from the CDC that I can trust. Burke said according to the to two of the people, Redfield defended his agency, but
there was general agreement that the CDC is in need of a digital upgrade. Oh, that'll fix the problem. What do you do an abacus counting? We're
relying on this data of who dies of what and oh,
Unknown: well, we're shootable. We've got more.
John: I actually have a couple of clips regarding this. One Fauci is the one that saying, Well, I think the numbers are probably a lot lower than they
really are.
Adam: I'm sorry, he's saying exactly the opposite. I have. He had a whole testimony where he said is probably double what it is. Yes, what I said no.
You said you said the opposite. He said the numbers are much lower. Say you said much lower.
John: No, I I would I would ask you to go back. But Fauci says that the numbers are. I probably put it poorly. You did. Fauci has been saying that the
numbers are higher than we're reporting. He says
Adam: he says he believes it's double.
John: And other people like you said you are saying the opposite,
Adam: including Burks, who is Fauci Burke's.
John: Well, listen to this one. I got a good one here. This one is doo doo doo doo doo doo doo bop. Like find find it I've got my clips are still not
well organized. Rick bright now. Trump, Trump Trump.
Adam: This is fun. love hearing you struggles. Okay, we got time. No one's going anywhere. I can play a little interlude music if you'd like while you
look for that. might might
John: well let's do the big con. Well, I want to go back to the damy clip first. You missed a little push little gotcha in there. She had. Okay. She
made the point. If she made a point. In that clip of saying that the report the democrats are not only wearing masks, but they were wearing a
balaclava so I heard it I laughed even with a lot of lavas black lava, whatever, however you pronounce it klava. Yeah. What is what? What are the, you
know what these things are? They're just like the Muslim thing. This brings us back to Sir-onimous. And his claim that we're being turned into a
Sharia state.
Adam: That's a good one. I forgot about that. Yeah. Yeah. balaclava. There's, well, a balaclava to me just looks like just some kind of curve chief.
John: Well, if you look it up, it's difficult or the full face once and cover your whole age. Right. Right. And then there's the ones that are the
ones that could be printed with.
Adam: That's, that's interesting, because I don't think a single person was wearing an actual balaclava, you're right.
John: That's not true at the meeting with Trump and the Colorado governor, his health director was
Adam: well, a balaclava the definition is a close fitting garment covering the whole head and neck except for parts of the face. So what happens is he
would have to go over your face over your head and you have the eyes and the mouth open. also seen in many clubs in Amsterdam. This outfit
John: is funny.
Adam: I found your clip. It's cold. desk exaggerated COVID
John: desk exam. Here's this is a classic
Unknown: for all we have to point out Illinois own state health director who had a recent
John: second. This is your buddy Laura Ingraham. And I have a few clips from her. But she I believe she actually says Illinois.
Unknown: For all we have to point out Illinois on state health director who had a recent press conference, just casually admitted this,
if you were in hospice, and had already been given, you know, a few weeks to live, and then you also were found to have COVID, that would be counted
as a COVID death, even if you died of a clear alternate cause, but you had COVID at the same time, it's still listed as a COVID death.
Adam: Well, this story, of course, has been told 1000 times on 1000 YouTube videos by 1000 doctors This is the consistent story
John: everyone knows is very consistent. In fact, those two doctors that were taken down, they was at work, same thing. were taken down by YouTube,
discuss this in great detail, but it just keeps coming up. Yes. And Shep Fauci right, Bochy says the opposite is true.
Adam: Yeah, Fauci says is probably double. Then he said that in testimony, and that's when everyone went apeshit once again. And I have the I Have you
ever met Ron Paul, I gotta rent. I don't know ron paul's book, I got a Rand Paul clip,
John: we have the Rand Paul clip. That's Rand Paul. I put ron paul because it was late.
Adam: Okay. Is it the same as mine? Because I already got a cued up? Let me see. Is it is it the testimony that you have or
John: I don't have the testimony? No, I have them discussing, I believe with Judy are one of the
Adam: Oh, well, how about this? Why don't I play what he said in the senate? Rand Paul, and then we'll go to what he said at Judy, how's that sound?
John: If it's, if it's related,
Adam: yeah, it's about the schools and about getting back to life.
John: I think he's just sitting here with Joe. He's just moaning.
Adam: Hold on. Let's listen to this with
Unknown: regard to going back to school. One thing that was left out of that discussion,
Adam: I should probably mention that Rand Paul, I think he's a physician is the ophthalmologist. But he's a physician.
John: He's an ophthalmologist. Yes, but he's still he's a doctor.
Adam: He's a doctor, he's
John: a doctor is an MD?
Unknown: Is mortality. I mean, shouldn't we at least be discussed? Put
Adam: it this way? He's more MD than tadros. That's for sure.
Unknown: Going back to school, one thing that was left out of that discussion, is mortality. I mean, shouldn't we at least be discussing what the
mortality of children is? This is for Dr. Fauci as well, you know, the mortality between zero and 18. In the New York data approaches zero, it's not
going to be absolutely zero, but it almost approaches zero between 18 and 45, the mortality in New York was 10, out of 100,000. So really, we do need
to be thinking about that we need to observe with an open mind what went on in Sweden, where the kids kept going to school, the mortality per capita
and Sweden is actually less than France, less than Italy, less than Spain, less than Belgium, less than the Netherlands, about the same as
Switzerland.
Adam: God bless the Swedes, man, God bless you. Thank you.
John: For Switzerland. He
Adam: mentioned nobody does Sweden. He's a Sweden's the one that stayed open. And I said, God bless Sweden. God bless him for doing that. Otherwise,
we'd
Unknown: have no other proof. But basically, I don't think there's anybody arguing that what happened in Sweden is an unacceptable result. I think
people are intrigued by it. And we should be. I don't think any of us are certain when we do all these modeling. There have been more people wrong
with modeling than right. We're opening up a lot of economies around the around the US. And I hope that people who are predicting doom and gloom and
saying, Oh, we can't do this, there's going to be a surge, sir, admit that they were wrong if there isn't a surge, because I think that's what's going
to happen in rural states. We never really reached any sort of pandemic levels in Kentucky and other states, we have less deaths in Kentucky than we
have in us in an average flu season. It's not to say this isn't deadly. But really outside of New England, we've had a relatively benign course for
this virus nationwide. And I think the one size fits all that we're gonna have a national strategy and nobody's going to go to school is kind of
ridiculous, we really ought to be doing it school district by school district, and the power needs to be dispersed because people make wrong
predictions. And really, the history of this when we look back will be of wrong prediction after wrong prediction after wrong prediction, starting
with Ferguson in England. So I think we ought to have a little bit of humility in our belief that we know what's best for the economy. And as much as
I respect to Dr. falchi, I don't think you're the end Hall. I don't think you're the one person that gets to make a decision. We can listen to your
advice. But there are people on the other side saying there's not going to be a surge and then we can safely open the account. And the facts will to
bear this out. But if we keep kids out of school for another year, what's going to happen is the poor and underprivileged kids who don't have a parent
that's able to teach them at home, are not going to learn for a full year. And I think we got to look at the Swedish model. And we got to look at
letting our kids get back to school. I think it's a huge mistake if we don't open the schools in the fall.
Adam: So Fauci is, is obviously being worshipped, certainly by elements in the media and politicians, and he's untouchable no matter how many times he
contradicts himself or said it was no big deal. And I think you've got some clips coming up. There's one thing I wanted to mention about Fauci. When,
now when when we were looking well, when the Vatican was looking for a new pope. I predicted this Pope by name. And I want to tell you, and I think I
explained how I did that. But I did it by looking for to well really, for looking for one that I knew was going to be some priests from South America.
And I knew it had to be a new world order guy because I am a firm believer that the last real Pope was pope john paul, the first to by the way, is was
eliminated after exactly 33 days. On on his papal throne, one of those magic numbers that we're always wary of,
John: yeah, he was. That was essentially what the Godfather three movie was about. Yeah. Well, assassination of a pope,
Adam: right?
Unknown: Well,
Adam: I think he was he was the real deal. And then they had to get some of these new world order guys in and then I saw that the Francis that he's a
Jesuit. Now, I only know one Jesuit. I mean, really, no, not, well, not really, really know, but I know him well enough. And that's the Padre from
twit. And looking at his psychological profile, which I think is representative of the, of the Jesuit model is that of, well, unwanted submission to
control. And there's also a lot of historical stuff about the Jesuits and Freemasonry. And before, you know, you're down the rabbit hole of
Illuminati. But it turns out Fauci is also a Jesuit. And then it kind of comes together. You've got the Pope. He's sitting there and the Vatican with
his billion dollar Empire. And here's Fauci sitting there at NIH with this billion dollar Empire telling people what to do. I think he has a bit of a
god complex and it's being played into, if not a much deeper agenda.
John: Yeah, that's an interesting point. I didn't know he was a Jesuit. I'd
Adam: only found out myself just a couple days ago, Mike, Oh, that's interesting. I really don't. Hey, if you're a Jesuit sitting at home, and you're
mad at me, then let me know what's going
John: on. I'm sure we have a number of Jesuits who listen to the show because they have to. Yes.
Adam: Yes. Exactly. Exactly. Something to follow, you know, people yeah.
John: So but now she mentioned Sweden. I want to bring up Laura Ingraham clip because this is when she did this. She's doing this new CES you know,
they got all these gimmicky things they do and she's got this traders frauds and winners or some I don't know what it is.
Adam: And I
John: datum angle finger kind of thing. She does. Okay, so she but this would once she did this little, little, little bit. These are all short. I
thought to myself, besides thinking about Sweden, I said, This isn't being covered very well. She's absolutely correct. And this is the Ingraham,
Florida and Georgia clip.
Unknown: And now on to the frauds. Let's start with Pennsylvania health Secretary Rachel Levine, who weeks ago ordered nursing homes to admit COVID
positive patients. Well, while 1000s of residents saw their loved ones and family members die, Levine quietly extracted her own mother out of harm's
way, reportedly moving her from a nursing home to a hotel.
My mother requested and my sister and I his her children comply to move her to another location during the covid 19 outbreak. My mother is 95 years
old. She is very intelligent and more than competent to make her own decision.
I'd rather have her mother be health secretary of Pennsylvania frankly.
John: Well, this Oh, that wasn't the Ingraham, Florida and Georgia clip was it?
Adam: I thought it was
John: I thought that was Ingraham on Pennsylvania health Secretary clip
Adam: on I apologize. It's the I Alright, now we try that again with with the curriculum.
John: No. Well, yeah, I want to go back to the Florida and drill but since you played
Adam: that clip, yeah. There's something to say about it.
John: I wanted I want to play it again because I want you to listen to this woman who is the Pennsylvania health secretary. She's a very strange
looking person. She's kind of a squat fat woman with a long gray scraggly hair. And she talks and sounds and if you listen to that clip, I don't
believe that if you look back on it, you think it was a woman at all? It sounds just like a guy. Now, is it a transgender person who is the health
secretary in Pennsylvania? an old, old transgender? I don't know. Well, let's just give voice that this woman is just just a head shaker.
Adam: Oh, okay. This is Rachel Levine. Oh, yeah. No, she's a she's a she's obviously a transsexual.
John: Okay, well, that makes sense with a voice. Yeah. Play played again. Listen to that. Okay, well, I don't even need to play it again.
Adam: Now onto the frozen to it.
Unknown: Let's start with Pennsylvania health Secretary Rachel Levine, who weeks ago ordered nursing homes to admit COVID positive patients. Well,
while 1000s of residents saw their loved ones and family members die, Levine quietly extracted her own mother out of harm's way. Reportedly moving her
from a nursing home to a hotel.
My mother requested and my sister and I his her children comply to move her to another location. During Yeah,
Adam: obviously. Yeah. Well, okay. That's an observation. I don't know if it's
John: off putting all right now here's, here's she is talking about this is the story that I did. Nobody's gonna want to cover apparently, if it's any
of its true, but this is the Florida and Georgia clip.
Adam: You don't want to talk about those elderly homes for a minute, you want to go straight to the Florida and Georgia? Well, I
John: all I was interested in is to is the fact that they would that this 95 year old woman was moved out of the home when they moved all the COVID
people in it's just kind of, well, no, this is worth this talk about this is it's the sick situation, I don't understand what very,
Adam: this is very important to stop. This is the this is the problem. So first of all, it's not discussed, because if it's brought up, and really you
delve into it, you will find that Governor Cuomo made a mistake. And at the end of March ordered sick people COVID-19 patients to be put temporarily
in nursing homes and homes for the elderly, and allowed for COVID-19 positive staff to continue working in nursing homes
John: that may lead him to be president.
Adam: But okay, so let me just let me just break this down for a second. This is obviously now that we have the numbers. And it turns out that over
60% of all infections took place in the home, and over 50% in New York of the deaths are in nursing homes. So I'm sure that Cuomo or whoever made this
decision is not an evil bastard. And it was a mistake, someone was not thinking probably because they were completely obsessed and preoccupied with
the surge and the hospital system. And this killed people. And it has to be admitted that someone has to say, you know what, we made a really big
mistake here. And we learn from it. But the in the United States in particular, but look at Italy, every other country, it's people over 75 and mainly
those who are in, in this case, state run cares, we don't give a shit about the elderly in the United States. We don't care about them.
John: Sorry, let me get this straight. What you're advocating is that somebody admitted to making a mistake, you have to because people are not judges
society like this, somebody's gonna make it you're gonna make a statement like that?
Adam: If so, if no one makes the statement, then what will happen is there will be lawsuits is going to be a horrible, that may happen anyway. But we
all for the death toll in general, we have all these people dead, whether it's legitimate count or not. It's important for us to understand it's not
children. And it's mainly people, the majority of people who died were elderly, in care in in nursing care facilities, who by the way, shared it with
COVID-19 positive patients and staff that would help people understand
John: this put forth. How does this put forth the Biden democratic agenda?
Adam: No, I'm not. I'm speaking as a human being. I'm not speaking as a media analyst. I'm speaking as someone who says that this will not fly. You
have to admit the mistake and because we know it already, the information is out there and no one's gonna take anything seriously. And I'm sorry Cuomo
or his team made a horrible mistake. And we have to acknowledge it and move on and mark it down as something we won't do in the future right next to
don't open up the hair salons 48 hours before they know. I mean, come on. This is this is a learning moment. I'm sorry people died.
John: This doesn't help the Trump clock. That's gonna go up.
Adam: Well, that's really, this is really sick that
Unknown: oh Hmm.
Adam: So what So what you're saying is in order to get it Trump, I cannot deduce this just what you are implying is Trump is hated so much. We have to
up the people dead. Who do we have? Um, pocket? How about those old people send some COVID over there. That's what you're saying. Yeah. Well, if
that's true, then God save the Republic.
John: Well, it's gonna need saving the way these guys are
Adam: operating. Now. You're being facetious. You don't really think that's true.
John: I'm not completely facetious. I'm skeptical. Wow. I know nobody's apologizing and that's not gonna happen.
Adam: But it's also good to know that most people really are not at a huge risk of dying. It's interesting. I had this I issue and we talked about it
on the show and then
John: Sunday after the show I wish I could take it a picture and posted it.
Adam: It was ugly. Sunday after the show I get email after email after text message. Dude, dude, dude, dude. This is this is this how it starts for
some people in fact, I I got Agent Orange who was down for 10 days he says Oh, it started with me with an infected eyelid and then the runny nose and
then the cough and then I was out for 10 days. And and one after the other. I'm like, Oh my god, how what poetic justice to give me the Rona. So of
course the eye passes. But the last night which is like after dinner is like 715 730 and we're outside drinking a coffee and all of a sudden my nose
starts running like crazy. like crazy
John: the power of suggestion ladies and gentle well and you know what i did
Adam: against that for the power suggestion I I thought to myself, what would Jcd do? So I immediately went and grabbed 50 50,000 mega mega box of
vitamin D hammer that shit down. And it's gone. I am not dripping from the nose so I don't know what it was. But I feel
John: good about it. They might have been right is a good thing to jump down to d3
Adam: is it ww Jcd came we came right and Ryan's not a doctor, you are not a doctor, but I was very happy.
John: Very happy it is I I think I had to say I had a similar not an eyeball thing. Followed by that. But I thought I was catching something during
the era that JC buzzkill jr had, he did have it. And apparently, Jesse had a diversion where you'd lost your sense of smell. Yes, I've
Adam: heard that I've heard this too.
John: During that little period, I was sketching something. And it was like this this is this and it was weird too. It wasn't like the normal kind of
like oh, I think I'm getting a cold I'm getting the flu or something. Right. And I just said I'm just taking the D I have to take some d3 and it was
going that was the end of that and it was all over. We'll see it down the road if you have antibodies anyway. Let's go to Okay, I think we're over
with dead load segment let's talk about the Florida and Georgia thing which is what I wanted to discuss initially
Adam: Yeah, that was the initial idea
Unknown: the two states that opened up first Florida and Georgia both are continuing to see declines and COVID infections while shocking the liberal
haters but not to you because we told you that the virus was probably weakening and that people would innovate to stay safe and
innovate
John: know what she means you innovate me six feet apart or who knows what to whatever how in the case nobody is discussing the you know when Georgian
more than Florida yes
Adam: they were they busted wide open so what's going on everything's fine
John: and everybody jumped all over the republican governor because you know Stacey Abrams wouldn't have done this no state
Adam: locked up in the Bay State yeah in the basement you'd be still
Unknown: yeah
Adam: she's a Stacey Abrams would never make a mistake like that but otherwise I guess it's just fabulous then
John: well well the whole This is just as getting more and more promises is not this is a new world order. I you know the amazing Polly found some
documents saying this whole thing was a test.
Adam: Of course I've seen amazing Bollea is amazing.
John: So amazing. Polly does this thing and it's and by the way, if you get the last newsletter is a link in there, it's still up it won't be up
forever cuz it People see this and they there's nothing in there that's inaccurate. She's just taking from official documents and showing them and but
they find ways to go, Oh, no, this is bad. It's bad influence on the done the youngins or something. I don't know why they take her down.
Adam: Well, the beauty of it all, is that in certainly in the United States, not so in other countries, but in the United States. It is all voluntary.
I mean, we have court case after court cases being struck down against people who are being arrested, etc. So it is really up to us. And and that's
it's actually much bigger and much more frightening to me that we have this social control of
John: shaming, shaming. Yeah, it
Adam: truly is shaming. I mean, just just because we're still on opening up and stuff. I have two clips about California. Because it's very confusing.
Is California open is a closed Mayor guard city at our city of Los Angeles County has extended the stay at home order through August.
Unknown: But what does that mean? Let's start with the stay at home orders. I know your top health official said yesterday expect to extend the orders
for another three months in order.
But explain exactly what that means. Sure, I think we have to all recognize that we're not moving to Arne COVID-19. We're learning to live with it.
It's important not to overreact. But it's important to take this serious because it is as dangerous today, as it was the first day that it arrived in
our cities in our country. So quite frankly, there's no so called Open state or open country that doesn't continue to have health orders, telling us
to cover our faces physically distance, and to tell people that you're safest working from and staying at home. That's all that the county health
director was saying. And we can't expect that to disappear in a matter of weeks or even a few months. At the same time. We're learning a lot of really
important lessons about how to safely reopen sectors and places. And we have to assess each of those steps give three or four weeks time to see Is
there any additional spread? Are we endangering more people? And how can we keep our most vulnerable safe, so we are learning to live with it at the
same moment that we are also learning the lessons of how to do that.
Adam: So I believe that, that he also recognizes he has absolutely no power to tell people or to keep people at home. They're just using new world
order terms. Now stay at home order doesn't mean you have to stay at home because they can't actually enforce it. It's a trick. It's a mind control.
Well, we're learning to deal with it stay at home, you know, it's learning to deal with it. We're learning here, now your mind controlling people into
feeling unsafe and afraid of other people. And so the restaurants like Texas, open up with spread out and I think it's 25% capacity, Max for the next
foreseeable, whatever. And then in California, I will say here's some of your innovation. All right.
Unknown: What do we got here? We've got Oh, look at look at this. Look closely at this.
That's a restaurant
that's using mannequins to fill out the half empty dining room.
What's the story behind this one?
Adam: Because it looks so crappy. They're putting mannequins at the other table. So the restaurant looks more fun and fool instead of actual people.
Smoke and Mirrors out there. lala land.
John: Wow.
Adam: Yeah, so that one, yeah. So it's
John: who's got that kind of money? Those things aren't cheap. Those good mannequins.
Adam: Who's got it? You can't You can't run a restaurant at 25% capacity. You can run it at 50 you can't run it. You can't It's crazy. What you don't
John: this shaming thing. Let's get back to the shaming. Okay, this is interesting. It's just like the whole thing is like the it's the democrats that
are the shamers because the democrats are the shamers let's just be honest about it.
Adam: No, no, but even johannah was she recognized it and said it she's I'd never expected this kind of shaming from liberals.
John: Yeah, shame, shame. Shame on you. Yeah. Which of course, eventually show tries to become Shame on you for voting for Trump. Shame on you for
being a Republican. Yes.
Adam: If you vote for Trump, you're voting for the virus. you vote. Vote for Trump.
John: Democrats strategies all over that mean? A vote for Trump is a vote for the virus giving
Adam: it away ladies and gentlemen that was $100,000 idea and two points of all the Media Buy dammit. dammit dammit dammit should have known better.
So what is going to what? It's weird because the testing is now has been kind of it's not really in the conversation at the moment is going to watch
it well. No, it's not not the way it was. But it's going to come roaring back because China just made their move. I think I think this is a move
against Trump. And Xi jingping. He says, the CCP will be testing 14 million people in Wu Han in 10 days time.
Unknown: 14 years old Trump
John: has been showing this chart,
Adam: go, yeah, this is an information war. And China is saying ha, look at you with your stupid orange man over there, we're going to test 14 million
people in Wu Han in 10 days, which means you've got about 15 you have to have that's 900 tests a minute, for 24 hours a day for 10 days. So I don't
know what kind of Army and if they're going to go into people's homes and Rouse them or how they're going to get that done in 10 days,
John: take a probe up them but
Adam: but this whole thing is, isn't it? I don't think it's true. It may well be but I'd be surprised. It's to make China look like they're the
they're the boss. They're doing it the best way. This is the way to go world health and World Health Organization we know what's up. Trump Bad, bad,
bad, bad. It's it's not going to end with this testing, which is like the ultimate we cannot go back to work. We cannot fully function until we test
everybody every day, five times a day. And
John: we had a vaccine. The irony did the testing is the obvious, which is that the more you test, the more cases you uncover, because most people
don't have symptoms and never will. Yeah, so you have so that makes the numbers go up. And then that numbers go up and makes you need for more
testing, which means the numbers go up even more, and then we got to stay at home longer. Because there's more numbers, there's a surge, there's more
cases, what are we going to do? We're all gonna die.
Adam: I'd like to do a quick review of the $3 trillion package that the Democrat Party announced to be discussed to be was introduced into the house
because I read it, and it wasn't hard to do because I
John: will. Okay, I want you can you do that after I give to play two clips? namely, Amy's take on it? Yeah, definitely. Trump's rebuttal.
Adam: Yeah, definitely.
Unknown: Okay.
Where are we?
John: Well, I guess this is not my day. But let's try this. Let's try the big con fab. Maybe that's the one that's got the stuff about the bill.
Unknown: Republican Rand Paul of Kentucky, the first senator known to No no, no, no,
Adam: that's can't be a loser relief bill promoted by dnn dn Is that it? DNS?
John: Yeah, that's apparently it.
Unknown: on Capitol Hill House Democratic leaders
Adam: have unveiled a map Don't be so damn creative with your titles because it's messing up the workflow the war.
John: That was a really bad title.
Adam: Loser, loser relief bill, promoted by dn od. I mean, that's a title man. That is a damn title right there.
Unknown: on Capitol Hill House Democratic leaders have unveiled a massive 1800 page Coronavirus relief package worth $3 trillion. The so called heroes
Act would fund expanded unemployment benefits through January 2021. Send most US adults another one time 12 $100 stimulus check and provide $1
trillion in assistance to hard hit state, local and tribal governments. It would also expand snap food benefits fund hazard pay for frontline workers
increased funding for COVID-19 testing and provide $25 billion in funding to the US Postal Service. The bill would not expand Medicare to cover
millions of newly uninsured Americans nor does it provide for rent and mortgage relief or recurring cash payments to US households. The bill would
expand the paycheck protection program to bailout corporate lobbyists firms. Climate activists say the bill also fails to close loopholes for big
polluters, Greenpeace USA tweeted quote fossil fuel CEOs will be rejoicing that Congress has once again left the door wide open for handouts to
struggling mismanaged oil and gas corporations. Just that
John: this was a slanted report as if this oil was a corrupt bill to protect polluters.
Adam: It is a crap I just want to respond to
John: Trump's response to this just one
Adam: thing before I before I forget the lobbyist thing. I just need to I just need to because that was that was the solution to how she reported that
Because it was it was really lame what she did there to provide
Unknown: for rent and mortgage relief for recurring cash payments to US households, that they'll would expand the paycheck protection program to bail
out corporate lobbyists firms. Okay.
Adam: So to say that because it there's, I read this thing, to my knowledge, nowhere in the bill does it say, oh, here's a special provision for
corporate lobbying firms. That is not reporting what Amy did there that is editorializing because there is a joke now going around in DC, that the
lobbying group that represents lobbyists, has said they need payroll Protection Act money. Otherwise, they can't help Washington. Right, very bills
they're voting on. So it's a circular thing that they want. They want money from the bill they helped write so they can continue to write bills. But
there's nothing in that bill that says he's going to help lobbying firms. But you I so I don't know why. Because it's really a slam against Pelosi,
I'm
John: not sure why, why she would die would think she would be all in. But maybe that's how she makes she imbalanced. She twist the story in such a
way that it's as though the debt the Republicans had some input in this doll their fault. Well,
Adam: believe me, the republican party I see on the hill had no hand in this. Right. Well, here's
John: what Trump is Trump on the Pelosi bill.
Unknown: You agree that stimulus should move forward? There's been some Republicans who suggest that
certainly not the package that I saw today. Basically, if you look at that package, what they want more than anything else, is it's a voting package.
They want to be able to make sure that Republicans can't win an election by putting in all sorts of mailing ballots. Now, that's the problem with mail
in ballots, are they going to dump a whole pile of ballots on your desk, just before the election? So the problem with the mail in ballots is subject
to tremendous corruption, tremendous corruption, cheating, that so I'm against it. And if you look at the bill that Nancy Pelosi is putting in has a
lot to do with elections and that we're not going to, we're not going to lose elections because of that.
Adam: I don't find that to be true. I don't think Trump's truthful, either. I mean, I went through this bill, I reviewed several different reviews of
the bill because there's a lot of legal ease is what this is. It's really and it's typical. It's an omnibus bill, so they take a whole bunch of stuff
that's been waiting around has been sitting, you know, it's been in the process being in committee. It's, you know, it's different people's important
little bills,
John: and like sweeping up the mesh,
Adam: and that yes, and they put it all together into this huge bill and and therefore, it's disjointed. The only way it flows together is by
continuously saying, we're going to get so an example $25 billion to the United States Postal Service to help combat the Coronavirus and COVID-19.
Understand how they do it. So it's just $1 billion to the no agenda show to help combat Coronavirus and COVID-19. If only So, a lot of existing bills
wrapped into one. Almost every inspector general gets a little extra an extra budget usually from a million to several million so that they can
accurately have oversight and investigate any misdoings with the money which is meant to investigate and to support and combat but to combat
Coronavirus and COVID-19 $100 million. And by the way, these numbers you realize like 100 million here 500 million here. It's really nothing we're
talking trillions is 1000 billion, so much money. So 100 million to violence against women and other domestic abuse victims. Community Oriented
Policing, which I I love it sounds like something I want a part of 300 million. There are state bailouts to compensate for revenue shortfall. 540
billion sounds about right. That's what that's what New York, California and an Illinois need. So that's in there. 25 billion, as I said to the United
States Postal Service, couple of billion for some work programs. Every single department gets a top up, you know, hey, you need some money. 30 million
extra for you to combat Coronavirus and COVID-19. Sadly, the Ryan White HIV program loses $10 million. They're taking that away from the dead aids boy
for COVID-19. I don't know why exactly, but they turn around and give half a billion to the NADN II D add which is Fauci his group. He gets $500
million Do you know to combat Coronavirus 7 billion for it states Child Care Services 90 billion for Schools. Then there's the student loan
forgiveness up to $10,000. And of course, there's a 12. Another second stimulus check of 12 $100. And extension of unemployment benefits
infrastructure. Oh, boy, they put it in there $15 billion for highways, which is like, no, that's nothing. But they did add another 15 billion
reserved for overrun, because that's how the government works. You know, it might be double that $100 billion $100 billion for rental assistance. I
don't know what Judy read, but it's right there in the document. $100 billion. For what
John: that would Amy,
Adam: Amy 11 billion assistance for the homeless?
John: Oh, what was she reading? everything you're saying here is an MBA had nothing to do with her interpretation?
Adam: I don't know. I'm, I'm just telling you what I saw 11 billion for the homeless assistance, which, interestingly, interestingly, was not worded
as people experiencing homelessness. It was just homeless assistance. And then they shored up the language around relief funds. So the stimulus so the
SBA loans who can have it, who can't and I think this is the big point that, you know, if you listen to Tucker Carlson, which I did not clip, they're
gonna give the money to illegals.
John: So it's not good enough, you don't need to clip no challenge just like him.
Adam: Nowhere in this document doesn't say that. But remember, this is the heroes act. So the heroes act wants to honor the heroes. And the Heroes is
John: trying to give again, this called the heroes act, right.
Adam: And the heroes include people who are what is the tour? What kind of workers do we have right now we have what we have essential and non
essential. Yeah,
John: so grocery store checkout clerks,
Adam: right.
John: Heroes.
Adam: And as we have discussed many times in the past, in the United States, if you are living here illegally, you are undocumented, if you have a
job, construction, domestic work restaurant kitchen, you can obtain from the IRS at TI n a taxpayer information number, and you can pay taxes every
single month or every two weeks. And you it's completely legit. So you're not committing tax fraud, even though you're here illegally and don't have
all your other papers in order. And of course, there's no payroll, the whole bunch of things that don't work, but this has been accepted behavior for
decades. As long as you pay your taxes in America, it's okay. So what they specified in this bill is how anybody should be eligible for relief funds
retroactively, as long as they have a taxpayer identification number. So you don't have to be here legally. And in addition to that, essential workers
Unknown: cannot be
Adam: deported. They need to be protected these heroes, because they work in kitchens, they work in cleanup, etc. And that's quite a lot of people, a
lot of heroes who are here illegally and work in those jobs and are thus considered essential, wildly legal. And that is it's an amnesty. Because once
you know if it's like hey, during Coronavirus, you can't deport people who work in kitchens, or work in cleaning services or etc. It's quite broad the
podcasters are also essential personnel literally stated podcasting.
John: So that guessing is actually mentioned in the bill.
Adam: Yes, yet not No, no, no, no, no, no, not this one in the one in the original from the federal government, under Media Services, under Media
Services, the original bill or the original recommendation, because there's no bill not sure that Yeah, I am because I put it in the show notes. I
remember these things.
John: I like to see it. God right after I'm just saying it's just that seems unusual. Okay. I've only said put in one document and that was the Los
Angeles County health department's
Adam: I'll get it for you. So anyway, that is, of course, a non starter because it's a sneaky way of providing some form of amnesty and until
Coronavirus is over which it never will be then these people could not be deported or could not be you know, dealt with as illegals
John: but then again, an interesting trick is a well did Tucker's right.
Adam: But but it's not entirely true. He says it. So then there are payroll tax cuts for corporate have employees working during the pandemic and then
all of a sudden a whole telecom section? No price gouging rules. There will be money for free Wi Fi at and around schools and libraries, emergency
broadband for those who cannot afford it. And if you can't afford any kind of phone, or any kind of device, we've got the new Obama phone, and it's a
they call it the enhanced Lifeline with 4g LTE, yeah, you got a 4g LTE Trump phone, exactly. Corona phone. And all of a sudden in there, and this is
how it's so obvious that this is just a bill stuck together by other bills. There's a heading that says Don't break the tea band. Like what? What is
this? It's clearly a slogan. And yes, it is the repeal of the tea band auction for telephony. That's very important for Coronavirus obviously and
whatever lobbyists from the telecommunications industry who put that in there with the existing headline Don't break the tea band that that was really
the for me,
John: that's pretty sloppy
Adam: the build through I was like okay, this is horrible. It's sloppy.
John: I mean, of course Trump already said is do and the Republicans aren't gonna vote for no no. So they're gonna have to redo it. But what if this
is this bad right off the bat and they're gonna massage a little bit could could it get worse? Because eventually something's going to get passed.
Adam: Well, let's listen to Pelosi on tapper just you can get we can get into her head. She's wearing her little crunchy fur around her reptilian
neck. I can say that because I don't like
John: levar she's wearing a bottle it's
Adam: not a buck Lavazza cushy, cushy,
Unknown: and the fact is that an all for the bills that have passed before they've all been bipartisan, and we've all in our caucus have agreed that
everything is Coronavirus, centric, and also in a timely way that relates to the virus. It's too deadly to our lives to our livelihood, to our
democracy, for us to use it for any other purpose. So when the money for state and local it's to lay the cost of the defray the cost of the outlays
they've made for Coronavirus and the revenue loss because of the Coronavirus Testing, testing the three pillars honor are here. This
Adam: is very interesting. Listen to how she doesn't she doesn't really care about anything. But power.
John: And yes. Did you notice that she was about to say yes. That's why starting testing that's
Adam: why I stopped it. She's about to say a number of things here which she just listened to what she's really saying. And you tell me if she's
concerned about the virus or about her position and party and and well, man bad
Unknown: Coronavirus Testing, testing the three pillars.
Adam: Okay, the three pillars? I thought it was gonna be testing, testing, testing, but the three pillars Oh, no, it's very different.
Unknown: I know our heroes, by supporting our state and local entities, honor our heroes so that they don't lose their jobs, these heroes don't lose
their jobs. Open up How
Adam: about opening up the hospitals for other things, Nancy, instead of Oh, honor that? What does it mean? How do I honor our heroes so they don't
lose their jobs? What can I do with my honoring them? How will that how will that possibly help?
Unknown: these heroes don't lose their jobs, open up government by testing, tracing, treatment, etc.
Adam: Testing. Wait a minute. So the most important question we have this is the most powerful woman in American politics. How do we open up our
states? I want to know opening up my state here in Texas,
Unknown: what do I need to do? Again, Nancy is telling us their jobs, open up government by testing, tracing, treatment, etc.
Adam: Testing, tracing treatment, etc. That's worse than Trump's plan.
Unknown: It's not that
Adam: maybe it's just me.
Unknown: And the third is putting money in the pockets of American people. All of it timed and centric to the Coronavirus. We would be an endless
amount of money if we put our wish list for the future and there, but that is not what the case is. And sometimes I get a little heat from my own
folks who say why can we do this in this bill and that and the best because that's not what the bills about. This bill is for this purpose. And it's a
big price. But it's a big problem. And as chairman of the Fed said Think Big because the interest rates will never be lower. And so we are they've
used the interest rates.
Adam: Here. Here it is. This is where she goes into full on partisan mode. She said well, the Secretary said interest rate too low they use it for
that we're gonna use it for this
Unknown: will never be lowered. And so we are they've used the interest rates to give confidence that credit will be available because the interest
rates are low. We want those same interest rates, and they use it to bolster the stock market. We want to use it to bolster the American people.
Adam: So true, Nancy, this woman is horrible. And that leads me to another horrible individual and only because you were talking about the Irish
helicopter money.
Unknown: With Yes, yeah.
John: Troy did you find this started throwing money out knife? I
Adam: thought I found another helicopter from the mooch
Unknown: Anthony, are they doing too much or too little? Well, I
John: think they need more helicopter money to be handed I mean, I we did that analysis. It's about $3,000 a person and 15 $100 for a child and
they're offering of 12 105 100 respectfully. So yes, I think they need to put up more helicopter money, they just injected or they're gonna pass a
quarter million dollar additional small business stimulus. And I predict that they will send more helicopter money to the average American this will
be a main street and Wall Street recovery program.
Adam: Helicopter money helicopter money helicopter money. I guess that should be as a show Title One day a man Geez. Hell helicopter money.
John: Why is he using the term? But maybe he
Adam: has a helicopter and wants to throw some cash out? I don't think I don't think I've ever heard that. I've heard the term but I it's like
helicopter parents. The parents aren't actually flying in a helicopter above the kid. Well, I did because I had a helicopter
John: hovering around. I actually did that.
Adam: Okay, so we've done the bailout. Excuse me?
John: Well, beside before we go on, because she Pelosi did say something there on the interest rates will never get lower. Let's play another Trump
clip from his when his little meeting there. Trump on negative interest rates
Unknown: turned Holliday said that he wasn't interested in bringing interest rates negative and that he saw a need for additional stimulus from
Congress. I know that you said we could wait and see on stimulus and that you, you want negative rates. So you react well
out of labor and negative rates only if other countries that are competitors, with Germany have third ally. They're friends of ours, but they're still
competitors on trade and other things. So Germany, Japan, others have negative rates. And I think if they do, we're the most prime of the world, you
know, where it's based in many countries based on the dollar the dollar is by far the strongest, most powerful currency in the world. We've made it
more powerful, we've made it stronger. And certainly if they're going to have the advantage of negative rates we should do I feel strongly we should
have negative rates, negative rates is basically where they pay you interest. If you borrow money. This is a new one. I've been looking for something
like that all my life. That's a pretty good one. Certainly, if other countries are going to be paid for putting out money, I mean, think of it they're
borrowing money instead of paying interest and getting paid. It's the craziest thing. But you know what other countries are doing it? Look at Germany,
look at Japan, look at others. And we're the most prime in the world right now. And we have this we have the currency and we have we have the power of
the dollar.
Adam: Wow, wow. Just step the hell back and take this one. Clip. So Trump is all in on the negative interest rates. Well,
John: there you go. Not always Yeah, he want he wants it. He doesn't want it and Pelosi is full of shit when she says it won't go any lower
Adam: the right. The end is near. Oh my god. So well. Of course, from his perspective, we're not competitive with our rates. So we have to go to
negative interest rates. Whoo, that's gonna be fun. And all of this a mere day or two before the Bitcoin happening? Oh, my goodness, what is gonna
happen in the world? You know, bitcoins gonna go to $400,000 in the next month or two. So I'm just saying,
John: Yeah, according to Max, you know, you can dump cash or coin and quit to show me.
Adam: Meanwhile, what and give up show business. Oh, yeah, I know. Meanwhile, the European Union is in such a disarray over over Germany. Because
Germany. I think the European Union is now kind of realizing that Germany actually runs the show. And there it is the new German Republic, the new
German Empire, they
John: finally figure this out. Even though the Brits have been telling him this forever. It's Yes. And they're very some Brits. Some Brits have
noticed that. But yeah, we've noticed it.
Adam: Yeah. Very, very dismayed over how things are going financially in the European Union,
John: huh? Yeah. Well, what's the French figured out? Didn't war.
Adam: Yeah, yeah, you're not kidding. Just a little update. I've been working a lot on my on my computer setup. That would I'm pretty much all command
line now. So I also took the time to there. Well, you know what, in
John: the future,
Adam: I have decided that computers are, first of all, they're just getting lower throughput into, from you to the machine and back. I mean, that's is
why we have pads and touch and please don't actually do anything, you can't get the computer do anything unless you unless you go to a system that
lets you program your apps and string them together yourself. It doesn't matter. I wanted to get rid of the contact list thermometer spam, because I
John: wait, wait, what? Okay,
Adam: I keep receiving emails, which is spam, for contact lists, thermometers. You know, the ones pointing your head to lists, which you cannot find
if you want to go buy one at CVS or anywhere. I mean, all thermometers are sold out. So this Spam is all over the place. And it keeps getting through
the spam filter.
John: I've never gotten one of these things ever.
Adam: Well, I'll never get one ever again. Because the word thermometer is the the one and only word banned now. But I figured out what they're doing.
They reverse engineer Basie and logic in the body of the message. So the subject line, they'll literally say contactless thermometer, you need it now
or something like that. And then in the body of the message, they've they have these sentences strung together, which will always include my first
name, and maybe a topic of interest to me, which I think they probably got from you know, maybe it's on a forum or from Twitter or something, they
scrape stuff. And through that, they literally go against the Basie and logic that would determine that to be spam. By putting these elements in and
the spam detector just can't stop it. It's you know who those guys should be advertising for real products? Because they know what they're doing is
very interesting.
John: Well, I'm glad that drove you to to go command line. No, I'm
Adam: totally I'm totally command line. It's actually I'm hjkl. That's where I live.
John: Okay,
Adam: I live in H you know what h J K L is? No, I
John: don't know what h j, k, l l, v, h, j, k, l
Adam: and K and L keys on the keyboard are the universal keys for navigation. on command line. So H is left j is down K is up L is right.
Unknown: And this little wordstar
Adam: Oh, it's the VI works that way. But also if you go to the if you go to Twitter, just the web, Twitter. And you go to just what doesn't matter
what it is hit the J key it'll go down, hit the K key, it'll go up, hit the L key it'll like that, that tweet hit the T key it'll do a retweet. So
this is this has been something that that efficient data engineers have been doing for a long time.
John: That's what they do for a living they
Adam: have two sets of keyboard they get to get things done. And as it turns out, this is what I do for a living I sit at the keyboard all day
managing data, managing emails, managing RSS feeds, managing stories, managing clips. exactly exactly why I did it. I'd like to talk about
John: the brain time What do you think? No,
Adam: no, I think we should do a quick thing on China and then we'll take a break
John: touchwood to China afterwards.
Adam: I'd like China Well it sounds like you've got some China well then we'll take a break
John: God really got no China that's the reason Oh, you just don't want me to do giant maybe I get no
Adam: no, you know what? Nevermind. We will go into a break. Oh, I
John: do have a china clip. Yeah, that's good. We're gonna do that.
Adam: No, no, no, we're gonna do that after the break. But before we before we do that, I do need to play this clip. You've got to ask yourself what
level has john McAfee sunk to if he's doing interviews on the NIC the rat show? clearly, clearly unawares of what the NIC the rat show is.
John: And wait a minute. Hold on. Stop.
Unknown: Hey, wait.
John: So you get a phone call. Hi. Would you like to do my show? What's it called the NIC the rat show. And he's oblivious to the name of the show
itself so much so that he doesn't figure out what's going on or even listen to an old show. JOHN Johnson is sore during a show.
Adam: JOHN McAfee does an interview with anybody. Any buddy regardless of Who you are where you are audience size, it doesn't matter. Which one of the
reasons why I have no interest in speaking with him because he's already been everywhere. But I think that Nick the rat deserves a Congressional Medal
Medal of Honor for asking the following question.
Unknown: We have time for one more question. Okay, one more question. Last question is,
do you know john C. Dvorak used to write for PC Mac,
Adam: I'm sorry, this is not safe for work. And I'm not in the habit of bleeping it out, but it's not safe for work. You have been warned, is he?
Unknown: Apparently, apparently you owe him a lunch.
Nonsense.
That motherfucker owes me way more than a
goddamn lunch. All right.
John: I'm just telling you now. Every time he brings you up, he's
Unknown: like john McAfee. He
owns he owes me a lunch and but I was wondering,
fuck that shit.
He owes me a good articles Matter of fact.
Thank you. My last question. Thank
you so much, john.
Adam: And interview ends of course after that after that fabulous question.
John: Yeah, of course. But you know, I've heard this because Nick sent me a copy, of course. And I thought to myself, first of all is dinner.
Unknown: Yeah, I know. I know.
John: This is this is the so that was irksome. Yep. And then McAfee is full of crap.
Adam: Well, when What is this? He you owe him a good article. What kind of side gigs you running Dvorak?
John: I'm not running anything that he just throws that in. He doesn't. Art. Okay. I'll give you a good article here. I'll mail it to you.
Adam: I think you should do an article about how McAfee is overexposed on low level podcast. Not including Nick the rat, by the way.
John: I have not written about john McAfee since he was doing he says he created the entire virus environment in con computers. It was pretty much
moribund until he popularized it right? He made he popularized it. For all practical purposes.
Adam: Of course he did. It was a brand he was a super brand McAfee was
John: me He first he created the idea of virus
Adam: and then he created viruses to sell virus software, didn't he? Is that how it worked? Well, we don't know that he
John: created any viruses but there's some suspicious, he retired rich because he sold off this whole company that he spent all his money. But
literally,
Unknown: hackers and
John: blow which is kind of but he he, I guess he would he says he I owe him an article because I'm thinking he feels that he's done so many
spectacular things. Not to say that he hasn't because he's definitely been a newsworthy guy. And I should have written something about it. Yes,
Adam: that's true. That's
John: what I think he's thinking, you know, McAfee gets plenty of ink. It doesn't. I don't know what good it's doing.
Adam: I would like I would just like anybody, just someone who's never done a podcast, just to contact McAfee and say, I want you to do a bucket just
make up a crazy name and see if he shows up.
John: Well, you could actually I bet you could do this. And then you could actually get an interview. Say I am going to inaugurate a new podcast Call
it whatever you want to call it called the john McAfee. Dog, john,
Adam: I really don't care.
John: But I think what he would do, he would do it.
Adam: I am very proud of our very own Nick the rat. You can hear Nick the rat Wednesday evenings, he broadcasts live from the sewer. And of course you
can often hear his show on no agenda stream.com where we have all these crazy people, including ourselves and trolls and all kinds of fun and with
that I'd like to thank you for your courage and say in the morning to you the man who put the sea in the China clip block. John
John: Dvorak when Mr. Donohue Mr. Adam Curry also in the morning all the ships as he boots on the ground feet in the air subs in the water and all the
dames and knights out there
Adam: in the morning to the trolls, mentioned them just a moment ago. Let's do a quick troll count. See how we're doing here? Ooh, por lo today 1550
usually like 16 1700
John: leveling off it is what people are
Adam: going back to work I think or have other things you know, Thursday people or other things to do now. Yeah, they
John: shouldn't be listening to a live stream seriously, you
Adam: must have
John: to get a live streaming get the internet. While you're while you're driving. You can probably put it on your car but
Adam: it's true the fun santro the trolls hang out and no agenda stream.com we have a chat there which is 24 seven is IRC you can log in all kinds of
different ways. Even on the go, you can talk to the trolls troll away. And we also simultaneously listen to 24 hours a day seven days a week have no
agenda stream podcast from all around the globe. All talk no commercials completely devoid and free of commercial interests. Therefore probably
stunningly fun to be a reminder that you can get an invite for no agenda social.com our node of the Federation of the true social network of the
internet the Federated mastodon servers We'd love to see you there. And of course you don't have to sign up. You can also just follow any of the
people with no agenda and sign up, just show up no agenda social.com and you can follow me Adam at no agenda social.com also big in the morning to our
artists for episode number 1241. We titled that one curtain Wranglers. And it was good to see cesium 137 back, back again and with a typical cesium
137 Classic piece of art. So well put together. The Chinese McDonald's french fries, the fries are hypodermic needles. We've got a little what was the
goofy? Oh, the Microsoft Bob.
John: Yeah, Microsoft Bob.
Adam: From the background. And a unique font. It was it was a beautiful piece Did we? Did we look at other things that we looked at? Yes,
John: we did. We looked at his competitors, a competitor to it that we looked at. And this was the one that had vaccines with big seanna and Amiga,
the ugly McDonald's, and that was done. But that was done by Nick de rad actually, coincidentally that he
Adam: came in later I think we'd already chosen
John: maybe not. I'm looking now let's see what maybe he may have but but the thing is, Nick and then Twitter said that that I know he came in earlier
actually then cesium cesium came in later I see it now. Yeah. And so he says Well, I Nick, who had me smeared on his show says on Twitter that I was
probably I not you as though I'm picking the art because just not true. Believe me. We both pick the art and we argue about it. He says that I
specifically was afraid of the clown. And then it created the threat of John's afraid of clowns, memes. Oh, boy, that must have kept you busy for an
Adam: afternoon.
John: No, it's just this is blocked. You can block
Adam: I saw the threat of comic strip blogger of being blocked by you. That was pretty funny.
John: Which one? I didn't know what it was.
Adam: Oh, no, exactly. Oh, he was just complaining that you that you blocked him and his his even though you literally said why you blocked him. He
say, hey, it's because he doesn't want me to ask his mother as much as
John: like, my mother's polish.
Adam: Your mother's not even with us. She's dead. She's sorry.
John: But she did lately she got an 890 which is kind of a goal. It's not bad. It's not bad. Not bad. It's not bad. It's not great. It's not like that
woman in Pennsylvania. The transgender woman has got the mom 95 and according to her is genius. Even at 95 anyway,
Adam: I just want to know, would you explain it very well. It's a back channel because it's split and then it's true because he had he sent me a
message back channel. dm, as to Barack Obama has not apologized. Meanwhile, he's asking you the same thing and you're blocking him for it. So it's
like I don't like that. Don't do that. That's what that's when my daughter used to do that. Daddy, can I have this? And then you know, the main Lima
already has gone to mom and gotten some kind of you know if they're tricky.
John: Yeah, it's a double dipping.
Adam: Now not that we don't love him. Cheese, man. I
John: think that's good work. Yeah.
Adam: Yeah, save this. Oh my god. Someone sent me.
Unknown: Oh,
Adam: I think I probably why did I not? Someone said the old comic strip blogger jingle but I don't remember what I did with it.
John: Now you'll find it. Let's do it. Let me let me read off. So
Adam: here it is. Here it is. Okay, this should be it.
Unknown: Comic Strip.
Comic Strip, comic strip.
Comic Strip,
comics,
comic strip.
Adam: It's not like we don't have jingles form and stuff. Wow. It's pretty official.
John: Well, let's talk about something that's more official, which is Christopher berry coming in with $1,000 and from Williams Ville, New York.
Adam: I'm sorry. I just like to thank cesium 137 one more time. No agenda generator calm and is this an instant knighting for Christopher Berry.
John: Oh, it looks like a blue Code Blue.
Adam: I think we have
our instant night sound.
John: I am Jesse rice longtime listener 500 sR 501st time donor led to be noticed surrender not Wave bender of Spark. Okay, he needs a DDoS
Adam: right hold on getting the douche up and the de-douche sauce he
John: says we both rock and he'd like a little goat karma you might die with a simultaneous to the head. Oh, I
Adam: think we can do that
Unknown: you might die
you've got
karma
Adam: did he have any does he have a name? That surrender not did nothing for the roundtable though right? No orders? Nope doesn't seem so okay.
John: All right good Harvey Smith Harvey Smith's Next on the list at $345.67 from Cambridge, Massachusetts. Seems US government has stimulated me into
making this value for value purchase. So you got a check in the mail. And we recommend everybody take some of that free money and send it our way. No
jingles but some great general purpose code comm would be lovely. Thanks for all you do.
Unknown: You've got
karma
John: followed by Jeff Anderson of Carmel, Indiana. $333 ITM john and Adam, thank you for a great show has changed how I view everything I used to be
a rabid republican beholden to the daily infotainment cycle and until a high school friend mentioned your show there's a good point by the way, thank
Adam: you. Yes,
John: a lot of Republicans were that listen to this show we have Democrats and Republicans
Adam: rabid I think rabid republican is a good a good discredited
John: republicans and they tend to listen to Alex Jones and Fox and then that was that hannity hannity. hannity
Unknown: is the worst.
Adam: Though I had we had him on for a second last night it's up they the New York toilet paper times, which I thought he says it over and over
John: I've said this before, he has got to be the hardest working guy in show business and
Unknown: it shows because
John: it's mediocre. He took over where James Brown left
Adam: the only thing is I eat the whole show the Washington toilet paper times, but I thought was funny is the either the Washington compost that one
I hadn't heard. I thought that was funny.
John: Oh, yeah, he's I think, Mark, I think, Mark
Adam: Well, anyway, it's tiresome if you do it. If you do it over and over again. It's like what do you do? compost is bad.
John: Alright, anyway, rabbit Dee is another one. Anyway, he goes on. He says until a high school friend mentioned your show since that time, I've
been happily taking my truth vaccine twice weekly will forever be free from any future. Migdal a swelling. That's true. I would like to call out David
Brantley who hit me in the mouth as a douchebag. And drew Williams has to douchebag because I do not believe they've ever donated. No, I would also
like to be de de-douche to got it.
Unknown: You've been de deuced.
John: I want to mention a little, just a little housekeeping here. too. Do donors that like to dish people and de-douche themselves? I believe
cosmically, it's quite likely that a deducing after calling out people for being a douchebag doesn't deduce you, but possibly deduces the douchebag.
douchebags.
Adam: Do we have any empirical evidence or just anecdotal?
John: It's just totally anecdotal. And I got it from sources. I got it from sources or intelligence sources familiar with the matter. And intelligence
sources agree. So
Adam: the intelligence community,
John: the intelligence community, they all agree on this. According to sources, yes. So put your deducing upfront upfront. Just for your own safety.
What can it hurt? anyway? No, no jingles? No karma yet, as I do not believe I've earned them yet. Oh, Jeff.
Adam: Thank you, Jeff. Thank you very much. Thank you for your courage.
John: Jonathan theodoric in Westminister California. Now the 333 which row zero. First off I want to thank you for the priceless information. It has
been essential for my mental health. Can I please get a DD
I would like to call up my smokin hot babe Leanna for being a douchebag as well as my friend Brandon. Okay, I have another piece of housekeeping here.
Unknown: Okay,
John: I'm noticing a trend for men and women both to use Exact same term smoking hot. Right? I am just requesting personally, that somebody dream up
another term indicating a similar concept. Oh, because I'm kind of tired of it.
Adam: I don't know about you basis. Hey, people supporting the show. You're doing it wrong.
John: I recently had the Abbott antibody test done. Oh, from Abbott Labs. Right. Right, right. Unfortunately, I tested negative I was really hoping to
boost my no agenda antibodies badge and not be a fraud. Looks like I'll be a fraud for now. This brings me to the question, by the way, there was a
report in may have it on my clipless that there's like 40% of these things are faulty. faulty. faulty. Yeah. That says No, they're not. I have I have
Adam: one data point. That's fun from our official no agenda pharmacist. The GC sent me a report. It's a it's a pharmaceutical industry report. The
serology testing? Do you know how big that business is? Or will be?
John: Billions 65
Adam: billion? Wow. 65 billion for for swabbing. swabbing and testing. Beautiful
John: it's probably a lot of blood tests coming in Yeah, well
Adam: whatever. There's no serology serology
John: means you know, serology and includes blood testing. Wrong, who cares a lot of money someone gets the antibodies and tests and tests positive.
Does this positive tests get added to the daily confirm new Coronavirus case, I
Adam: hope would hope so.
John: I was supposed to, isn't it? That would obviously be a major discrepancy. But considering how problematic the date has been, I would not be
surprised. Hopefully you guys can shed some light. Thanks again. Boys. Can I get a Carmen a dealer's choice? sergej from the land of scruffles
butters.
Adam: What kind of dealer's choice hadn't really thought about something? You got something you want to play? I'm good. Well, we have to do something.
I've marked it down specifically to ask you. Oh,
John: yeah, there was one I had in mind, but I can't think of it. Oh, nevermind. I gotta right now
Unknown: you've got
karma flat footed.
John: Yeah. rodentia told me earlier, I could have been thinking about
Adam: I'll say it was a surprisingly
John: sly script from now on. Shipping pronounced this. Lies, lies, lies. lies I SS le Calvert in New York. Yes. For 303030 Here we go. Tonight's
number. ITM just donated for my smoking. smokin hot wife Dame Adriana and her daughter? violet. Another girl named violet. We have a lot of effect.
Yes, we have a couple of women that went to the Oakland meetup. There was a little baby named violet. That's a nice name. On May 13, she donated last
week to herself so please de-douche me you guys
Unknown: deuced
John: if you turn 303 on its end it spells mom.
Unknown: Is that why do
Adam: I like that? Mama? mama mama mama mama mama mom 303 is the mom donation. Good one.
John: What's up with your mom? 303 College smokin hot sanko Joseph going down associate executive producer starting with Lucas. Ty Hema taima ty Oh X
ray this I'm sorry. I'm thinking okay, Lucas timer in Oleg gush d h. Gitmo
Adam: books deeds Hussein boost. Boost
John: guest
Unknown: boost taste will get
John: close enough. But ever 256 is obviously in Holland. yearly podcast feed for 2020
Adam: Yes, thank you.
John: Happy enjoying this. Oh show ces 2019 work? Yes.
Adam: He's been with us for a long time. So nice.
Unknown: Thank you.
John: Jordan Olsen and Nebraska Bellevue to be exact $233.33 por la manyana What am I so my my ride on the Zephyr due to the wish calm flu. And I
figured I would put that money to good use. I like to call out my buddy's dad max for being a douchebag blink blink drip drip? Can I get some I got
ants followed by a goat carpet. Well, we can't do
Adam: the whole thing but we always do like to play the little intro and the first bit of the ants song.
Unknown: I got ants.
Karma
John: Ashley loves Sage in Waukesha, Wisconsin to 3333. From ash, the thrash, la Sage iitm jantz, from the great state of Wisconsin where a Supreme
Court is just struck down or unconstitutional. Stay at home order. Yes. Right, which is an article that we could have been discussing on the show.
They did strike it down with because it's illegal. Yes.
Adam: Well, we talked about we mentioned this happening. We
John: mentioned it. Yeah, it's, it's funny. Whoo. In other states, I was rightfully called out as a douchebag. Last week, and I'm in desperate need of
a dee doo
Unknown: dee doo.
John: Matthew, my cousin Matthew rock, rock wall, rotch wall, whatever, hit me in the mouth about a year ago and a year and a half ago. And I haven't
missed an episode since he's a very intelligent young man, but has always had different insights that I don't get from the news or talk radio. I could
not express how grateful I am for all the work you guys do to provide us with this podcast. Times are tough. We put a lot of work into this podcast.
Yes, we times are tough as an elder millennial, with a shrunken amygdala. But I'm thankful I get relief for a few hours twice a week now I continued
to do my due diligence and return the value for value that you've been providing me. I'm also happy to report that we've been recruiting new listeners
in our circle of friends and family faster than the spread of COVID-19. Yes. Keep up the incredible work and thank you for your courage. Can I get a
goat camera for the tristin onion Martins, who is finally able to have his back surgery today and a that's true for Mike the shark? Because we use it
in our daily conversations and it's hilarious.
Adam: Trust me, it'll get old eventually. john and i, we've even gotten over it wasn't gonna say about this. That's true. I was going to say yeah,
about this show, actively, for every show. And this is kind of the secret of the value for value model. There are hundreds of people producing every
single episode, and just listen to who was being thanked. Besides these financial producers who were supporting us. We have void zero and bemrose and
Darren Oh, and we got Nick the rat and we got CSB. And we got Paul Kosar, Paul couture for the art generator. And that can go on and on and on and on.
Hundreds of people per episode. That's why it's the best one in the universe, people. It's
Unknown: true.
You've got
karma.
John: Neil is in St. Petersburg, Florida. 200. Only mentioning because john and Anna always talk about his name pronunciation. Yeah, we've had trouble
with it. This donation is dedicated to the birthday of my smokin hot wife Amanda.
Adam: Yes, thank
John: thank you for the show, which supports our mental health brings us closer together and strengthens our relationship. Adam.
Adam: Yes.
John: Thanks for inspiring me to finally getting a ham radio license. Well, thank you very much. See
Unknown: how that works.
Again,
John: happy birthday Amanda. In j&k. nk, Neil. k. oh four ACM? 73.
Adam: Yes. 73 kilo five alpha. Charlie Charlie now was of course influenced by john to get my ham ticket. Of course I did the real deal. I'm a general
and john Yeah, he's like a walkie talkie guy. meter 70 centimeter
Unknown: Yeah,
Adam: I am. I did the real test man did like the little entry test there. But okay. Yes, we are. We are hams and proud of it. No agenda hams.com check
it out. Yet another group of fantastic people supporting the show.
John: You know, I do have a call signing when all hell breaks loose and I have to save the day. Yeah. And I can pretty much use any gear I want.
Adam: Oh, yeah. You're just gonna try and figure out how to configure it to work with the repeater and then hat and then after the Hello Eddie. Okay,
here we
John: were to the next step.
Adam: One question one question during the entire Rhona crisis. Have you once turned on the radio your handheld to see if you could reach anything or
even listen for one one minute? Answer No. This is this is what hams were born for. Man. We're in the middle of this is the apocalypse. This is the
apocalypse. And all you can do is is joke around, we need to take your ticket back.
John: I gotta renew it in in November, I may upgrade it to extra. Now here we have ham radio, guys, ham radio is the public service network of last
resort when the apocalypse comes
Unknown: where the guys who are going to save the world. Right? Right.
Adam: Well, we're it deer producer, Adam and john where the hams are going to save the world. I see. Okay. So you know,
John: and we need more people to get their license Tom Turner Meanwhile, in Salt Lake City, Utah, Tom, if you got your license, you have 200 bucks
here for us. Thanks. Hello ingredients for the moderate to low risk and low alcohol content. Content State of Utah. been listening to Adam since he
was on Rogan is another one. And this is my first donation. What I liked about the Rogen people and there's been about I think you've probably picked
up a lot of listeners five, not not 1000 you know, a lot, a lot. Okay, and they got into the donating mode faster than a listers from other sources.
Adam: I agree.
John: I agree that you're right, because they come in pretty. And they come in at the Executive Associate executive producer level pretty quickly.
There may be some $5 subscribers, but I'm impressed with Rogan's Rogan's audience. And that says to me, do the show again?
Adam: Well, first of all, we're not calling them audiences. We call the media tribes now, and there's huge overlap between his tribe and our tribe and
people who produce this show. Listen to his show. So and I'd love to go back Joe is I mean, I was trying to get Joe over here. He's complaining. It's
like, I told him that we went to Lonesome Dove and I sent him the menu was like, Oh, we were thinking about renting a plane. We can't eat anything. We
can't go anywhere. We're all bummed out about him. Like, go rogue and rent the plane come by us him.
Unknown: Come on, hang out.
Adam: But I'm sure I'll be invited back on eventually.
John: You should be one of those guys on standby but
Adam: hold on a second. Hold on. I don't want to be the guy on standby.
John: He's you want to get on if you could be on stage. Excuse me. All right, nevermind. This is not twit is the dry Rogen show to get on the
overnight show. I've just had been unsuccessful.
Adam: What overnight show
John: the oldie of what used to be you know, that overnight show. It's called overnight and he's the name of it. somebody knows the name in the chat
room. It's the one that talks about you know, flying saucers at coast to coast coast to coast that's Yeah, we can get your show I want to
Adam: see I don't want to be on that shows. Anyway, yeah,
John: I do I want to be on coast to coast.
Adam: Okay, well, someone please set that up. And is John dvorak.org. Do not repeat do not email me and do not not email Coast to Coast AM and pretend
you're me or john and fill out a form and put our email addresses No.
John: Anyway, he continues on his note I'll be working diligently towards night who is I'm wishing to beat my overachieving limy father in law who's
actually very close to receiving a real knighthood from the queen who loved the show and deliberating possible knighthood names such as Sir Thomas of
the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter Day Saints.
Adam: Please. Okay, well,
John: Tom, the underachieving son in law that overachieving limey father in law, thoughts?
Adam: Sounds like all that all winners to me.
John: Regardless, thanks for the incredible show and take and take care. All right, take care of yourself, Tom.
Adam: Thank you very much, Tom. Of course, he's from St. Salt Lake City. So we have a lot of LDS producers as well. We take them all. We'll take your
rabid Republicans, we'll take your lib tardes we'll take your your lip Joes. We'll take your dev Joe's the lib devs will take anything.
John: Yeah, I'll tell you the lip tardes and the lip Joes Don't let don't like to show it shakes up their worldview and
Adam: they don't like it makes them uncomfortable to them uncomfortable. Yeah. Well, we're pretty comfortable knowing that we have at least some tribe
out there who is supporting the work and happy with it and I love seeing the trolls. The trolls are very active today in the in the troll room.
John: Before before I can do I have to mention something. It's raining. It's raining. We're in the middle of May in California, that desert.
Adam: They had it's raining. They had snow in New Yorker earlier this week. Very strange. Well, it's harp. It's all part of the program.
Unknown: Herb herb,
Adam: thank you to our executive producers and associate executive producers for this episode 1242 It is highly appreciated and we will be thanking
more people in our second segment but these are the ones that really can go immediately to put these titles to good use they are true entertainment
titles if you're looking for stature or maybe just work put it on your LinkedIn apparently people have some success with that and we will be here for
another program on Sunday please support us at the following website address John dvorak.org
Unknown: slash and
Adam: a once again you're up to speed on all things Rona. Where we are Rona central
Unknown: our formula is this we go out for hit people in the mouth
premature
John: should probably also mentioned that the younger producers executive producers can can incorporate this credit into their pickup lines as they
reopen the bars absolutely
Adam: and I just remembered I would like to give a special jobs karma to our very own sir Jean Duke of the south as the Rona has taken away all of his
clients and he didn't ask for this but I'm gonna give it to him
Unknown: jobs, jobs, jobs and jobs that's my job
karma
Adam: cuz you know when when someone is like hey man, I gotta I gotta find a client. Like who do I know how can I think of anything? I'm like shit
I've got the most powerful weapon at my disposal the jobs karma Why am I messing around thinking about who I can call? Yeah, so that's hopefully
hopefully Ghostbusters. Jobs karma will do will do its business.
John: I mentioned somebody that happened to Guardian printed this article. I don't know why cuz they're Woody Allen's on the outs but this is a
guardian article and it says Woody Allen's a rainy day in New York tops global box office. So they've been rolling out this movie that was paid for by
Amazon Amazon Studios kicked woody out. After you know, Dylan Farrow made a fuss again, even though this has been done in court. And one of Woody's
other kids says bullcrap, but he's been accused of being a molester. And so they won't let his booty so they won't even show he's been out. It's not
out of what's the word canceled so badly that they won't even release this movie in the United States. And I saw this movie. It wasn't
Adam: on Amazon.
John: No, no, Amazon refused to put it on.
Adam: I thought they had it on briefly. Where did you see it?
John: I got a screener. interwebs Yeah. I got a screener. And I watched this movie I said as a coach, little after it came out. I think this is maybe
one of his best New York he said a series of new movies he's done about New York. I think this is one of his best ones. I think is award worthy. I
mean, it's a it's a it's a got neurotics in New York again, but it brings us a little bit more about celebrity and the shallowness of New York and
it's just a it but it's a but it's an ode to New York I think is one of his best New York movies ever. And unfortunately the American public will
never get to see it in the theater of course who cares nowadays know all the theaters was the
Adam: renewed interest in in in canceling him was it the was it Ronan Farrow's me to work or what was the
John: it was some of Ronan Farrow and Dylan came out again, started making a fuss. They made a big fuss and they did it using canceled culture
techniques. They started hounding Amazon because Amazon had picked his car. Right, right. Right. Right. And so they started how and and it Amazon, you
know, did he also was supposed to do some TV work for them. And he did this horrible, really bad piece of work. And he gave it to them. It's just
junk. And I think
Adam: Amazon was just so hypocritical, you know, I mean, I'm not a huge Woody Allen fan of his movies. I've seen you know, some, of course, there are
some seminal ones that we can you know, how could you ever live without it? Just seeing some of these great movies, but you're really into it. And I'm
like, and
John: I know I've always said I've been a fan since I saw a movie.
Adam: Yeah. Which was that was the first one.
John: Well, the first actually this first movie was, was a kind of an overdub. Listen to it. First of all, he was take the money in the real for real
first, please take the money and run. Daniel. sign over. It gives a gun the note to the teller. He's gonna rob a bank in the teller says, I've got a
gubb What's a gubb? To give me your money? I've got a gub gub No, it doesn't say gub. And he says yeah, it does here.
Adam: Yeah, it says gun gun. Everything you always want to know about sex I saw probably when I was nine
John: yeah it's a cute ah
Adam: yeah anyway okay well I'm glad thank you for that Woody Allen update relevant to know and I really appreciate it that's
John: really good average he's relevant got
Unknown: bad China China
Adam: let's talk about China for a second China cannon cannon
John: cannon I have my one China clip
Adam: yeah you want to do your one China clip
John: yeah let's do this clip because this clip is kind of like I don't know what to did they don't know quite what to do how to handle this clip
because they did Chinese influence news media I'm sure as you have mixed feelings but they got around this story
Adam: I liked how you say big Chinese hackers I like how you say influence and you can just say control but influence is just warm and fuzzy. Yes. CBS
CBS CBS is on a tear Here we go.
Unknown: Tonight the FBI and federal cybersecurity agents are warning that hackers linked to the Chinese government are trying to steal research on
Coronavirus vaccines and therapies. The FBI says the potential theft could jeopardize the treatment of patients here in the US. Here's CBS Chief
Justice and homeland security correspondent Jeff gays.
Well, the Coronavirus was sweeping across parts of China in January.
Adam: My God Jeff is in. He was official
John: say stop one second, I want to mention something in this particular thing, especially when he's reporting from home. I am now wondering since we
all you'd like to make fun of Jeff and
Unknown: Come on, it's
John: really a great reporter but he's got this funny voice. I think he's got the same condition that JFK Jr. Robert Kennedy Jr. Has
Adam: Oh, really? Oh,
John: when you hear him reporting from home, that's when you're gonna hear it. And I never looked into it. But I bet she's got the same condition
because he's got these qualities. Well,
Adam: I don't know why you have to take my joy away that he's just has to prove
John: I mean is did I like it?
Unknown: Do this report real quick.
Dirty correspondent Jessica gays.
Well, the Coronavirus was sweeping across parts of China in January. US officials say Chinese hackers were already focused on the United States trying
to steal research from universities and pharmaceutical companies that were working on a cure. JOHN de MERS is the Assistant Attorney General for
national security
that Chinese for years have targeted biomedical research. And there's nothing more important than COVID-19 research right now in that field. The
hacking
charges ratcheted up tensions over the virus between the US and China, which should have been stopped at the source which was China, but it's not just
China, or Iran is also on the attack. Researchers at the cybersecurity company recorded futures say the Iranian state target in an executive and
Gilead Sciences, the manufacturer of the promising Coronavirus treatment drug remdesivir. But demurrers said China is desperate to be first with a
vaccine you call this a holy grail of of information that these foreign hackers are going after.
There's nothing more important right now than these treatments, and perhaps most significantly for China for geopolitical value to be able to say that
they were the first to develop a vaccine.
Tonight in a statement Chinese officials said the accusations were without evidence, but US officials say anyone working on a vaccine should be on
hyper alert. Margaret.
Adam: Well, when I heard him speak, kind of in the interview, I heard it what the condition is called spasmodic dysphonia as Robert Kennedy Jr. Has,
it could be could be that he has some of that. It sounds more like you just overworked his voice.
John: I don't know what happens when you blow your voice shot but it could sound interesting.
Adam: Well, CBS is doing all kinds of reports about China and this was 60 minutes this past Sunday. It was just kind of interesting how they their
version of the timeline of Corona and China
Unknown: and Trump told us to direct questions about the origin of the virus. To the Director of National Intelligence. The Chinese Communist Party
has also blocked the truth. In the earliest days, the doctor and Wu Han who discovered the outbreak was silenced by local officials. He later died of
COVID-19. In February, the Chinese did allow a visit by an international team of experts, including American scientists.
We are coordinating with the Chinese government and working closely together on the coronavirus outbreak in China.
Initially President Trump praised China, but in the following weeks testing in the US failed to catch up to the need vital equipment with short bodies
filled refrigerated trailers. And science was continuously challenged,
don't dump dump, dump, dump, dump, dump, dump, dump,
dump dump dump the disinfectant in a minute, one minute, and is there a way we can do something like that? by injection,
as the US led the one illness and death, White House move the focus to the Chinese government. That's where this began. Last Sunday,
Secretary of State Mike Pompeo attempted to resurrect a debunked theory that the virus was man made in China.
Adam: A debunked theory. This has got to stop reporters journalists. Just saying something is a debunked theory is not journalism. Let's see. That is
the mighty CBS 60 minutes pompeyo was trying to revisit he debunked
John: the conspiracy theory. There is never been debunked. Of course it
Adam: hasn't been debunked.
John: But about why is he saying it's debunked CB versus evidence that is debunked just because somebody else said it wasn't the case. Because it's in
it and we still you know, here's what's not resolved. People keep saying this. They say there's no bats being sold at that at that wet market. And
other people said, well, it came from bats being sold at a wet market. And other people say there's they don't sell bats at that wet markets is a
seafood place, as our president himself says,
Unknown: covering up the spread of the Corona, virus. Everybody knows what's going on there.
Adam: Everybody knows what's going on. Did you see the altercation with the Asian American reporter?
John: gets perpetual. Which one is this? Oh, this
Adam: is a new one. This was this was a new reporter. And she's one of the activist activist reporters that are now showing up to these conferences.
Men and women are good looking. They're young, the good looking. The guys are you know, they're kind of hunky The girls are really cute. And this, of
course, if they have anyone who's either of color, journalists of color. But if you can get an Asian American to ask a question about China, that's
even better. But this, I think she jumped the shark on this one. You'll hear why.
Unknown: Rob? Okay. Yeah, go ahead, please.
said many times that the US is doing far better than any other country, when it comes to testing. Yes. Why does that matter? Why is this a global
competition to you if everyday Americans are still losing their lives, and we're still seeing more cases every day?
Adam: So it's like, typical, unimportant unimpressive question that is only meant to attack the President's demeanor or how he talks about something.
And and this, she's wasting our time with this. But then this happens
Unknown: while they're losing their lives everywhere in the world. And maybe that's a question you should ask China. Don't ask me has China that
question, okay. When you ask them that question, you may get a very unusual answer. Yes, behind you. And
Adam: here's what's really interesting. She came back after he said, Well, why don't you go ask China about that, which he's very consistently say
China knows, everybody knows is China. But remember, she's Asian American. So she gets to ask this follow up question,
Unknown: sir. Why are you saying that to me? Specifically,
I'm telling you, I'm not saying it specifically to anybody. I'm saying that anybody that would ask a nasty question like
that, and nasty, please go ahead.
Adam: Do you really think she expected the president to say Well, clearly you got splitty? Is your goat? What do you want? I mean, what the hell are
these people doing? Is that really what she thought? Is that really why she Why do you say that to me? Is because I look Chinese? This is infantry.
John: Why? You know, it's the it's the White House can ban these people. I don't know why they let him in. Well, then
Adam: you're banning a woman of color.
John: Well, it's it wasn't I would blame. ABC. He's the one who heads up the correspondents to get to go to that thing in the first place. Of course,
Adam: he's the guy that's bringing all the activist journalists in. Yeah. And then and then another good looking journalist from CNN,
Unknown: why does it matter? Okay. Anybody else? Please go ahead. The back place. Two clouds. Okay.
I have two questions.
What's your next next place
that you did you call it on me?
I did. And you didn't respond. And now I'm calling on sorry, I just young lady in the back, please. I just wanted to let my colleagues okay, but can
ask Ladies and Gentlemen, thank you very much. Appreciate it. Thank you very much.
Adam: clearly, clearly some kind of attitude or something. And he's like, I'm not you anymore. And oh, but then we just like, That's not fair. You
called on me. It's my time. It's
Unknown: my last question.
John: I forgot a question. I want to question a bunch of kids. I'm sure. What's her name, the Kaley. She also walks out. I mean, at some point, are
you just dare to be harangued by the media there? You're not there's not these are not legitimate questions. Well, they're legitimate questions if
your national enquirer or you know, or not even there, no, it's this. These are, these are just questions to harass the president. And he's not. He
doesn't have to even show up. Ball bomb, I think went over a year without doing a press conference at one point. I mean, Trump's doing a favor. I
mean, if they're going to ask the actual questions, but I didn't hear any questions there was just like, no, are you showing a chart? You know, it's
not what kind of a question is that? What I'm showing the chart? Because I think it's interesting. You know, and I wanted to show it, I'd be what
can't you can answer it yourself. Why you showing a chart?
Adam: Well, we are in, in a modern kinetic war, which means there's no bullets, but the the kinetics come from money and regulation, and maybe viral
warfare. But the Trump administration is now talking to as many chipmakers as possible about building fabs in the US, which some are, of course, going
to do. Apple is moving a significant amount of their iPhone production from China to India. It was kind of interesting to see Van Jones, he had to
some backpedaling to do he was supposed to speak at some conference. And he tweeted, I guess he found out by himself that oh, my God, I'm glad that
this got canceled because I couldn't have ever even done it. And I found out it was it was sponsored by Huawei. And that my takeaway is that's exactly
what's going on. There's so much because Van Jones wasn't just going to go speak just to be a nice guys getting paid
John: all these people to speak for free generally. I mean, some people do, but their speeches are worthless. Yeah.
Adam: But But I guess the understood even here professor in Arkansas University
John: money because he thought, way me he, okay, somebody bought, okay. The way it's usually done, somebody books you to begin with, right? You don't
just show up to speak, right? So somebody calls you up and said, I'm going to do it that we're doing a conference, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, we're
gonna pay you so much money. And his case, he probably makes pretty good money. 10 grand minimum. And, okay, I'll do that in this because it then you
tend to because you have to give a speech to this audience, the next thing you do. And I would say all speakers do this, you check out the event. So
you go to their webpage and see who's going to be there and who the audience is because you got to adjust your speech to the people. If it's a woman's
a bunch of all women, you got to think about this. So you go to the thing, and you'd go to the web page, and the webpage really tells you the sponsor.
Adam: At the start of the show two hours ago, you said I don't know why people think I'm a misogynist. But really, you got to be careful if it's a
conference with all women.
John: Oh, yeah. So I'm not gonna deny it. So. So you go to Yeah, cuz Yeah, you do. I mean, I'm not an idiot. So you go to the website, you check it
out. And you get on the website. The most important thing you see on there is who's sponsoring the thing. And the Huawei people would be front and
center. Well, this is no surprise is full of shit. This guy.
Adam: Well, you walked right into it. Because this was a conference of the NA BJ. Which makes it even worse
John: National Association of blow job artists
Adam: close, no black journalists. And so the National Association of Black journalists are sponsored by the Chinese just want you to understand that.
And so Wow. And he tweeted, I accepted invite. This is verbatim I accepted invite to play he's already speaking Chinese. I accepted my role today. I
accepted invite to participate in na beejay webinar. Oh, webinar, warning black community about COVID misinformation. I said yes. Without knowing the
sponsor. Glad na BJ canceled I would not have participated. I'll keep raising alarm about pandemics impact on vulnerable people though. And he has it
posted it says
John: Hold on a second. So he cancels after they can't correct and now they just To virtue signal, yeah. But I am not buying it
Adam: but what he's doing is he's busting the National Association of Black journalists that they're in bed with the Chinese. He's busting
John: it because they canceled his money making event. Okay.
Adam: Now Thank you. We always comes down to the money. Professor at the University of Arkansas arrested for undisclosed ties to China. Arkansas man
Arkansas at least went to Arkansas. Another one of these 1000 talents program did not disclose the the money the deals that he had. They are they
charged in arrest these guys now this is this is not some slap on the wrist.
John: Well, good. Yeah,
Adam: I think so too. And I think we should talk about Flynn. Flynn.
John: Oh, yeah, I got
Adam: I got Flynn clips. Well, it's time to do it now. Because we are in a very interesting situation, where really the news wants to focus on death
and destruction and Corona and scary things. We have all kinds of documentation coming out. That seems and appears to back up pretty much everything
that has been said about the Muller investigation, the Russia collusion investigation, about the spying on the president. The President is now also
tweeting. Trump gate. Is that what it is? Obama gate? I'm sorry, Obama, Obama gate. Oh, my God. jingles are showing up
Unknown: Obama gate.
This is better. This
tag Obama gate. It's what's trending.
There you go.
John: Yes, Jennifer. That is Jennifer.
Adam: It's what's trending.
John: She has a very distinctive voice is very, you can you can she just from a professional point of view from listening to do doing voices? Yeah. I
mean, I don't do voice about just listening to voice. She's borderline professional voiceover she has a couple of anomalies. Once they're corrected,
they're very minor. She has got the voice of that's worth a lot of money. Whoa, that's
Adam: quite the endorsement. I mean, the way I hear it, she would fit perfect in our in our morning zoo is like everybody, it's out of a job.
Don't you think she would fit perfectly?
John: She would she would do a zoo.
Adam: What did she What does she What does she need to be corrected? Do you want to correct her live? Do you want to lie? Well,
John: there's a there's an inconsistency. There's an inconsistency in hers in her sweet sexiness. Hmm. And it is and I can only express it this way.
It's it's not Maine. It's like when you try to do your one of your voices and like an imitation of somebody you can't maintain it. You can do a bit. A
little bit. Yeah, you can do a little short thing. It sounds like Christopher Walken, or someone. But you can't really do it, maintain it. And she,
she is at that point where she can do it. But there's a maintenance issue. And so she apparently she just needs to be able to hang in there a little
bit longer with the sexiness.
Unknown: Alright. A major maintenance issue.
John: Okay. Maintenance and maintenance by maintenance. I mean, maintaining the
Adam: maintaining the level of voice I got you. Yeah. Okay. So it's very interesting. What I would suggest everybody read and I put it in the show
notes and a show notes calm. And yes, I'd like to reiterate search.na shownotes.com and Bing it.io. no longer work. The developer who made the search
engine is abandoned at the beginning of the year I've ever had multiple people have tried to reach out to him. It the the site doesn't even work now.
You could still go to na shownotes comm drawback, all the show notes? Yeah, it is a drawback. All the show notes are there. Everything is in
structured XML data. So if anyone wants to build a new search engine, please feel free. We'd be happy to resurrect search.na, show notes calm. And so
we're back to
John: the
Adam: Yeah, we really I don't know if it exists. I have three clips. Okay, I just want to give a little background here. And then what your clips. We
really need a daily Flynn podcast because this is truly about the deep state and it's, it's going to, if we didn't already have a wedge in in this
country is going to get a lot more interesting. And I want to I just want to say that Sidney Powell who is Flynn's Mike, General Michael Flynn, and
how this all fits together, hopefully your clips will start to explain it. Sidney Powell is his new lawyer, and she's the one that has pretty much
successfully brought all this to light. She has a complete timeline of everything that's taken place. And I will sum it up as follows. The Obama
administration, and the democrat party with Hillary Clinton, were keeping tabs on Trump. That's why they had this research that was done and paid for
by Clinton and a law firm. And this was all known that this was they even worked with Russians to get it because they just needed some they didn't
really think it was going to win. And, and just to make sure everyone got in the game, and we figured out how to use some phony baloney information
from multiple people to go through the Pfizer, the foreign surveillance for Surveillance Act court, to be able to wiretap and listen in, while not
actually get previously recorded conversations from multiple people, one of them being General Flynn. And just so everyone understands why this is a
big deal, we have a constitution in America, you can't do that. We have a fourth amendment, Fifth Amendment, there's a number of other amendments this
would violate but after 911, we all as a country said, you know, if we had only know more about these turrets than we could have caught them and all
these people wouldn't have died. So the Patriot Act, which was written a long time before that, but it showed up, and in that there was a new deal.
You could listen in on American citizens, which is unconstitutional in at the heart. But we made a special law that you could do that if you got a
warrant from a secret court secret, but you could trust it, don't worry, it's secret, because it will be of the highest bar, it will be so difficult
to get a warrant to spy on an American citizen. It's I mean, we might as well not even have the court at all. And of course, you have to be very
truthful and confident in the evidence you show to that court to obtain this warrant. None of that happened in this case. And spying was done. Here's
where it all went wrong. In my opinion. Trump one, the Obama administration and all the people who were involved with this, everyone who had, quote,
unquote, unmasked, a Flynn call with the Russian ambassador, they were in on it, including Joe Biden. And that's documented. And they had a discussion
on it on January 5, just right before the transition. And Obama said, All man, we got to do it by the book, but everyone sat in that room. And then
they knew that if they handed over all of the information, they have what you're supposed to do, from one president to the next, and the transition
one administration to the next. If they if they truly were honest, and gave it all then Trump would know, immediately he had been spied on and who had
been doing it. So they suppress that and they doubled down trying to implicate Trump in a Russian spying scheme. With Flynn, kind of the point of the,
of the spear, which serve two purposes. One, we had to get Flynn out of there, because Flynn would be the one to investigate and figure it out. And,
and to we needed a fall guy to really stick the knife into Trump. And that's now starting to unravel because they didn't get Trump out in time. They
weren't able to impeach him. And I presume the President's just been sitting on this. And now it's time to release it. And I think every day we'll get
a new piece. And this latest piece that we've received is a list of 39 people 39 or 29. Think is 20 lot. So around 30 people who all requested
unmasking unmasking of these of these phone calls. And if you want I have a two minute clip of NSA director, Admiral Mike Rogers explaining how that
works is an older clip.
John: Because he's the guy to play that and then I'll play these three this about Biden mostly Yeah, but it also brings in Trump and Trump do be the
last clip and Trump previews what's coming for predicts right there we go on.
Adam: So here is how the process works of someone obtaining the call that they're interested in, and then we have an American citizen, who would be
redacted and now we have to know who that person is so we can understand what the call is about.
Unknown: So the respect to unmasking. The following criteria is apply. First. For the National Security Agency we define in writing who has the
authority to unmask a US person identity? That is 20 individuals in 12 different positions, I am one of the 20 in one of those 12 positions, the
director. Secondly, we outline in writing, what are the criteria that will be applied to a request to unmask in a report, and again part of our
process under 702, to protect the identity of us persons as part of our minimization procedures, when we think we need to reference a US person in a
report, we will not use a name, we will not use an identity we say us person, one us person to us person three, that report is then promulgated. Some
of the recipients of that report will sometimes come back to us and say I'm trying to understand what I am reading, could you help me understand who
is person one or who is person two, etc, we apply two criteria in response to their request. Number one, you must make the request in writing. Number
two, the request must be made on the basis of your official duties, not the fact that you just find this report really interesting. And you're just
curious, it has to tangibly tied to your job. And then finally I said to but there's a third criteria. And that is, the basis of the request must be
that you need this identity to understand the intelligence you're reading. We apply those three criteria, we do it in writing, and one of those 20
individuals then agrees or disagrees. And if we unmask, we go back to that entity who requested it. Not every individual who received the report, but
that one entity who asked for us, we then provide them the US identity. And we also remind them the classification of this report, in the sensitive
sensitivity of that identity remains in place by revealing this us person to you we are doing it to help you understand the intelligence, not not so
that you can use that knowledge indiscriminately, it must remain appropriately protected.
Adam: And so the 29 people got to see this.
John: And even though you'd notice Roger says there's 20 people qualified to ask.
Adam: Yeah, that was all I'm a little unclear whether that means it's I thought it was 20 people can approve someone who can who can look at it. But
that's it's a little unclear to me. What is interesting, though, is the response from the New York Times, and the New York Times who they cannot deny
the the paperwork that is coming out over this. Their headline is Trump White House, rewrites history, this time about Flynn. And their article shows
a different picture by omission. So they're leaving a lot of things out in background and it's quite
John: sad. trouble.
Adam: It's quite sad to see them. I think they're in trouble because not only can not just anybody go looking at these names, but to leak that name to
the press, which happened repeatedly. And I think there's some documentary evidence of that. That's a that's a jailable offense. Remember,
John: nobody's gonna get getting tried these guys are well, sadly I have. I have a ringer.
Adam: Yeah. Sadly, I have thoughts on who but let's listen to your to your joke clips. And let's get into the see how this will affect our future.
John: There is a kind of a follow kind of a cascade effect from Joe Biden going on. Good morning, America. And so this is beef just before the list
comes out. Joe goes on. This is kind of edited down but this is biting on CMA buzz GMA contradiction. Here we go. I know nothing about those moves to
investigate Michael Flynn number one, number two, I thought you asked me whether or not always kill that clip. I'm sorry. That's the clip. I have to
play that clip later play clips from GMA one. Sorry, I know nothing about those moves to investigate Michael Flynn, number one. Number two,
Unknown: this is all about diversion. This is a game this guy plays all the time. The country is in crisis. We're in an economic crisis, a health
crisis.
And if you were reported to be in a January 5 2017 meeting, where you and the president were briefed on the FBI his plan to question, Mike Michael
Flynn over those conversations he had with the Russian ambassador Kislyak?
No, I thought you asked me whether or not I had anything to do with him being prosecuted.
Okay. I'm sorry.
I was aware that there was that there that they asked for an investigation. But that's all I know about it.
Adam: I saw this and I have an observation. Well, wait.
John: Okay. Well, give me your observation first, but I did I have an interesting point to make.
Adam: My observation is when this question was being asked and the follow up, Joe had an eye FB and he was wiggling it in his ear and he cocked his
head to the left. And I guarantee you someone was saying
Unknown: this right? That's not the right answer.
Adam: And you can see his face tilt again in recognition. And then he comes back with an O note. I was talking about this. He was being Sue flayed.
John: Is that the oil? I'm, I believe now that you bring that up? I would say you're probably right, because he asked who was asked one question. He
says, I thought you were talking about prosecuting it, which was the second part when you take the first part from this earlier part of the
conversation. And then you put the second part, which is what I have here in this contradiction clip. When you take those two together, this is what
you're really got. He never said anything or even thought anything about your question being about prosecution.
Unknown: Listen to this clip. I know nothing about those moves to investigate Michael Flynn number one, number two, I thought you asked me whether or
not I had anything to do with him being prosecuted.
John: There it is. Yeah.
Adam: Yeah, but he switched midstream.
John: I'm telling you switch. Yeah, you're probably right. Because he's so dumb, that he never thought that that he's already made the mistake. No, I
thought you said something else. So you're you said that you wanted orange juice? I didn't know. You said milk.
Adam: And Tina, Tina and I were watching last night. And I said, Did you see that? And I roll it back? And she saw it too. It's like he's getting
instructions. He, you know, the holding your left hand? What did I have B is the is the intercom? And you're the depending on how it's set up? It
could have been Joe's people talking to him. It could be the the TV network talking to him. It could be you know, just same thing. Exactly. And you've
seen it before where the news reader goes, hold on, hold on, I'm getting important information One moment. So he makes one of those moves with his
hand. He's cocking his head, and he's getting information. He's being told what to say, this is going to be great. I hope there's a debate with Trump.
But sadly, I think something else is going to happen. Well, are you ready for it? But someone has to go down for this spying. And Biden's name turns
up on the list. As and we know why did in he's lying here clearly because he knew all about it. He heard the call. Well, but hold on. Why is Biden
being highlighted besides it being Joe? I think it's time to finally take them down. So Hillary can come in?
John: Well, I'm not going to, of course, I still have never pulled my Hillary prediction. So I'm going to stick with it. But let's go on with this
theory of yours in mind. And this is Ron Paul says Ron Paul, but it's not as Rand Paul. And he's talking about the Biden unmasking questions that
Unknown: have run I'll address the acting intelligence official. Senator, where does that stand? Is Rick Grinnell going to testify to your committee
if you've got confirmation of that?
No. But I did send a letter last evening to the Director of National Intelligence, Rick Grinnell and asked him if he would declassify this. And we got
this information today and released it. And I think this is astonishing, that Vice President Biden and really all of President Obama's inner circle,
individually, we're requesting the unmasking of a political opponent. And you know, you remember there was a hole to do about trying to impeach a
president saying that we're using the power of government to go after a political opponent. This is this is a smoking gun, if there ever was one, that
Vice President Biden was using the power of government abusing that power to go after a political opponent. Essentially, unmasking someone is the
equivalent of illegally wiretapping them. The government had permission to listen to the Russian ambassador, but to protect Americans, we mask their
identity. But you got the whole President Obama's inner circle clamoring around listening to the private conversation. I think you'll legally and I
think with Ill Ill Ill gotten motives.
To You know, Senator, whether these unmasking requests then in each and all of these cases occurred after the election. I mean, obviously, the
assessment was prior to the election that Hillary Clinton was going to win. Obviously, that didn't happen. So did a lot of this then dreads fire after
the election itself.
Yes, the document that we got listed all the names and listed the date that they did the unmasking. So vice president unmasked, General Flynn to
listen to his conversation, which I think is reprehensible. but so did James combing. So to James Clapper, so did john brennan. So did Samantha
powers, and so did President Obama's chief of staff and a dozen other people. So think about this. It's illegal to listen to people's private
conversations you can listen to if you have a national security matter, a foreigner, but it's thus the foreigner saying we're gonna blow up the
capital, will you help me you don't get to listen to the other person. conversation if they're just talking.
Adam: Rand Paul Graham
John: answers the question, but the conversation took place after the election. There was no other reason to do it. But now we have the president
chiming in on this, and he talks about it at that meeting of the two governors. And here he is on a mat on unmasking. And he puts a little predictive
thing at the end here, which makes you wonder what's coming next.
Unknown: And on the release of those names of all the unmasking is a massive, massive thing. It's, I just got to listen to this. It's who can believe
a thing like this. And I watched Biden yesterday on Good Morning America being interviewed by one of your colleagues, George Stephanopoulos, and he
said he knew nothing about anything. He has no idea what he knows nothing about anything. Nothing at all. And then it gets released today that he was
a niggling masker. So I didn't know nothing. If you're one of the unmask years. It's one of the very big stories, and I suspect you'll have if it's
possible, even bigger stories coming out. Yeah.
Adam: It's, he's been holding on to this. He's been Wait, I think he's gonna hold on Obama until after the election, because he wants Obama down. I
know he does, because this is Trump. When that that White House
Unknown: press one
Adam: press Correspondents Dinner. That's when Obama dressed him down. That's
John: that's a publicly ridiculed him. That's called dressing him down. Is
Adam: it not? Oh, I
John: thought he was a transsexual. Sorry.
Adam: You are on a roll today hate for women confused about transexuals.
John: For women, I
Adam: don't know what to do with you, man. I'm telling you.
John: I love the smoking hot lady. All kinds
Adam: of issues with you today. So where we're at now is Bill Barr the department. The Attorney General said, Hey, to the judge, I think is in
Washington, DC. we're dropping all charges against Flynn. Clearly. He was railroaded. We have evidence we have hand written evidence of what the of
what the FBI agents were doing. You know, you know, some of the names like struck I mean, come on. It's very clear. And the judge said, No, man, I
don't know about that. I think we should bring in another we need to have some voices chime in here. So one, he's he's got a retired judge who's going
to come in and tell everybody, Flint should be drawn and quartered. And at the same time, kind of this doesn't happen often. But I lost my train of
thought the whole point was,
John: no, no,
Adam: I know. I remember the 2000 names. They got the 2000 name list for the lawyers who were always writing everything. Prosecutor lawyers.
John: Yeah. 1000. attorneys say Trump sucks.
Adam: Yes, that's exactly what they did. Again, they sent out a message to the email list. You have the list. Well, you had the list. You have all the
angel list. I
John: have it. Yeah. It's always if you go back and look at the story cuz I bailed a couple of these guys to see if they were religious or alive. And
they were they're all part of a Trump hating crowd.
Adam: Hold on. Let's do this. Let's look at how many stories we've had about the 2000 prosecutors. So February 17, Bill Barr resignation more than
2000 former prosecutors. Okay. Let's see what else we have. That's all February. Let's go back a little bit further, because this has been used over
and over again, hasn't it?
John: Yeah, by the media loves it.
Adam: So it was those guys who wanted barters there wasn't another example, though.
John: Oh, they wanted all kinds of stuff is Yeah, I don't know how you search for it.
Adam: 2000 prosecutors is the search I'm doing and it's popping up everywhere. But it's I have to go back further away. I can do tools. Let's do it.
Let's do last year, see past year. That's past you need anyway, it's it's the same group. And they all ended like Oh, hey, we got I got an email from
the group. What do we do sign it, okay. So that's where we're at. And that's going to be very interesting to see what happens. But someone's got to go
down and it would be great. If it was comi. It would be it would be great if they closed the FBI. But Brandon, I think Brandon could be in trouble.
But man
John: branch coordinate, everybody's in trouble, but he's not in trouble. And I'd like to know if anybody can confirm that his security clearance was
pulled. I never heard that it was confirmed. I don't know you're
Adam: talking new stories from three years ago.
Unknown: Okay,
Adam: all right. Did not Did you have more on the
John: now that's all I got? I just got the Biden stuff and I think you're probably right this may be the one it may not be the one because you still
have the same old the john Cooper's out there these guys who are you know, old tax democrat party and they're the ones who pushed Obama past Sanders
because you're not putting up with the need to lose and all that banking background well that bankers money and the bankers all said and abandoned
democrats are more beholden to the bankers and the republicans are from what I can tell seems and the book sold on 123450 my god
Adam: that Zephyr?
John: No, that's the coastal coming down to the from Seattle,
Adam: but the coastal is always live, but I thought it was six last time now it's five.
John: Now it's five, it's normally 12. That thing isn't bad. You know,
Adam: you know what that means? What negative interest rates,
John: it probably has something to do with these three states because the Zephyr goes to Chicago and this comes from Seattle, it goes down to Los
Angeles. And the states are all democrats and Oh, God, you know, don't get on a train. Anyway, where was I?
Adam: I was going while I was gonna switch gears if we're done with Flynn, I want to do a quick thing on Bill Gates. And then thanks for more people.
Okay. On show number 780 of this no agenda show best podcasting universe from December 10 2015. This is what we discovered. And Trump isn't yet Bill
Gates knows what's going on. Oh, man. Apparently, at the time, Trump was all
Unknown: over Bill Gates. And we have to do something we have to go see Bill Gates and a lot of different people that really understand what's
happening.
Adam: He was apparently he was all in on Bill Gates. I don't think so so much anymore. And here is the the obligatory one to show clip of Bill Gates
telling us what's going to happen, what's needs to happen, and it's gonna be an RNA vaccine, and sure people will die. But it's the only way to go.
Unknown: There's an approach called RNA vaccine that people like Madonna Karabakh, and others are using, by
Adam: the way, these are the companies that either he personally, but certainly the Gates Foundation has put money into Madonna would be the number
one. It's why he mentioned it in that in 2015, we've identified that is very promising, for pandemics and for other applications as well. And so if
everything goes perfectly with the RNA approach, we could actually beat the 18 months, we don't want to create realistic expectations. the efficacy of
vaccines and older people is always a huge challenge. You know, it turns out the flu vaccine isn't that effective and elderly people most the benefit
comes from younger people not spreading it because they're vaccinated. This is an interesting little tidbit. And I just kind of like highlighting that
since we know that the previous flu shot the 2017 2018 increased the likelihood of the person who received the shot of developing a respiratory virus,
by virus, infect infection by 36%. And so if you've got old people in nursing homes, who I'm sure are pretty much told you're getting this, this
vaccine, even Bill Gates knows they're not very effective on older people because of the state of their immune system. And also, in order to make it
effective, they got a jacket up, which is, is that I think that's what you use the adjuncts for the hamburger helper of vaccines. And that could make
that viral infection even worse, possibly.
Unknown: And that that benefits on a community basis, the elderly here, we clearly need a vaccine that works in the upper age range, because they're
most at risk about and doing that so that you amp it up. So it works in older people and yet, you don't have side effects, you know,
we have in a one in 10,000
side effects that's, you know, way more 700,000
you know, people who will suffer from that. So, really understanding the safety at gigantic scale across all age ranges, you know, pregnant male,
female, undernourished, existing comorbidities. It's very, very hard and that actual decision of Okay, let's go and give this vaccine to the entire
world. Governments will have to be involved because there will be some risk and indemnification needed before that can be decided on.
Adam: Here's the question with all this Madonna and all this work on the RN a vaccine which is in no means a vaccine in the traditional sense because
it's changing RNA versus building immunity by introducing a toned down and or dead version of the violated attenuated well here's my question with all
this focus from Bill Gates clearly on this RNA vaccine What if it doesn't work? Are we in parallel doing the old growing it in an egg thing?
John: I don't hear anyone talking about it. Because now what I mean we are not buddy Coronavirus apparently does not isn't. That's why they sit on
their couch he said himself in one of these little ditties. There may never be a vaccine for Coronavirus is one of those is like AIDS is one of those
things
Adam: well, like it is like MERS like SARS, like all these things like like Ebola,
John: yes all these things. Bullet they do have something but it changes just enough that it can't really be a vaccines ineffective and what they mean
generally speaking by changes enough not so much with with age but with these Coronavirus is that they degenerate. And then next thing you know,
they're not effect they don't really have the impact anymore. laura ingram mentioned it. The French guy who talks about this together win the Nobel
Prize in Medicine that guy thinks is nuts because he's goes against the grain who says is bullcrap this thing isn't going to last year, no more than a
year because it's going to just turn into dust. So can't reproduce
Adam: and live. You're not on the right program today, man.
John: What do you think that is? And that is what Trump thinks too. Yeah. So this whole thing is that's why they're in such a rush to get a vaccine so
they can at least have something to sell. Right? Well, then we just get back to the chlorine hydroxychloroquine. Let's play one last clip from Laura.
This is Ingraham on OC Q.
Unknown: Now, I told you about seven weeks ago that hydroxychloroquine was likely saving lives. And now another study confirms that conclusion. And it
was conducted by NYU Grossman School of Medicine where researchers looked at 932 COVID patients who are on hydroxychloroquine along with zinc and
azithromycin. They concluded that the triple combo that they were that they were 44% less likely to die from the Coronavirus. Good news take that FDA.
Adam: Yeah, I like the I like the practical results more than just these damn studies that are rigged and you've got you know, certain age groups
whether it's positive or negative. I like hearing this from Texas.
Unknown: What happened to this nursing home was one of the first big tests of its kind in Texas.
I thought the risk of seeing 15% of that nursing home die was just not an acceptable risk. A third of patients said this place in Galveston county got
the Coronavirus. So Dr. Robin Armstrong used hydroxychloroquine pills to treat 39 of them. Most of
the patients who've done well. You said most of the patients have done well. Somebody listening to this might say wait
he qualified with most Have there been some who have not done well with it? Well, I would say I would say all the patients of goodwill. On Sunday
these patients finished their five days of treatment and Dr. Armstrong said no one experienced any side effects.
But this 65 year old anti malarial drug has suddenly become controversial. President Trump said it was promising for COVID-19 patients. Armstrong
admits he supports the president,
but democrats correctly caution that this drug remains unproven. For the Coronavirus.
Well, let's say that the President didn't bring this drug up when we would be having this conversation now. I
wonder, sir, that is about the best question I've had so far. And I don't think so. I don't think this would even be a conversation. Honestly.
Adam: No, I think the news reporting would be hopeful results. Good news, senior saved elders. It's not a death sentence. I mean, all of this could
have no but no. And when all is said and done, and 10 years from now, when we look back, we're gonna see that there was a lot of stuff that could have
been done that the actual hate of the President, not even the president hate of a man. A man with orange hair resulted in death.
John: Yeah, these democrats are murderers
Adam: and Democrats, Democrats. They're idiots. It's the it's the
John: as many Republicans that hate Trump too. But this is political. If they do everything you keep hearing about hydroxychloroquine is totally
political. The Democrats, doctors in the rest of it. Oh, no, it's no good. And then Republicans. Yeah, it's good. It works. We've done it. I mean,
come on. When is this going to end? going to end in the election in November. I'm going to
Unknown: show my little boy Joe nice to know agenda. Imagine all the people who could do. Well. Yeah, that'd be fun.
John: Jamie, we got a few people attending for sure, starting with James Niemeyer in Tulsa, Oklahoma $124.20. And he says he found a show on snitcher
What is
Adam: snitcher? Isn't that stitcher?
John: Oh, Stitcher.
Adam: I don't like Stitcher. I never used it stitcher makes a copy of our show. And then they have different formats and quality and they put an ad in
front of it. That's really the if you really want people ripping us off, then you should use that. Well. We have an open source policy.
John: NET Did you just get it some other way? net stormo. Lina and when he got it, he got came in with $124.20. That was highly appreciated. Nestor
Moline and Walker in Michigan. Key. He's at $100. Then we have sorry, Christopher, revolt rebels. I wonder if it's reveled or revolt?
Adam: I would just say revolt.
John: I'm Ryan Mr. revolt.
Adam: Who is easy? 100 Chris revolt with you everybody. It's a great name. I love it.
John: It would be a good Yeah. Chuck name
Unknown: yakni jock name,
John: shock name. Christina Thomas and drums, Pennsylvania. 100. Sir, how now brown cow in Arlington, Virginia. 85. One of our Arlington fans. We love
those guys. Forrest Tucker and Eagle River Arkansas. Arkansas, Arkansas, Arkansas. Cody. No
Adam: way. No, no. Alaska, Alaska.
John: Yeah, I'm sorry. He
Adam: even says he even helps us with it. With a little prompt there, aka
John: Arkansas dummies. He writes.
Adam: You know how you can remember AR ar 15 it's, you know, the South Arkansas AK. It's almost almost near Russia. Ar 16. Alaska is near Russia. So
it's ak 47. There you go.
John: Wow, that works. Yeah, it does. Cody Wilson works to Neff so they can send us $66 from Rosanna Victoria, Australia. And he needs to call out
Pippa McNamara as a douchebag Colin Wilson as a douchebag. Meanwhile, Tara recent Urbana, Illinois 6533 David Forbes in Shakopee, Minnesota 606 sir
not appearing on this podcast in Richland, Washington. 5678. Jag, Jase Jace Han line handline han Hey, hey line halen I don't know.
Adam: Maybe Hanlon handling
John: mainland us halen. 5588 Norcross, Georgia. David Russell in Aurora, Colorado. 5510. And he's gonna be a night. Yeah. Sure. He's got the
accounting and he's on the list. scherbak of 2112 in Charleston, beautiful city to five bucks and he's got a South Carolina Yeah, he's got a much. He
says he wants to wishes smokin hot wife, Dame Jennifer we know her from animated no agenda and the voice that she's working on. A happy birthday
weekend. Oh, be fun. Yes. He says the Jennifer's the best wife in the world. And you guys stay away from her. I'm the luckiest man in the world. I
tell her all the time. That but she doesn't believe.
Adam: He's like, Hey, what's up with these? What's up with these new agenda people around you all the time. I'm not liking that so much.
John: g the man security guy comes into 551 dollars and 11 cents. As Mr. Show since Adam on Rogen. Ah,
Adam: right on
John: that says no agenda exactly the podcast he needed to add to his rotation. Nice. You go
Adam: for your podcast. He listens. He said he also hit his dad in the mouth not shortly after and started listening. He started listening now to Oh
man. This Rogen appearance has got a seven new people. At least.
John: Skylar Sanders in Oklahoma I'm
Adam: sorry, I'm sorry. He asked for deducing we missed. You've been D douchey. Man, the security guy.
John: Well, some business partners are helping out Skyler Sanders in Oakland, California. 5111 says that he started listening about a month and a half
ago at the behest of one of his business partners cool. I also a show producer. So he will Be you will be called out for a birthday today
Adam: for his wife who is also a registered nurse. Very good.
John: He says he's a business owner in Oakland with insight information, leading to a boiling scandal by city officials that will partially they'll be
partially precedent for Martin, Elon Musk Tesla's lawsuit against Alameda County. He's probably have a lunch now. Read it reach out to you and your
special note. Yeah, we do have a one Elan musk clip they're talking about this. Thomas. Jatin in vinata. There's a lot of double A's in this. Yeah.
$50.33 takes me to knighthood. All right. TJ, you got it. TJ and the following peeler $50 note donors name and location story with Robert kerbeck. in
Essex Ville, Michigan. Cassidy Eastwood in Oklahoma City, Brandon sub wha I'm sure is a Sure sir Brandon in Port orchard, Washington sir lineman of
the net and Anna Anna, Illinois. Or as some people would pronounce it Illinois. Kimberly Redmond and Toronto, Ontario Tyler Boyd parts of knowing sure
lab rat of the hill country over there in Universal City, Texas. A lot of booze makers in that area. Clayton Clayton done event in Greenfield,
Wisconsin. Sure. Big Papa moose of the Ogallala Aquifer in liberal Kansas. Michael Burlington Odessa, Florida. Ross in touch cough in London, UK. And
last but not least, our favorite Dame Patricia Worthington. They're in Miami. She's actually a Baroness in Miami, Florida. And that concludes our
producers and well wishers for show 1242 dan, we
Adam: appreciate the production help from everybody also those who helped produce under $50 usually for anonymity if it's right around the 50 but
there's several programs we have that are sustaining for us and recurring for you. We have 3333 1111 we got $5 a show $5 a month it's all
explained@divorce.org slash na and thank you very much once again, the hundreds of people have come together to bring you this episode of the best
podcasting universe known as the no agenda show as requested a couple karmas
Unknown: jobs, jobs, jobs and jobs. Jobs. Karma and remember
Adam: us for our Sunday show devora.org
Unknown: slash n A.
Adam: Got a couple of birthdays to celebrate today is the 14th of may 2020. Joseph says Happy Birthday to his smokin hot wife Dame Adrian and his
daughter violence and that will be for I was yesterday so we're one day late. Tim who says Happy Birthday to his daughter Anna she turned 16 sir Andy
of terrigal Beach. Happy birthday to his dementia be mother Carol who turns 78 today and she still reads the newspaper without her glasses. Neil IDEs
has Happy Birthday to his smokin hot wife Amanda sternbach of 2112 Happy Birthday to You guess that his smokin hot wife Dame Jennifer and Skylar
Sanders says Happy Birthday to his wife we say happy birthday for everybody here at the best podcast in the universe. We have 1234 we have 1234 Wow,
four nights and a dame sounds like talk sounds like the beginning of a song. Oops, sorry. Uh, tripped over the wire. You
John: need this? Yes, that's
Adam: it, and I got to pick mine up now. Thank you. onstage please. Christopher Berry, Jonathan Frederick. David Russell. Thomas, john tienen. All of
you have supported the no agenda show in the amount of $1,000 or more so have you taken a long time mama bear I'm looking at you and we're very happy
to pronounce the cake all of you as surrender not wave bender of The Spark. Sir j from the land of squirrel butters sir Russell, sir john tienen and
de mama bear of Essex dangerous for you. We've got hookers and blow red boys and Chardonnay. rubenesque women and rosae we got guys and sock a bucket
Villa Bong gets a bourbon sparkling cider. Henceforth ginger ale and turbos, breast milk and pablum. And, of course, mutton and Mead. It's all here at
the table for you. Thank you for your support. We love honoring you here at the roundtable. And on your way out head over to no agenda nation.com
slash ring. So Eric, the show can get that off to you. As soon as we get them in. We got another batch on the way soon I'm reliably informed. Thank
you again, and Remember, we'll be back on Sunday devora.org slash na. And let's see if we had anything else interesting.
John: I got it covered as I'm promised to do the Tesla, the Tesla store. So here's an Elan musk update from democracy now. Okay.
Unknown: In Northern California billionaire Tesla CEO Elon Musk has restarted work at Tesla's huge electric vehicle factory in Fremont, daring
government officials to arrest him for violating a Coronavirus lockdown. On Tuesday, President Trump tweeted California should let Tesla and Elon Musk
open the plant now it can be done fast and safely the president tweeted, Elon Musk tweeted back thank you. Musk has repeatedly downplayed the threat
of the Coronavirus and cold government imposed quarantines fascist, Los Angeles County's top public health officials said Tuesday stay at home orders
will be extended for the next three months. At least 1300 deaths in LA have been linked to COVID-19 California State University's president Tuesday
announced plans to cancel most in person classes during the fall semester.
John: Yeah, the cook you know I can't do this not good.
Adam: quick trip around the world. I've got. I have Corona in Brazil and Africa, which is an interesting little report
Unknown: not so in Brazil, which is emerging as a serious epicenter. Even though president gyre bolson arrow supporters still cheer him on.
He's provoked outrage
as a COVID denier who still won't social distance. And this weekend, he went for a provocative spin on a jet ski
as the number of Coronavirus deaths passed 10,000 local authorities put a COVID message on Rio's famous Christ, the Redeemer statue, have a heart wear
a mask?
Adam: They topped us they
John: were definitely I mean, they have like 10,000 dead and we have at Cushing 90,000. Yeah, and we shut down the country and Brazil didn't and our
population is 350, there's 250. So they're there, their numbers should be higher. I mean, it looks like an experiment they don't want to do. Because
Boston, our balsan, our bolson arrow is is a right winger, supposedly a kind of a business oriented guy. The left press down there hates him, they go
is basically a fascist. And so you got the same kind of politics going on with Brazil. You know what I want? The numbers aren't really being I don't
think their numbers are high enough to know they're not No,
Adam: they're not. But you know, just just throwing surge and dead and whatever. So you have to see the statue with the with that big
John: to see the statue in person. That's a beautiful statue.
Adam: What I think we should do here in America is we choose to put a big mask on the Statue of Liberty.
John: Yes. I think that's exactly what I was thinking.
Adam: Let's go to Africa,
Unknown: in Africa and Southeast Asia, the virus does appear to be spreading more slowly, maybe because the population tends on average to be younger.
Adam: Wow, that's all you got. You don't have anything about anti-malarials. Okay.
Unknown: But no one is sure. And it's
quite possible that the worst is yet to come. You know, a
Adam: surge is quite possible worse has yet to come they can't stand it. Boris Johnson goofed up during Prime Minister's question time.
Unknown: Thank you, Mr. Speaker. I thank the Prime Minister for his update on progress of testing and tracing this invisible killer, but can you
confirm to the people of West Oxfordshire that the new systems that we are putting in place will in the fullness of time be able to detect local flare
ups is indeed Mr. Speaker and the intention is that the COVID alert system in time will be sufficiently sensitive and flexible as to detect local
flare ups. So that for instance if a COVID is detected in the water supply in a certain town or wherever then then steps can be taken.
Adam: So people immediately went What did Coronavirus can be in the water supply,
John: please?
Adam: Well what he meant course he meant in the sewage system.
Unknown: Uh huh.
John: Yeah. Well, that did maybe that's not saying much for the water supply in England. No kidding. I have one last clip. And this is just a wacky
clip that the mainstream won't pick up on and Amanda Bernie Bernie bros won't pick up on but Bernie it along with Ihara Ilhan Omar, these two
communists have decided that they think that they're all just one The banks don't want this guy by the way, they're never gonna he's never gonna be a
candidate should realize this. If you listen to this insanity
Unknown: for mock independent senator Bernie Sanders and Minnesota democratic congress member Ilhan Omar have joined more than 300 lawmakers around
the world calling for the cancellation pouring up.
John: You had to start over. But I just wanted to dance. What 300 lawmakers she says 300 law makers around the world. This includes like the
communists in Venezuela, and the socialists here in the socialists, there should disease 300 law makers around the world aren't anyone in their right
mind, but go on that plate again.
Unknown: For mock independent senator Bernie Sanders and Minnesota democratic congress member Ilhan Omar have joined more than 300 lawmakers around
the world calling for the cancellation of poor nations debts as they struggle with the COVID-19 crisis. This comes as the United Nations warns as many
as a half a billion people could fall into poverty due to the pandemic and a letter to the leadership of the World Bank and the International Monetary
Fund Tuesday, Senator Sanders writes quote in the face of a horrific pandemic and a worldwide recession, we cannot allow poor countries to get
adequate money that should be going towards protecting the health and safety of their people to pay off unsustainable debts we cannot allow these
countries to be deprived of the resources they need to purchase food medicine protective gear and medical equipment senator said
John: he wants to read by
Adam: everybody else cancel everyone else's debt except ours.
John: Yeah, cancel all the debts around the world which is a you got yourself in this situation and you want to just have it cancel. you hoped that it
gets Canada he also wants to cancel all student loan debt. And he just wants to cancel everything. So I don't know if he understands and Omar the rest
of it even though how the system works. We're not a socialist society. We're not China. We're not we're a capitalist country. It's just bullshit. I
mean, I find it to be offensive.
Adam: It's also short sighted look at what President Trump is saying. His idea I like his idea is let's get negative interest rates and then
ultimately when you take out a loan for school you'll get paid for it it's real simple I don't understand why people don't understand this is great. I
can't wait for negative interest rate waiting for all my life everybody's been waiting for that. Well cnn is and these will be my last clip cnn just
like when the Malaysian airliner was last you know they they went on for over a year every single day and that items and special shows so that cnn is
doing what they do best they've got to do they're gonna do their special show, so let's check out a promo for one of them
Unknown: taking on Coronavirus in hockey communities of color. Join Don Lemon advantage with Dr. Regina Benjamin and Robert Smith. Plus messages from
Mario Lopez Samuel L. Jackson and more the color of COVID live tomorrow at 10 on CNN the color of
Adam: COVID within Did you say inspiring messages hopeful messages.
John: Even one black person who watches cnn
Unknown: plus messages of hope or Mario Lopez
Adam: plus message of hope plus messages of hope from podcasters you love from around the world. Yeah, that's there's that and then we have this
little ditty just as fun.
Unknown: Join Anderson Cooper and Dr. Sanjay Gupta with former acting CDC director Richard besser, former Health and Human Services Secretary Kathleen
Sebelius, and activist gratitude for Coronavirus live Thursday at eight
John: I'm glad you got that.
Adam: I can't wait it's tonight credit to
John: Enberg what the hell does she have to do with Coronavirus?
Adam: Well she had it so what yeah did that
John: so you're an expert because you caught you caught a cold so now you're a doctor.
Adam: Oh and Van Jones is a is an expert on Coronavirus. Yeah.
Unknown: Come on, man. If
Adam: you got to enjoy the little things, this is fun. This is you know, it's
John: gonna be a turd. It's
Adam: it's really fun, man. Come on.
John: Well, I got one. I got one then. Let's listen to some other. Another idiocy. This is Rick bright. He's going to testify in front of Congress.
He's well on. He's a virologist, but somehow he's become magically become an epidemiologist.
Unknown: Tomorrow on Capitol Hill, Rick Bryan the administration's former top vaccine researcher who is pushed out of his position will testify that
if the response is not ramped up work 2020 will be the darkest winter in modern history.
Yes,
Adam: it'll be a cold and lonely Christmas without you. I don't believe Have it anymore. I really don't care. It's,
John: it's quite the beat.
Adam: I don't believe any of it anymore and tiresome. It is a little tiresome.
John: But it's amazing. We can put a show together. I mean, it's I have to struggle.
Adam: Well, that's a very good point. Because we both I know that we both were digging deep and hard for for material for today. If you don't want to
bore people, you know, you got to come up with new stuff. And here you go. Yeah. c span is still beautiful thing.
John: Yeah, we've got some stuff from them.
Unknown: Coming up. If
Adam: you want to hear the full of Nick the rat interview with john McAfee, that'll be a no agenda. stream.com You know, I like how these guys think,
very smart here at the no agenda stream. And we have a couple of end of show mixes we've got Oh, Rolando Gonzales, which had promised to play from the
last show. We've got Jason Lewis and Jesse Coyne Nelson. And we would love to see you back with us again to produce another episode of the best
podcast in the universe on Sunday. Until then, I'm coming to you from the opportunity zone 33 here in Austin, Texas, FEMA Region number six on the
governmental maps in the morning, everybody. I'm Adam Curry,
John: and from Northern Silicon Valley, where we're all wondering, whatever happened to him, hands up, don't shoot. I'm John Dvorak.
Adam: We return on Sunday right here on no agenda. Remember us at the vortec.org slash na until then adios mo follows ends.
Unknown: You know, the nursery rhyme that goes Hickory dickory dock, the mouse ran up that Trump death clock.
So the clock is a billboard that hangs over time square. And what it shows is an estimate of the number of us COVID-19 deaths that resulted from the
President and his team's
failed response to the coronavirus outbreak
here on Sesame Street. Today's guest
is right over there.
thanks to Dr. Fauci and leading epidemiologists, we now know that happened mitigation guidelines been put into effect just one week earlier, on March
9, instead of March 16 60% of us COVID-19 deaths would have been prevented.
Ready to run up the Trump death clock is ready to strike. The Trump death clock stands at 46,485 and growing. Travel.
John: podcast
Unknown: you know we're not like
show me
where in
class.
You always act surprised.
How are you? Nice.
This should never have happened.
This virus should not have spread all over the world. They allowed us to go into our country. This should never have happened.
More than a dozen children in the New York City area have ended up in intensive care with severe symptoms, possibly linked to Coronavirus. The finding
has not been peer reviewed a rate of infection is rising
very fast heart rate, high fever and their heart rate still stays very high,
they will come
to the ICU for extra support.
There is now a more powerful mutant strain of the virus.
They couldn't put up the fire.
The rate of infection is rising like bringing a camera into focus. These techniques give us a far clearer picture that help us to inform our actions
going forward.
Thank you very much.
A new study finds the novel Coronavirus that emerged in China mutated in Europe in February to become more contagious speeding and spread around the
globe to study drugs. We become Without the virus that might not hold up for further scrutiny.
What's that all
Adam: about? Absolute fear over getting sick.
Unknown: The rate of infection is rising. Again, I
encourage all businesses that are allowed to do so only if they follow the guidelines to keep us safe.
More people are reading.
I actually am scared I lose sleep
over all this. The rate of infection is rising.
They send it to the European Council in Northern European Council. They send it back to the European Parliament in April a few days ago. He sent it to
the European Council of European Council they sent it back to the European Union. In April a few days ago. They sent it to the European Council of the
European Council they send it back to the Eurogroup
the rate of infection is rising
John: like this a lot shut up slave. like this a lot
Adam: shut up slave.
Unknown: The rate of infection is rising.
mopho John dvorak.org
slash n A
masks