Adam: Adam Curry,
John: John Dvorak,
Adam: Sunday, May 17 2020. This is your award winning gitmo-nation Media assassination Episode 1200 43. This is no agenda. Texas,
John: Silicon Valley, I believe Adams turned into a Democrat. I'm Jesse devorah.
Adam: Figured I'd try and see how it works with the mask seeing is that is what we're going to be coerced into no matter what we want.
John: Well, I've read these orders, and none of them say you have to be wearing a mask all
Adam: the time, correct? You do not. So
John: why are people wearing the mask all the time? They're wearing them in their car? I'm wearing them at home.
Adam: Yeah, yeah, I have done some investigative work on this. And, unfortunately, this is a result of the, I would say the, the society that we've
created, certainly younger people, and it goes like this, you have to wear a mask to keep me safe. Okay, you have to wear the mask to keep me safe. So
if you're not wearing a mask, but I'm wearing a mask, I'm keeping you safe, but you're a douchebag. And that's the bottom line, you're not going to
get away from it. People are mad, they're angry. And I think that if we want to just open up, I have a suggestion. It's completely optional. So
wherever you go, a store doesn't have to force you to wear masks, but they can. And if they do, then you should will respect that. Any other place
where you want me to wear a mask so that you feel safe is good, I'll wear the mask, and to make sure I feel safe. And I'm protected from you. I'm
going to open carry my firearm. And I'm going to do this in Texas. So that you can see I'm not a Democrat.
John: Democrats have guns.
Adam: open carry? No, I don't think so. in Austin, no double No. Not at all.
John: A couple of things here. I I questioned your premise. By that, I mean, I'm not absolutely sure that all these douchebags wearing a mask actually
think that they're wearing the mask to protect you from them? No, it's
Adam: it's all virtue signaling. But that is that's what that's the reasoning that's given. That's the rationale. It's not even really true.
John: But then why shouldn't be wearing the mask in their car?
Adam: Well, that's okay. If they want to feel that that's their business. I don't care if they want to look like idiots. But I'd like to get away from
this. We're never going to open up fully until we agree on some social things. And if it's going to be masked, oh my god, so be it. Go ahead, force
everybody to wear a mask. That's we need to do something and I'm willing to compromise. But again, I'm going to open carry which is legal. As long as
you have your concealed carry in Texas, you can open carry and I intend to do that in my car to an A on the street.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah, it's,
Adam: you know, there's I don't think there's any other way for us
John: to go. So you don't have you have a whole street yet?
Adam: Oh, I have several wholesalers. In Italy. They're opening up on Tuesday. And they will have social distancing. I've got a little report from
Willow. So they'll have all that set. But masks shall be worn until there's a cure or a vaccine. So I'm seeing what's going on, we're not going to get
away from this is going to be an endless fight with a whole bunch of idiots and we just have to become Japan. We're already on our way financially
into the Japanese debt trap. So we might as well just go the full nine yards. I don't see
John: a note from where Duke and Duchess or the Duke anyway, which you either have it.
Adam: I'd like to read it during the donation segment. But I have some
John: it's kind of I think I might want to read it. nothing's really exactly what
Adam: all right, all right, well, okay. I have a report from China as well. This is from sir mark and Dame Astrid, the Duke and Duchess of Japan and
all the disputed islands in the Japan sea. And we will read most of this on during the donation segment but masks work is the Japanese reasoning, and
the whole country wears them for flu season every year, especially on the most crowded mass transit system in the world, he gives us a month numbers,
they've only had 739 deaths for a population of 126 million, which is very good. Compare that. So that's what he put here. That's like, it's like 10
times less than the United States. If you believe the numbers, of course,
John: yeah. Then it Well, there you go.
Adam: Well, hold on, hold on, we'll get we'll get back we'll get there. Mass usage went up with COVID. But it also meant that it was the weakest flu
season and over 10 years, interestingly, that's not the same here. In fact, the mortality rate in Japan for March was also down on top of this, if you
feel you have symptoms, and this I think is kind of cool Japan is doing you're asked to go to one of the many hotels that have been commandeered for
isolation hub. So you don't go to the hospital and infect everybody. You don't go home and infect everybody. You go to one of the designated hotels,
and the government has options and over 120,000 hotel rooms across the nation that I think is a pretty good idea.
John: That if you think about if you're a traveler, well, this room previously occupied,
Adam: nobody's traveling. Nobody's traveling. Nobody's traveling. But yeah, if you want to go to, to the to the obvious hurdles, but maybe just a
quick update from Wu Han. One of our producers is back. And I'll read his notes. or hers anonymous, we're back in Wu Han Friday. Wu Han. This is Wu
Han said they were going to test 11 million people in 10 days. Yeah, yeah. And I looked at the math and said, I don't know how that's gonna work, but
we have a little more data. Our producer says back in Wu Han Friday, Wu Han tested just over 113,000 people. Our hotel slash Department called us and
we'll schedule our test this coming week. My clients are testing the workers at work in the Chinese government is setting up testing stations and
local hate neighborhoods. They will test everyone in 10 days it's not really even a blip on most people's day. One client has a parking lot that is
full of tables and trailers that has two tests. Blood and throat swabs takes less than 10 minutes to stand in line and go through the process. Yeah,
that is 11 million people times 10 minutes I'm just I really want to see how they're gonna complete this. And so far only 113,000 done. I had to do
this went bull crap. That's how I had to do this when I first arrived in Wu Han so I couldn't start work. This will be my third test is coming back to
China Wu Han is mostly open. Some restaurants have dining inside while others are takeout only. I can't use DD which is their version of Uber only
taxis because they track you and you need a Chinese ID to register to be tracked by the Chinese Uber. Our local wet market is open but not inside then
move the market to the sidewalk and made it one way traffic. Enter on one side and walk through to the to exit the opposite side. You need to have
your temperature scan before you enter any place and show the QR code having fun and Wu Han when we first arrived a few weeks ago pollution level was
great. We had blue skies and some stars at night. Now it's back to gray skies and burning eyes. So
John: I've never I've never seen a blue sky in China.
Adam: Well, I think it probably did happen when it was was all shut down. That's what he says.
John: Yeah, I bet it probably was quite phenomenal.
Adam: So in order not to go through all of that tracking and everything I suggest the mask I really do. I mean I hate it. I'm against it. But it's we
have to sacrifice somewhere this them and Republicans need to shut up and just get on board move on. Let's do it. We can always do something later on
and maybe people will forget about it. But this is not the hill anyone should take a stand on in my opinion, because we're dying. I was reading a
fashion a column about the fashion industry this morning. You know it that the nothing could take what's her name from Vogue magazine? Oh my goodness
and a winner Anna Wintour, the Anna Wintour famous editor of Vogue magazine with the glasses Devil Wears Prada movie made about her. the fashion
industry is saying Well, it looks like nothing could take her down but the Coronavirus that can take her down and the fashion industry is obliterated.
Doesn't this the fashion designers are out of business or going out of business. Not that I'm crying about it. But you know there's a lot of people
that work in the fashion industry. It just the longer we we do this the longer it's going to be a problem and assholes like Fauci and all these people
need to get out of the way will wear some masks, make it optional for people to requirement and let's go let's move on. No, no, no, we can't do that.
Here's Austin. They've gone back to the color codes of a threat level of 911.
John: Tonight amid state
Unknown: demands to rollback its Coronavirus restrictions. Austin Travis County is now releasing new pants guidelines divided into five stages. The
chart suggests what actions to take based on community's risk of contracting the Coronavirus stage one is where we want to be the charts separate
suggestions by the general public low risk individuals and those at high risk such as anyone over 65 years old.
So if you're a high risk individual, then the suggestion is, is that
even in stage one,
that you still avoid gatherings for everyone else social distancing and mask wearing appears at stage two. Austin public health says we're in stage
three right now. This means avoiding groups of more than 10 people and avoiding non essential travel Mayor Steve Adler says hitting stage five means
the city is in a pretty bad place and needs to take extreme measures.
Adam: You look at this thing. It's like a grid with colors and numbers. And you know, and it's reverse order. So stage five is worse. Stage One is
good. is dumb, is dumb. pussies. Man's go, go go.
John: And what is what is his preoccupation with non essential travel? What does that even mean? What is non essential travel?
Adam: It's everything is non essential travel unless you're an essential person.
John: But if you go into the store,
Adam: no, I think travel means I don't know. I don't know. I don't care. It's all bull crap. They can't force actually
John: what I said, Yeah,
Adam: but but we can sit and bicker or we can get going. And I'm very I'm getting a little worried here in Austin, which is different from the rest of
Texas. And the rest of Texas is doing it a little differently. And moving a little faster. Now here we all have to be pansies. And meanwhile, just get
back to the numbers because that's really the problem. There are increasingly more there's increasingly more evidence that this death count is really
really full of crap. And do you remember I said that I think Burks might have flipped and she was all kind of on Trump's side and maybe anti
establishment that she's trying to save herself from the impending doom that these people will meet when we finally figure out where all the money is
coming from and going and, you know, Judicial Watch is doing all kinds of FOIA requests on the Fauci and the NIH, you don't want that. You don't want
that. And I'm sure he hasn't covered everything else. You
John: don't want that he
Adam: doesn't want that. Fauci doesn't want that you don't want Tom Fitton on me, you don't want Tom Fitton in Judicial Watch making a stink about
your business, which has been, as far as I can tell, very shady for a long time. So this is a CNN report. Jim Acosta. It was a very long report. I
chopped it down because it was really billed as tensions rise between the administration and let me get the exact, exact title here. Tensions rise
between the White House and CDC as Burke's critiques, virus tracking and the death rate in control of the Coronavirus message coming from the
Unknown: White House President Trump is giving the administration a pat on the back for the US response to the pandemic with the enormous weight of
the pandemic hanging over the White House sources tell cnn administration officials are questioning the accuracy of the Coronavirus death toll in the
US and whether the number of dead is being over counted, but that would fly in the face of testimony from top administration health expert Dr. Anthony
Fauci, who said deaths are likely being under counted as some residents and hard hit New York died at home and were never counted as COVID-19
fatalities.
So in direct answer to your question, I think you are correct that the number is likely higher. I don't know exactly what
percent higher
but almost certainly it's higher.
The President suggested New York's
Adam: I love how they did that. First they say the numbers are bullcrap. And then they get cut straight to Fauci out of context. And but it's all no
tire is definitely higher. This is a good report from CNN when it comes to propaganda, teen fatalities.
Unknown: So in direct answer to your question, I think you are correct that the number is likely higher. I don't know exactly what tire but almost
certainly it's higher.
The President suggested New York's number of dead was too high last month.
I see this morning where New York added 3000 deaths because they died and they're now saying rather than it was a heart attack, they're
saying it was a heart attack caused by this Trump allies on Fox News have zeroed in on Fauci as an obstacle to reopening the country, blasting the
doctors cautious approach to the pandemic. Is this the guy you want to chart chart the future of the country? Maybe not. This is a very serious matter
the decisions we're making right now. Tony Fauci has not been elected to anything Fauci to be very blunt is the face of this failed administrative
leave got a question. The entire premise of this was the chief buffoon of the professional has
Dr. Anthony pouchy also seems to pay for what the democrats want. And that is massive restrictions. With no end in sight with all due respect to Dr.
Fauci his expertise, and no one elected him to anything,
but there's one big problem for the White House, a CNN poll found a solid majority of Americans trust Fauci, not the president. So the
Adam: whole point is, they don't really really interested in talking about the facts of the death rate. Let's just go ahead and say Fox News are
assholes and Fox News is doing the same to CNN. But every day I could play a report like this when police
Unknown: in Cortez, Colorado found 35 year old Sebastian yellow in their city park on May 4. coroner George Deaver is quickly determined what killed
the man.
Adam: It wasn't COVID it was alcohol toxicity Yes, he did have COVID but that is not what took his life.
Unknown: In fact, yellows alcohol level was point five five, nearly double the amount that's fatal, so he literally drank himself to death.
Adam: Yes,
Unknown: exactly. dever is tested yellow for COVID-19. After his death, and the test was positive. The coroner said he was surprised to see the state
then show COVID deaths in Montezuma County, go from two to three, with Sebastian yellows counting as number three
Adam: before the death certificate was signed.
Unknown: They had
John: already listed it as a COVID death before the death
Unknown: certificate was even signed. dever said he's been trying to get the state health department to explain how a case of fatal alcohol poisoning
was classified as a COVID death
Adam: and they should have to be recording the same way that I do. They have to go off the truth and the facts enlisted as such.
Unknown: It's not the first time the state health department has come under fire for reclassifying deaths as COVID fatalities. Last month. I CBS for
investigation found attending physicians at this Centennial Nursing Home Rule three deaths were not related to Coronavirus, but since the residents
had tested positive for covid 19. The state then listed them as Coronavirus, deaths.
Adam: There you go every day, you could have one of these reports every single day, but
John: it's just one every show shift started. Exactly just the beginning. We've done one of these days just this is you don't see Where's the other
reports? In other words, you know if they've heard under county how right or wrong rageous reports coming constantly. No,
Adam: we can't have that there'll be none of that. I put in the show not doable. I put in the show notes a report from BMJ that's a big deal. What
does BMJ stand for something? medical journal? What is it the BMJ
John: British Medical Journal?
Adam: Think it's c? BMJ i think is BMJ calm Let me see what is it? Oh BMJ yeah bmj.com. Now the leading edge there it is. They don't even expand the
acronym u A holes. The BMJ is the something of medical journal. Okay. Anyway, whatever it is, it's a real medical journal real medical report
abstract. This is a cluster randomized trial of cloth masks compared with medical masks. And the objective was to see if there's a difference what is
good, what is not good. It's all marked up one of our producers actually was kind enough to do this conclusion. The study is the first of cloth masks
and the results caution against the use of cloth masks which is what we're all using because, you know we don't have enough disposable medical masks,
moisture retention, reuse of cloth masks and poor filtration may result in increased risk of infection Whoo. Right there in the BMJ so we are not
getting good information. This is what's frustrating. This is what's driving people I think nuts I have a one of our producers works in a store which
is starting to open up and this is believe it or not a store with Democrats. And I just listened to this note that has been written to the managers of
this place managers I've been in the store for 90 seconds and two of the first nine people I walked past first thing are not wearing their face masks
while within six feet of other staff are in public space as all uppercase now I am disappointed and what I thought was a team of individuals who were
appreciated and employer that had as much concern for them as they do themselves. We've spent the last month net losses as a result of our selfless
act of closing the stores and paying everyone for four weeks so that we can do our part in trying to keep our staff and their families healthy, safe
as well as mentally and emotionally secure in very uncertain times. all caps still, that won't happen. We can't get our money back but I damn sure
will take action to make sure it was not in vain. Va any misspelling we will do absolutely everything in our power to prevent sickness and the risk of
having to close our doors again. Bla bla bla bla, let me be clear In writing, so there's no misunderstanding, I won't do the voice anymore. Wearing a
face mask is great wearing a face mask by employees and sub i just spit all over my screen, wearing a face mask by employees and subcontractors
requirement while conducting company business at anytime, anywhere. And while I property for any reason, following company protocol for preventing
COVID-19 spread at a rate of 100%. It's a requirement. The grounds are simple. Employees terminated for being a clear and present danger to health,
safety and well being of our team members and customers by not taking the measures required by company policy wearing a face mask to help prevent the
spread of COVID-19. That's pretty serious. Why would you run into this little screed? One of our producers, who I'm going to keep anonymous works
there, and this was sent to her. Yeah, it's really this. That's why I'm saying who cares? Let's just go for it, do it. Get over it already. So we can
just move on because we'll never get out of this. We'll never ever get out of this, by the way, the CDC data, which I have the link for in the show
notes, a couple of our producers record this data and, and you know, from week to week, etc. And this producer said I went to update my spreadsheet
notice that they have increased all of the 2019 2020 season numbers even though most weeks have been listed as 100% reported before, increased total
deaths by literally 1000s per week, even though they said in there and then we have the proof their own documents. This is 100% counted, or 100%
reported. And then they re they updated it and they just added 1000s to several weeks.
John: What Yeah, yeah.
Adam: The CDC isn't is not a
John: good outfit. No, it's just been corrupt for years.
Adam: Now to go back to your your statement about this not being a requirement and not being a law that we have to adhere to. You know, of course,
absolutely right. Here's Dr. Drew, who was still I don't know if he's on Fauci sphere squad anymore, or if he's freewheeling but here's his latest.
And let's remind ourselves, the CDC never recommended shut down.
Unknown: They never recommended shut down. They recommended social distancing. And let's not confuse social distancing and shut down. Those are two
very different things, shutting down businesses isolating in place those those are far reaching measures beyond mere social distancing. So the real
question is, was that necessary? Might there have been a more rational intermediate step to take clothes, some businesses closed, some schools isolate
nursing homes? Might that have been a more sophisticated way to do this? And given that in California, we overshot by somewhere between a factor of 10
and 50.
Evidence we did suggest we did a great job. And maybe we did too good a job depending on how bad or how our economy is hit.
Adam: Brother. So now I have probably the most frightening thing of the day, I'll get it out of the way right away. Thank you. While we cannot, while
we have not been forced to shut down, we've been compliant, very compliant Human Resources doing as we're told social engineering and great play,
we're being shamed into compliance. And the ultimate question is, when a vaccine comes around, how is that going to work now? We'll probably dive in
later into the this Rick bright character who keeps coming back, who was slated to be the guy running the program. Now the military is going to do
that we'd already said I think a couple weeks ago, there was going to be warp speed operation warp speed was the get the vaccine but done and in and
out and ready for distribution by January of 2021. So when that comes out, do we will we all have to take it is it going to be optional? Will you take
the vaccine, john?
John: I know nobody in the family's taking this vaccine. And what
Adam: if you were forced to take the vaccine? That's not gonna happen? Here is a constitutional lawyer Alan Dershowitz. Let's be very clear
Unknown: how we break down this issue. The City of New York, the state of New York has the power to close a park, based on their view that it would be
helpful in defeating the pandemic. Absolutely no question about that the Supreme Court has case after case after case saying that public health
justifies closing down parks closing down public areas. The next question is does the governor have the right to do that Governor's generally are not
authorized to make the law. They're authorized to enforce the law, so you'd have to look to see If there were legislative authority, allowing the
governor to close the bar, if there is, then it would be legitimate. Let me put it very clearly you have no constitutional right to endanger the
public and spread the disease. Even if you disagree, you have no right not to be vaccinated, you have no right not to wear a mask. And if you refuse
to be vaccinated, the state has the power to literally take you to a doctor's office and plunge a needle into your arm. If the vaccination is designed
to prevent the spreading disease, the vaccination is only to prevent a disease that you will get, for example, if there's a disease that will kill
you. You have the right to refuse that but you have no right to refuse to be vaccinated against a contagious disease. Public Health the police power
Constitution gives the state the power to compel that there are cases in the United States Supreme Court.
Adam: Holy crap. I was not aware that that was a constitutionally somehow possible.
John: Well, I'd like to hear other interpretations. Dershowitz has got one opinion about a lot of stuff.
Adam: Right. But we typically like what Dershowitz has to say can't just because you disagree, you can say
John: yeah, you know, he's become a bit of a waiver recently. I mean, he's a D league. I mean, he's what he's saying is probably true. But I'm sure
there's other ways of dealing with Well, this is not going to happen, we're not going to get a shot. Remember, h1 and one, swine flu,
Adam: we're still waiting for you.
John: Still waiting for this show. We discussed Oh, they're gonna remember that whole rigmarole is gonna have to be two shots, maybe three and then
down to one and then become part of the flu shot. And it was all these different things. That's what that era when people at because I took pictures
and put it in the newsletter, where they were giving the shots out in Albany. They had a line,
Adam: though. I remember that.
John: Yeah, yes. Yeah, opening a Star Wars. The public will line up for this shot in such a way to such a degree. Yeah, that you there's not gonna
they're gonna force anyone to get the shot, because there's gonna be so many people getting the shot, they're gonna probably run out of it. Yeah,
that's
Adam: a good point. That's a good point.
John: don't line up, lined up a mile long.
Adam: And as the President says,
Unknown: a fully approved vaccine for everyone, the full public or a partially approved vaccine with emergency, you know, we're looking for
a full vaccine for everyone that wants to get it not everybody's gonna want to get it. There you go. But we're looking at a fall vaccine. Is that a
correct statement? Yeah, we'll
see that. So the answer, what
Adam: is the question? We're looking at a full vaccine? What is that, like a half of a man? I'll take the quarter a quarter.
John: She was asking me something that's not quite fully approved. I
Adam: understand. I understand.
Unknown: Get that info vaccine. Is
that a correct statement? That will? Yes.
So the answer is the answer is yes, we're working for a fully approved vaccine. But we'll also use the tools we have, for instance, emergency use
authorization, as appropriate. We use all of our regulatory tools to bring vaccine available for the entire American population by January.
Okay. And then Mr. President, can you just clarify? Sure, some of you wearing a mask? And why are some of you not wearing a No,
please, we've all been tested. I've been tested, we've all been tested, and we're quite a distance away. And we're outdoor. So I told them, I gave
them the option or they could wear it or not. So you can blame it on me. But I gave them the option we could wear it or not.
Adam: So the President is there saying kind of what I'd like optional vaccine, optional masks and also optional, open carry. So Rick bright was the
guy who was who has traditionally for many years, he's been in and out of government and back to the pharmaceutical industry multiple times. And he is
the guy that was supposed to be in charge of the vaccine. This is the BARDA, the biomedical Advanced Research and Development Authority. And this was
unceremoniously taken away from him as he was pushed out. And now of course, he's a whistleblower. So Oh, yeah, we he has a job, but listen to this
guy's career and you start to understand why you really don't want him in the business of vaccines. In this case, certainly, as he started a while in
Atlanta, Georgia vaccine research center, 98 to 2002. We worked at the CDC in Atlanta, where he studied influenza a virus and the h5 and one from
2000 2003. He went to the pharmaceutical industry, which is always great when you're in government, and then you go to the private industry and then
you can change Apart stuff in. So he went to altea therapeutics is that which is also in Atlanta, and he was a senior research for their vaccine in
immuno immunology programs. In 2003. He went back to the CDC, so only a year that it was in private business, and then he was still in Atlanta, but
then he was focused on the avian flu. And he was there until 2006, then 2006 to 2008, he went to Nova Vax, like the number one penny stock of vaccine
bullcrap on the stock market. During that time, he participated in World Health Organization committees on vaccine development and pandemic
preparedness. And then in 2008, he worked at the Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation. And then in 2010, he came back to the Department of Health and
Human Services. So the guy is way too in entrenched in in the pharmaceutical business. I don't think you want this guy running the show. And the fact
that he's so pissed off about and so angry that he's become a whistleblower, I think tells us I'm sorry, go on. I think that tells us that, you know,
this was not the way it's supposed to go. This is we are going to learn eventually so much about the pharmaceutical and medical industry and all the
egos and all the money that takes place. And it's gonna, it's gonna blow us away. Because the scandal and the bullcrap and the money is 10 times
bigger than then then movies, especially.
Unknown: Today, this
Adam: is Rick bright testified because of course, we got to testify
Unknown: today The world is confronting a public health emergency unlike any we've seen in over a century. We are facing a highly transmissible and
deadly virus, which not only claims lives, but also disrupts the very foundations of our society. The American healthcare system is being taxed to the
limit, our economy is spiraling downward, and our population is being paralyzed by fear stemming from a lack of a coordinated response. And a dearth
of accurate, clear communication about the path forward. Americans yearned to get back to work, to open their businesses and to provide for their
families, I get that. However, what we do must be done.
John: What is he like in charge. So he gets he sounds like is the premier of Canada,
Unknown: get back to work, to open their businesses and to provide for their families, I get that.
Adam: But this is the this is the attitude of these people, I am king.
Unknown: However, what we do must be done carefully. And with guidance from the best scientific minds, our window of opportunity is closing, if we
fail to improve our response Now, based on science, I fear the pandemic will get worse and be prolonged.
Adam: Yeah, this is my favorite part is now we're bringing it all back around to science and trust the
John: republicans in particular, don't believe in science,
Unknown: there will be likely a resurgence of COVID-19. This fall, it'll be greatly compounded by the challenges of seasonal influenza, without better
planning 2020 could be
John: this, these guys this goes on with Biden to where's this science? Where's the science that says it's going to recur? And in the fall of 2020?
Oh, well, there's, there's no specifically what science? No, he's talking about science, science, science, no. Science specifically named something.
What study? Do they know for a fact that this thing's not falling apart? I mean, is there any evidence whatsoever, this is all speculative?
Unknown: Without better planning, 2020 could be the darkest winter in modern history. First and foremost,
Adam: I love could be the darkest winter in modern history. Have you heard of the hunger winter a whole,
Unknown: without better planning? 2020 could be the darkest winter in modern history. First and foremost, we need to be truthful with the American
people. Americans deserve the truth. The truth must be based on science. We have the world's greatest scientists.
Adam: Now, the truth must be based on science is a very interesting phrase. And I think we're going to hear this a lot more. Because there's really
only truth in one thing, and that's mathematics. And what they're showing us is mathematics. And there's no truth in it. You know what I'm saying?
Science is is not always truth. In fact, it's kind of never truth. But we've been through this with global warming, and the green new deal and climate
change, and it's just coming back and please ignore the math that we showed you that was all wrong. Trust in science equal. Americans deserve the
truth. The truth must be based on science. We have the world's greatest scientist, let us lead. Let us speak without fear of retribution. There you
go, john. Let us leave Lead us lead. They want to give the power to the scientist to let them lead you.
Unknown: We must listen. Each of us can and must do our part now. On Tuesday, Dr. Fauci delivered a message in a voice that is clear and trustworthy
has encouraged us to act with caution as we return to our daily lives. We should listen to him and other scientists sharing their expertise.
Adam: Yeah, it's so bad that to push the science and believe the science truth is in science. CNN did a special Sanjay Gupta anderson cooper bringing
John: on to that I have to play a couple of things because because bright testimony was a fiasco and it was a disaster. And I want to play two things
that pray looted this little, this spiel, which everybody clipped about all we're going to have this dark winter and all the rest of it listless. Now
this thing actually began. This is the bright testimony confusion.
Adam: Okay, here we go
Unknown: five minutes for an opening statement?
Well,
you don't think it's resolved?
Adam: Well, are we going to ask if he wants to be represented by counsel and then who the counsel is?
Unknown: Dr. Bright Do you wish to be represented by counsel?
Yes.
John: Okay. And then could she identify herself for the
Unknown: for the record would
counsel please state your name?
My name is
Debra Katz. I'm an attorney representing Dr. Rick bright with the law firm of cats, Marshall and banks. All right.
Thank you.
I think that's all we needed to do. Good. Parliament's All right.
Well, gentleman is recognized for his
Adam: parliamentary parliamentary questions. I'm glad you got this job. This is very good. precedent. So
Unknown: gentlemen, status parliamentary Yeah,
Adam: it will the witness
Unknown: be under oath, because if you have a witness whistleblower testimony under oath, and I, a witness would normally be under oath. And if not
today, he's under oath, not under oath, then if we get into whistleblower allegations, how can we be sure that the witness is telling the truth under
under oath, if they're not under oath? And if they're not under oath, that how can you talk about the whistleblower complaints, I think,
in a fair in a fair and equitable manner,
I thank the gentleman for his inquiry. All witnesses know that it is illegal to lie to Congress, and in our subcommittee, unlike Oh, and I, they are
the only subcommittee that I mean, it's a practice of It's a tradition. But we don't swear people in. But witnesses know that
it is illegal to lie to crown Congress,
John: you ID 1003 or something.
Unknown: Thank you.
John: Now a couple of things. One, that's just an issue. That's, that's heading this subcommittee, and she doesn't know what she's doing. And so the
republican guy has to tell her how to do things properly, and they have to walk through a bunch of things. But this is lying to Congress thing I
didn't realize and apparently, some us code. So what about James Clapper?
Adam: No, that doesn't count. See, the thing is that we're living in a world of calling out hypocrisy. And that's all anyone does all the time. And
and it's it's, it has no it's no benefit. doesn't go anywhere,
John: that it hasn't gone anywhere. So far, which let's get to part two. This is another that now the head Republican, whose name I wrote on the back
of an envelope, I got it back there. He's from Oregon. He's a congressman. He's very good. By the way, this guy, and I'll get as I go get the
envelope. But now this is the beginning of the the kind of the true confusion. And then this makes the whole thing of a joke and a fiasco. And in
fact, and they brought up this lawyer, he wants to be represented by counsel. He says, Yeah, I want to be represented by counsel. She says absolutely
nothing the whole time. He never once asked her a question, so that she's just up there's a joke. And so this part of it makes it even more of a
Josias
Adam: representative Walden, I believe Walden Walden, Greg Walden from
John: quite good, quite good. We have asked for in this committee should hold hearings to find a path forward reform the
Unknown: Strategic National Stockpile, to increase domestic manufacturing of critical supplies and disentangle our supply chains from China. We should
be exploring strategies for increased testing so we can begin to safely reopen our economy. We need to find ways to improve access to mental health
and provide relief both for our healthcare providers on the frontlines treating COVID-19 cases and our health care workers who have been furloughed
because their hospitals are closed. We should be conducting rigorous oversight of the trillions of dollars and myriad new policies Congress
has appropriated and enacted in the last three months and we should be investigating Really investigating allegations like Dr. brights that raise
concern that are about our nation's Coronavirus response. That does not appear to be Why are actually here today. And frankly, it saddens me, Dr.
Bright,
your allegations are serious, they deserve a real investigation. I know the Office of Special Counsel with whom you filed your complaint will do just
that. And I know they take their work seriously and will hear
you out.
And importantly, will give those named in your complaint, an opportunity to have their side heard as well. I must tell you that many of us on our
committee were confused when we learned from a tweet this hearing was scheduled in the wake of your complaint. As you know, that's certainly not how
we do things at the Energy and Commerce Committee. Not long after the notice of this being a whistleblower hearing. We were advised you are here as a
government witness, not a whistleblower. But then we were told you are not representing the government but yourself. The hearing title suggests the
hearings about protecting scientific integrity. Yet the chair invited a witness who will not be speaking to that issue. So it's all pretty confusing
and unusual to say the least. Here we are in the middle of a pandemic, and we aren't given time to secure our witnesses conduct appropriate research
or require documents that could aid in our understanding of the situation you face in the country face.
John: So the whole thing is a sham.
Adam: Of course it is
John: that was set up so Brian can go up there
Adam: and lie and do whatever he wants. He didn't have to do whatever
John: he wants. But the joke is he didn't do a very good job of any of it. Except that one click one click play, which is pretty much what everyone
played. So that was a I consider the whole thing an epic fail. Well, I was honest about Yeah,
Adam: but going back what the push now and that's really wanting to want to prove with that clip. The push is for truth, science is truth. That's the
push. And that's and let the scientists Lee we kind of heard that. But now he's this this guy. He's the Pied Piper. And he's supposed to say the
things everyone's going to repeat. And you'll hear well, as Dr. Bright said, you know, you're gonna hear that I
John: don't think so.
Adam: So we had the big Rona special on CNN with Anderson Cooper and Sanjay Gupta. And there she is the expert when it comes to science, all things
science, the ever so idealistic, gratitude, Mary,
John: can you talk about online to is just how important it is to listen to experts and listen to science. And this is a time when you know, I was not
a very good science student. When I was in school, oh, but this is a time it seems that the scientific community is so critically important. And we're
really seeing just how important it is to follow science.
Unknown: Yes, yes, exactly. And, and I hope
John: that she is, is she a PhD?
Adam: Oh, yes, listen to her message, she'll do 50 seconds of the same thing.
Unknown: We can see now that the scientific community are stepping up, and they are, they are speaking out more than they have done before.
Adam: But you know, I gotta tell you, for a 16 year old Swedish girl, that term stepping up, like the scientists are stepping up is an odd thing for
her to be using just in my opinion, you know, that? Our kids talk about that.
John: Oh, the Swedes, that's all they talk about stepping up?
Unknown: Yes, yes, exactly. And, and I hope that we can see now that the scientific community are stepping up, and they are, they are speaking up more
than they have done before. Because obviously, this is a crisis that would require the scientific community to speak up. And
and I hope that people really, it feels like science is getting there, the role of science is, is changing. Now it's becoming more people are starting
to realize that we are actually depending on science, and that we need to listen to scientists and experts and I, I really hope that we, that that
stays. And that's that also
is for other crises, such as the climate crisis and the environmental crisis that we understand that we have to listen to, to the scientists
John: saying that the climate folk are freaked out about this whole situation because they've been talking about being put on the back burner. They've
been taken off the stove.
Adam: Yeah, they're back in the pantry, where they belong. And I think so that's why it's important to have gretta back on the scene so she can
maintain her profile people forget pretty quickly,
John: but Okay, we have Anderson Cooper, like you said, the big three there was Anderson Cooper, who sounds legit. He says he was not he was a lousy
student, too. And he didn't get flunked science. So he's an idiot. And so then you get credit tuned. Barry who's who was a kid? She's just a kid.
Let's face reality. And then you have the MD a doctor.
Adam: Yeah, but Doogie Howser was only just to handle. Doogie Howser was only this as a kid as well. You know, it's like these kids can be very smart.
They can be geniuses. Remember who you talking to your average cnn viewer?
John: to CNN viewers, which is a small group of people, let's face it, yeah. So under a million, generally speaking, is we probably have a bigger
audience probably is the dumbest audience that watches television and thinks they're keeping up. Well, I guess you have to you have to imagine you
think you're keeping up because it's all about news, news, news, news. Oh, no. opinion, opinion,
Adam: opinion. The Central Intelligence Broadcast System, I think really did a good job in pitting the two main people that it's all about who's going
to lead us that's, that's what it's coming down to this week. I haven't seen the Sunday shows, but I'm sure it's part of it. Who is going to lead us
Trump the president or Fauci, the God,
Unknown: President Trump continues to push the country to quickly bounce back and says he does not consider that happening without reopening schools
claiming the virus has had very little impact on young people. But you're right, his own top health experts disagree.
Loki wants to play all sides of the equation,
President Trump pushed back against the warning Dr. Anthony Fauci delivered at a Senate hearing the day before,
there is a real risk that you will trigger an outbreak as you might not be able to control we don't know everything about this virus. And we really
better be very careful, particularly when it comes to children.
Adam: Just to interrupt. I'm a little tired of we don't know very much about this virus. Why not? I mean, if you've been studying this for 40 years,
it's similar to other SARS virus. I don't feel very comfortable hearing we don't know. We don't know, we don't know, but then telling me it's gonna be
the worst winter in history. This is a very contradictory, very
Unknown: careful, particularly when it comes to children
are surprised by the answer actually,
because,
you know,
it's just, to me, it's not an acceptable answer, especially when it comes to schools.
But a new CBS News poll finds that most Americans trust Dr. Fauci though his unfavorable rating among conservatives has increased since April,
the country needs guidance of the nation's best medical and scientific experts. These literally are matters of life and
death, as Democrats demand more guidance from the federal government. Today, the administration's former top vaccine researcher Rick bright, will
testify before House committee that if the response is not ramped up, 2020 will be the darkest winter in modern history.
Adam: I think CBS does a good job of wrapping up the messaging that they want. Trump bad Fauci good.
John: What exact same messaging that PBS is using, no is going to their they had Shields and Brooks on and they went on and on. And
Adam: let's hear it. Let's hear it. I want to hear it. I want to hear what you got.
John: Well, we got a few things here. I get the lot of stuff I'm biting. But if I know,
Adam: well, Biden will come let's finish up the Rona.
John: Let's do Shields and Brooks on PBS research notes.
Unknown: And it reveals that Joe Biden is a very transparent person, the culture they describe as certainly the culture I knew when I was covering
Senator Biden
John: go to go to shields on reopening she's battled PBS
Unknown: president and he said it again today. We need to move ahead. Whether we're reading or not on the, you know, in the direction of opening up,
the SEC did duty. The President proves once again. He's not actually strategic or tactical and his political fights that he engages in. He's visceral,
he's instinctive. He went out you should always if you're going after somebody politically stop, talk to somebody.
John: We're gonna have to start this over because you got to listen to what he did. She She says Trump wants to go ahead and reopen the country. And
he This is like this messaging that you just brought up on CBS and it's also being played out on PBS and elsewhere. It says though, the overlying
talking points the message or something else sneaks in as a as a given conversations that were shouldn't so she's asking them to the President wants
to reopen the country. And his response is, he doesn't know how to pick his battles. He's not strategic. Wait a minute. He wants to reopen the country
is not a battle who's at battle with who?
Adam: Well we know.
John: It's assumed They already know what the battle is about between Fauci and Trump because they want to lower Trump's numbers. Put somebody else
You know, they call the shots and help continue ruin the country. And so the world
Adam: not just the country, the world, the world, the world. Yeah.
John: World World Government will take care of that.
Adam: Although although every country has their own Fauci
John: Yes, every country has
Adam: their own Fauci Yeah, all connected over Fauci got pictures of Fauci on on the background on their desk, man, Fauci, his disciples, disciples,
the pope disciples.
John: So you have this replayed again, this
Adam: clip now that we have that you want to play
John: it over? Yeah, with it in mind that what she says and then what he jumps in with his discrepant
Unknown: president, and he said it again today, we need to move ahead, whether we're ready or not on the, you know, in the direction of opening up,
as he did duty. The President proves once again, he's not actually strategic or tactical and his political fights that he engages in. He's visceral,
he's instinctive to why you should always if you're going after somebody politically, go after somebody who's a lot weaker than you are politically or
less popular. I mean, Democrats won five consecutive presidential elections, running against Herbert Hoover, because they're the depression and
unpopular as a Republican president. But he picked Anthony Fauci, Dr. Fauci. David mentioned, it's been it's been there since the Reagan years. But
not only that, when in a presidential debate, when george HW Bush was asked to cite a contemporary American hero, he cited Dr. Anthony coachy.
Adam: Whoo, what a hero. Not anymore. My book. And I'll remember, the in order to get back to work, it really is about nine things
Unknown: Testing, testing, testing, tracing, tracing, tracing, isolation, isolation, isolation. So
Adam: we got a test here, we got a trace here, we got an isolate You and I have been identifying along with some of our no agenda lab personnel, that
the antibody tests are increasingly difficult to put together, the the material they're receiving from, I'm not sure where it comes from, I think some
of it, if not all, from China, seems to be faulty, not the same results. And this is the this is what the certainly the a lot of people want and feel
is necessary to go back to work as we have to test for the antibodies. And obviously the leading group on the test for antibodies is run by Who else
could it be? The Gates Foundation, it's not really run by them, but their major funder of this group and the FDA has stepped in the Food and Drug
Administration halted a Coronavirus testing program promoted by billionaire Bill Gates and Seattle health officials pending reviews. The program
sought to send test kits to the home of people both healthy and sick to try to bring the country to the level of testing officials say is necessary
before states can begin safely reopening. The program, which has already gone through 1000s of tests found dozens of cases that had previously been
undiagnosed. The Seattle Coronavirus assessment network said on its website that the FDA has asked it to pause testing while it receives additional
authorizations but maintained its procedures are safe, the story is so underplayed that you can't even get a clip you have to get a computer voice
reading the copy,
John: you know that somebody like computer voice sounds like another one of these online commentators bill still.
Adam: Oh, really, I had to put the cut it to put pauses in to make the transition natural. It's so bad. But that's how underreported This is nobody,
nobody wants to really let you know that it's failing. Meanwhile, without a doubt, science based science based New York has some great ideas for
getting back to work. And New York has problems but they do want people to at least go back and play some tennis
Unknown: every player unless they're from the same same household has
to bring their own tennis balls
so that you don't
touch other people's tennis balls.
With your hands,
you can kick their balls, but you can't touch them.
Adam: Okay is that
Unknown: you can't touch them.
John: It gets
Adam: it gets better because she recognizes what she's doing. And this is our humorous moment of the show
Unknown: with your hands. You can kick their balls,
but you can't touch them.
Of course if you're if you're playing with someone in your
household, you can catch those tennis balls.
confusion between balls, you can use a marker Sharpie
Adam: I give her a Hi Mark. For that, high marks I love it that everyone's cracking up. We just needed that moment of like, okay, okay, okay, it feels
so much better now.
John: Number The balls like,
Adam: she got a number and the ball boys, they can't be grabbing everybody's balls, they only can only get the balls on their side of the bed from
their team, you can only touch your team's balls. It goes on forever. Obviously, you can have a lot of fun with this. I have since it's also being
obfuscated. I have an update from a New York City nursing home, where a good half of all of New York City patients died. Would you like to hear this
from a dude named Ben who works in it?
John: from a lot of the Yeah,
Adam: yeah. So the what we've been discussing and what is death Mills? Yeah. What is on our radar? is the fact that the governor signed a number of
orders, which really put sick people back into the nursing homes without proper separation without not all of them but really unprepared and that
infected a lot of people and killed a lot of people. And he doesn't want to own up to it. I don't think he will. I think it I'm not blaming him
specifically shit happens in an emergency. This is not a good one. But, you know, I don't want to be talking about the hypocritical nature of it.
Obviously, we know if this was a republican who had done it, the media would have been talking about it. But even even Fox News isn't really talking
about this, no one wants to know. So here's our report boots on the ground dude named Ben. That's not really his name, but a dude named Benny works in
it for a large New York City nursing home. A few facts about how our Governor Cuomo has handled this vulnerable population. From the beginning, we
were told by the government and New York State Department of Health that we cannot test staff and residents, as there is not enough testing supplies
and hospitals are more important. That's Mistake number one. The only way we could test a patient was to transfer them to the hospital, then they were
tested. The only way we could test staff is to have them go to the private doctor, get them to call the state testing hotline and if symptomatic, get
an appointment for a testing center. Therefore, there was a very low death rate reported by nursing homes since they couldn't test and therefore could
not confirm the desperate COVID-19 related. Then Cuomo ordered all nursing homes to accept COVID-19 positive discharges, that's people from the
hospital. Most nursing homes are unprepared for this do not have sufficient PP or staffing nor the ability to isolate. We partnered at that time with
a large New York City Hospital system created a dedicated COVID-19 recovery unit and gladly accepted positive patients patients once we put in place
the appropriate infection control procedures and received sufficient PP from our hospital partner. Then Cuomo woke up and realized many nursing homes
were not equipped to handle COVID-19 positive patients and the death count went up and issued another executive order forbidding nursing homes from
accepting COVID-19 positive patients, they will surely backup hospitals and create an artificial surge then Cuomo mandated just crazy that all nursing
home patients and staff be tested. We had a team of 20 from the Department of Health here this week tested all residents and staff over four days, we
now have to put a plan in place by five by May 20th. How we're going to continue to test staff twice a week even though they're not enough testing
supplies, lab capacity, logistical ability, nurses and doctors to swab and costs of millions of dollars per month per facility will become a financial
hardship. If we don't have a plan, we risk losing our license and I really don't look forward to having my brain poked an additional two times per
week going forward. You too are so spot on and much of your analysis. Thank you for all you do to spread the truth analyze the tissue, stay safe keep
your six foot social distance figure out how to wear a mask during haircuts. Thank you. So again, Cuomo certainly but I think in general doesn't care
about the elderly doesn't care about old people cares about the hospital, and the money that they can make. I'm just gonna say that in the state and
getting a bailout he does not like did not care for the actual people who needed
John: No, he's about 20
Adam: Yes. And it's it's disturbing.
John: When you rise disturbing, and so far, it seems like worship along with Fauci by the democrats and especially the ones that kind of whoa bite and
put moves aside so Cuomo could take over you know, we've already shown on this show that that's not even a possibility because Colombo's commentary
where he says America has never been a great country, which is all you have to do. Just keep playing that audio forever and then he's never gonna vote
Yeah. the dumbest thing anyone could ever say, yeah. So as a politician, I mean, people can say it, right? But, but it's just politician
Adam: is so sad than you were arguing about the wrong things. No one. And the media, of course, has not been your friend for a long, long time. But
it's just gotten so bad. Very bad. I
John: have people who I get notes from is saying that the media, I mean, the media has been bad for a long time. And we've documented for the last 10
years. And then as we go back in history, and go back to the Gulf of Tonkin, and those other things that took place for me, it fell fell off the boat
decide. Me has never been any good.
Adam: Well, and it was it was interesting. I was talking to the keeper about the church commission. Because I think it always it always been like the,
you know, this indoctrination into the media. I said, Yeah, in 75. There was a big, a big hearing the church commission, and the CIA sat there said,
Yeah, yeah, we Yeah, we have people on staff or who, who send in stories to reporters in the printed press. And then the question came in. Well, do
you have anybody at major television news network? Well, that had to be discussed in private setting. And the same for anyone at the New York Times?
Well, we think we should discuss that in private setting. So yes, and if you think it went away, it did not.
John: Why would it
Adam: no good mechanisms works well for them. But unfortunately, we're a lot of recycling topic suffers a member the the Pennsylvania secretary of
health that we discussed and that you had questions about the Secretary's appearance.
John: And you're seeing the appearance of the of the health Secretary from Los Angeles.
Adam: Well, let's stick with Pennsylvania for a second.
John: Go on.
Adam: So you were your hunch was correct. We didn't know much about the psychology, transsexual woman that transexual Exactly. trans woman. Well, the
guy there's a guy. There was a guy who was not you, who pretty much pretty much got cancelled, because he too made fun of the health secretary of
Pennsylvania. And here's a little story about it. Robert
Unknown: Porter Gallo is the owners of peppers and at here in Braddock, super popular restaurant in our region. Porter Gallo is coming under fire for
recent Facebook comments that he posted on his personal page comments that some say are transphobic these are the Facebook posts that Robert Porter
Gallo shared on his page
Adam: now what's interesting is what you see is a picture of him with a wig on and looking like that. And then you see a picture of the the secretary
of health next to each other above that, which I think was funny. And the actual joke not this is not a trans joke was a picture of of Wayne from
Wayne's World with the stupid glasses looks exactly like the the secretary of health so I think he was he was saying oh, you look like Wayne from
birth.
Unknown: Yeah, tagging his restaurant peppers and in one of the posts portabello is wearing a wig glasses and pearls, appearing to mimic the look of
Pennsylvania secretary of health Dr. Rachel Levine
what an outrage
who is a transgender woman. Another post shows porticciolo appearing to impersonate Dr. Levine holding a news conference around rolls of toilet paper
with a caption. Now we know who hoarded all the toilet paper, while protocolo says his intent was to be funny. Members of the LGBTQ community aren't
laughing
Adam: and you should see this video is this spokesperson or I'm sorry member of the LGBT community is wearing a rainbow mask. Pink flags you know and
it's weird to hear this person see the person talking with the mask over their face. She's
Unknown: done nothing but be a wonderful compassionate leader in guiding the Commonwealth and making sure they stay safe. Christine Bryan is with the
Delta foundation of Pittsburgh whose mission is to fight for the LGBTQ community.
I know there's a lot of people that didn't realize that she was a member of the transgender community and truthfully, it doesn't matter. Yeah, she's
just like everybody else with an extensive resume. That is so impressive.
Adam: so impressive, but listen, shut up. That was not an LGBT joke. It was about Wayne's World and it was humor we can have humor use
John: humor and by the way it is a battle ax whether it's a transgender battle ax an old woman, or even an old man doesn't
Adam: matter but no let's let's immediately take it into all and by the way, it's okay to make fun of the president and his orange hair. Orange man
bad ads. Okay, but Oh no. Oh no. This immediately has to be taken into LGBTQ Shut up. So annoying.
John: Yes, the appearance, bigotry needs to be consistent
Adam: in, in text you can
John: mock the president for being orange, or a clown or whatever you want to call him. Let it be your open, open game is open. So you can go after
anybody
Adam: think. It think but no. See? Yes. So the final things I have is what's going on locally here in Texas. As you know, there's a lot of pushback
from people who want to open up. And you know, there's what we're seeing now across the country is some of the more rigorous mayors and or government
more mayors than anything but governors as well. They will take away your license so you can operate you know, doing anything to shame you or thwart
you from conducting your business legally, which, you know, it's legal as this is not a violation of law, it's a violation of some kind of social
standards that we're now tied into. So in Texas, we have the traveling economic malicious, and this is, this is new. These guys are going all over
Texas, and they are protecting businesses that want to open up and they stand in front with their rifles, and of course, all kinds of intimidating
looking gear and you know, what businesses are open and that I think is sad that it has to go that way.
John: I like it is great that he has to go that way. And really
Adam: and you know, I would participate in in that if someone was having problems I'll jump right in Stan and no one's gonna This is why we have guns
when this type of situation appears. Let's look at a country that just took away their guns in New Zealand and let's see what kind of powers they've
given to their prime minister.
Unknown: This bill enables the police to enter a home without a warrant. Madam Speaker, the police have never held that power at all. They have never
held that power. And this bill this bill enables police just on reasonable cause to enter in to your home
Adam: suite.
John: It just like the good old king King George the Third they used to put in the house too That's why they put it in the Bill of Rights when we told
him to Sod off
Adam: Yeah, good times over there.
John: Yeah, Brazil, New Zealand so I want to play the one I mean, I do have said I have around the world tour which has got some good stuff but I had
to get this out of the way before we go to the break which is something that doesn't get a lot of play I looked into it seems to be true it's history
accurate report it's not a joke. It's not that disaccharide to be whatever that that thing is the new onion. The sour lab report,
Adam: what is it the B the be the Babylon be the Babylon Babylon be
Unknown: the P sorry,
John: what sorry.
Unknown: The P for lab at the Wu Han Institute of virology has come under scrutiny as a potential source of the virus. According to an NBC report, a
hazardous event may have happened at the lab in October last year. Three people familiar with the matter told NBC that US intelligence agencies are
reviewing an unofficial report on cell phone location data. The report found there was no cell phone activity around the high security part of the P
four lab between October 7 and 24th last year. The report suggests there may have been a hazardous event. There's some time between October 6 and
11th. That required the lab to be closed during that time. The report talks about images from October 14 to 19th last year, showing no outbound
traffic from the lab. It's suspected a roadblock was set up to prevent cars and people coming and going. This is in contrast to satellite images from
August to October 6, which show a lot of activity. The next instance of activity was on October 25. US Senator Tom Cotton also spoke about the data
and an interview with Fox News. Cotton said normally 1000s of mobile phones are in use around this area. Well, Han has about the same population
density as New York. He has the sudden drop in cell phone usage is likely an indicator of when the virus first began spreading. He said we could get
to the bottom of it a lot faster if the Chinese regime was more transparent. US intelligence officials say the evidence is not enough on its own. They
are still investigating.
Adam: So where does this report come from?
John: This came from a news operation called NTD which is Chinese operation, an entity sensor new Tang Dynasty and it turns out that these are the
same group that comes out of the like The epoch the Epoch Times.
Adam: Right? Right, right, right. Right. Right.
John: Right. we're gone. We Yeah,
Adam: that's uh, they're they they hate to the Chinese, obviously, they
John: hate the giant was following Gong and it's Falun Gong are banned in China. And it was. And I will be writing an essay about this because the
Falun Gong phenomenon is quite interesting. This operation only began in the 90s. There was a moment there was a moment in history where this there's
all these different movement practices in China. And Qi Gong was one of them, it goes back, I think, three or 3000 years at least. And it became for
some unknown reason, a super popular again, it began, his popularity began in the 50s. And then it gets incredibly popular in the 90s. And it's like
Tai Chi Chi Gong, there's a bunch of these are all interconnected Gong also, this is like Kung Fu, all these different movement. ideologies are part
of Chinese culture and, and in the mid 90s, this Qi Gong is extremely popular. And they and an offshoot called follow on Gong came up, and became so
popular so quickly, that it garnered like 70 million followers within a couple of years. And by the end of the same decade, it was banned in China
because it was seen as dangerous. Yeah. And then Ever since then, has been this, this blood feud between these, these people in the Chinese Communist
Party?
Adam: I'm glad you, you went into that. And, and whenever I see, you know, the Epoch Times I bear that in mind, they have an agenda. But I think a lot
of people don't even know this don't even know that. It's Epoch Times. And what else? What's the other online thing? Oh,
John: this one here is NTD. The new service there's also something else called Happy morning or something that happened is MTD stands for new Tang
Dynasty. Oh, and the Tang Dynasty is interesting because that's the one that took place between about 609 100 very early and early in modern Chinese
history. And that there was a 300 year reign with a with a hole in the middle of it. Where the evil Emperor is Whoo.
Adam: Oh rule
John: that little era was the only full Empress in the history of China that actually had total complete power that wasn't she was evil. He was a
whore apparently was somehow gotten to government and which does happen now was that before before the Wu Tang
Adam: clan or a
John: little bit before just before the Wu Tang clan All right. No Chinese just
Adam: a little bit of history for everybody and stuff.
John: This stuff has its implications in this these these fallen gun guys have got some very serious this good journalism they've been producing. To
be honest about it. I mean, I know it's slanted to but it's pretty well done. Well, all news is slanted, but you still have to pick out what you can
as long as you know, this story about the lab getting shut down, which has been debunked core lab having something to do with it is not being played
by anybody. And it apparently NBC did have the story, but they kind of got
Adam: caught. Mm hmm. So what is your takeaway with that then?
John: The virus came from the Chinese lab, I think just like the French guy, the French Nobel Prize winner in medicine who discovered the AIDS virus
is the guy who is I think is right and they all call everyone calls him a crackpot. And now
Adam: Yes, now they do.
John: It's like a Nobel Prize. He's got his his chops. And you know, yet he's a crackpot. This
Adam: is happening. Yeah, this is happening everywhere. In the Netherlands. There's a very famous statistician and pollster. His name is Maurice de
Holmes. And that translates interestingly, to Maurice the dog. That is, that is literally his name. And Maurice, he's probably he's got 10 years on
me. I've, I've worked with him in the past, but he's very famous. He's the guy that whenever there's elections, He's everywhere on television. He
tells you shows everybody the charts, the numbers, he's got it all down. He's very good at understanding data. And he's been doing it since I was a
child almost in the country watching him. He has been shut out entirely banned from all mainstream, and he's now appearing on podcasts. And I'm
actually considering because he speaks perfect English. I'm considering doing an interview with him because it's easy to get right now. And and it's
because he said, Look, the way you're collecting the data is shoddy. You have completely incorrect data. The numbers are no good. Your models no good
good by Maurice the dog. So it happens. It's happening everywhere. Francis got that crackpot get rid of him. Maurice de Haan, I think his career is
over. Not that he you know, he has I'm sure he's plenty of money. But it's it's odd to see. The guy that I grew up watching is the authority on data
and statistics and numbers to be completely shut out. Because he had a different opinion canceled my man is canceled
John: now before started off as a podcaster you don't have this problem that's right.
Adam: Before we take a break we do have very important public service announcement that is something I'd like you all to listen to very carefully.
Unknown: In the morning no agenda producers when writing the no agenda show we know you all want to refer to your significant others as smoking hot.
When everyone uses the same term to describe their lover it can get quite repetitive so when writing the no agenda show please consider using an
alternative term such as alluring angelic arm candy attractive arousing banging beautiful bit of crumpet bombshell bomb diggity breezy cutie cutie
cutie pie cookie cupcake charming Chiquita Banana, dazzling dime piece delicious delphis dreamboat Enchantress, Foxy glamorous gorgeous good looking
head turning how to eat hot sexy mama knockout lovely magnificent perfect 10 ravishing sent you a sexy sex kitten or crafty Cougar smashing stunning
sensational Stone Cold Foxy titillating tremendous Twinkie licious vivacious yummy are simply wonderful. The no agenda show appreciate your
cooperation and compliance through these difficult times if your significant other doesn't like the description you use Be sure to tell them to relax
while you hit them in the mouth.
Adam: And with that I'd like to thank you for your courage say in the morning to you the man who put the CD in crafty Cougar john
John: Are you Mr. Adam Curry also in the morning all ships and sea boots on the ground feet in the air subs in the water and all the dames and knights
out there by the way was that Darren O'Neal
Adam: the one and only
John: recognize his voice I just as I was listening to that
Adam: yeah
John: I've just a message to Darren the logo though. He is the director yes feedback is he is one inch away from be able to do a perfect rush
limbaugh.
Adam: Well, I hear the slots opening up soon.
John: Haha. Whoa.
Adam: Sorry, bad DJ joke is what it does. Yeah, Darren is it well, he gets enough practice
John: to do a limbo. He just needs to drop it down a little bit slow down. I mean, I know exactly what would me he's he's already got the tones. He's
got the tonal qualities he just needed.
Adam: And he has to say stuff like ditto heads. If he does that megadose I don't even do that anymore. But yeah, Darren O'Neill thank you very much
and I have to say in the morning to our trolls there in the in the troll room. There's over 1900 of them did a quick troll counter. Thank you all for
showing up and for showing your enthusiasm and helping and weighing in with your comments which are often not suitable for air but we do appreciate it
no agenda stream.com is where all of that partying takes place we do the show live on Thursdays and Sundays the Welcome to go in there listen live
troll around chat around there are people who stay logged in for months on end never leave it's just part of their life. Has it No. Oh yeah, no agenda
stream.com and also when you're there hit someone up for an invite for no agenda social.com It is our little note on the Federated social network The
Future of Social networking and where they're nice and early and getting on the ground floor Just follow me Adam at no agenda social calm and john
cedars. Is it John Dvorak? It no agenda social calm that you're thanks. I think so.
John: I think I don't know.
Adam: You do log in from time to time?
John: I don't know because you know,
Adam: you just logged in I understand. Exactly. Then I'd like to say in the morning to the artists who brought us the artwork for episode number where
we 1242 Let me bring up our little show notes page here this art while the title of the show was smokin hot. This art done by Nick the rat really
moved move people's emotions. And when art does that it's genius. He had the handcuffs, the two arms with the handcuffs and the mask in the middle of
the handcuffs as if you're being shackled by the mask. It was a dynamite piece there was no question I think that this and people responded to it.
John: It was an excellent piece of symbolic art
Adam: and we had there was a lot of pieces a lot yeah
John: we a lot of pieces for some reason, like a lot
Adam: and and i would say a special commendation to Comic Strip blogger who did his rendition of the National Black journalists Association. If you
recall, it's the he
John: thought Yes Yeah.
Unknown: If you want to see it go look at it. He does
John: these every once
Adam: well I appreciate he did it because he knew that no way of getting this art picked. But uh man, it certainly gave me joy so thank you for that
CSB but above all Thank you Nick the rat when Nick comes in and does it he does it right. No agenda Art generator.com please go have a look at all of
the fantastic different submissions and if you want to you can join into it's tough because these artists have stuff done by the end of the show we
pick the art probably about 15 minutes after we're done after you know the cleaning up the opening and the closing of the show and doing the credits
we're right into that so it's an amazing thing that they do and fantastic value for the show is one of the few podcasts anywhere in the world that has
fresh album art for every episode no agenda generator comm Thank you. No agenda art generator, calm. Thank you, Nick.
John: You might have to put the time code down for that. Got it? We do have a few people think for sure. 1243. And I'm gonna have you read because you
read part of this note already. And you know where you read where you didn't read yet. And this is from sir mark and de master Duke and Duchess of
Japan and all the disputed islands of the Japanese sea. And they came up with two and $33.33 and with a whole bunch of nice pictures of themselves,
their staff. They are wearing masks and bragging about
Adam: Yes, dear john, Adam, thank you for your courage. The last few months of your virus deconstruction has been the best. I want to give you an
update from the frontline here in Japan, we have dodged the bullet so far have only 739 deaths for a population of over 126 million. That's 5.8 deaths
per million compared that to the US with 267 deaths per million. Of course, that includes people who drink themselves to death in the UK with 511
deaths per million, which is definitely people who drink themselves to death. Japan is an incredible 100 times less than the UK. We had that I'm
curious. They must be I bet you the Japanese are accurate with their diagnosis of death, the cause of death. What do you think?
John: I would agree with I have a feeling that the Japanese are known for precision. Yeah,
Adam: yeah. And everything we're not know apparently, everything has to have a stamp of approval. So
John: Rolex is such a good car, the ones made in Japan.
Adam: Is it is that why the Lexus is such a good car?
John: It's one of the reasons.
Adam: Okay, now, back to masks. And he says we've been doing it right. Yeah, masks work. The whole country wears them for flu season every year,
especially in the most crowded mass transit system in the world. You wear them so you don't give your code to others. And people have been doing this
for years and it's no big deal, no stigma attached. It's also meant that we had Oh, it's also important that we had more stock Yes, several billions
of them there was just enough to go around. Mass usage went up with COVID but it also meant that it was the weakest flu season over 10 years and we
went through the hotels that he spoke about contact tracing is big here not electronic just lots of legwork. All the resources have been put on that
and on put on that and on phones in mass transit on I'm sorry. And on tracking COVID clusters we might have been lucky getting a weaker strain but it
helps not having to shake hands just bow no Huggy kissy Greetings, no talking on phones and mass transit, hand sanitizers almost everywhere high
adoption of touchless electronic payment systems as well as burner cards. Finally, the healthcare system it has a low barrier to entry my kids can go
to the local doctor themselves, just take their national health card mom might rock up later very much neighborhood policing system. But yes, it's a
very sophisticated, disciplined society. Which has a lot of downsides to the kids get a feeling for what's going on. it's by no means perfect that
prevention testing majors can be seen as flawed. The reporting flaw Japan is flawed, but all the micro actions combined make it a rather safe place to
be right now. There's a lot to be learned from this fuzzy logic and staying calm sir mark, and de master Duke and Duchess of Japan and all the
disputed islands in the Japan sea. Thank you so much for your courage and I can't wait to see you guys in Japan hope to go this year.
John: Hope to go any flights. Yeah. Delicious Fred Lybrand in medfield Massachusetts $333 the direction of Adam I've sent it 333 to produce the next
episode. My last donation was Episode 12 to two to add deducing and sprinkling of job karma would be appreciated Emma de-douche
Unknown: been de deuced
John: my son Flyknit Junior flying not Junior.
Adam: Yeah, I've seen him around.
John: I have May 25 birthdays The other one is E days. On the birthday list you might want to check out here's an update on what's going on with the
medical PP its ties to some of the cayley Mac net net mcenany quotes that are making the rounds. One of my manufacturing sites produces layers used in
in 95, surgical masks. Here's a part of what I think has been going on with the lockdown and how PP played a role. One a one. As the COVID hit to us,
we started summarizing more clearly what we knew about the industry. We guessed that the US would make about 6 million in 95 minutes per day. And the
government was supposed to have a stockpile of 90 million based on 2000 on a 2004 paper. But when created, there was never more than 85 million at the
start of the wrona it had about 12 million as an example California his first request was for 20 million. In late February, HHS said 90 million was
wrong. The correct number should have been at 330,000,007 days later HHS has the right number was really 3.5 billion. As we've dealt with the military
via the defense production act, my guess is that the military and the rest of the US government did the same math and realize that the whole situation
was hopelessly out of whack. Wait, we can make how many masks? That's not enough. At this point, the nature with the nature of the disease being very
unclear. The best option was to simply shut things down and give the supply chain time to get caught up. mass and PP will be part of the national the
meanwhile you can impeach Trump over this of course. Of course NPP will be part of national defense strategy going forward is hoping that the rumored
bill that is a version of the berry amendment for medical supplies is passed soon. The berry amendment is the legislation that requires the military
to buy certain items from producers in the continental US. Kaylee makhdum, in ne ne mcenaney had a great quote in a recent briefing. Furthermore, what
krimson contagion brought us in that President Trump was right all along about misguided economic and trade policies that left America vulnerable to
pandemics.
Adam: Well not too vulnerable to pandemic but vulnerable due to a pandemic.
John: Yes, yes.
Adam: Yes, but I totally get it. So you Fred and Jr. are on the list. Thank you very much. You see, he seems to have a thing for Kaylee McInerney.
Yeah, I think that's the first time she's ever been mentioned in a donation segment. The
John: first two times, maybe one donates again, you can assume it's gonna happen one more time.
Adam: Here's your jobs, karma. Fred jobs,
Unknown: jobs, jobs and jobs.
Let's vote for jobs.
You've got karma,
Adam: man. Thank you for the support.
John: What's your read this one? Well, I look for the one after that.
Adam: Yeah. This is from producer Jacob 333. And he says is Jacob your favorite lobbyist? Yes. This is one of our lobbyists, producers. And Amy
wrongfully said it would be probably one of your clips that quote corporate lobbying firms are being Oh, that's right. We talked about the corporate
lobbying firms being bailed out. She's wrong. There's no bailout provision for lobbyists. I think we explain that but he says people should not
misinterpret what that means. lobbying firms, including our own are making all time high profits thanks to the abundance of new bailout slash
appropriation appropriations bills. The biggest problem of this The biggest problem will be a lack of lobbyists next year because so many will retire
following this year of record profits. The stage II believe that shit the stage four and stage five stage five stimulus packages are coming stage five
he's talking about are coming next and will likely include up to $5 trillion of new spending this is coming from the one of the money guys in DC so
you can take that as some version of future future prediction. Send some of the rock record profits to your way. No agenda producers who need help of
an evil corporate lobbyists can reach us in case you need an evil corporate lobbyists, you can reach the official no agenda lobbyists firm at lobby
me@protonmail.com Jacob thank you very much for your courage and it's appreciated, especially the knowledge of the stage five is coming up to $5
trillion. Whoo. Everybody, everybody knows about money party man party. Well, at least he's sharing it with us. That's good news.
John: Associate executive producer. The first one is Ernest celmins. I can't find any note from him. He said $289.56 he is in he Is that Estonia or
Adam: Estonia? Yeah, that's Estonia
John: is in Estonia. Oh, yeah. Tallinn
Adam: allow me to use my nifty new search bar in Microsoft out. No, I don't have it either. Let me see search show.
John: The Joanne Brady's Next on the list at $220.22 by the way, aren't as if you got something that you want us to say we'll send it along. In 22 in
Phoenix, Arizona, please accept Corona cash, the best podcast ever. Thanks. Also call out my brother Michael Brady for being a douchebag
Adam: Okay, Dame
John: Jennifer artists appears to be a service I'm going to get that straight Dame Jennifer's Next on the list of 200 bucks. Here's to your share of
the very generous contributions we received recently regarding animated no agenda. I still have major Rona brain, but I am so thankful I stumbled onto
nogen almost 10 years ago. A big Nettie is, as bugged Nettie as I am lately. I shudder to think how much crazier I would be without So in other words,
she's one of the nervous wrecks. I'd shudder to think how much crazier I'd be without your show and the wonderful producers I've met along the way. No
jingle is just good. You definitely use a huge jobs Carmen, maybe the Trump Pelosi combo to shake things up. She puts that as a question mark. And
Mike, my answer to that is no. Why
Adam: don't listen, I don't know. Don't take the way you
John: don't want to shake things up with experimental sketchy x jingles. You know, x is in like an experimental vehicle. The Rona has not been kind to
the bottom line. Please also sprinkle it out to the producers who are having trouble these days. PS The 17th is my actual birthday. And I feel so
lucky that this is also a show day. Well, that sounds like she should be on the birthday list. He
Adam: is on the birthday list. Actually.
John: That's funny. Show day. Thank you all for your courage and support. Our tribe is amazing. Good old, dangerous
Adam: and dangerous. Jennifer Of course just did another fabulous episode of animated no agenda, which was the helicopter, helicopter money. People
don't understand us. They think that we really don't understand the concept of helicopter money. But interestingly, it's not it's heli payments is a
whole different deal. heli payments in Ireland is not the same as helicopter payments that come from the Federal Reserve. I thought it was Did you see
it? Do you see the I had not
John: I didn't know it came out.
Adam: Oh my god, it's your bit.
John: I'll check it out. For sure. It's
Adam: very funny. Very, very fun love
John: seeing my own bits.
Adam: Your bid is your bits of the best you should put them using marker to make sure that no one takes your bit. Thank you damn, Jennifer. And here
we go with the only jobs karma that makes a difference. jobs, jobs, jobs and jobs.
Unknown: Let's vote for job.
Karma today.
John: on the list, Forrest Martin 200 bucks Parts Unknown.
Adam: He should be on the birthday list. And let me see if he is I thought I saw him there earlier. It could be wrong.
John: Just making my yearly birthday donation, he writes, and congratulations Adam and the keeper on their anniversary.
Adam: Now he remembered it's the 19th. So that's two days away. Thank you, Forrest.
John: Also thanking you both gentlemen, for everything you do, keeping people informed and entertained, I would like to get an official deducing
reduced as it got lost in the shuffle last year. And since my job situation has improved, since I was first able to donate a year ago at jobs, karma
for everybody who needs it.
Unknown: jobs, jobs, jobs and jobs. That's the job.
Karma.
John: Man, that's our list of associate executive producers and executive producers for show at 1243. Back to our normal amounts. I think everyone's
over COVID I guess I don't know.
Adam: Well, what I appreciate the most of of the shows you've done in the past couple months is people feeding back just like Dame Jennifer said, no
matter what it is. People seem to find some comfort in listening to us and and i'm, i'm proud and happy about that. But I want to thank everybody
because it's really it's the producers. Long ago, we noticed that it's better to have producers than listeners, because they actually do stuff and
produce and make things happen. There's no way this show would be what it is without you Without the people who support us financially the clips.
Thank you extra thanks to so many producers who are sending if you send a YouTube video pre queued with the timecode it's saved. So much time, thank
you listings of time codes pre clip, it's incredibly appreciated. Because that's what it is. And that's why we're the best podcast and universe End of
story. These people, of course, are executive producers and associate executive producers, and they can use these credits wherever they want to,
because they're official. And when people see a credit, they recognize it, it gives you stature, and maybe a gig, which is what a lot of people are
going to be looking for soon, if not already. Thank you again, for all of your courage. Remember, we do have another show coming up on Thursday. And
to support us for that go to John dvorak.org.
Unknown: Slash and
Adam: a lots of mouth hidden going on. Good to see it. We're happy to have you aboard.
Unknown: Our formula is this. We go out or hit people in the mouth.
Adam: The kid was blowing up on me. Sorry about that.
John: So over the last few days, Biden had this event. And
Adam: I even I have Biden clips today.
John: Well, Biden had this horrible advantage of gifts. Oh, I don't even know. I mean, you have let's look, let's look at some things objectively. You
have NBC MSNBC, is owned by Comcast. And their big promoters are big haters of Trump. What does it take for Biden's techies to go and get a hold of
Comcast to say, hey, look, we're gonna do a bunch of these events down out of Biden's basement. What is the chance of getting some real high speed?
Just kick ass connections? You guys can help us. We consider it a contribution from the life of campaign contribution, whatever you want to want it to
be called. But we do need some help here. Can you give us your best guys and get us some? Just no.
Adam: Thumbs up? Cool Who said that? This wasn't their best guys. It's Comcast. Have you tried Comcast connection?
John: Come on you we know they can do better than this. I mean, it's funny, it's funny line. But the fact is that this is this is this one was so bad.
It was almost like watching that movie. You know, they're they're here or whatever this color where you put the glasses on, you see? Oh, monsters?
Unknown: Yes.
John: Yeah. And so every time Biden move, you know, his head stayed there and one side and it became a skeleton head. And there was no, it was the
worst. Yeah. But before we play that I do have this one a clip I want to get out of the way, which is Biden. And apparently he was on. They were
talking about him. Scarborough and what's her name? Mika. Mika Brazil, discussing Biden's commentary when he was on GMA, and I'm gonna play this clip,
because the combination of Biden telling why he's heightened Biden's height and he's in his basement scared to death. And the two of them are going on
and on about how great it is because he's a winner.
Unknown: Now, and everybody says, you know, Biden's hiding? Well, let me tell you something. We're doing very well. We're we're following the
guidelines of the medical profession. We're following the guidelines of the experts, Dr. Fauci of the world. We're doing very well. And Matter of
fact, we're winning. If you look at the polling data, I'm not saying that's going to last till November. I don't know enough to know that. But right
now, the idea that somehow we are being hurt by my keeping to the rules, and following the instructions that are that have been put forward by the
docks is absolutely bizarre. I reject the premise that somehow this is hurting us. There's no evidence of that. I'm following the rules. following the
rules, the president should follow the rules instead of showing up a place without masking the whole the whole thing. I'm sorry, it's just such like
he wins that. Yeah. Every time. He wins that checkmate. Every time. Yeah, you know, really,
I i understand
the president and people, some people inside the White House, most of them understand they're Whistling past a political graveyard. But, you know,
Donald Trump snapping doctor's
advice. There is a
pandemic that's killed Now, over 80,000 people, we have new estimates, it's going to kill 140,000 150,000 people after Donald Trump. doctor's advice
early on and said this was nothing to worry about. He loses to a dude who says hey, I'm gonna follow the doctor's advice, because guess why? Most
Americans are following their doctor's advice to the doctor. So, I mean, Joe Biden's right
Adam: The burzynski child, and the douche knuckle tease
Unknown: me. Oh, god, it's gonna
Adam: come in close to banning them.
John: Yeah, yeah, you can't resist.
Adam: It's the Mika Brzezinski child. She's pretty fun.
John: Which brings me to just a little break in the show here. Yeah, I have my list of ISOs which includes the top one. Checkmate. Oh,
Adam: hold on a second man, I got it here. I got it here the ISO Yes.
Unknown: Yeah, check me
Adam: I have one I'd like to try on you. Okay, okay, try this one.
John: So I'm walking around with the Coronavirus. I'm asymptomatic I got it.
Adam: You got the Rona? Is that what's going on here? I didn't know you had the
John: Coronavirus strike this one let's try this one. Try it. This isn't a geese.
Unknown: Okay,
that's the geese here in the background.
Adam: Okay,
John: that was Biden. Okay, let's go this one another Biden is following rules.
Adam: following rules. Where are we? Got it.
Unknown: I'm following the rules.
Adam: No, I'm sorry. It just none of it competes with
Unknown: kick their balls.
Um,
John: if that wasn't so echoey
Adam: o so now we have to go to rule follower.
John: Well, let's No no. Let's go to another one. Try this one pandemic. Okay.
Unknown: We're, we're, we're. We're in the middle of a pandemic. Yeah,
Adam: that's the one. That's That's the one. That's done. I like it. That's a good one.
John: I got one last one.
Adam: No, you have more. But wait, there's more. Okay.
John: put up or shut up.
Unknown: Shut up. Shut up.
Adam: Now. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Yeah, I think you nailed it with where
Unknown: we're where it says we're in the middle of a pandemic that
Adam: it's, it's so it's so perfect for before you do more Joe clips. May I take you back in time for a moment? Sure. Let's get in the time machine
for a second. Let's
Unknown: go back
Adam: to may 20. of 2013. Episode 512. So this is quite a while ago of the no agenda show. This is what happened.
John: That's not gonna happen as I said the dream. I think it's called a hallucination.
Adam: I had a had a real dream last night. I woke up from this. Put this in the red book just for just for yucks. All right. I and it was vivid. Okay,
it was vivid. And maybe because we've played a couple of clips of him recently I've been watching video of him. Are you ready for this? Joe Biden was
president I am from the future ladies and gentlemen. I am from the future. It's in the red book I think you should be able to find that will be a
disaster.
John: All right. So we have blind give me as little event I got I got some miscellaneous clips and then some some research on him. Okay. Let's go with
the bind event clips I got I got three of them. I got anyone you want to pick and play the short little one, which I think is similar to the pandemic.
One is Biden's event with the guvs blather
Unknown: exists because you know, a few nations that every major crisis we faced in our history has been in a situation where we have come out
stronger, come out stronger. And what I'm finding and maybe we can go back to this later, but I'm finding that you know, this whole crisis sort of
taking the blinders off. Most people you know, the people who weren't,
Adam: I think geese in the background.
Unknown: Yes. necessarily prejudice but just in focus. That's the geese you hear in the background.
Most Canadian geese are are trying to get away from the virus anyway. Okay, this is what happens is that what I'm finding people who are constantly
calling me and I know, we're all in place, but we have on the phone probably six hours a day, or people are talking about how they didn't realize that
it was somebody making, you know, seven bucks an hour's making had their back. You know,
Adam: by the time he got to the end, I had no idea what he was talking about.
John: Exactly. Exactly. That was the point of that clip there. Well, it worked. And there's a little sub clip here. This is byte and event with the
guvs blather one wha Ah, oh yeah,
Adam: I got it.
Unknown: We got a lot of ground to cover. So let's Start with this. No. Oh, that Iris can hit anyone. But it doesn't affect every community to say,
Adam: oh shoot. Oh no, I just connected my head you know I got a real problem with these headphones and I'm not going to hear you for at least seven
seconds so you can fill up the void while I'm well
John: that was that was a classic example of both how stupid This event was. This is widened into three governors. But the lousy connection none of
them could none of them in fact all three plus byte and couldn't talk for at all. Sorry, we're all
Adam: like you said Iris. Now I got one clip of Joe with the number mix up. Do you have that one?
John: Nobody had this last one from this series. Okay. And this is says bite an event with guvs blather and it has no other moniker on there.
Adam: Okay
Unknown: exists because you know a few nations that Evernote
Adam: right that's the one we played. We played it first.
John: Now the one you played first should have been guvs. Blathers, zero, z w
Adam: e. Oh, no, we
John: didn't play the one it says 00. Okay,
Adam: yes, I have it here. We desperately need your we did not play zero. We played
John: a zero pleasure. Yep,
Unknown: desperately need your copies going? And this is
Adam: what would help if it didn't cesario if
John: you can I recommend this correct.
Adam: I thought it might have been like I have to
John: humiliate me in public. I know how to spell
Adam: unless humiliating. I'm telling you that I if I want to get you this easy, I was saying I thought I thought it might be a CEO clip or something.
John: It's fine. Believe me, you could take these Joe Biden clips out of order it doesn't matter. Does not matter desperately
Unknown: need your company's going. And this is not a moment for excuses or deflections or blame game where we're we're, we're in the middle of a
pandemic that has cost us more than 85,000 jobs as of today. lives of millions of people.
millions of jobs.
Adam: That's the one I mean, I know that everybody shakes their head and says,
Unknown: Joe is gonna win the race. You know, and we're in a position where, you know, we just got new unemployment insurance this morning, numbers
36 5 million claims since this crisis.
And almost 3 million new claims in the last week, the unemployment rate is nearing 15%, the highest it's been since the Great Depression. But I did
not tell you all that. Of course, if it's the least well off or be hit the hardest 40% of the households making $40,000 or less, experienced a job
loss just in March. And we're going to have to work harder and smarter than ever before to pull ourselves out of this economic tailspin.
Adam: And this is the problem with with Joe is that when he gets a sentence out, it's really nothing there's just nothing in it. We're gonna have to
work hard pull together. He doesn't really have any I've not I think I've not heard one single policy oriented solution even for African Americans, he
came out with the big the big joe biden's Black Agenda, which was you know, that I think is called lift of what we will lift all voices, which is not
pandering at all, to the religious black Americans. Any and what he says in there, oh, we're gonna we're gonna do a study and do a study to see if we
should do some reparations. I mean, this is the kind of crap that is not going to fly. But I know what sorry.
John: Does this makes this so the clip?
Adam: Oh, yeah, there's another 40 seconds and seven, seven seconds to go.
John: I'm sorry. It seems like it seems like weeks go by.
Unknown: All of you know,
Adam: I'm having my second anniversary has already taken place. This clip is so long,
Unknown: only way out of this is by following the science, listening to the experts talking and taking responsible precautions, that they're gonna
help us reopen the economy as a fleet as quickly as possible. And as we do, there's got to be federal support to state and local levels of our
government in my view, so that we be able to come out of this crisis stronger and more united. We have an opportunity, in my view, to transform the
economy as we come up to build a more inclusive and more resilient middle class. And I think that can withstand the next next public crisis, whatever
it is, however it comes about, not just reward the people who are well off and well connected. It's time for us to ensure everyone gets a fair shot
success in this country. Science I don't believe in science.
John: One last clip, I want to get to get this series completely out of the way. They talked about this on PBS. Little bit. And, Judy, this is the
Judy smear. She does just smear that she slipped into this little announcement discussing the Biden event.
Unknown: In the day as other news, former Vice President Joe Biden says that if elected president he would not pardon Donald Trump or his associates
of any crimes. Instead, he says he would let any investigations play out. The presumptive Democratic nominee spoke in a virtual Town Hall on msnbc
last night, and he accused Mr. Trump of abusing his power.
We never saw anything like the prostitution of that office like we see it today. It is not something the President is entitled to do to direct either
a prosecution and or decide to drop a case. That is not the President's role or responsibility. And it's a dereliction of his duty.
Adam: What is he? Is he talking about Flynn? Is that what he's what he's saying?
John: Yeah, I think it's about Flynn. Well, I have the clip that where he is easy enough to is up to his eyeballs in this Flynn thing. Yeah. By the
way, this was a smear when Judy says that he's not going to pardoned Trump that it the way it was presented was as though Trump had had created a
actual crime.
Adam: Well, let's go to the crime. Let's go to the town hall. And let's see how this came about. The Judy did not play the source material because it
was a request from an audience member here it is,
Unknown: would you be willing to commit to not pulling a President Ford can give him Donald Trump
John: a pardon under the pretense of healing the
Unknown: nation? In other words, are you willing to commit to the American ideal that no one is above the law? Absolutely, yes. I commit.
Adam: I know it was a spiked call or whatever. But like commit these commitments, please, look, but this but this town hall was very interesting for
another reason, all of a sudden, and this was a Joe Biden special event, the msnbc I think it was Lawrence, what's his name? No. lawrence o'donnell.
So he's hosting it. And all of a sudden, we've got Lawrence in the middle Joe on the right, and Stacey Abrams pops up on the left hand box and
hilarity ensued, as we watch Stacey Abrams slowly lose her soul on live TV.
Unknown: So I want to begin this with a question to Joe Biden, because Stacey Abrams is here because Joe Biden invited Stacey Abrams to be here. And
so was Vice President, do you have an announcement to make? Is this an audition is there? What is the reason that you decided it's time for me to get
John: what would you say stop the hammering?
Unknown: Get on TV with Stacey Abrams? Well, because Stacey Abrams has done more to deal with a fair vote and making sure there is a fair vote in
anybody. And she, she has a great, great capacity to explain things.
Adam: Mind you, she's sitting here right now saying nothing looking in the camera in her own box on the left, the smile started to slowly fade, and to
lay out exactly why it's going to be so critically important in this election.
Unknown: This president's already said when the put in was stimulus package, the Congress first passed the money to provide for mail in ballots. He
already said, I'm not for that. If we do that. Will no no republican ever win or something to that effect? He's made it clear. This is the guy who
said he wants to defund the post office from being able to deliver balanced I mean, so Stacy knows what she's doing. And she's incredibly capable
person.
Adam: So since then, that said nothing. He sent her up if you want to make an announcement, he of course everyone's think, oh, my goodness is going to
be the VP announcement. Nothing.
John: No, it's embarrassing. Just think. And by the way, when did Trump say he wanted to defund the post office because so they wouldn't deliver a
batch.
Adam: I love that too. I thought it was that was a nice time
John: she say that? I
Adam: don't I don't think I don't I don't think he ever said that. That was Jo someone told Jay just make make it up.
John: So I did see part of this. I didn't take any clips from it, but it's pathetic. Casey Abrams is really a dud. I just don't understand what why he
was so jacked up about it. And I will say it again. I'm gonna remind everybody my thinking on this, having been a Democrat. There's not a woman in the
democrat party that will have Stacey Abrams as president until a white woman is President first.
Adam: If I may we this was a big topic on more facts. And, and we discussed the VP slot specifically from an A das perspective. And Stacey Abrams is
not wanted is not going to be it is being shunned. And the reason why which I thought was, I hadn't really considered. She is the Oprah candidate. And
when she ran for governor of Georgia, Oprah, remember Oprah went down. Jay Z, promoting who Yonsei everybody was there and she couldn't win. And I
think that and remember Oprah, of course, she, she feels that she made Barack Obama and she had a big hand in it, for sure. And this is her candidate,
just think Oprah can't run herself. But this would be kind of like an Oprah like an Oprah ugly, you know, and, and, and the Democrat Party wants
nothing to do with her. And I think wants nothing to do with Oprah. Certainly after seeing the combo, Oprah and Stacey Abrams in in Georgia failed,
and they're probably questioning all kinds of celebrity endorsements if they really are worth it anymore. So no, Stacy, according to mo and I think he
laid out the I think he laid out the case for that is not going to be vice president there's no doubt about that. Not going to be the vice
presidential nominee. But she's she'll do anything she'll even show up and and be publicly embarrassed.
John: Well, I I'll just add to my thinking on this is that no black woman will be the vice president or candidate under Biden, which takes a little
further than just targeting Stacey, because again, they were white women that are Democrats are more racist in the republicans by a lot, having been
in both parties. And they will not put especially when Hillary was snubbed, they will not allow a black woman of any sort, Stacey Abrams or otherwise,
that's why Kamala and the rest of them are allowed to for other reasons. I'm sure you can target them. But because they want a white woman as the
first female president, period,
Adam: and you think they're that racist, the Democrat Party.
John: Yeah. I do that, oh,
Adam: they're already misogynist or not I'm sorry, Mr. misanthropic by saying it can only be a woman you can't be a man because we don't qualify.
We're no good. We're stupid. Just look at Joe.
John: Is it gonna be a white? If it's not a white woman, Amy Klobuchar would be at the top of the list. I would say that he wants to go for some other
ethnic possibilities. Again, I'll bring in Lu Han. Grisham out of New Mexico and somebody sent us a note going on and on about how that was good in
particular. You saw that note?
Adam: Yeah, I did. I'm actually I'm gonna grab the clip for you. Here's the clip that brought this comment on homos again. And
Unknown: our Secretary of State insisted, and this broke the meeting up basically, in terms of influence that this be called Lou Han virus,
Adam: which was our producer. Well, he just gave away just giving away who
John: it's gonna be who made the vice presidential pick, it was in the back of his head. He couldn't just not say it. That's a logical, very logical
agenda style thinking I agree. But, you know, I'm still I'm hedging my Luan bet. I'm putting her in the second spot under Amy.
Adam: Oh, I'm sorry. Amy Klobuchar. My clover char is now my, my heart. Amy. Amy, she would be kick ass as vice president. I'm sure she would.
John: Well, she's the except for the fact that she throws staplers and yells at her staff and she's mean, was suppressed. It's just such an extreme
that we have heard none of these stories. They were only apparent at the beginning of the campaigning, too, which makes me think that she may be a
possibility for the VP slot. Sister, they're sanitizing her as we speak.
Adam: So let's just to be clear, Amy Klobuchar is my Amy. And you have a Amy from PBS.
John: No fairy la cracy now
Adam: Yeah, from democracy. That's your Amy and Amy.
John: Thank you very much. I yeah. My my.
Adam: I get my Amy you get your ad. Hey, I have sports news. Are you ready for some sports news coming from me?
John: Oh, this should be
Unknown: rich going into this season coming up.
Adam: This is from Fox Sports, Fox Sports Fox Fs one Fox Sports and that comes with a huge asterisk and hopefully there is a season. There's probably
going to be a season and doing games with no fans. Which will be difficult. I think Fox and these networks have to put crowd noise under us, too. To
the naked
Unknown: experience at home,
John: you think they'll do that?
Adam: I do. Yeah, I
Unknown: really would. In fact, I
Adam: know they'll do it. And they are. let them finish let him finish yelling through my sports clip. It's not that often that I bring one.
Unknown: In fact, I
Adam: know they'll do it. And they are too
Unknown: that's not the conversation right now. That's, that's it's pretty much a done deal. I think whoever is going to be at that control is going
to have to be really good at their job and be realistic with how a crowd would react depending on what just happened on the field. So
it's really important that on top of that, they're gonna put, they're looking at ways to put virtual fans in the stands. So when you watch out, it
looks like the stadium is jam
Adam: packed. Hey, sports fans, you're not needed. You're completely replaceable. In fact, they should just play the games in a big blue screen. Green
Screen auditorium can do all kinds of cool stuff. You
John: know, this is telling you you know what this tells this confirms the basic no agenda thesis is that all sports are rigged.
Adam: No kidding.
John: This is taking the rigging to a to a maximum. Have fake fake audience fake noise, fake applause the whole thing you know, it's a canned laughter
again, which put canned laughter to get a canned laughter guy in there and have him just Yuk it up. It's unbelievable.
Adam: Oh my god. I can't believe it's an interception. Oh, no, he drops he fumbles.
John: That's the best we can do.
Adam: That's about all I got. Oh, my god, there's a cruise missile. There's a cruise missile going over the stadium. What can we do about it the
cruise missile? I have nothing else. Yeah, that'd be very sad. But it'll fit with the fight fake outcome of these games. So that's good. Oh, yes. I do
have one more. Biden related clip short one. The convention, which is coming up in what is there is the democrat was supposed to be in August. Have
they moved? It is that I know
John: maybe it was in July? They moved to August? I don't know. August is the last I heard here is the
Adam: communications director of the DNC regarding the convention. And I think this, maybe I'm reading too much into it. But it felt a little bit
like, not everyone in the party is on board with Joe Have a listen.
Unknown: I mean, there's a real possibility of the convention doesn't happen or it happens in a virtual sense. Is that correct?
Well, first of all, our convention has to happen because we are not officially nominating Joe Biden, in order to take Donald Trump. So our convention
is happening, there is business that has to happen. Now, when it comes to what our convention is going to look like, I can guarantee you that our
convention will ensure that the safe that we have safety first, whether it is our delegates, the people of Milwaukee or all of those involved in a
convention, we will make sure that they are safe, whatever that level is, and that they vote for our nominee.
Adam: Did you catch the beginning of how she phrased that?
Unknown: I'll play it again.
I mean, there's a real possibility of a convention, does that happen? Or it happens in a virtual sense? Is that correct as
well, first of all,
our convention has to happen because we are not officially nominating Joe Biden, in order to take Donald Trump. I like
John: how I did notice that Hey,
Adam: could Donald Trump I thought that was an interesting use of words. Is that how they see it to take Donald Trump?
John: Well, that's their only goal. But did you listen to it carefully? This is our convention is not to nominate Joe Biden.
Unknown: Is that correct?
Well, first of all, our convention has to happen because we are not officially nominating Joe Biden, in order to take Donald Trump. So our convention
is happening. There is business we're not.
John: We're not nominating Joe Biden is what she said,
Adam: told you there's something weird in that clip, and she seems like she's not. I know for a comms director. I think she let out a little bit too
much there. My personal personal opinion.
John: Oh, yeah. They don't care about anything. But Donald Trump. That's just what you can't win elections that way.
Adam: All right. I am very excited to have a second half of show coming up for you, which is a send in from one of our producers. But first, I think
we should thank some more people who are on the spreadsheet for today. I'm going to show
Unknown: my little to no agenda.
Imagine all the people who
could do that. Oh, yeah, that'd be fun.
John: Yeah, we do have some people think starting with john Patrick. And he came in with $100 even nice. Why don't you read a couple of these because
I do have a couple of notes. I do want to read.
Adam: Well, we don't typically read these. I'm not sure but okay. Johnny, Dad, give me down to where it says I got a note. I gotta go to the desk and
get the note. Oh, you just make me do it. Okay. JOHN Patrick Decatur, Illinois. $100. Much respect for you both for COVID sanity, anonymous $100 has a
douchebag call out and is from an anonymous Parts Unknown. Don't mention full name location just Well, we're just doing anonymous. I'd like to call
out. Oh my goodness. I'd like to call out Dame Jennifer as a douchebag for never sending an invoice for some voiceover work she did. Well, how about
that?
John: She's two days Jennifer
Adam: good for this world to good. JOHN Cooper, Downers Grove, Illinois. You have the notes.
John: As a note, here's where I was doing it. This is another note this is a note as good. I want to read it. I am new to your show after hearing Adam
on Jr. A. nother notch in your belt, while waiting to wait to hear more about that guy.
Adam: I gotta tell you, Joe and I were texting. And Joe keeps mentioning me on his show.
John: I noticed a couple of mentions. Yeah,
Adam: but here's the thing. So Tina, the other night we're sitting on the couch watching TV. And I'm texting Hey, who are you texting? I said my
friend Joe. She says she says she says Joe digenova
John: yeah that sounds
Unknown: classic
Adam: Yeah, anyway onward. Yes, though, that this has done well. This is eight people so far who have come over to our tribe from Jerry I'm very
John: very pleased with that. JOHN continues I've always disliked the media but in the last few years the mask has really come off. It is awesome
finding like minded people I look forward to joining the meetup wants to not lock down is lifted. Thanks for all you do to keep people away from the M
five m fear porn and keep them Migdal. As small I have managed to figure out most of the insider terminology. This is always a problem with the
newbies. But I have a few questions. Okay, what is the significance of the number 33 are you big fans of Rolling Rock beer?
Adam: Well
John: let him stew in this one.
Adam: Really? Well. Let me just say one thing. We've noticed over time that when the number 33 shows up in news reports there's typically something
very fishy going on with the report or with the situation now of course we have it's we've taken it so far that and this has been going on since
almost the first day we did the show that people are noticing it everywhere and during the this rohner crisis it was everywhere 33 this 33 that 33
people are sick 33 to 30 and we have so that's it is the magic number whenever we see 33 we pay attention we're never sure what it's going to mean but
some of it
John: yes code it's code it's and here's another one he brings up which I think should be reading this because this is good stuff to reiterate for the
new comers. It seems harsh to call people douchebags that have not donated but I will not become a douchebag have included my donation 100 But okay,
let's start. Let's start with that concept. This was not our idea. Oh, ever Nope.
Adam: Nope. We also don't do it if you realize we are reading the notes that people send in we're not calling them douchebags.
John: Anyway, he goes on he says he goes on just thanking us for the show. Appreciate the insights on audio production and proper microphone usage. I
love benefiting from people's expertise in areas where I would otherwise not get it my ears now much more tuned. Excellent. I thought you'd like to
take this course
Adam: thank you john.
John: So anyway, onward to forest Morris the forest I love the name forest
Adam: forest Morris the fourth
John: forest more another one
Adam: another one what well he's forest
John: is the second notice right behind this other one I think no I don't know forest. No,
Adam: no, no, no. I'm going to read you the note when I say another one it's something else for us more as the fourth $99.96 for Murfreesboro,
Tennessee where we have a lot of producers forest the mass Barbara here listening since Joe Rogan experience withholding two cents for John's opinions
on barbers and stylists not listening and not needing any time to professionally handle health and safety and two cents for his mask as he will need
to wear one at his haircut. Keep up the great work would like some karma for tips. Yeah, we'll get we'll get some karma for the at the end of this.
John: So he's sleeve Braille, Braille I think it eo boobs donation
Adam: and this is a first donation. First donation so he says a do using deducing is in order.
Unknown: You've been de deuced
John: got it to her Blam of the URL of Georgia Sugar Hill, Georgia 808 Ronald shal came into the pop money donation, Joe Weiss in Miami, Florida 7777.
He has the note that he wrote this check in and I just another note, I put aside for this reason, a quick message from Miami where they're trying to
move south Florida into a new normal this morning when I was taking my daily walk. I was listening to yesterday's podcast while 41 john just started
to talk about the morons who are wearing masks while driving alone. And no sooner Did that make that statement within four minutes I witness three
separate mass commandos alone driving in their vehicles fighting off the corona with the
Adam: air conditioning off and the windows up
John: with your recommendation also listen to to our interview with the JFK Jr. interview. He says it was great treasure trove of good information and
we do recommend that interview if you can find
Adam: the show notes use RFK jr
John: RFK what I say no JFK Jr. I bet that's a mistake. I probably did say JFK, Arnold. Tyler Arnold's Next on our list. $75 he says says he's sorry
he's just hate mail. You're going your way at him. Nope. I
Adam: miss I just want to you know, thank you, but it's really it's hate mail for john that I this gets sent to me and I don't understand they keep
doing it. Tyler, thanks.
John: Well all hate mail to john should go to Adam curry.com sure, milkman and Arcadia ga 6669. Sir Jake, of the IP bowgun it bowgun I'm sorry.
morayfield The Queensland Australia 5959.
Adam: And he's got his old man Jeff, on the birthday list. Got that?
John: Daniel Mariano in pflugerville. Texas. 5510 scherbak of 11. of 21 1255. Yes, so the birthday needs
Adam: needs to be stopped Happy Birthday from scherbak of 2112. To my beautiful caring talented, pretty lady. Yes. It is Dame Jennifer of animated
nogen. This is her husband.
John: This is Dame Jennifer show.
Adam: Pretty much. Dave. Jennifer. Would you mind doing the show for us?
John: smokin hot now she's beautiful.
Adam: Well, he listened to the warning that you gave. We're not allowed to do that anymore. You were very, very
John: suggestions. Darren has some good ones in there. Yes, classics. I like the Microsoft bot wash Bish in racing Wisconsin. $55.
Adam: His brother Rick is who hit him in the mouth. I know he's listening but he has not done it. So he donated so he needs to be called out as a
douchebag.
John: Ilana Mark ghoulish $51 Carl Vogler $50.33 or dh slammer haven't heard from him for a couple weeks. Baron is central California coast. Ventura
to Santa Cruz $50.33. Sir, again, he's got a warning for Cyrus. Sir Christopher Barron of Brown County in Green Bay, Wisconsin. 50. The following
people are all $50 donors name and location, beginning with sir Chris Lewinsky will actually Sir Christopher Behringer brown County's Chris Lewinsky,
Christopher molar in Cedar Park, Travis fricker in Philadelphia, got a birthday el liebel in Newark, Delaware, Joseph Harper and Arnold, Maryland and
john camp and antlers Oklahoma want to thank all these folks listed de-douche as producers of showed 1243. And thanks for helping us out.
Adam: Yes, and also those who came in under 50 for anonymity and we have a lot of these programs, subscriptions that you can participate in and people
actually get pretty fun with those. We have a lot of knights and dames, who have been on the longer layaway programs. All of it is appreciated. The
value for value system is real simple. Whatever you think the show is worth. That's what you send us if it's not worth anything, don't send us
anything. But what we see here today is great. Thank you so much. And as we said we'll be back on Thursday you can support us again, all you have to
do is go to devora.org
Unknown: slash n a
health and jobs karma jobs, jobs, jobs and jobs. Let's vote for job.
You've got karma
Adam: no title changes but birthdays Yes. Ilana Margaret says Happy Birthday to her heartlands harlands father's Zach force Martin celebrates today
Travis stringer. says Happy birthday was smokin hot wife Becky she turns 33 she turned 33 on the 15th of 2112 Happy birthday was beautiful, caring
talented wife named Jennifer she is celebrating today on the 17th as is Damien he is sir Aaron Yoho son. He turns 11 damn Jennifer wheat up says Happy
Birthday if you serve Greg Davies now you know sir Greg Davis was our our Knights who passed away. We missed him dearly. He would have been 44 years
old tomorrow we celebrate him still of course sir Jake says Happy birthday was father, Jeff Kenyon. 59 on the 20th and Fred Lybrand says Happy
Birthday to his son fly not Jr. who will be celebrating on the 25th and Fred himself will be celebrating on the 31st Happy Birthday for everybody here
at the best podcast in the universe. Clue we do know we actually we have a meet up report a very short one. I guess there was Yeah, there were some
people are diehards. And I appreciate it. This is Vernon This is the May 16 Marcellus New York Nine Mile Creek meetup report. The Atom there were
plenty of people sitting around maskless at the picnic tables and benches near the baseball diamond at marsellus Park. But no one asked me about no
agenda. People did ask me about my white cockapoos red boots, which was the indicator I was the meetup leader. I guess not many people look at the
website. They have no podcast meetup announcement is made. There you go. So I guess it was a one person meet up. Darden. Sorry, Verdun. Better luck.
Next time when the Rona is over.
Unknown: Sometimes you want to go hang out with
me.
Adam: Are you ready for some segment
John: to take before we go into note before we do that I get a little entre mon. Okay. And Curiously, this is 43 seconds. And it looks a little like
the Joe Biden stuff, which is really less than two minutes, but it went on forever. For some unknown reason. Isn't it never gonna be no, this is a
apparently all the virtue signaling celebrities, mostly are out there showing at doing commencement speeches. Yes,
Adam: yes. Including the president. Right.
John: They're all do I didn't know that he was doing one. But if he
Adam: do it, I'm sorry. President Obama, I meant not the present. President Obama has been doing commencement speech.
John: Oh, yes, that would be true. But they're all doing them virtually. And they're in a bucket. They usually in a bucket or they find a good place
to put the mic. It's a little bucket on the side. And they're all in a bucket. And they're all given these commencement speeches that are lame, and
they're terrible. But I decided I'm going to look for the worst.
Adam: Oh, yay.
John: So this is short snippet from Tom Hanks. Giving a commencement speech to some small Western case or suddenly I get the name of the school here
somewhere. It's a right state what your rights and never heard of the right state. Sorry, anybody, right state alums. So he's giving this speech. He's
reading it kind of, but he kind of lost track. And I think he started off with saying the wrong thing he tried to make up for it and, and he just
could never really caught up to it. So the speech became this discombobulated piece of crap. Here it is, congratulations to you chosen once.
Adam: Wow, stop right there.
Unknown: This is
Adam: I don't understand how they allow this to happen. This sound is just beyond me. beyond me,
Unknown: congratulations to you chosen once. And
I am calling you the chosen ones because you have been chosen. In many ways.
You have not returned to the starting line like all of us generations before, you're just approaching it now for the first time. You've just to run
your chosen in that way to enter into the competition of life just when so many have had to recover and refresh and restart and re awaken and to
retake up the hard work and the unshakable responsibilities admitted making the world not only our own, but of your Oh,
wow.
John: Talk about you start. Here's what happened. He says Congrats. I think he kind of had lived the beginning thing is going to be cool. And he said,
congratulations to the chosen ones. And then he thought to himself right on the spot. Wait a minute. I'm old Jews. And this isn't offensive when I'm
saying here and so He then goes and tries to make up for an instant by what I buy and what I mean by chosen ones. And then the whole thing falls apart
and it's just an embarrassment and he's in his home with a brick wall behind him and he's trying to read off his notes that this is just should not be
people should not be doing that was
Adam: pretty much the definition of phoning it in. It was really bad from the sound to the copy to everything and even the intent. Even the intent.
Why does he why why are they doing that? Very odd. And if you're gonna do it do do make it memorable. Not like oh, I'm Tom Hanks in a bucket.
John: Yeah, the other thing is, these guys are all no production values. And people like Tom Hanks is a good example. He's not like he's a producer.
Yes, he's a producer. He could produce a video and he could put to good sound with it. He's got nothing else to do. He's, he's holed up in his
mansion. He could put he could put a track behind himself. He could have a green screen. He could be in Paris. I mean, there's a million things you
could do to make it lively. But no, he's just bought what walks through a bucket presentation. It's embarrassing. These guys are just showing that
they really are they really producers, or are they just front men? That is with no talent?
Adam: What What was the school he was doing this for as its build by the way on new sites as Tom Hanks inspiring 2020 commencement address inspire
inspiring. Who was it for though?
Unknown: state? Was that
Adam: his alma mater?
John: I don't know. I didn't go that deep into it,
Adam: though. They quote no one will be more fresh to the task of restarting our measure of normalcy than you. You Chosen One's brother. Now I find
all right, Tom Hanks.
John: Um, so that is the worst commencement speech I could find.
Unknown: In a while. It's
Adam: been a while second half of show. I received multiple emails this over the past few days, about the earthquakes in Nevada. Exactly. I didn't
know either. I'm like there's earthquakes in Nevada. What's going on? It
John: was I saw a couple of headlines about earthquakes in Nevada.
Adam: Yeah. So we had Dame Angela, who said it but like 30 or 40 of them. It was all day long. Yeah. And people were a little concerned. But
John: now sort of fracking going on somewhere.
Adam: Well, that's what you think. But we have a boots on the on the ground report from sir Joel. So he's royalty. You know, he's legit. Sir Joel, the
skinny trucker Battle Born black Baron of the Northern Nevada. Certainly you've heard of him. Here he is with his earthquake report.
Unknown: Hey, Adam and john. This is Joel, the skinny trucker, also known as surgical The Battle Born black bear in of Northern Nevada. Just wanted to
give you my update on the Nevada earthquake that we had early this morning on Friday, May 15th. I was driving through pretty much the epicenter
exactly when it happened. felt the truck shake a bit. And I was wondering what's going on. It's pretty windy. But as I was going up the road highway
95 there was one crack and I'm like, Oh, that's strange. That wasn't here when I drove down to tonopah from Reno. And then there was another crack and
then a third crack. And I'm like, oh, there must have been an earthquake. And lo and behold, there was but interesting thing that I noticed as this
was happening. I was looking up on the ridge line of the mountains to the west, and I saw this bright blue light behind the mountains and I'm like,
Oh, I wonder what that is because it didn't look like an airplane or any kind of truck light. It looked like something else. So if you guys know the
area middle Nevada, western Nevada is a lot of federal land. There's a huge Army Depot just north in Hawthorne, and you know, area 50 ones not too far
away. So who knows, maybe get the theramin out some tinfoil hat. And hopefully some other producers have some information that maybe you can shed some
light on the subject. But that's my take from Northern Nevada. It's a Battle Born black Baron. Joel, in the morning. Thank you. Thank you for your
courage
Adam: in the morning. Thank you for your courage.
John: Well Northern Nevada and area 51 there's there's not even close.
Adam: No I but I don't think he was insinuating was aliens. I've been paying attention to this weird weather. We have had torrential downpour,
literally just Texas. It's been very interesting to see the weather patterns. And maybe there's some heart firings going on. Who knows I don't know
what's happening. But the blue light out there. That's odd. And these earthquakes as that happened before, like 3040 earthquakes on a day in Nevada,
maybe
John: it has I don't know. There's an area in Nevada where they have a lot of quakes. It was, but that was due to fracking. Right? Um, well, I don't
know. We'll keep an eye on it. I'm sure that we'll find out nothing.
Adam: Oh, you're so positive.
John: We'll keep looking. We'll look and look. Not gonna get anywhere with this.
Adam: All right.
John: Any more screwball reports?
Adam: No, I don't have that. But I do have an update on 1000s of sealed indictments. Yes, yes. Yes, I'm telling you. Everyone's out of the Woodworks.
We've got everyone talking clappers on TV. Brennan's on TV. Everyone's getting their points in I think a good backgrounder is to go to the man who is
the mainstream gateway for 1000s of sealed indictments, Lou Dobbs on Fox Business News. And here is who I think is a good journalist john Solomon, to
bring us the lowdown,
Unknown: everyone I've talked to today has been exasperated by the judges conduct. But at the end of the day, it's a lot of show for an inevitable
conclusion. At the end of the day, these charges are going to be dismissed against General Flynn because the law requires it when both parties go in
as they do in this case. And when there is a preponderance of evidence as there is in this case of wrongdoing, the courts have consistently allowed a
vacation or vacating of, of a conviction like this, it's just going to extend the drama a little longer, but it's going to inevitably end up whether
it's at the Supreme Court, the appellate court, or the district court, it's going to end up getting the the charges are going to be dismissed.
Finally, and I do say Finally, Lindsey Graham has scheduled a hearing to dig into these very serious issues. I know his investigative staff very well,
they're very competent, they've been working very hard behind the scenes, they're going to have some big, big revelations that are not yet public,
that will move this narrative along and show just how far reaching the corruption inside the bureaucracy was. As for the issue of President Obama, you
know, there's gonna come a moment after that first evidence is laid out in his hearings, where people are going to obviously say, hey, it started at
the top with President Obama. And then I think lindsey graham will have to face the music of his own evidence and decide what he's going to do. And I
think that moment, May, when the evidence is all out there. There'll be an even more pointed question to the to the chairman. Why aren't you talking
to President Obama? And I think, Well, you know, let's see what the evidence comes out. But keep in mind over the last few months, there's been a lot
of information taken from the National Archives, from the Obama administration, they lay out a very powerful case, we're going to begin to see that
evidence over the next three, four weeks. And all I can say from what I know from my reporting is buckle your seat belt.
Adam: Buckle your seat belt,
John: huh? Well, first of all, I am not buckling my seat belts. For starters, Uh huh.
Adam: Yeah, no kidding.
John: because nothing's coming up any of this?
Adam: Well, I'm not so sure. I think that something's going to happen. We, you know, this Flynn stuff and the unmasking and FISA court abuses, I think
something will come have that. But we'll what let me finish. It's easy to say, I have I have some some I've received a BA, I have some receipts, I
have some backup. The there's a lot of running around of people coming out who haven't spoken for a long time. And I think they're all jockeying and
positioning clapper seems to be the the top guy. Now this was cnn it was people call this differently than it was. The way it was posted is Oh, look,
he asked him a tough question. And then the connection breaks. But it actually you can hear a little truly an audio glitch. It froze right after the
first question. So he didn't he probably didn't even hear the second one. But that doesn't mean that he wasn't removed from this zoom call. So we
could not answer here's to clapper, former director of national intelligence and a liar, a liar to Congress. But unindicted
Unknown: Okay, so asking for names. Nothing wrong with that unmasking in of itself,
nothing wrong with that leaking
classified information. And by definition, these phone calls were classified. That's a problem, correct?
Absolutely. It is. And if anyone
Adam: you hear that, that's when he cut out but we'll do the question anyway.
Unknown: Did
leak the contents of these conversations with or without the name? That would be a problem? Yes. We've lost the shot. I wonder if we can at least get
him on the phone. To finish this. Let's try to get Director Clapper back.
All right, we're gonna work. We're gonna work on getting that shot. Yeah,
Adam: so of course they did get him back later. This question didn't come up, but was he willing to testify? Yeah, can you come in and testify?
Unknown: Given my age demographic? I'd be happy to come after I've been vaccinated for COVID-19. Would you testify?
I could do it remotely as the case with the files to hearing or respond to questions or, or, or that sort of thing. But I don't particularly want to
put my life without a my wife in life in jeopardy for impro in person testimony.
Adam: So basically not intending to testify to anything at all, because Corona COVID. The other guy out and about was former CIA director john
brennan. And I have you heard, do you know yet if his clearance has been removed? No, I
John: got no information one way or the other,
Adam: we just don't know. I'd like to remind you john Brennan's stance on the law and when you are guilty, or when you should be sentenced or charged
to very short, he's very clear
Unknown: people are innocent until well alleged to be involved in some type of criminal activity.
Adam: So this would be guilty, john brennan, who is alleged to have some part in criminal activity. And this is a longer clip. But I think it's extra
good, because you can hear well, we'll we'll discuss it, Chris Hayes. And john brennan, there does seem to be a bit of a shift in the last several
months with William Barr at the Department of Justice with Richard Grinnell at DNI such that the actual machinery and tools of government are being
kind of applied along the lines of the rhetoric of the President. How do you see things right now? Well, Chris says exactly
Unknown: why I think the recent developments are so worrisome, because Mr. Trump has removed individuals, the head of the intelligence community, as
well as from the FBI as injustice. And he's trying to put people in who are going to do his bidding. So we saw recently with the acting director of
national intelligence, Richard Grinnell, a handpicked individual who I think has demonstrated his loyalty to Mr. Trump over the years, releasing
declassified the names of individuals who had unmasked some names in intelligence reports, with the implication that that was wrongdoing, and what
wasn't carrying out our responsibilities correctly. But then when I look at the Attorney General Mr. Barr, now,
Adam: so of course, there's no diving into the fact that it was 39 people who were witness to or who had requested and received unmasking. But I guess
that's just the job carrying out our responsibilities correctly.
Unknown: But then when I look at the Attorney General, Mr. Barr,
and how he has repeatedly
demonstrated that his interest is being the President's lawyer, as opposed to being the people's lawyer, you need to get
the updated memo Brennan, that's pretty old hat you're repeating there. And I'm very worried that the instruments of governance, the instruments of
intelligence and law enforcement and justice, are now being exploited and manipulated and Mr. Trump's hands, and I think that's something that should
worry all Americans, it's one thing to have policy differences. And we can have arguments in public about that. But if he's going to try to bring
charges against individuals trumped up charges, because of his political interests, and he's going to have individuals who are going to help make that
happen. That is something that I saw overseas in my career, my next 3d career. And I never thought I would see that happening here in the United
States. That clearly back in the last century, the 1970s, we had an instance where President Nixon tried to use
the FBI
and CIA and others for political purposes. And we had quite an uproar at that time when President Nixon was forced out of office. Sad to say that it
sounds like we are now back in the same type of environment, where an individual in the White House is now using those organizations and using people
in senior positions and intelligence and law enforcement for his own purposes.
Adam: Like yourself being yourself makiko door to health. That is the best example of projection. I've heard from him and says, just like Richard
Nixon, clearly, this president was using the intelligence apparatus to get at his enemies. It's exactly what happened allegedly with the whole Obama
administration
John: if that isn't, you know, not rewriting the History The history of Nixon is also solid. Yes, get get Nixon out of the picture. These guys. This
guy is the worst. I think there's a fall guy though. Yeah, he should be embarrassed that he was ever part of their operation.
Adam: Yeah, this one little quick thing real quick bite I got here, which may be the Fall Guy cuz someone's got to go Hoping that individuals
Unknown: like Chris rea, who is a remarkable public servant, will continue to stay strong in the face of this type of
John: volatile, vulnerable.
Unknown: abuse of authority.
Adam: So Chris Ray's on the block is
John: Obama bowl.
Adam: Oh, let's listen. Did you say Obama? Wow, yeah.
Unknown: Individuals like Chris rea, who
is a remarkable public servant will continue to stay strong in the face of this type of
volatile
abuse of authority.
Adam: Oh, man, Obama bowl. That's great word. Obama Obama bowl, but I think Christopher rea is on the block.
John: I think that may have been what you just heard there that clip. I think, put put him on the block.
Adam: Well, that that would have been part of the part of the point. Obama bowl.com. registered, done. I don't know why. I need it. And it's
available. Right. Obama bowl.com That's right, everybody. I do a podcast. You can find it at Obama. bowl.com. Yeah. And I think that some other stuff.
John: Well, I got a few things I want.
Adam: Yeah. Then we have our round round the world, the rubber round around around the world.
John: You want to hear a few of those
Adam: run around the world.
John: Well, let's start with the funniest one. And I actually have a sub clip for this is COVID New Jersey.
Unknown: Ah, always a good time. With summer right around the corner New Jersey announced this week that beaches would be opened by Memorial Day
weekend with some restrictions. The openings are weeks behind other coastal states like Georgia and Florida, but as one of the state's hardest hit by
the covid 19 pandemic. Local officials say they are proceeding cautiously at exactly 10am yesterday, barriers that had been blocking the boardwalk and
beach and Seaside Heights, New Jersey were pushed aside. An announcement made it official
speeches are now officially
officially open. It's a sign that things are returning to normal and
this quintessential jersey shore town, sort of.
We're looking to see how we deal with the social distance. And that's going to be our test today.
Tony vase is the mayor of Seaside Heights.
After nearly two months of
being closed because of COVID-19. Visitors can now walk and ride bikes on the boardwalk
provided they heed the rule of six feet between groups of people.
On the beach, there's no swimming or sunbathing. But the public can walk fish and even surf. Nirvana says it's just the first phase of Seaside Heights
is reopening.
I'm optimistic that this is a good first step. Obviously I would love to see everything open. I would love to see a swimming and so forth. But we have
to recognize that we have to take this in steps.
Seaside Heights is one of more than three dozen communities along the Jersey Shore grappling with how best to reopen in neighboring Seaside Park
beaches are already open to sunbathers provided beach goers and their distance
John: you know more interested in this this Tony vase guy. He sounds identical to Joe Pesci. He
Unknown: does a little bit does a little bit.
John: I actually have a clip from further on in that in that that presentation. And this is a 16 seconds of him talking. This guy has a voiceover gig
anytime he wants one Danny but by the way he's wearing a mask so he's kind of muffled but this is Tony vas talking a little bit more
Unknown: if we just obey the rules you know you're gonna stop at a stoplight then we're gonna we're gonna whack him. That's a rule. So you know if
it's social distancing and social distancing if you know it's another mandate following it has to get better I don't have the magical number when it
will get better.
Adam: Yes, nailed it. We should find him and ask him to do some stuff for us.
John: I was thinking about it but then again, I'm thinking I'm getting called back saying you think I'm funny. You're
Adam: gonna visit I'd very good. I like that. But sad man. What is new jersey become? I lived there for you know, 12 years. jerseys. sad, sad, sad.
No, I'm not 12 nine years.
John: Just back back to the rundown. That was jersey. Let's go to the COVID. Eu update with an emphasis on Greece
Unknown: COVID eu border Fender money and Switzerland was dismantled last night. It's part of an agreement by those countries as well as Austria to
begin opening borders again.
German Prime Minister Angela Merkel said earlier this week that she would like all emergency border controls in Europe's 26 nations Schengen zone
removed by June 15. Also in Germany, the country's Premier Soccer League Bundesliga resumed play today without fans. It is the world's first major
Soccer League to start up following a two month pause due to the coronavirus pandemic.
Adam: Did they have fake? Fake audiences? I have not heard I have to check that out
John: so far no.
Unknown: In Greece more than 500 public beaches reopened today is the country experienced its first heatwave of the year. beachgoers were required to
keep their distances official stipulated how many people could be on the beach and exactly how far apart umbrellas needed to be. Yes, the beaches are.
Opening beaches
is the first major easing of Greece's Coronavirus lockdown to date it has had just a fraction of the cases of many neighboring countries
including Turkey. Starting tomorrow Greeks will be allowed to attend church and tourism officials hope to welcome back foreigners in July.
Adam: No. Wow.
John: So they got nothing going on. Stop is underreported. Nobody wants to talk about Greece. Why they have less cases. Maybe there's something there
taking them maybe taking a prophylactic like hydroxychloroquine is
Adam: can be could never that doesn't work. The ship doesn't work you need remdesivir that's the one that keeps you alive somewhat longer. I don't
know. You need the approved one.
John: COVID Brazil PBS
Unknown: Brazil we are really doing a run around Brazil's health minister resigned last night after just one month on the job. The shake up comes as
the number of coronavirus infections in Brazil continues to rise. Nelson did not provide a reason for his resignation, but it came just a day after a
Brazilian President Jair bolsonaro pressured him to accept the use of chloroquine to treat COVID-19 patients. The drug which is used to treat malaria
has been praised as a therapeutic for the new disease by bolson. ro and President Trump, though it lacks scientific support
Adam: has become an epicenter of the Coronavirus, setting daily records for infections each of the last three days. On Friday, the health ministry
confirmed more than 15,000 new infections despite relatively low rates of testing. If I may compliment you. It takes a real professional to hold on to
a surprise added clip until the very end of the show. I commend you sir. That was well done. Very good.
John: catch you off guard.
Adam: Yes, you did not have it China. You made me feel good.
Unknown: overseas in China official said they marked one full month with no new COVID deaths. But vulnerable populations like here in Bangladesh are
bracing for a blow in this crowded camp home to 1 million Rohingya Muslims. The first Coronavirus case was confirmed just today.
John: You have it?
Adam: Yeah. I thought our boots on the ground from Wu Han was better.
John: Well, anything is
Adam: better. At least we got people on the ground and Wu Han.
John: Well, is that the same guy was the note initially when this whole thing broke? Oh, yes.
Adam: Yes, yes. Yes. That's the guy. Yeah. We good. We have some of the best. Let me just check and make sure I didn't miss any of these. That the
worst thing home nursing home the Wu Han, I want to thank Dr. disorder for sending us our no agenda mass, not the ones we ordered. But he was a
cancellation. So he said that the keeper wants the 1984 mask, which is coming. I hope she wants to proudly wear that. Which is a good one.
John: I think Yeah. Israel will be good. I do I can play a little more with the bite and I can play the Shields and Brooks on the pvh Resort. Oh,
Adam: God, let's get out of here on something happy.
John: That's happy. Okay.
Adam: What is it?
John: Express it's the same side of the political agenda who's standing there in their homes, and one of them worried sick, the other one too old to
care,
Adam: less listen to Shields and Brooks.
Unknown: And it reveals that Joe Biden is a very transparent person, the
culture they described is certainly the culture. I knew when I was covering Senator Biden, and the person I know him to be. And it raises more
skepticism about the claims. I would say this and in addition, there's a political reporter looking into some terrorists past allegations, in other
cases, other parts of her life. And I think the bottom line is if you were a person who was saying should this issue be a problem for me and voting
for Joe Biden? I think the arrow has moved into less of a problem. We don't know that it didn't happen. We can event but certainly the degree of
skepticism has to be a little higher because of this reporting.
And Mark, I mean, you're somebody who's covered the city for a long time you've walked the halls of the senate office buildings, but what do you come
away with here?
Well, I Callaway, first of all, with great admiration for both Lisa and Dan. I mean 74 people on the record is remarkable. That's been a couple of 100
calls. They had to make To get that
John: okay now what I wanted to write played that clip because it was gonna play a series of clips where they PBS may play maybe played next Thursday,
they took their to Lisa Dejardin and some other guy. And they went and they investigated, Lisa, they spent a fortune investigating the terrorist story
by talking to old staffers and they talked it, they tried to contact 200 people. And they contacted 75 and got Oh, got 75 on the record. Uh huh. And
shields is impressive. They got 75 people on the record to do full interviews. And I'm, as I'm listening to so one overlooked fact here is that the
New York Times and The Washington Post, do stories with nobody on the record. They don't talk to 200 people, right? They don't talk to anybody. And
they have just as sources, somebody thinks that somebody else somebody else said something about something.
Adam: No, they talked to the campaign about it. That's, that's what they did. And they removed a part of their reporting that talked about the pattern
of him fondling and touching people, which was not a problem at all.
John: So you end up with the anomaly where PBS, just a TV show is not even any good anymore. Get 75 people to talk on their record about a specific
thing. And the newspapers who have people that are supposed to be doing this making a lot of phone calls, they get nobody for anything. It's
unbelievable. Well, I just thought it was it was remarkable that the PBS say But why do they have to do that many people? What were they trying to
prove?
Adam: And did did they talk about any of their research? Or is that the series of clips? You want to do that on? You wanna do that? Now? The series of
clips Wow, yeah,
John: we have time I'll do this series of clips. Let's start. There's only three of them. Okay. And the longest one is the first one. And we'll play
that
Unknown: two months ago, allegations arose accusing former Vice President Joe Biden of sexual assault. Tara Reid, who in 1993 worked in the office of
then Senator Biden said that he assaulted her. Biden has categorically denied the allegations, which now face examination from the public. Our own Dan
bush and Lisa Dejardin did extensive reporting, talking to 74 former Biden staffers to learn more about the Vice President, the culture in his
offices, and their thoughts on the allegations. The to join me now to share what they've learned. Hello to both of you. And I'm going to turn to you
both. But, Lisa, to you to begin. Take us through what you did, and and what you learned in all from talking to all these people.
Yeah, God, we reached out to try to reach out to some 200, former Biden staffers of that we were able to have in depth interviews with some 74 of
them. Now, 62 of these former staffers were women, and to a person God, those women told us, they had never had any experience that was uncomfortable
with the former vice president or had ever heard of any experience that was uncomfortable or worse. Many of them said they had spent time with Him
alone during work hours. And that they had, they wanted to say that they most of them didn't want to reflect on whether what Tara Reid is saying is
true or not. But they did say that it did not reflect their experiences at all, especially in a workplace that Dan and I both heard from them, they
felt empowered women.
That's right, at least I would add to that also that a lot of the former staffers we spoke to said that while they never felt uncomfortable, they did
confirm what we all know about Joe Biden, which is his history, his habit of reaching out making physical contact with people he speaks to touching
them. We spoke to people who said at the time of this, it was known about Biden that he would rub rub your shoulders, squeeze your shoulders, give
people hugs and kisses. And again, while the people we spoke to said that they themselves didn't feel uncomfortable. They did acknowledge that vice
former Vice President Biden doesn't seem to have strong a strong social signal in terms of when that kind of contact is wanted or not. That came up
last year on the campaign trail. And now again here.
Oh, man.
John: Now they did dig up two interesting little tidbits, which are, I don't know if they're important or not I they're trying to they're really going
out of their way to protect Biden. So I know Biden is the candidate. Let's face it. No kidding. Yeah. Let's listen to clip two.
Unknown: And Lisa, you also uncovered frankly, new details that reflect on Tara Reid's allegation that she says she was forced out of the office
because she complained about being uncomfortable about this sexual incident. It tells us exactly what you learned about that and why it matters.
Well, Tara Reid says that she complained about previous sexual harassment in the office, and that after she complained, she says she was retaliated
Against and for in a couple of ways, and that that eventually forced her out of the office. We spoke to the man who shared an office with her. His
name is Ben Savage. They work together on constituent mail. Ben savage told us that actually, it was a performance problem with Tara Reid, that he
himself raised to supervisors. In some cases, he said she was throwing out constituent important records of constituent mail, and that the problem was
bad enough that he raised it to supervisors he believes that's why she left. And here's some of the interview that I had with him over the phone.
And the robot people who held that position. She's the only one during my time there who couldn't necessarily keep up or who found it frustrating.
We of course, reached out to Tara Reid, she declined our request for an interview but her attorney did give us detailed responses to our questions
among them to this exact issue. He said that story is flat wrong. Here is what Doug winder wrote us in response, he wrote Miss Reed recalls that there
was a lot of nitpicking regarding her performance in the office. She was also very nervous at that point and distracted so it's possible that from
time to time there was a mistake made but her performance had nothing to do with her termination. Judy, we we do know that read worked in that office
for about nine months.
Adam: Wait a minute, she says she was I thought she left she was terminated
John: Yeah, hmm.
Adam: Well, then let's get then there's then there's a termination letter and there's something there that I
John: gotta have some documentation for this. And by the way, how what kind of a job are you going to mail? This is not a complicated job that you
can't Kiyoshi can't keep up. Come on with bullcrap I worked in the government does a
Adam: fully did they? Now how is this report presented this? Is it this is the presentation of their findings or they have a package or
John: no, no, there's no package. But there's a little bit of a package in this last clip where this guy goes on to the bush I have to explain after
the presentation. This is the part three.
Unknown: And and Dan, you also learned new information from Reid's attorney about the location that Tara Reid says is where Joe Biden assaulted her.
So tell us about that.
That's right. Judy Reid's attorney provided us with new information about this assault of this alleged assault, saying the reclaims that it took place
somewhere between the Russell building where Biden had an office at the time and the US Capitol bill. We want to show you what these spaces look like.
So this is the hallway where Biden's office was is essentially unchanged to now to get to the Capitol, you go down a flight of stairs, and then take a
tunnel where there's a subway, that takes lawmakers to the Capitol Building. Now, anybody who has been to this part of the Capitol knows that there
are a lot of people moving through these spaces, especially when Congress is in session. Lawmakers, their age reporters, there's a police presence as
well. And what a lot of these former Biden staffers told us is, look, these are public places. If this allegation is true, if it took place, it would
have been extremely brazen, Judy, because the likelihood that it would have been seen by someone was very high. Man, if
John: well, to give you an explanation, what he showed, first, he showed the big long hallway, there was nobody there. Then he showed a spot where
there's that little little subway system and there's a crowd there. And then he showed another shot. There was zero people. He's going on and on about
all the
Adam: photos, the empty photo empty, empty corridors. Well, I don't know what happened. We we will not know we'll never know, believe all women,
whatever. The fact of the matter is, look, here's the deal. Joe Biden is not qualified to run for anything. It's a sham. I don't know what's going on.
I don't know why they're doing this. It makes no sense. And I would hope that we remember the people who were speaking so glowingly and lovingly about
Joe Biden about his experience and what a great president he'll make it in these days specifically because I'd like to talk to those people after
whatever happens happens because it'll become apparent that this was a scam whether he gets an office or not is going to be apparent
John: Yeah, I don't get it personally. I don't know what the what's the point of it in less is just to put somebody in the vice president slot that
you know, you can't get elected. Amy Klobuchar be a good example. No one's voting for her she did poorly and all the primaries but you can get her in
its president and she'd be a good bureaucrat and and as long as she's a globalist is good to go. I'm going to try and get a globalist back in the in
the office and get back on track here. Turning the country over, or national sovereignty should be turned over to a one world government. That's
obviously what's going on. And there are people that advocate for that. And that's the coronas thing is all about that?
Adam: Well, I think Joe Biden is right. I think he's very smart. He stays in his basement. I think it's very intelligent of his campaign. They do not
let any outsiders in from Comcast or any smart people who are going to come in and fix their sound, because the likelihood of him being killed is high
right now. Certainly, in the Corona, period, we'd have a great excuse. I fear for Joe's life at this point, there's no way anyone who was running any
show at the Democratic National Party Democratic Party thinks that this guy is actually going to be something worth anything as a president.
John: It's just a guy just totally disagreement with you. You're speaking from a logical perspective as if the democrats are logical.
Adam: I'm waiting for you.
John: I just think they're real logical. I think they're, they're sincere. I think they sincerely think this guy is going to be a great president.
They're keeping most of the gaffes are out of the public eye so that so the public doesn't notice. And so he can get in. They, they believe their own
publicity. So when they see a Washington Post poll that says that Biden's gonna be trumped by 10 points, they all blow I think they believe it. I
don't think they think that that is bullcrap. I think, well, this guy's a winner. This guy can beat Trump. That's all we want. This guy can beat
Trump. Yeah, maybe he won't be the best guy. But he can beat Trump. And he's a good guy. He's one of ours. He's one of our guys. And he's Next on the
list. And he's the guy who's up next up to bat,
Adam: no matter what strategy you look at, it's apparent that people are being chosen around him or sold or selected, or people are getting ready in
case he either dies in office. And, okay, we disagree on this. But the way this is being run, and if you telling me that the people who run the DNC
I'm not talking about Democrats, I'm talking about the prostitutes on television, they're just doing what they're told to do, I'm sure they believe.
But this to me sounds like a setup for someone who was not nominated someone who was not running someone who is going to have to come in and save the
day when something bad happens to Joe, that is a scenario that has to be looked at.
John: But that brings Hillary back into the mix. Thank you very much.
Adam: That's all I can think of. And if not that, then yeah, then people are just delusional because this man is not appropriate for any kind of
public knows the right word, any kind of public office.
John: Well, Hillary, again, is the one that could be targeting the whole thing. She could be behind everything. I mean, they're their machines still
exists. And there's a lot of support for it. And I think the general public in the United States will get extremely irked at this point. If Hillary
swoops in because I think they're going to see the whole thing was was a setup and what what's the point what is that what's wrong with the democrats
that they can find anybody?
Adam: How about this first scenario? Wait a minute, let me she's flying over Hold on. You gotta be careful what you those low fly by she does her
little dangerousness a seal the flapping of her wing
John: aiming for Trump's hair, like a search nest.
Adam: So how about this? How about we choose an African American woman for Vice President Joe croaks then we get Hillary as president black Hillary as
vice president.
John: How does Hillary get in both of Joe croaks is he going to cook before after No no.
Adam: No before the nomination of course before
John: Yeah, of course before they're gonna have to croak within the next two months.
Adam: And the clock is ticking. The Biden crock croak countdown clock has started. t minus two months. I hope not. But I don't know. Well, I
John: hope not too. I'd rather see Joe in it.
Adam: Much more entertaining, but much, much more entertaining. That is it for our deconstruction for today. We have end of show mixes coming up from
Jesse Coyne Nelson, we've got us Aaron Aaron yo who supported the show earlier today. And after this, I know agenda stream.com mo facts Episode 37 a
shell game. hear more about that Biden BP scenario. Until then, I am coming to you from opportunity zone 33 here in Austin, Texas capital The Lone
Star State FEMA Region number six on the governmental maps if you're looking for my body bag, and please remember us@devora.org slash na to support
the no agenda show after all, you were producer to in the morning, everybody. I'm Adam Curry and from Northern
John: Silicon Valley, where it rained again last night which is very screwy. Maybe it's got something to do with something I don't know. I'm John
Dvorak. We return on
Adam: Thursday right here on no agenda until then adios mobile groups of
Unknown: people standing outside an ice cream parlor or maybe they're playing pickup basketball sharing a sidewalk. I don't nice day weeks ago, is
your everyday activities, but the Coronavirus has changed everything.
I see some things that I don't think is right, especially now,
I'm going to challenges social distancing, complaints
are drawing shame on social media and calls to the police.
Adam: Corona, Corona,
Unknown: Corona, virus, virus virus, Corona viruses like this.
Let's listen to the scientists vaccine, vaccine, vaccine or no vaccine.
John: driving
Unknown: out she
don't be stupid.
We're watching you.
Adam: Neil Ferguson Imperial College model jacked up his
John: mistress when he was supposed to be sheltered in place.
Adam: You recall that he built these models not on rock and roll but on 13 year old undocumented
Unknown: presidents
and presidents
you president's
presidency.
Someone in that troll room is out of control
mopho.org
slash n A,
where we're we're we're in the middle of a pandemic.