adam curry
john c divorce it's sunday may
17th 2020
this is your award-winning
kitmo nation
media assassination episode
1243.
this is no agenda
and from northern silicon
valley i
believe adam's turned into a
democrat
i'm john cena buzzkill
in the morning yeah i figured
i'd try
and see how it works with the
mask
seeing as that
is what we're going to be
coerced into
no matter what
we want
well i've read these orders and
none of
them say you have to be wearing
a mask
all the time correct
you do not so why are people
wearing the
mask all the time they're
wearing him in
their car
i'm wearing him at home yeah
yeah i have
done some
investigative work on this and
um
unfortunately this is a result
of the i would say the
the society that we've created
certainly
younger people
and it goes like this
you have to wear a mask to keep
me safe okay
you have to wear the mask to
keep me
safe so if you're not wearing a
mask
but i'm wearing a mask i'm
keeping you
safe
but you're a douchebag and
that's the bottom line you're
not going
to get away from it
people are mad they're angry
and i think that if we want to
just open
up i have a suggestion
it's completely optional so
wherever you
go a store
doesn't have to force you to
wear masks
but they can't and if they do
then you should will respect
that any
other place
where you want me to wear a
mask so that
you feel safe
is good i'll wear the mask and
to make
sure
i feel safe and i'm protected
from you
i'm going to open carry my
firearm
and i'm going to do this in
texas
so that you can see i'm not a
democrat
democrats have guns open
carry no i don't think so in
austin
no double no not at all
a couple of things here i i i
question
your premise
and by that i mean i'm not
absolutely
sure
that all these douchebags
wearing a mask
actually think that they're
wearing the
mask to protect
you from them no it's it's all
virtue
signaling but that is that's
what that's
the
the reasoning that's given
that's the
rationale it's not even really
true well
then why is somebody wearing
the mask in
their car
well that's okay if they want
to feel
that that's their business i
don't care
if they want to look like
idiots but i'd
like to get away from
this we're never going to open
up fully
until we agree on some social
things and
if it's going to be masks oh my
god so
be it
go ahead force everybody to
wear a mask
that's we need to do something
and i'm
willing to compromise but again
i'm
going to open carry which is
legal as
long as you have your concealed
carry in
texas you can open carry and i
intend to do that in my car too
and on
the street
yeah yeah it's you know there's
i don't
think there's any other
way for us to go so you don't
have do
you have a holster yet
oh i have several holsters um
in italy
they're opening up on tuesday
and uh
they will have social
distancing i've
got a little report from willow
so they'll have all that set
but masks
shall be worn until there's a
cure or a
vaccine so
i'm seeing what's going on
we're not
going to get away from this
it's going
to be an
endless fight with a whole
bunch of
idiots and we just have to
become japan
we're already on our way
financially
into the japanese
debt trap so we might as well
just go
the full nine yards
i don't see it it's not worth
it from
our duke and duchess or the
duke anyway
would you i don't know if you
have it
well i'd like to read it during
the
donation segment but i have some
it's kind of just i think i
really might
want to read it now this is
really
exactly what you're talking all
right
all right well okay
i have a report from china as
well uh
this is from sir mark and dame
astrid
the duke and duchess of japan
and all
the disputed islands in the
japan sea
and uh we will read uh most of
this
on uh during the donation
segment but uh
masks work
is the japanese uh reasoning
and the whole country wears
them for flu
season every year especially on
the most
crowded mass transit system in
the world
he gives us some
numbers they've only had 739
deaths for
a population of 126 million
which is very good uh complete
so that's
uh what did what do you put
here that's
like uh
it's like 10 times less than
united
states if you believe the
numbers of
course
yeah then well there you go
well hold on
hold on we'll go
we'll get there mass usage went
up with
covid but it also meant that it
was the
weakest flu season in over 10
years
interestingly uh not the same
here in
fact the mortality rate in
japan from
march was also down on top of
this if
you feel you have symptoms
and this i think is kind of
cool japan
is doing you're asked to go to
one of
the many hotels
that have been commandeered for
isolation hub so you don't go
to the
hospital and infect everybody
you don't go home and infect
everybody
you go to one of the designated
hotels
and the government has options
and over
120 000 hotel rooms across the
nation
that i think is a pretty good
idea
of you not if you're enough
think about
you if you're a traveler
well this room previously
occupied
nobody's traveling nobody's
traveling
nobody's traveling uh but yeah
if you
want to go to uh
uh to the to the obvious
hurdles but
maybe just a quick uh
update from wuhan one of our
producers
is back and i'll read his note
uh or hers anonymous we're back
in wuhan
friday wuhan this is you know
wuhan said
they were going to test
11 million people in 10 days
yeah
and i looked at the math and
said i
don't know how that's going to
work but
we have a little more data
our producer says back in wuhan
friday
wuhan tested just over 113 000
people
our hotel slash apartment
called us and
we'll schedule our test this
coming week
my clients are testing the
workers at
work and the chinese government
is
setting up testing stations in
local
neighborhoods they'll test
everyone in
10 days
it's not really even a blip on
most
people's day
one client has a parking lot
that is
full of tables and trailers
that has two
tests
blood and throat swabs takes
less than
10 minutes to stand in line and
go
through the process
yeah that is 11 million
people times 10 minutes i'm
just i
really want to see how they're
going to
complete this
and so far only a hundred and
thirteen
thousand done
um i had to do this went
bullcrap
i had to do this when i first
arrived in
wuhan so i couldn't start work
this will
be my third test since coming
back to
china wuhan is mostly open
some restaurants have dining
inside
while others are take
out only i can't use dd which
is uh
their version of uber only
taxis because
they track you
and you need a chinese id to
register to
be tracked by the
uh chinese uber our local wet
market is
open but not
inside they moved the market to
the
sidewalk and made it one-way
traffic
enter on one side and walk
through to
the to exit the opposite side
you need to have your
temperature
scanned before you enter any
place and
show the qr code having fun in
wuhan
when we first arrived a few
weeks ago
pollution level was great we
had blue
skies and some stars at night
now it's back to gray skies and
burning
eyes
so uh i've never i've never
seen a blue
sky in china
well i i think it probably did
happen
when it was when it was all
shut down that's what he says
yeah but
it probably was quite
phenomenal so in
order not to go through all of
that
tracking and everything i
suggest the
mask i really do
i mean i hate it i'm against it
but
it's we have to sacrifice
somewhere this
and republicans need to shut up
and just
get on board
move on let's do it we can
always
do something later on and maybe
people
will forget about it but
this is not the hill anyone
should take
a stand on in my opinion
because we're dying i was
reading a
fashion
a column about the fashion
industry this
morning
you know and it and that the
nothing
could take
uh what's her name from vogue
magazine
oh my goodness and a winter and
a win
tour dana winter famous
editor of vogue magazine with
the
glasses devil wears
prada movie made about her uh
the fashion industry is saying
well it
looks like nothing could take
her down
but the coronavirus
that can take her down and the
fashion
industry is obliterated
doesn't the fashion designers
are out of
business or
going out of business not that
i'm
crying about it but you know
there's a
lot of people that work in the
fashion
industry
it's just the longer we we do
this the
longer it's going to be a
problem
and assholes like fauci and all
these
people need to get out of the
way we'll
wear some masks
make it optional for people to
requirement and let's go let's
move on
no
no no we can't do that here's
austin
they've gone back to the color
codes of
a threat level of 911. tonight
amid
state demands to roll back its
coronavirus restrictions
austin travis county is now
releasing
new pandemic guidelines
divided into five stages the
chart
suggests what actions to
take based on community's risk
of
contracting
the coronavirus stage one is
where we
want to be
the chart separates suggestions
by the
general public
low risk individuals and those
at high
risk such as anyone
over 65 years old so if you're
uh
in a high risk individual uh
then the
suggestion is
is that uh even in stage one
that you still avoid gatherings
for
everyone else social distancing
and mask
wearing appears
at stage two austin public
health says
we're in stage three
right now this means avoiding
groups of
more than 10 people
and avoiding non-essential
travel mayor
steve adler says
hitting stage five means the
city is in
a pretty bad place
and needs to take extreme
measures you
look at this thing it's like a
grid with
with
colors and numbers and you know
and it's
reverse order so stage five is
worse
stage one is good
it's dumb it's dumb pussies man
go go go i wonder what this what
where this is preoccupation with
non-essential travel what does
that even
mean
what is non-essential travel
it's uh
everything is non-essential
travel
unless uh you're an essential
person
but if you go into the store no
i think
travel means
i don't know i don't know i
don't care
it's all bull crap they can't
force
exactly what i said
yeah yeah but but we can sit in
bicker
or we can get going and i'm
very i'm
getting a little worried here
in austin
which is different from the
rest of
texas and the rest of texas is
doing it
a little differently and moving
a little
faster now here we all have to
be
pansies
um and meanwhile just get back
to the
numbers because that's
really the problem there are
increasingly more there's
increasingly
more evidence
that this death count is really
really
full of crap
and do you remember i said that
i think
berks might have flipped and
she was all
kind of on trump's side and
maybe
anti-establishment that she's
trying to
save herself from the
impending doom that these
people will
meet when we finally figure out
where
all the money is
coming from and going and you
know
judicial watch is
doing all kinds of foyer
requests on the
fauci and the nih you don't
want that
you don't want that and i'm
sure he
hasn't covered everything he
don't want that he doesn't want
that
fouchy doesn't want that you
don't want
tom fish not me you don't want
tom
fitting in judicial watch
making a stink
about your business which has
been
as far as i can tell very shady
for a
long time
so uh this is a cnn report jim
acosta it
was a very long report i
chopped it down
because it was really billed as
tensions
rise
uh between the administration
and let me
get the exact uh
exact title here tensions rise
between
the white house and cdc
as burke's critiques virus
tracking and the death rate in
control
of the coronavirus message
coming from
the white house president trump
is
giving the administration a pat
on the
back for the u.s
response to the pandemic with
the
enormous weight of the pandemic
hanging
over the white house sources
tell cnn
administration officials are
questioning
the accuracy of the coronavirus
death
toll in the u.s and whether the
number
of dead is being over
counted but that would fly in
the face
of testimony from top
administration
health expert dr anthony fauci
who said deaths are likely being
undercounted as some residents
in hard
hit new york died at home
and were never counted as covet
fatalities so in direct answer
to your
question i think you are correct
that the number is likely
higher i i
don't know exactly what percent
higher
but almost certainly it's higher
the president suggested new
york's
numbers i love how they did that
first they say the numbers are
bull crap
and then they get cut straight
to fauci
out of context
and but it's all no it's higher
it's
definitely higher this is a
good report
from cnn when it comes to
propaganda 19
fatalities
so with direct answer to your
question i
think you are correct
that the number is likely
higher i i
don't know exactly what percent
higher
but almost certainly it's higher
the president suggested new
york's
number of debt was too high
last month i
see
this morning where new york
added 3 000
deaths
because they died and they're
now saying
rather than it was a heart
attack
they're saying it was a heart
caused by this
trump allies on fox news have
zeroed in
on fouchy as an
obstacle to reopening the
country
blasting the doctor's cautious
approach
to the pandemic
is this the guy you want to ch
chart the
future of the country
maybe not this is a very
serious matter
the decisions we're making
right now
tony fauci has not been elected
to
anything fauci to be very blunt
is the
face of this failed
administrative
statement totally we've got to
question
the entire premise of this
the chief buffoon of the
professional dr
anthony pouchy
also seems to favor what the
democrats
want and that is
massive restrictions with no
end in
sight with all due respect to
dr fauci's
expertise
no one elected him to anything
but
there's one big problem for the
white
house a cnn poll found a solid
majority
of americans trust
fauci not the president so the
whole
point is
they don't really interested in
talking
about the facts of the death
rate let's
just go ahead and say
fox news or assholes and fox
news is
doing the same to cnn
but every day i could play a
report like
this when police in cortez
colorado
found 35 year old sebastian
yellow
in their city park on may 4th
coroner
george
devers quickly determined what
killed
the man it wasn't coveted it
was alcohol
toxicity yes he did have covet
but that is not what took his
life in
fact
yellow's alcohol level is .55
nearly double the amount that's
fatal so
he literally drank himself to
death
yes exactly devers tested
yellow for
covet 19
after his death and the test was
positive
the coroner said he was
surprised to see
the state then show cova deaths
in
montezuma county
go from two to three with
sebastian
yellows counting as number three
before the death certificate
was signed
they had already listed it as
it go to
death
before the death certificate
was even
signed divers said he's been
trying to
get the state health department
to
explain how a case of fatal
alcohol
poisoning
was classified as a covid death
and they
should have to be recording the
same way
that i do
they have to go off the truth
and the
facts
and listed as such it's not the
first
time the state health
department has
come under fire for
reclassifying deaths
as covet fatalities
last month a cbs4 investigation
found
attending physicians at this
centennial
nursing home
ruled three deaths were not
related to
coronavirus
but since the residents had
tested
positive for covet 19
the state then listed them as
coronavirus deaths
there you go every day you
could have
one of these reports every
single day
but it's just
what every exactly since the
beginning
we've done one of these
there's just this is you don't
see
where's the other reports
in other words you know for the
word
under counting how right i
don't have
those
outrageous reports coming
constantly no
we can't have that
there'll be none of that uh i
put in the
show not doable
i put in the show notes a uh a
report
from bmj that that's a big deal
what
does bmj stand for
something medical journal what
is it the
bmj
british medical journal i think
it's uh
let me see bmj i think this is
bmj.com
let me see what is it
oh bnj yeah bmj.com oh the
leading yeah
there it is
they don't even expand the
acronym you
a-holes
the bmj is the something of
medical journal okay anyway
whatever it
is it's a real medical journal
real
medical report abstract this is
a cluster randomized trial of
cloth
masks compared with medical
masks
and the objective was to see if
there's
a difference what is good what
is not
good it's all marked up one of
our
producers actually was kind
enough to do
this conclusion
uh the study is the first of
cloth masks
and the results caution against
the use
of cloth
masks which is what we're all
using
because you know
we don't have enough disposable
medical
masks moisture retention
reuse of cloth masks and poor
filtration
may result in increased risk of
infection
it's right there in the bmj
so we are not getting good
information
this is what's frustrating this
is
what's driving people i think
nuts i have a one of our
producers works
in a store which is starting to
open up
and this is believe it or not a
store
with democrats
and uh i just listened to this
note that
has been written to the
managers of this
uh place managers i've been in
the store
for 90 seconds and two of the
first nine
people i walked past first
thing i'm not
wearing their face masks while
within
six feet of other staff and in
public
spaces
all uppercase now i am
disappointed in
what i thought was a team
of individuals who appreciated
an
employer that had as much
concern for
them as they do themselves
we spent the last month in net
losses as
a result of our selfless act of
closing the stores and paying
everyone
for for our week so that we can
do our
part
in trying to keep our staff and
their
families healthy safe as well as
mentally and emotionally secure
in very uncertain times all
caps still
that won't happen
we can't get our money back but
i damn
sure we'll take action to make
sure it
was not in vain
v-a-n-e misspelling we will do
absolutely everything in our
power to
prevent
sickness and the risk of having
to close
our doors again
blah blah blah let me be clear
in
writing so there's no
misunderstanding
i won't do the voice anymore
we're
wearing a face mask
wearing a face mask by
employees and sub
i just spit all over my screen
wearing a face mask by
employees and
subcontractors is a requirement
while conducting company
business at any
time and anywhere and while our
property
for any reason
following company protocol for
preventing covenant spread at a
rate of
100 percent is a requirement
the grounds are simple employees
terminated for being a clear
and present
danger to health safety and
well-being
of our team members and
customers by not
taking the measures required by
company
policy of wearing a face mask
to help
prevent the spread of overnight
pain
that's pretty serious where
would you
run into this little
screed one of our producers uh
who i'm
going to keep anonymous
uh works there and this was
sent to her
yeah it's really there's
that's why i'm saying who cares
let's
just go for it do it
get over it already so we can
just move
on because
we'll never get out of this
we'll never
ever get out of this by the way
the cdc
data which i have the link for
in the show notes couple of our
producers record this data
and uh and you know from week
to week
etc
and this producer said i went
to update
my spreadsheet notice that they
have
increased all of the uh 2019
2020 season numbers even though
most
weeks have been listed as 100
percent
reported before
increased total deaths by
literally
thousands per week even though
they said
in their own and we have the
proof their
own documents this is 100
counted or 100 reported and
then they
re they updated it and they
just added
thousands
to uh to several weeks what yeah
yeah the cdc is is not a a good
outfit
no it's been corrupt for years
now to go
back to your
uh your statement about this
not being
uh a requirement and not being
uh a law that we have to adhere
to
you're of course
absolutely right here's dr drew
who was
still i don't know if he's on
fouchy's
fear squad anymore or if he's
freewheeling but here's
his latest and let's remind
ourselves
the cdc
never recommended shutdown they
never
recommended
shutdown they recommended social
distancing and let's not
confuse social
distancing and shut down those
are two
very different things shutting
down
businesses isolating in place
those those are far-reaching
measures
beyond
mere social distancing so the
real
question is
was that necessary might there
have been
a more
rational intermediate step to
take close
some businesses
close some schools isolate
nursing homes
might that have been a more
sophisticated way to do this
and given that in california we
overshot
by somewhere between a
a factor of 10 and 50.
evidence we did suggest we did
a great
job and maybe we did too good a
job
depending
on how bad our economy is hit
oh brother so now i have
probably the
most frightening thing of the
day i'll
get it out of the way right away
thank you while we cannot while
we have
not been forced to shut down
we've been
compliant
very compliant human resources
doing as
we're told social engineering
and great
play we're being
shamed into compliance
and the ultimate question is
when a
vaccine comes around
how is that going to work now
um we'll
probably dive in later into the
this
rick bright character who keeps
coming
back who
was slated to be the guy
running the
program now the military
is going to do that we already
said i
think a couple weeks ago there
was going
to be
warp speed operation warp speed
was the
get the vaccine but
done and and and out and ready
for
distribution
by january of 2021 so when that
comes
out
um do we will we all have to
take it is
it going to be optional will
you take
the vaccine john
uh no nobody in the family is
taking
this vaccine and what if you
were forced
to take the vaccine
no that's not going to happen
here is a
constitutional lawyer alan
dershowitz
let's be very clear how we
break down
this issue
the city of new york the state
of new
york has the power to close a
park
based on their view that it
would be
helpful in defeating the
pandemic
absolutely no question about
that the
supreme court has case after
case after
case
saying that public health
justifies
closing down parks
closing down public areas the
next
question is does the governor
have
the right to do that governors
generally
are not authorized to make the
law
they're authorized to enforce
the law so
you'd have to look to see if
there were
legislative authority allowing
the
governor to close the park
if there is then it would be
legitimate
uh
let me put it very clearly you
have no
constitutional right
to endanger the public and
spread
a disease even if you disagree
you have
no right not to be vaccinated
you have no right not to wear a
mask and
if you refuse to be vaccinated
the state
has the power
to literally take you to a
doctor's
office
and plunge a needle into your
arm if the
vaccination
is designed to prevent the
spreading
disease if the vaccination
is only to prevent a disease
that you
will get for example if there's
a
disease that will kill you
you have the right to refuse
that but
you have no right to refuse
to be vaccinated against a
contagious
disease
public health the police power
of the
constitution gives the state
the power
to compel that
and there are cases in the
united states
supreme court
holy crap
i was not aware that that was a
constitutionally
somehow possible well i'd like
to hear
other interpretations
dershowitz has got one opinion
about a
lot of stuff right but we
typically
like what dershowitz has to say
can't
just because you disagree he
can't say
yeah you know but he's become a
bit of a
uh uh
arm uh s waiver recently i mean
he's
he d i mean he's what he's
saying is
probably true but i'm sure
there's
other ways of dealing with it
well this
is not going to happen we're
not going
to get a shot
do you remember h1n1 this wine
flew yeah
we're still waiting
still waiting for the video on
this show
we discussed oh there's gonna
be two
remember the whole
rigmarole is gonna have to be
two shots
you know maybe three and then
it could
come to one and then become
part of the
flu shot and there's all these
different
things
that's what that era when
people at uh
because i took pictures and put
in the
newsletter
where they were giving the
shots out in
albany they had
a line oh i remember that yes
yeah
opening a star wars
the public will line up for
this shot in
such a
to such a degree yeah that you
there's
not going to they're going to
force
anyone to get the shot because
there's
going to be
so many people getting the shot
they're
going to probably run out of it
yeah that's a good point that's
a good
point
don't line up but it'll be
lined up a
mile long
and as the president says do
you mean a
fully approved vaccine for
everyone the full public or a
partially
approved vaccine with emergency
use no
we're looking for a full
vaccine for
everyone
that wants to get it not
everybody's
going to want to get it there
you go
but we're looking at a full
vaccine is
that a correct statement yeah
will
issues yes synthetic so the
answer what
is the questioning we're
looking at a
full vaccine what is that like
a half
hey man i'll take the uh a
quarter a
quarterback
she was asking are you gonna
something
that's not quite fully approved
i understand i understand you
could have
a full vaccine is that a correct
statement yeah will
issues yes so the answer is the
answer
is yes we're working for a fully
approved vaccine but we'll also
use the
tools we have for instance
emergency use
authorization
um as as appropriate we use all
of our
regulatory tools to bring
vaccine
available for
the entire american population
by
january okay and then mr
president can
you just clarify
why are some of you wearing a
mask and
why are some of you not wearing
a mask
oh please we've all been tested
i've
been tested we've all been
tested and
we're
uh quite a distance away and
outdoor so uh i told them i
gave them
the option they could wear it
or not
so you can blame it on me but i
gave
them the option we could wear
it or not
so the president is there
saying kind of
what i'd like optional vaccine
optional masks and also
optional uh
open carry so rick bright
was the guy who was who has
traditionally for many years
he's been in and out of
government and
back to
the pharmaceutical industry
multiple
times and he is the guy that was
supposed to be
in charge of the vaccine this
is the
barda the biomedical advanced
research
and development authority
and this was unceremoniously
taken away
from him
as he was pushed out and now of
course
he's a whistleblower
so oh yeah we he has a job but
listen to
this guy's career
and you start to understand why
you
really don't want him
in the business of vaccines
in this case certainly as he
started
um well in atlanta georgia
vaccine
research center
98 to 2002 we worked at the cdc
in atlanta uh where he studied
influenza
a virus and the h5n1
from 2000 2003 he went to the
pharmaceutical
industry which is always great
when
you're in government and then
you go to
the private
industry and then you can
shepherd stuff
in so he went to
altea therapeutics is which is
also in atlanta and he was a
senior
research for their vaccine and
immuno immunology programs in
2003 he
went back to the cdc so only a
year that
he was in private business
and uh then he was still in
atlanta but
then he was focused on the
avian flu and he was there
until 2006
then 2006 to 2008 he went to
nova vaxx like the number one
penny
stock of
vaccine bull crap on the stock
market
during that time
he participated in world health
organization committees on
vaccine
development and pandemic
preparedness
and then in 2008 he worked at
the bill
and melinda gates foundation
and then in 2010 he came back
to the
department of health and human
services so the guy
is way too in entrenched in
in the pharmaceutical business
i don't
think you want this guy
running the show and the fact
that he's
so pissed off about it and so
angry that
he's become a whistleblower
i think tells us i'm sorry god
i think that tells us that you
know this
was not the way it's supposed
to go this
is
we are going to learn
eventually so much
about
the pharmaceutical and medical
industry
and all the egos and all the
money that
takes place
and it's going it's going to
blow us
away
because the scandal and the
bull crap on
the money is
ten times bigger than than than
movies
especially
today this is rick bright
testifying
because of course we got to
testify
today the world is confronting
a public
health emergency unlike any
we've seen
in over a century
we are facing a highly
transmissible and
deadly virus which not only
claims lives
but also disrupts the very
foundations
of our society
the american health care system
is being
taxed to the limit
our economy is spiraling
downward and
our population is being
paralyzed by
fear
stemming from a lack of a
coordinated
response
and a dearth of accurate clear
communication
about the path forward
americans yearn
to get back to work
to open their businesses and to
provide
for their families
i get that however what we do
must be done what is he like in
charge
so he gets he sounds like he's
the
premier of canada
get back to work to open their
businesses and to provide for
their
families
i get that yeah but this is the
this is the attitude of these
people i
am king
however what we do must be done
carefully
with guidance from the best
scientific
minds
our window of opportunity is
closing if
we fail to improve our response
now
based on science i fear the
pandemic
will get worse and be prolonged
yeah
this is my favorite part is now
we're
bringing it all back around to
science
and trust the scientists
because the republicans in
particular
don't believe in science
there will be likely a
resurgence of
cobit 19 this fall
it'll be greatly compounded by
the
challenges of seasonal influenza
without better planning 2020
could be
the darkest
these guys this goes on with
biden too
where's the science where's the
science
that says it's going to
recur in uh in the fall of 2020
oh well
there's no specifically what
science no
he's talking about science
science
science specifically name
something what
study do they know for a fact
that this
thing's not falling apart
i mean is there any evidence
whatsoever
this is all
speculative without better
planning
2020 could be the darkest
winter in
modern history
first and foremost i love could
be the
darkest winter in modern history
have you heard of the hunger
winter
a-hole without better planning
2020 could be the darkest
winter in
modern history
first and foremost we need to be
truthful with the american
people
americans deserve the truth the
truth
must be based on science
we have the world's greatest
scientists
now the truth must be based on
science
there's a very interesting
phrase and i
think we're going to hear this
a lot
more
because there's really only
truth in one
thing and that's mathematics
and what they're showing us is
mathematics and there's no
truth in it
you know what i'm saying
science is is
not always truth in fact it's
kind of
never truth but we've been
through this
with global warming
and the green new deal and
climate
change and
is just coming back and please
ignore
the math that we showed you
that was all
wrong trust in science people
americans deserve the truth the
truth
must be based on science
we have the world's greatest
scientists
let us lead
let us speak without fear of
retribution
there you go john let us lead
let us
lead
they want to give the power to
the
scientists to let them lead you
we must listen each of us can
and must
do our part now
on tuesday dr fauci delivered a
message
and a voice that is clear and
trustworthy
has encouraged us to act with
caution as
we return to our daily lives
we should listen to him and
other
scientists sharing their
expertise
yeah it's so bad that to push
the
science and believe the signs
truth is in science cnn did a
special
sanjay gupta anderson pooper
bring it in
to that i have to play a couple
of
things because because
bright's testimony was a fiasco
and it
was a disaster
and uh i want to play two
things that
preluded this little
this spiel which everybody
clipped about
oh we're gonna have this dark
winter and
all the rest of it let's listen
to how
this thing actually began
this is the pro bright testimony
confusion
okay hold on here we go five
minutes for
an opening statement
well you don't think it's
resolved well
are we going to ask if
he wants to be represented by
council
and then who the council is
dr bride do you wish to be
represented
by council
yes okay and then
could she identify herself for
the
record and for the
record would uh council please
state
your name
my name is debra katz i'm an
attorney
representing dr rick wright
with the law firm of cats
marshall and
banks all right thank you
i think that's all we needed to
do good
parliament
all right well the chairman is
recognized for
his father you've got a
parliamentary
parliamentary question i'm glad
you got
this john this is very good
it's president so gentleman
state is
parliamentary
yeah it will the witness be
under oath
because if you have a witness
whistleblower testimony under o
and i a
witness would normally be under
oath and
if not today
he's under oath not under oath
then if
we get into whistleblower
allegations
how can we
be sure that the witness is
telling the
truth uh uh
under under oath if they're not
under
oath and if they're not under
oath
then how can you talk about the
whistleblower complaints
i think that's in a fair and
equitable
manner
i i thank the gentleman for his
inquiry
all witnesses know that it is
illegal
uh to lie to congress and in
our subcommittee unlike o and i
uh they are the only
subcommittee that
i mean it's a practice um it's
true it's
a tradition
uh but we don't swear people in
uh
but witnesses know that um it is
illegal to lie to congress usc
1003 or something i believe
thank you
now a couple of things one this
is anna
eshoo that's that's heading this
subcommittee and she doesn't
know what
she's doing
and and so the republican guy
has to
tell her how to do things
properly and
they have to walk through a
bunch of
things
but this lying to congress
thing i
didn't realize and apparently
there is
some us code
so what about james clapper oh
that
doesn't count
the thing is that we're living
in a
world of calling out hypocrisy
and
that's all anyone does all the
time
and and it's it's it has no
it's no benefit it doesn't go
anywhere
it hasn't gone anywhere so far
so let's get to part two this
is another
uh that now the uh
uh the head republican whose
name i
wrote on that back of an
envelope i got
it back there he's from oregon
he's a congressman he's very
good by the
way this guy
and i'll get his uh go get the
envelope
but
uh now this is the beginning of
the
the kind of the true confusion
and the
hook and this makes the whole
thing a
a joke and a fiasco and in fact
and they
brought up this lawyer he wants
to be
represented by
council he says yeah i want to
be
represented by council she says
absolutely nothing the whole
time he
never once
asks her a question so that
she's just
up there as a joke
and so this part of it makes it
even
more of a joke this is uh
uh representative walden i
believe
walden
walden greg walden from uh he's
quite
good quite good
we have asked for and this
committee
should hold hearings to find a
path
forward to reform the strategic
national
stockpile
to increase domestic
manufacturing of
critical supplies and
disentangle our
supply chains from china
we should be exploring
strategies for
increased testing so we can
begin to
safely reopen our economy
we need to find ways to improve
access
to mental health and provide
relief
both for our health care
providers on
the front lines treating covet
19 cases
and our health care workers who
have
been furloughed because their
hospitals
are closed
we should be conducting rigorous
oversight of the trillions of
dollars
myriad new policies congress has
appropriated and enacted in the
last
three months and we should be
investigating
really investigating
allegations like dr
bright's that raised concern
that our about our nation's
coronavirus
response
that does not appear to be why
we're
actually here today and frankly
it
saddens me dr bright
your allegations are serious
they
deserve a real investigation
i know the office of special
accounts
with whom you filed your
complaint will
do just that
and i know they take their work
seriously and we'll hear you
out and
importantly
we'll give those named in your
complaint
an opportunity to have their
side heard
as well
i must tell you that many of us
on our
committee were confused when we
learned
from a tweet this hearing was
scheduled
in the wake of your
complaint as you know that's
certainly
not how we do things at the
energy and
commerce committee
not long after the notice of
this being
a whistleblower hearing we were
advised
you were
here as a government witness
not a
whistleblower but then we were
told you
were not representing
the government but yourself the
hearing
title suggests the hearings
about
protecting scientific integrity
yet the chair invited a witness
who will
not be speaking to that issue
so it's all pretty confusing
and unusual
to say the least
here we are in the middle of a
pandemic
and we aren't given time to
secure our
witnesses conduct appropriate
research
or require documents
that could aid in our
understanding of
the situation you face in the
country
face
so the whole thing is a sham
of course it is it was set up
so bright
can go up there and say
something
present and lie and do whatever
he wants
he didn't have to
do whatever he wants but the
joke is he
didn't do a very good job of
any of it
except that one clear one you
played
which is pretty much what
everyone
played
so that was a i consider the
whole thing
an epic fail
well i was being honest about
it yeah
but going back like
the push now and that's really
wanting
to want to prove with that clip
the push is for uh
truth science is truth that's
the push
and that's
and let the scientists leave we
kind of
heard that but now he's
this this guy he's the pied
piper and
he's supposed to say the things
everyone's going to repeat and
you'll
hear
well as dr bright said you know
you're
going to hear that i don't
think so
so we had the big uh rhona
special on
cnn with anderson pooper
and sanjay gupta and there she
is the
expert when it comes to science
all
things science the
uh ever so idealistic gratitude
i've seen you talk about online
too is
just how important it is to
listen to experts and listen to
science
and this is a time
when you know i was not a very
good
science student um
when i was in school but this
is a time
it seems
that you know the global
scientific
community
is so critically important and
we're
really seeing just how
important it is
to to follow science yes yes
exactly and
and i hope that is she a phd
oh oh yes listen to her message
she'll
do 50 seconds of the same thing
we can see now that the
scientific
community are stepping up
and they are they are speaking
out more
than they have
they're done before you know i
gotta
tell you for a 16 year old
swedish girl
the term
stepping up like the scientists
are
stepping up is an
odd thing for her to be using
just in my
opinion you know you
i don't know is that how kids
talk about
that
oh the swedes that's all they
talk about
stepping up
yes yes exactly and and i hope
that
we can see now the the
scientific
community are stepping up
and they are they are speaking
out more
than they have
they're done before because
obviously
this is a crisis that would
require the
scientific community to speak up
and um and i hope that people
really
it feels like uh science is
getting
the role of science is is
changing now
it's becoming more
people are starting to realize
that we
are actually depending on
science and
that we need to listen to
scientists
and experts and i i really hope
that we
that that stays and that's that
also
um is is for for other crises
such as
the climate crisis and the
environmental
crisis
that we actually understand
that we have
to listen to to
the scientists
don't you think that the
climate folk
uh are freaked out about this
whole
situation because they've been
talking about being put on the
back
burner they've been taken off
the stove
yeah they're back in the pantry
where
they belong
yeah i think so that's why it's
important to have greta back on
the
scene so she can maintain her
profile
people forget pretty quickly
but i'll tell you okay we have
anderson
cooper
like you said the big three
there was
anderson cooper who
immediately says he was not he
was a
lousy student
and he didn't get flunked
science so
he's an idiot
and so then you get greta tune
barry
who's who
it was a kid she's just a kid
let's face
reality
and then you have a the md a
doctor yeah
but
it was only just a panel doogie
houser
was only just as a kid as well
you know
it's like these kids can be
very smart
they can be geniuses
remember who you're talking to
your
average cnn viewer
they're cnn viewers which is a
small
group of people let's face it
it's under a million generally
speaking
uh is uh we probably have a
bigger
audience
probably is the dumbest
audience that
watches television and thinks
they're
keeping up
because you have to you have to
imagine
you think you're keeping up
because it's
all about news news news news
oh no opinion opinion opinions
it's all
about opinion
the central intelligence
broadcast
system
i think really did a good job
in uh
pitting the two main people
that it's
all about who's going to lead
us that's
that's what it's coming down to
this
week i haven't seen the sunday
shows but
i'm sure it's part of it
who is going to lead us trump
the
president
or fauci the god president trump
continues to push the country
to quickly bounce back and says
he does
not consider that happening
without reopening schools
claiming the
virus has had very little
impact on young people but
you're right
his own top health experts
disagree lucky wants to play
all sides
of the
equation president trump pushed
back
against the warning dr anthony
fauci
delivered at a senate hearing
the day
before
there is a real risk that you
will
trigger an outbreak
that you may not be able to
control we
don't know everything about
this virus
and we really better be very
careful
particularly when it comes to
children
just to interrupt i'm a little
tired of
we don't know very much about
this virus
why not i mean if you've been
studying
this for
40 years it's similar to other
sars
virus
i'm i don't feel very
comfortable
hearing we don't know we don't
know we
don't know but then
telling me it's gonna be the
worst
winter in
history this is uh very
contradictory
very careful particularly when
it comes
to children i was surprised by
his
answer actually uh
because you know
it's just to me it's not an
acceptable
answer
especially when it comes to
schools but
a new cbs news poll finds that
most
americans trust dr
fauci though his unfavorable
rating
among conservatives has
increased since april the
country needs
guidance
of the nation's best medical and
scientific experts
these literally are matters of
life and
of death
as democrats demand more
guidance from
the federal government
today the administration's
former top
vaccine researcher rick bright
will testify before house
committee that
if the response is not
ramped up 2020 will be the
darkest
winter in modern history
i think cbs does a good job of
wrapping
up the messaging that they want
trump bad fouchy good
it's the exact same messaging
that pbs
is using
the obs has been going to they
had
shields and brooks on and they
went on
and on
well let's hear it let's hear
it i want
to hear it i want to hear what
you got
well we got a few things here i
got a
lot of stuff i'm biting but if
you know well biden will come
let's
finish up the rona let's do uh
shields and brooks on pbs
research notes
uh and it reveals that joe
biden is a
very transparent person the
the culture they describe is
certainly
the culture i knew when i was
covering senator biden go to
go to uh shields on reopening
seas
battle pbs
president and he said it again
today uh
we need to move ahead
uh whether we're ready or not
on the you
know in the direction of
opening up
yes he did judy and the
president proves
once again
he's not actually strategic or
tactical
in his political
uh fights that he engages in uh
he's
he's visceral
uh he's instinctive he went out
you
should always if you're going
after
somebody politically stop go
somebody
we're gonna have to start this
over
because you gotta listen to
what he
did she she says trump wants to
go ahead
and reopen the country
and he this is like this
messaging that
you just brought up on cbs and
it's also
being played
out on pbs and elsewhere it's
as though
the
the overlying talking points
the message
of something else
sneaks in as a as a given
conversations that where it
shouldn't so
she's asking them to
the president wants to reopen
the
country and his response is
he doesn't know how to pick his
battles
he's not strategic
wait a minute he wants to
reopen the
country is not a battle
who's a battle with who well we
know
it's assumed they already know
what the
battle is it's a battle between
fauci
and trump because they want to
lower
trump's numbers
he put somebody else you know
that
called the shots and helped
continue
ruin the country
and so the world not just the
country
the world yeah the world the
world yeah
the one world world government
will take
care of that although although
every
country has their own fauci
yes every country has their own
fauci
yeah
all connected own saucy got got
pictures
of fauci on the background on
their desk
man
they're all fouchy's disciples
disciples
the pope disciples
so you have this so we played
again this
clip now that we have that yeah
you want
to play it over here with it in
mind
that what she says and what he
jumps in
with is
discrepant president and he
said it
again today
uh we need to move ahead uh
whether
we're ready or not on
the you know in the direction
of opening
up yes he did judy and
the president proves once again
he's not
actually strategic or tactical
in his
political
uh fights that he engages in uh
he's
visceral uh
he's instinctive he went out
you should
always if you're going after
somebody
politically
go after somebody who's a lot
weaker
than you are politically or
less popular
i mean democrats won five
consecutive
presidential elections
running against uh herbert
hoover uh
because of their the depression
and
unpopular as the republican
president
but he picked anthony fauci dr
fauci uh
david mentioned it's been been
there
since the reagan years
but not only that when in a
presidential
debate when george
h.w bush was asked to cite a
contemporary american hero
he cited dr anthony fauci
what a hero not anymore in my
book
and now remember the in order
to get
back to work
it really is about nine things
testing
testing testing
tracing tracing tracing
isolation
isolation isolation so we got
to test
you we've got to trace you
we've got to
isolate you
and i have been identifying
along with
some of our no agenda
lab personnel that the antibody
tests are increasingly
difficult to put
together
the the material they're
receiving from
i'm not sure where it comes
from i think
some of it if not all from china
seems to be faulty uh not the
same
results
and this is the this is what
certainly
the um
a lot of people want and and
feel is
necessary to go back to work is
we have
to test for the antibodies
and obviously the leading group
on the test for antibodies is
run by who
else could it be
the gates foundation it's not
really run
by them but
they're a major funder of this
group and
the fba has stepped in
the food and drug
administration halted
a coronavirus testing program
promoted
by billionaire bill gates and
seattle
health officials pending reviews
the program sought to send test
kits to
the home of people both healthy
and sick
to try to bring the country to
the level
of testing officials say is
necessary
before states can begin safely
reopening
the program which has already
gone
through thousands of tests
found dozens
of cases that had previously
been
undiagnosed
the seattle coronavirus
assessment
network said on its website
that the fda
has asked it to pause testing
while it
receives additional
authorizations but
maintained its procedures are
safe
the story is so underplayed
that you
can't even get a clip you have
to get a
computer voice
reading the copy you know it's
from
money that computer voice
sounds like another one of
these online
commentators bill still
oh yeah really i had to put i
had to cut
it to put pauses in to make the
transition
natural and so bad but that's
how how
under-reported this is nobody
nobody wants to really let you
know that
it's failing
meanwhile without a doubt
science-based
new york has some great ideas
for
getting back to work
and new york has problems but
they do want people to at least
go back
and play some tennis
every player unless they're
from the
same household has to bring
their own
tennis balls
so that you don't touch other
people's
tennis balls
with your hands you can kick
their balls
but you can't
touch them okay is that iso
worthy
you can kick their balls but
you can't
touch them
it gets it gets it gets better
because
she recognizes what she's doing
and
this is our humorous moment of
the show
with your hands you can kick
their balls
but you can't touch them
i'm gonna blush sorry um of
course if
you're
if you're playing with someone
in your
household you can't touch those
tennis
balls
uh to avoid convince to avoid
confusion
between
who's
i give her high marks for that
hi marx
i love it that everyone's
cracking up we
just needed that moment of like
oh okay
okay okay okay i feel so much
better now
you have to number the balls
like they
do you got a number
and the ball boys they can't be
grabbing
everybody's balls they only can
only get
the
balls on their side of the of
their from
their team
you can only touch your team's
balls it
goes on forever obviously you
can have a
lot of fun with this
i have since it's uh
also being um obfuscated
i have an update from a new
york city
nursing home
where a good half of all of new
york's
city patients
died uh would you like to hear
this from
a dude named
ben who works in i.t from yeah
i love
the uh yeah yeah so the the
what we've been discussing and
what is
death mill
what is on our radar is the
fact that
the governor signed a number of
orders
which really put sick people
back into
the
uh nursing homes without proper
separation without
not all of them but really
unprepared
and that infected
a lot of people and killed a
lot of
people and he
doesn't want to own up to it i
don't
think he will
uh i think i'm not blaming him
specifically shit happens in an
emergency this is not a good one
but uh you know i don't want to
be
to talk about the hypocritical
nature of
it obviously we know if this was
a republican who had done it
the media
would have been talking about it
but even even fox news isn't
really
talking about this no one wants
to know
so here's our report boots on
the ground
dude named ben that's not
really his
name but a
dude named ben who works in i.t
for a
large new york city nursing
home a few
facts about how
our governor cuomo has handled
this
vulnerable population
from the beginning we were told
by the
government and new york state
department
of health
that we cannot test staff and
residents
as there is not enough testing
supplies
and hospitals are more important
that's mistake number one the
only way
we could test a patient was to
transfer
them to the hospital then they
were
tested
the only way we could test
staff is to
have them go to their private
doctor
get them to call the state
testing
hotline and if symptomatic
get an appointment for a
testing center
therefore there was a very low
death
rate reported by nursing homes
since
they couldn't test
and therefore could not confirm
the
deaths were coveted 19 related
then cuomo ordered all nursing
homes to
accept kovid 19
positive discharges that's
people from
the hospital
most nursing homes are
unprepared for
this do not have sufficient
ppe or staff ignore the ability
to
isolate
we partnered at that time with
a large
new york city hospital system
created a
dedicated covet 19 recovery
unit and
gladly accepted positive
patience
patience once we put in place
the
appropriate infection control
procedures
and received sufficient ppe
from our
hospital partner
then cuomo woke up and realized
many
nursing homes were not equipped
to
handle covet 19 positive
patients and
the death count went up and
issued
another executive order
for bidding nursing homes from
accepting
covet 19 positive patients
they will surely back up
hospitals and
create an artificial surge
then cuomo mandated this is
crazy that
all nursing home patients and
staff be
tested
we had a team of 20 from the
department
of health here this week tested
all
residents and staff over four
days we
now have to put a plan
in place by five by may 20th
how we're
going to continue to test staff
twice a week even though there
are not
enough testing supplies lab
capacity
logistical ability
nurses and doctors to swab and
cost of
millions of dollars per month
per
facility will become a financial
hardship
if we don't have a plan we risk
losing
our license and i really don't
look
forward to having my brain
poked an
additional two times per week
going
forward
you two are so spot on in much
of your
analysis thank you for
do to spread the truth
analyzing tissue
stay safe keep your six foot
social
distance figure out how to wear
a
mastering haircuts thank you
so again cuomo certainly but i
think in
general
doesn't care about the elderly
doesn't
care about old people cares
about the
hospital
and the money that they can
make i'm
just going to say that
in the state and getting a
bailout he he
does not like did not
care for the actual people who
needed
um no he's about the money yes
and it's it's disturbing
when you raise this disturbing
and so
far he's like worshipped
along with fauci by the
democrats and
especially the
the ones that kind of hope bite
and put
moves aside so cuomo could take
over you
know we've already
shown on this show that that's
not even
a possibility because
cuomo's commentary where he says
america's never been a great
country
which is all you have to do is
just keep
playing that audio forever and
then
he's never going to get a vote
it's the
dumbest thing anyone could ever
say
yeah so as a politician i mean
people
can say it
right but but it's just
politicians all
of it is just
it's so sad and you were
arguing about
the wrong
things no one and the media of
course
has not been your friend for
a long long time but it's just
gotten so
bad
very bad a lot of people get
notes from
is saying that the media
i mean the media has been bad
for a long
time and we've documented for
the last
10 years and then
as we go back in history and go
back to
the gulf of tonkin and those
other
things that took place in the
media
philip
fell off the of the side uh
the media's never been any good
well
and that was it was interesting
i was
talking to the keeper about uh
the
church um
commission uh
i think she said it it has it
always it
always been like uh
you know this indoctrination
into the
media i said yeah in 75 there
was a big
a big hearing the church
commission and
you know the cia sat there
saying yeah
yeah we
yeah we have people uh on staff
or who
who send in
stories to reporters in the
printed
press and then the question
came in
well do you have anybody at a
major
television news network well
that had to
be discussed in private setting
yeah and the same for anyone at
the new
york times well
we think we should discuss that
in
private settings so yes and if
you think
it went away
it did not so why would it
no it's a good mechanism it
works well
for them but
unfortunately we're a lot of
people are
welcome we're sucked into public
suffrage
remember the the pennsylvania
secretary
of health that we discussed and
that
you had questions about the
secretary's
appearance
have you ever seen the
appearance of the
of the health secretary from
los angeles
well let's stick with
pennsylvania for a
second yeah go on
um so you were uh your hunch
was correct
we didn't know much about uh
the secretary of the
transsexual woman
they're transsexual
exactly trans woman well uh the
guy
there's a guy there was a guy
who's not
you
uh who pretty much pretty much
got
cancelled
because he too made fun of uh
the health secretary of
pennsylvania and
uh here's a little story about
it
robert portagalo is the owners
of
peppers and at here in braddock
super popular restaurant in our
region
but portogallo is coming under
fire
for recent facebook comments
that he
posted on his personal page
comments that some say are
transphobic
these are the facebook posts
that robert
portagalo shared on his page
now what's interesting is what
you see
is a picture of
him with the wig on and looking
like uh
and then you see a picture of
the uh the
secretary of health
next to each other above that
which i
think was
funny and the actual joke not
this is
not a trans joke
was a picture of uh of wayne
from
wayne's world
with the stupid glasses looks
exactly
like the
uh the secretary of health so i
think he
was he was saying oh you look
like
wayne from waves at birth yeah
tagging
his restaurant peppers and at
in one of the posts portogallo
is
wearing a wig glasses and pearls
appearing to mimic the look of
pennsylvania's secretary of
health
dr rachel levine oh what an
outrage who
is a transgender
woman another post shows
portogallo
appearing to impersonate dr
levine
holding a news conference
around rolls
of toilet paper with the caption
now we know who hoarded all the
toilet
paper while puerto gallo says
his
intent was to be funny members
of the
lgbtq community
aren't laughing you should see
this
video this
this spokesperson or i'm sorry
member of
the lgbt community
is wearing a rainbow mask uh
pink flags
you know and it's weird to hear
this
person
see the person talking with the
mask
over their face she's done
nothing but
be a wonderful compassionate
leader in
guiding the commonwealth
and making sure they stay safe
christine
bryan is with the delta
foundation of
pittsburgh whose mission is to
fight for
the lgbtq community
i know there's a lot of people
that
didn't realize that she was a
member of
the transgender community and
truthfully
it doesn't matter
yeah she's a human being just
like
everybody else with an
extensive resume
that um is so impressive so
impressive
but listen
shut up there was not an lgbt
joke it
was about
wayne's world and it was humor
we can't
have humor
you said by the way
is it battle x whether it's a
transgender battle axe an
old woman yeah or even an old
man
doesn't matter but no
let's let's immediately take it
into all
and by the way it's okay to
make fun of
the president and his orange
hair
orange man bad that's okay but
oh no
oh no this immediately has to
be taken
into lgbtq shut up
so annoying
yes uh the appearance uh bigotry
needs to be consistent in uh in
texas
you can mock the president for
being
orange
uh or a clown or whatever you
want to
call him uh
let it be you're open it's open
game
it's open so you can go after
anybody
you'd think
you'd think but no uh
see yes so the final things i
have is
what's going on locally here in
texas as
um you know there's a lot of
pushback
from people who want to open up
and you know there's uh what
we're
seeing now across the country
is some of the more rigorous
mayors and
or government more mayors than
anything
but governors as well
they will take away your
license so you
can't operate
you know doing anything to
shame you or
thwart you from
conducting your business
legally which
you know
it's legal is this is not a
violation of
law it's a violation of some
kind of
social standards that we're now
tied into so in texas we have
the
traveling economic militias
and this is this is new
these guys are going all over
texas
and they are protecting
businesses
that want to open up and they
stand in
front with their rifles
and of course all kinds of
intimidating
looking gear and you know what
businesses are open and that i
think is
sad that it has to go that way
i like it i'd like to think
it's great
that it has to go that way
and perfectly and you know i
would
participate in in that if
if someone was having problems
i'd jump
right in and stand there no
one's gonna
this is why we have guns
when this type of situation
appears
let's look at a country
that just took away their guns
in new
zealand
and let's see what kind of
powers
they've given to their prime
minister
this bill enables the police to
enter a
home
without a warrant madam speaker
the
police have never
held that power at all
they have never held that power
and this
bill
this bill enables police just on
reasonable cause
to enter in to your home
sweet it's just like the good
old
king king uh george the third
they used
to
put all the houses too that's
why they
put in the bill of rights when
we we
told them to sod off yeah
good times over there yeah
new zealand's a wreck the place
is a
mess i want to play the one
closer
excuse me
i mean i do have some i have to
round
the world tour which has got
some good
stuff but i had to get this out
of the
way
before we go to the break which
is the
uh
something that doesn't get a
lot of play
i just looked into it seems to
be true
it seems to be an
accurate report it's not a joke
it's not
the the sakura the bee
or whatever that that thing is
the new
uh onion
the soccer lab report what what
is it
the b the b
the babylon b the babylon b the
p4
sorry what sorry go go the p4
lab at the
wuhan institute
of virology has come under
scrutiny as a
potential source of the virus
according to an nbc report a
hazardous
event
may have happened at the lab in
october
last year
three people familiar with the
matter
told nbc that u.s intelligence
agencies
are reviewing an
unofficial report on cell phone
location
data the report found there was
no cell
phone activity around the high
security
part of the p4 lab
between october 7th and 24th
last year
the report suggests there may
have been
a hazardous event
there sometime between october
6th and
11th
that required the lab to be
closed
during that time
the report talks about images
from
october 14th to 19
last year showing no outbound
traffic
from the lab
it's suspected a roadblock was
set up to
prevent cars and people
coming and going this is in
contrast to
satellite images from august to
october
which show a lot of activity
the next
instance of activity was on
october 25th
u.s senator tom cotton also
spoke about
the data in an interview with
fox news
cotton said normally thousands
of mobile
phones are in use around this
area
wuhan has about the same
population
density as new york
he adds the sudden drop in cell
phone
usage is likely an indicator of
when the
virus first began spreading
he said we could get to the
bottom of it
a lot faster if the chinese
regime was
more transparent
us intelligence officials say
the
evidence is not enough on its
own
they are still investigating
now where
did this report come from
this came from a news operation
called
ntd
which is chinese operation uh
an ntd
center new
tang dynasty and it turns out
that these
are the same
group that comes out of the uh
like the
epoch the epoch times uh right
right
right right right right same
operation
yeah that's uh they they hate
the
chinese
obviously they hate the chinese
was
falun gong yeah that's falun
gong or
banned in china and it was uh
and i will
be writing an essay
about this because the following
phenomenon is quite interesting
this
operation only began in the 90s
there was a uh a moment there
was a
moment in history where this uh
there's all these different
movement
practices in china
and uh chi gong it was one of
them that
goes back i think three or three
thousand years at least and it
became
for some unknown reason
a super popular again it began
its
popularity began in the 50s and
then it
got
incredibly popular in the 90s
and it's
like tai chi
chi gong there's a bunch of
these are
all interconnected and gong
also this is
like
kung so kung fu all these
different
movement
uh ideologies are part of
chinese
culture
and in the mid 90s this qi gong
is
extremely popular and they in an
offshoot called
fallon gong came up and became
so popular so quickly that it
garnered
like 70 million followers
within a
couple of years
and by the end of the same
decade it was
banned in china because it was
seen as
dangerous
yeah and then ever since then
it's been
this this blood feud between
these uh
these people in the chinese
communist
party
i'm glad you uh you went into
that and
and whenever i see
you know the epoch times i bear
that in
mind they have an agenda but i
think a
lot of people don't even know
this don't
even know that
it's epoch times and what else
what's
the other online thing well
this one
here is ntdd there's a new
service
there's also something else
called
happy morning or something
they're doing
happy endings
this ntd stands for new tang
dynasty
oh and the tang dynasty is
interesting
because that's the one that
took place
between about 600 and 900
uh very early and or early in
modern
chinese history
and that there was a 300 year
reign with
a with a hole in the middle of
it where the evil empress woo
oh we ruled that little era it
was the
only full uh
empress in the history of china
that
actually had total complete
power
that was and she was evil she
was a
whore apparently who somehow
got into
government
and which does happen now was
that
before before the wu-tan clang
or uh
a little bit before just before
the clan
all right whoo little chinese
system
a little bit of history for
everybody
the stuff this stuff has its
implications and this
these uh these falun gong guys
have got
some very serious this is a good
journalism they've
been producing to be honest
about it i
mean i know it's slanted too
but it's
pretty well done well all news
is
slanted but you still have to
pick out
what you can as long as you
know what's
going on
this story about the lab
getting shut
down which has been debunked
of course having something to
do with it
is uh not being played by
anybody and
and it apparently nbc did have
the story
but they kind of they got
crushed
so what is your takeaway with
that then
the still the
virus came from the chinese lab
i think
just like the french guy the
french
nobel prize winner in medicine
who
discovered the aids virus
is the guy who's i think is
right and
they all call it everyone calls
them a
crackpot
and now yes now they do it's
like got
his nobel prize he's got his
his chops yet he's a crackpot
this is
happening
yeah this is happening
everywhere in the
netherlands
there's a very famous
statistician and
pollster his name is maurice
duhont
and that translates
interestingly to
maurice the dog
that is that is literally his
name and
maurice
he's probably he's got 10 years
on me
i've i've worked with him in
the past
but he's very famous he's the
guy that
whenever there's elections he's
everywhere on television
he tells he shows everybody the
charts
the numbers he's got it all
down he's
very good at
understanding data and he's
been doing
it since i was a child
almost in the country watching
him he
has been
shut out entirely banned from
all
mainstream
and he's now appearing on
podcasts and
i'm actually
considering because he speaks
perfect
english i'm i'm uh considering
doing an interview with him
because it's
easy to get right now
and and it's because he said
look uh
the way you're collecting the
data is
shoddy you have completely
incorrect data the numbers are
no good
your models are no good goodbye
maurice the dog so it happens
it's happening everywhere
france has got
that crackpot get rid of him
maurice de jong i think his
career is
over not that he you know he
has i'm
sure he's plenty of money
but it's it's odd to see the
guy that i
grew up watching is the
authority on
data and statistics and numbers
to be
completely shut out because he
had a
different opinion
my man is cancelled
now before i started off as a
podcaster
you don't have this problem
that's right
before we take a break we do
have a very
important public service
announcement
that is something i'd like you
all to
listen to
very carefully in the morning
no agenda
producers
when writing the no agenda show
we know
you all want to refer to your
significant others
as smoking hot when everyone
uses the
same term to describe their
lover it can get quite
repetitive so
when writing the no agenda show
please
consider
using an alternative term such
as
alluring
angelic arm candy attractive
arousing
banging beautiful bit of crumpet
bombshell bomb diggity breezy
cute cutie
cutie pie cookie
cupcake charming chiquita banana
dazzling dime piece
delicious dollface dreamboat
enchantress
foxy glamorous gorgeous
good-looking head-turning
hottie hot
sexy mama knockout lovely
magnificent
perfect ten
ravishing sensuous sexy sex
kitten or
crafty cougar
smashing stunning sensational
stone cold
foxy titillating tremendous
twinkie-licious vivacious yummy
or
simply
wonderful the no agenda show
appreciates
your cooperation and compliance
through
these difficult times
if your significant other
doesn't like
the description you use
be sure to tell them to relax
while you
hit them in the mouth
and with that i'd like to thank
you for
your courage say in the morning
to you
the man who put the sea in
crafty cougar
john
any more to you mr adam curry
also in
the morning all ships of sea
boots on
the ground
feet in the air subs in the
water and
all the dames and nights out
there by
the way was that uh darren
o'neill
the one and only well i could
recognize
his voice i just as i was
listening to
that
yeah i'm just a message to
darren a
little
little positive feeling he's the
director yes feedback he is he
is
one inch away from being able
to do a
perfect rush limbaugh
well i hear the slots opening
up soon
whoa sorry bad dj joke is what
it does
yeah darren is it well he gets
enough
practice
he just needs to drop it down a
little
bit slow down i mean i know
exactly what
what i mean he's he's already
got the
tones
he's got the tonal qualities he
just
needs
and he has to say stuff like
ditto heads
yeah if he does that or mega
dudos i
don't even he does that
anymore but yeah darren o'neill
thank
you very much and i have to say
in the
morning to our trolls there in
the in
the troll room
there's uh over 1900 of them
did a quick
troll count
thank you all for showing up
and for
showing your enthusiasm
and helping and weighing in
with your
comments which are
often not suitable for air but
we do
appreciate it no
agendastream.com is
where
all of that partying takes
place we do
the show live on
thursdays and sundays you're
welcome to
go in there listen live troll
around
chat around
uh there are people who stay
logged in
for months on end never leave
it's just
part of their life
that's it oh yeah oh yeah no
agendastream.com and also
when you're there hit someone
up for an
invite for no agendasocial.com
it is our little node on the
federated
uh social network the future
of social networking and we're
there
nice and early and get in on
the ground
floor just follow me adam no
agendasocial.com and uh
john c david is it john c
devorak at
nodejuntosocial.com
is that your handle there i
think so i
think so
i think so i don't know you do
log
in from time to time that's why
i don't
know because they you know yeah
you just
logged in
i understand exactly uh then
i'd like to
say in the morning to uh the
artist who
brought us the artwork
for episode number were we
1242. let me
bring up our little show notes
page here
this art well the title of the
show was
smoking hot
this art done by nick the rat
really
moved people's emotions and
when art
does that
it's genius he had the handcuffs
the two arms with the handcuffs
and the
mask in the middle of the
handcuffs as
if you're being shackled by the
mask
it was a dynamite piece there
was no
question i think that this
and people responded to it
it was an excellent uh piece of
symbolic
art
and we had there was a a lot of
pieces a
lot
yeah we got a lot of pieces for
some
reason like a lot and uh
and i would say a special uh
commendation to comic strip
blogger
uh who did his rendition of the
national
uh
black journalists association
if you
recall it's the
he oh yes yeah right if you
want to see
it go look at
he does these everyone saw it
just
well i appreciate he did it
because he
knew they had no way of getting
this
art picked but oh man
it it certainly gave me joy so
thank you
for that csb but above
all thank you nick the rat when
nick
comes in and does it he does it
right
no agenda artgenerator.com
please go
have a look at all of the
fantastic
different submissions and if
you want to
you can join in too it's tough
because
these
artists have stuff done by the
end of
the show we pick
the art probably about 15
minutes after
we're done
after you know uh cleaning up
the
opening and the closing of the
show and
doing the credits we're right
into that
so
it's an amazing thing that they
do and
fantastic
value for the show as one of
the few
podcasts anywhere in the world
that has
fresh album art for every
episode no
agenda art generator
thank you no agenda
artgenerator.com
thank you nick
you might want to put a time
code down
for that got it
uh we do have a few people to
thank for
show 1243 and i'm gonna have
you read
because you read
part of this note already and
you know
where you read and where you
didn't read
yes and this is from sir mark
and dame
astrid duke and duchess of
japan and all
the disputed islands of the
japanese
sea and they came with 333.33
and with a whole bunch of nice
pictures
of themselves
their staff they're all wearing
masks
and bragging about oh yes dear
john adam
thank you for your courage
the last few months of your
virus
deconstruction has been
the best i wanted to give you
an update
from the front line here in
japan we
have dodged the bullets so far
and have
only 739 deaths
for a population of over 126
million
that's 5.8 deaths per million
compared
that to the us
with 267 deaths per million of
course
that includes people who drink
themselves to death
and the uk with 511 deaths per
million
which is
definitely people who drink
themselves
to death japan is an incredible
times less than the uk
we have that i'm curious they
must be i
bet you the japanese are
accurate with
their diagnosis
of death the cause of death do
what do
you think
i would agree with i have a
feeling that
this is the japanese are known
for
precision
yeah yeah and everything
apparently
everything has to have a stamp
and an
approval so they're not going
to mess
with it alex is such a good car
the ones made in japan yes
is it is that why the lexus is
such a
good car is that it
it's one of the reasons uh okay
now uh
back to uh
masks and he says we've been
doing it
right yeah masks work the whole
country
wears them for flu season every
year
especially the most crowded
mass transit
system in the world you wear
them so you
don't give
your cold to others and people
have been
doing this for years and it's
no big
deal no stigma
attached it's also meant that
we had oh
it's also
important that we had more
stock yeah
several billions of them there
was
just enough to go around mass
usage went
up with cobit but it also meant
that it
was the weakest flu season
over 10 years and we went
through the
hotels that he spoke about
contact tracing is big here not
electronic just lots of leg
work all the
resources have been put
uh on that and uh on let me
put on that and on phones in
mass
transit oh no i'm sorry and on
tracking
coveted clusters we might have
been
lucky getting a weaker strain
but it
helps not having to shake hands
just bow
no huggy kissy greetings no
talking on
phones in mass transit
hand sanitizers almost
everywhere high
adoption of touchless
electronic payment systems as
well as
burner cards
finally the healthcare system
here has a
low barrier to entry my kids
can go to
the local doctor themselves
just take their national health
card mom
might rock up later very much
neighborhood policing system
well yes
it's a very sophisticated
disciplined society which has a
lot of
downsides too
the kids get a feeling for
what's going
on it's by no means perfect the
prevention
testing measures can be seen as
flawed
the reporting flaw japan is
but all the micro actions
combined make
it a rather safe place to be
right now
there's a lot to be learned
from this
fuzzy logic and staying calm
sir mark
and day master duke and duchess
of japan
and all the disputed islands in
the
japan sea
thank you so much for your
courage and
uh can't wait to see you guys
in japan
hope to go this year
hope to go if there's any
flight yeah
nick's on the list
lybrund in medfield
massachusetts nuts
333 dollars
uh the direction of uh adam
i've sent
333 to produce the next episode
my last
donation was episode
122 uh two uh d douching and
sprinkling of job karma would be
appreciated give him a d douchey
you've been deduced
my son flyknit junior
fly not junior yeah i've seen
him around
uh has a may 25th birthday he's
got one
so does he
uh these on the i think they're
both on
the birthday unless you might
want to
check yeah here's an update on
what's
going on with the medical ppe
it's ties
to some of the
kaylee cayley mcinanni
quotes that are making the
rounds one of
my manufacturing sites produces
layers used in n95 surgical
masks
here's a part of what i think
has been
going on with the lockdown and
how ppe
played a role
one a one as the covet hit the
u.s we
started summarizing more
clearly what we
knew about the industry
we guessed that the u.s would
make about
6 million n95 masks per day
and the government was supposed
to have
a stockpile of 90 million based
on 2000
on a 2004 paper but when
created there
was never more than 85 million
at the
start of the rona it had about
million
as an example california's
first request
was for 20 million
in late february hhs said 90
million was
wrong
the correct number should have
been a
330 million
seven days later hhs says the
right
number was really
3.5 billion as we've dealt with
the
military via the defense
production act
my guess is that the military
and the
rest of the us government did
the same
math and realize that the whole
situation was hopelessly out of
whack
wait we can make how many masks
that's
not enough
at this point the nature with
the nature
of the disease being very
unclear the
best option was to simply
shut things down and give the
supply
chain time to get caught up
masks and pp will be part of the
national the meanwhile you can
impeach trump over this of
course of
course mass and pp would be
part of
national defense strategy going
forward
there's
hoping that the rumored bill
that is a
version of the barrie amendment
for
medical supplies is passed soon
the
barrie amendment is the
legislation that
requires the military
to buy certain items from
producers in
the continental u.s
kayleigh mcnamara makame uh
had a great quote in the recent
briefing
furthermore what crimson
contagion brought us in that
president
trump was right all along
about misguided economic and
trade
policies that left america
vulnerable to
pandemics
well not too vulnerable to
pandemic but
vulnerable
due to a pandemic
yes yes yes but i totally get
it so
you fred and junior are on the
list
thank you very much
uh you see he seems to have a
thing for
kaylee mcananny
yeah i think that's the first
time she's
ever been mentioned in a
donation
segment the first two times
he donates again you can assume
it's
going to happen one more time
here's
your jobs karma fred
jobs jobs jobs and jobs
let's vote for jobs
you've got karma and thank you
for the
support
once you read this one while i
look for
uh the one after that yeah this
is from
producer jacob
333 and he says it's jacob your
favorite
lobbyist
yes this is one of our lobbyist
producers
amy wrongfully said that would
be
probably one of your clips
that quote corporate lobbying
firms are
being oh that's right we talked
about
the corporate lobbying firms
being
bailed out she's wrong there's
no
bailout provision for lobbyists
i think
we explain that but
he says people should not
misinterpret
what that means lobbying firms
including
our own are making
all-time high profits thanks to
the
abundance of new bailout
uh slash appropriations bills
the biggest problem love this
the
biggest problem will be
a lack of lobbyists next year
because so
many will retire
following this year of record
profits
the states can't believe that
shit the
stage four and stay five stage
five
stimulus packages are coming
stage five
he's talking about
are coming next and will likely
include
up to five trillion dollars in
new
spending this is coming from
the one of
the money guys in dc
so you can take that uh as some
version
of a
future future prediction
uh sent some of the rock record
profits
to your way
um no agenda producers who need
help of
an evil corporate lobbyist can
reach us
in case you need an evil
corporate
lobbyist you can reach the
official no
agenda lobbyist firm at
lobby me at protonmail.com
jacob thank you very much for
your
courage and it's appreciated
especially
the knowledge of the stage five
is
coming up to five trillion
dollars
woo everybody everybody nothing
but
money
party man party well at least
he's
sharing it with us that's good
news
uh uh the associate executive
producer
the first one is ernest selmons
i can't
find any note from him he said
dollars and 56 cents
he is in ee i think is is that
estonia
or
estonia yeah that's estonia
he's in
estonia oh yeah talent
allow me to use my nifty new
search bar
in uh microsoft no i don't have
it
either let me see
search the joanne brady's next
on the
list at 220
and 22 cents or by the way
arness if you
got something that you want us
to say
we'll
send it along uh in uh 222 in
phoenix
arizona please accept
uh corona cash you're the best
podcast
ever thanks
also call out my brother
michael brady
for being a douchebag
okay dame jennifer arnis
appears to be a
sir so i'm gonna get that
straight
dame jennifer's next on the
list of 200
bucks
uh here's to your share of the
very
generous contributions we
i've received recently regarding
animated no agenda
i still have major rhona brain
but i am
so thankful i stumbled on the
no agenda
almost 10 years ago a big nutty
as as bug nutty as i am lately i
shuddered to think how much
crazier i
would be without
another one she's one of the
nervous
wrecks
uh i'd started to think how
much crazier
i'd be without your show and the
wonderful producers i've met
along the way you know jingle
just could
you definitely use a
huge jobs karma maybe the trump
pelosi
combo to shake things up
she puts that as a question
mark mike my
answer to that is no no
why let's not shake things up
no don't shake those you don't
want to
shake things up with
experimental
sketchy uh x uh
jingles you know x is in like an
experimental vehicle the rona
has not
been kind to the bottom line
please also sprinkle it out to
the
producers who are having
trouble these
days
p.s the 17th is my actual
birthday and i
feel so lucky
that this is also a show day
well that sounds like she
should be on
the birthday yeah she is on the
birthday
list actually
funny uh show day thank you all
for your
courage and support
our tribe is amazing good old
dane
jennifer and
dame jennifer of course just
did another
fabulous uh
episode of animated no agenda
which
was the helicopter helicopter
money
people don't understand us they
they
think that we
really don't understand the
concept of
helicopter money
but interestingly it's not it's
heli
payments it's a whole different
deal
heli payments
in the ireland is not the same
as
helicopter payments that come
from the
federal reserve
so i thought it was did you see
it did
you see the i have not i didn't
know it
came out
oh my goodness it's your bit
it's well
i'll check it out
for sure it's very funny very
very funny
i love seeing my own bits
your bitters your bits are the
best you
should put use a marker to make
sure
that
no one takes your bit thank you
dame
jennifer and here we go with
the only
jobs karma that makes a
difference
jobs jobs jobs and jobs
let's vote for jobs you've got
karma today is your birthday
on the list forest martin 200
bucks
parts unknown he should be on
the
birthday list
and let me see if he is i
thought i saw
him there earlier i could be
wrong
uh just making my yearly
birthday
donation he writes and
congratulations
to adam and the keeper on their
anniversary
now he remembered it's the 19th
so
that's two days away thank you
forest uh also thanking you both
gentlemen for everything you do
keeping people informed and
entertained
and i would like to get an
official d
douching
you've been deduced as it got
lost in
the shuffle last year
and since my job situation has
improved
since i was first able to
donate a year
ago a jobs karma for everybody
who needs
it
jobs jobs jobs and jobs
let's vote for jobs
karma
and that's our list of associate
executive producers and
executive
producers
for show at 12 43 it's back to
our
normal
amounts i think everyone's over
covered
i guess
i don't know well what i
appreciate the
most of the
of the shows we've done in the
past
couple months is is people
feeding back
just like
dame jennifer said no matter
what it is
people seem to find
some comfort in listening to us
and i'm
i'm proud and happy about that
but
i want to thank everybody
because it's
really it's the producers
long ago we noticed that it's
better to
have producers than listeners
because they actually do stuff
and
produce and make things happen
there's
no way this show would be what
it is
without you without the people
who
support us financially the clips
thank you extra thanks to so
many
producers who are sending
uh if you send a youtube video
pre-cued
with the time code it saves so
much time
thank you listings of time codes
pre-clipped it's
incredibly appreciated uh
because that's what it is and
that's why
we're the best podcast in the
universe
end of story these people
of course are executive
producers and
associate executive producers
and they
can
um use these credits wherever
they want
to because they're official
and when people see a credit
they
recognize it it gives you
stature
and maybe a gig which is what a
lot of
people are going to be looking
for
soon if not already thank you
again for
all of your courage remember we
do have
another show coming up on
thursday and
to support us for that go to
dvorak.org n
a lots of mouth hitting going
on good to
see it we're happy to have you
aboard
our formula is this we go out
we hit people in the mouth
[Music]
the kid was blowing up on me
sorry about
that
so over the last few days biden
had this
event
and i even i have biden clips
today
uh well biden had this horrible
advantage so i don't even know
i mean you have let's look
let's look at
some
things objectively you have
uh nbc msnbc is owned by comcast
and they're big promoters or
big haters
of trump
what does it take for biden's
techies to
go and get a hold of comcast
and say hey
look we're going to do a bunch
of these
events
down out of biden's basement
what is the
chance of getting some real
high-speed just kick-ass
connections you guys can help
us uh
would consider it a
contribution from
the like the campaign
contribution
whatever you want to
want it to be called but we do
need some
help here can you give us your
best guys
and get us some
just no
who said that this wasn't their
best
guys it's comcast
have you tried comcast
connection oh
come on we know
they can do better than this uh
i mean
that's funny it's funny line
but the
fact
is that this is this is this
one was so
bad
it was almost like watching
that movie
you know they're
they're here or whatever it's
called
everywhere where you put the
glasses on
you see
monsters yes yeah
and so every time biden moved
you know
his head stayed there on one
side and it
became a skeleton head and it
was
oh it was the worst yeah but
but before
they we play that i do have
this one
a clip i want to get out of the
way
which is biden uh
and apparently he was on um
they were talking about him
scarborough
and what's her name mika or
mika brazil discussing biden's
commentary when he was on gma
and i'm
going to play this clip because
the
combination of biden
telling why he's hiding biden's
height
and he's in his basement scared
to death
and the two of them are going
on and on
about how great it is because
he's a
winner
now you know everybody says you
know
biden's hiding well let me tell
you
something
we're doing very well we're
we're we're
following
the guidelines of the medical
profession
we're
following the guidelines of the
experts
the dr faucis of the world
we're doing very well and that
matter of
fact we're
winning if you look at all the
polling
data i'm not saying that's
going to last
until november i don't know
enough to
know that
but right now the idea that
somehow we
are being hurt by
my keeping to the rules and
following
the instructions
that are uh that have been put
forward
by the docs uh
is absolutely bizarre i reject
the
premise that somehow
this is hurting us there's no
evidence
of that
i'm following the rules
following the
rules the president should
follow the
rules instead of showing up at
places
without masking the whole
the whole thing i'm sorry he
wins that
yeah
every time check me he wins that
checkmate
every time yeah you know really
i i
you i i understand the
president and
people some people inside the
white
house most of them understand
they're
whistling past a political
graveyard but
you know donald trump snubbing
doctors
doctor's
advice in the middle of the
pandemic
that's killed now
over 80 000 people we have new
estimates
it's going to kill
140 150 000 people after donald
trump
yeah whatever doctor's advice
early on
and said this was nothing to
worry about
he loses to a dude
who says hey i'm gonna follow
the doc's
advice
because guess what most
americans
are following their doc's advice
following advice to the doctor
so
i mean joe biden's right
the brzezinski child and the
douche
knuckle jeez you know god
it's gonna we're coming close
to banning
them
yeah yeah you can't resist come
on hey
you're right
it's the mika the brzezinski
child she's
pretty funny
which brings me to just a
little break
in the show here
yeah uh i have my list of isos
which
includes the top one
checkmate oh hold on a second uh
shit yeah i got it here i got
it here
the iso yeah checkmate
yeah oh checkmate i
i have one i'd like to try on
you okay
okay try this one
so i'm walking around with the
corona
vice i'm asymptomatic i got it
you got the rona is that what's
going on
here i didn't know you had the
corona
virus
let's try this one let's try
this one
dry this is not a geese
okay that's the geese you hear
in the
background
okay that was biden okay let's
go let's
go this one another bite
is following rules following
rules where are we uh
oh got it i'm following the
rules
you know i'm sorry it just none
of it
competes with
you can kick their balls but
you can't
touch them
if that wasn't so echoey i'd
say yes oh
so now we have to go to rule
follower
well let's no no let's go to
another one
try this one pandemic
okay where where where where is
it we're
in the middle of a pandemic
yeah that's
the one
[Music]
that's the one that's done i
like it
that's a good one i got one
last one
no you have more but wait
there's more
okay
put up or shut up pull up or
shut up
no no no no no no no no no i
think you
nailed it with us
before you do more joe clips
may i take
you back in time for a moment
sure let's just get in the time
machine
for a second let's go back
to may 20th of
2013 episode
512. so this is quite a while
ago of the
no agenda show this is what
happened is
that
that's not going to happen is
that that
is the dream yeah that is
i think it's called a
hallucination i
had
i had a real dream last night
and i woke
up from this
put this in the red book just
for just
for yucks
all right i and it was vivid
okay
it was vivid and maybe because
we've
played a couple of clips of him
recently
i've been watching video of him
are you ready for this joe
biden was
president
i am from the future ladies and
gentlemen
i am from the future it's in
the red
book i think
you should be able to find that
it'll be
a disaster
all right so we have brian
giving his
little event i got i got some
miscellaneous clips and then
some some
research on him
okay um let's go with the biden
event
clips i got
uh i know i got three of them i
got
anyone you want to play i can
play the
short little one which i think
is
similar to the
pandemic when this biden's
event with
the govs blather
exists because you know in a
few nations
that every major crisis we've
faced in
our history
has been in a situation where
we have uh
come out stronger come out
stronger and
uh what i'm finding
and maybe go back to this later
but uh
i'm finding that
you know uh this whole crisis
sort of
taking the blinders off
most people you know the people
who
weren't are there geese in the
background
yes necessarily prejudice but
just
didn't focus
that's the geese you hear in the
background the little pond out
here
and those canadian geese are
trying to
get away from the buyers anyway
all kidding aside what happens
is that
uh um
what i'm finding people who are
constantly calling me and i know
we're all in place but we have
on the
phone
probably six hours a day or
people are
talking about how
they didn't realize that it was
somebody
making you know
seven bucks an hour is making
had their
back you know
by the time he got to the end i
had no
idea what he was talking about
exactly
exactly that was the point of
that clip
yeah well it worked
and there's a little sub clip
here this
is biden event with the govs
blather
one w-a-h-o
yeah i got it we've got and i
know you
all stand for that we got a lot
of
ground to cover
so let's start with this you
know that
iris can hit anyone but it
doesn't affect every community
oh shoot
oh no i disconnected my head
you know i
got a real problem with these
headphones
and i'm not going to hear you
for at
least
seven seconds so you can fill
up the
void while i'm waiting well
that was
important
that was a classic example of
both how
stupid this event was this is
widened
three governors but the lousy
connection
none of them could none of them
in fact
all three plus biden couldn't
talk for
at all they were all
i like you said iris now
i got one clip of joe with the
the
number mix up do you have that
one
no but i have this last one
from this
series okay and this is says
biden event
with gov's
blather and this has no other
moniker on
there
okay exists because you know in
a few
nations
no wait that's the one we
played we
played that one first
no the one you played first
should have
been uh
uh gov's blather zero z-w-e-o
no we you didn't play the one
that says
zero
oh okay uh yes i have it here
we go
desperately need your
this is we did not play zero we
played
oh this is zero play zero yeah
desperately need
your company's going and this
is it
would help if it didn't say
zuio if yeah
i thought it might have been
like you
don't have to humiliate me in
public i
i know how to spell i'm not
humiliating
you i'm telling you that i
if i want to humiliate you
that's easy i
was saying i thought
i thought it might be a ceo
clip or
something i didn't know that was
zero it's fine they've already
believe me you take these joe
biden
clips out of order it doesn't
it doesn't
matter
it does not matter desperately
need your
company's
going and this is not a moment
for
excuses or deflections or
blame game where we're we're
it's
we're in the middle of a
pandemic that
had cost us more than 85
000 jobs as of today lives of
millions
of people that's the ones the
people
millions of jobs that's the one
i mean
everybody shakes their head and
says
joe's gonna win the race
you know and we're in a
position where
you know we just got new
unemployment
insurance
this morning uh numbers 365
million
claims since this crisis began
and
almost
3 million new claims in the
last week
the unemployment rate is
nearing 15
the highest it's been since the
great
depression but i need not tell
you all
that
of course it's uh it's the least
well-off for
being hit the hardest 40 of the
households
making 40 000 or less
experience the job loss just in
march
and we're going to have to work
harder
and smarter
than ever before to pull
ourselves out
of this economic tailspin and
this is
the problem with
with joe is that when he gets a
sentence
out
it's really nothing there's
just nothing
in it we're gonna have to work
hard
pull together he doesn't really
have any
i've no i think i've not heard
one
single
uh policy oriented solution
even for
uh african americans he came
out with
the league the big joe biden's
black
agenda
which was uh you know i think
it's
called lift all
we will lift all voices which
is not
pandering at all
to the religious black
americans um
any and what he says in there
oh we're
gonna we're gonna do a study
and do a study to see if we
should do
some reparations i mean this
is the kind of crap that is not
gonna
fly
but i know what sorry is this
mike
is that still the clip oh yeah
there's
another 40 seconds and seven
seconds to
go
i'm sorry it seems like it
seems like
weeks go by but all of you know
i'm my second anniversary has
already
taken place this clip is so
long the
only way out of this
is by following the science
listening to
the experts
talking and taking responsible
precautions that
are going to help us reopen the
economy
i say fleeing as quickly as
possible
and uh as we do there's got to
be
federal support to state and
local
levels of our government in my
view so
that we'll be able to
come out of this crisis
stronger and
more united
we have an opportunity in my
view to
transform the economy as we
come out
to build a more inclusive and
more
resilient middle class
and i think that can withstand
the next
next public crisis whatever it
is
however it comes about not just
reward
the people who are well off and
well
connected
it's time for us to make sure
everyone
gets a fair shot of success in
this
country
that's science i don't believe
in
science
one last clip i want to get to
get this
series completely out of the way
they talked about this on pbs
uh a little bit and judy this
is the
judy
smear she this is smear that
she slipped
into this little announcement
discussing
the biden
event in the days other news
former vice
president joe biden says that if
elected president he would not
pardon
donald trump or his associates
of any
crimes
instead he says he would let any
investigations play out
the presumptive democratic
nominee spoke
in a virtual town hall
on msnbc last night and he
accused mr
trump of abusing his power
we never saw anything like the
prostitution of that office
like we see
it today
it is not something the
president is
entitled to do
to direct either a prosecution
and or
decide to drop a case that is
not the
president's role
responsibility and it's a
dereliction of
his duty
what is he is he talking about
flynn is
that what he's what he's saying
yeah i think it's about flynn
well i
have the clip that
where he is i think he's in up
to his up
to his eyeballs on this flynn
thing
yeah by the way this was a smear
when judy says that he's not
going to
pardon trump that
the way it was presented was as
though
trump had had cr
created an actual crime well
let's go to
the
crime let's go to the town hall
and
let's see how this
came about the judy did not
play the
source material because
it was a request from an
audience member
here it is
would you be willing to commit
to not
pulling a president forward
and giving donald trump a
pardon under
the
pretense of healing the nation
in other words are you willing
to commit
to the american ideal
that no one is above the law
absolutely
yes i commit
i don't know it was a spiked
call or
whatever but i commit
these commitments please but
this
but this town hall was very
interesting
for another reason
all of a sudden and this was
the joe
biden special event
the msnbc i think it was uh
lawrence what's his name uh no
laura lawrence o'donnell so
he's hosting
it
and all of a sudden we've got
lawrence
in the middle
joe on the right and stacy
abram pops up
on the
left-hand box and hilarity
ensued
as we watch stacey abrams
slowly lose
her soul on live tv so i want
to begin
this with a question to joe
biden
because
uh stacey abrams is here
because joe
biden invited stacey abrams to
be here
and so uh mr vice president uh
do you
have an announcement to make
uh is this an audition is there
uh what is the reason that that
you
decided it's time for me to get
what would you say stop the
hammering
and on tv with stacy abrams
well because
stacey abrams has done more to
deal with
the fair vote and making sure
there is a
fair vote than anybody
and she's she has a great great
capacity
to explain things
mind you she's sitting here
right now
saying nothing
looking in the camera in her
own box on
the left the smile
started to slowly fade and the
layout
exactly why it's going to be so
critically important in this
election
this president's already said
when they
put in the stimulus package the
congress
first passed
money to provide for mail-in
ballots
he already said i'm not for
that if we
do that
well no republican will ever
win or
something to that effect
he's made it clear this is the
guy who
said he wants to
defund the post office from
being able
to deliver ballots i mean
so stacy knows what she's doing
and uh
and she's a incredibly capable
person
and so since then that said
nothing he
set her up if you want to make
an
announcement
of course everyone's thinking
oh my
goodness is going to be the vp
announcement
nothing no that's embarrassing
did you
think and by the way when did
trump say
he wanted to defund the post
office
because so they wouldn't deliver
absentee i love that too i
thought it
was
that was a nice touch why did
you say
that no i don't i don't think i
don't i
don't think he ever said that
that was joe someone told you
hey just
make make it up
so i did see part of this i
didn't
take any clips from it but it's
pathetic
abrams is really a dud i just
don't
understand what i was so
jacked up about well and i will
say it
again i'm going to remind
everybody my
thinking on this
having been a democrat there's
not a woman in the democrat
party that
will have
stacey abrams as president until
a white woman is president first
if i may uh we this was a big
topic on the mofax and uh
and we discussed the vp slot
specifically from an ados
perspective
and stacy abrams is not wanted
is not going to be it is being
shunned
and
the reason why which i thought
was i
hadn't really considered
uh she is the oprah candidate
and
when she ran for governor of
georgia oh
remember oprah went down
oh yeah promoting beyonce
everybody was
there and she couldn't win
and i think that uh and
remember oprah
of course she she feels that
she made
barack obama and she had a big
hand in
it
for sure uh and this is her
candidate
just think
oprah can't run herself but
this would
be
kind of like an oprah like an
oprah ugly
you know and and
and the democrat party wants
nothing to
do with her
and i think wants nothing to do
with
oprah certainly after seeing
the combo
oprah and stacey abrams in in
georgia
failed and they're probably
questioning
all kinds of celebrity
endorsements if
they really are worth it anymore
so no stacy according to mo and
i
i think he laid out the uh
i think he laid out the the the
case for
that is not going to be
vice president there's no doubt
about
that not going to be the vice
presidential nominee
but she'll do anything she'll
even show
up and and be publicly
embarrassed
well i i'll just add to my
thinking on
this is that
no black woman will be the vice
presidential candidate
under biden which takes a
little further
than just the
targeting stacy because again
the
white women that are democrats
are more
racist than the republicans by
a lot
having been in both parties and
they
will not put especially when
hillary was snubbed they will
not allow
a black
woman of any sorts they say
abrams or
otherwise that's why
camel and the rest of them are
all out
too for other reasons i'm sure
you can
target them
but because they want a white
woman as
the first female president
period and
you think they're that racist
the
democrat party
yeah i do there are no
they're already misogynist or
no i'm
sorry miss anthropos by saying
it can
only be a woman it can't be a
man
because we don't qualify we're
no good
we're stupid
just look at joe there's going
to be a
white
if it's not a white woman amy
klobuchar
would be at the top of the list
i
i would say that he wants to go
for some
other ethnic possibilities
again i'll
bring in uh luhan
uh grisham out of new mexico and
somebody sent us a note going
on and on
about how
that was me in particular since
i've
been promoting her you saw that
note
yeah i did i'm actually i'm
gonna grab
the clip for you here's the clip
that uh brought this uh comment
on hold
on a second
and um uh our secretary of state
insisted
and this broke the meeting up
basically
in terms of her influence that
this be called the lujan virus
which was our producer said
well he just
gave away the just gave away
who it's
going to be
who had the vice presidential
pick it
had this luan was in the back
of his
head he couldn't just not say it
so it's a logical
you know i'm still i'm hedging
my luhan
bet
i'm putting her in the second
spot under
amy yeah but
oh i'm sorry amy klobuchar my
amy
klobuchar is now top spot
amy amy she would be kick ass
as vice president i'm sure she
would
well she's the
except for the fact that she
throws
staplers and yells at her staff
and
she's mean
which they suppressed to such
an extreme
now we have her none of these
stories
they were only apparent at the
beginning
of the campaigning so which
makes me
think that she may be
a possibility for the vp slot
since they're they're
sanitizing her as
we speak
so let's just to be clear amy
klobuchar
is my amy
and you have uh amy from uh pbs
no democracy now yeah from
democracy
that's your amy and amy
klobuchar's mike
thank you very much yeah that's
my
my you get your amy hey i have
sports
news
are you ready for some sports
coming from me oh this should be
rich going into this season
coming up
this is from fox sports
fox sports fox fs1 fox sports
and that
comes with a huge
asterisk and hopefully there is
a season
there's probably going to be a
season
in doing games with no fans
which
uh will be difficult i think
fox and
these
networks have to put crowd
noise under
us
to to make it a huge designing
experience at home
you think they'll do that i do
yeah i
really
i know in fact i know they'll
do it um
let him finish let him finish
you're
yelling through my sports clip
it's not
that
often that i bring one in fact
i know
they'll do it um
and they are that's that's the
conversation right now
that's that's it's pretty much
a done
deal i think whoever's going to
be
at that control is going to
have to be
really good at their job and
and be realistic with how a
crowd would
react depending on what just
happened on
the field so
it's really important then on
top of
that they're going to put uh
they're
looking at ways to put virtual
fans in
the stands so when you see a
wide chat
it looks like the stadium is
jam-packed
hey sports fans you're not
needed you're
completely replaceable
in fact they should just play
the games
in a big blue screen
green screen auditorium and do
all kinds
of cool stuff
you know this is telling uh you
know
what this tells this confirms
the basic no agenda thesis is
that all
sports are rigged
no kidding this is taking the
rigging to
it to a maximum
you have fake fake audience
fake noise
fake applause the whole thing
you know
it's the canned laughter again
once
put canned laughter to get a can
laughter guy in there and have
him just
yuck it up uh it's unbelievable
oh my
god i can't believe it's an
interception
oh no he drops he fumbles
that's the best we can do
that's about
all i got
oh my god there's a cruise
missile
there's a cruise missile going
over the
stadium what can we do about it
the
cruise missile
i have nothing else yeah
that'd be very sad but it'll
fit with
the fight fake outcome of
of these games so that's good
uh oh yes
i do have one more
uh biden related clip short one
the convention which is coming
up in
what is there
is the democrats supposed to be
in
august have they moved it is
that
i don't know maybe it was in
july they
moved to august i don't know
august is
the last i heard
here is the uh the
communications
director of the dnc
regarding the convention and uh
i think
this
maybe i'm reading too much into
it but
it felt a little bit like
not everyone in the party is on
board
with joe have a listen
i mean there's a real
possibility that
the convention does not happen
or it
happens in a virtual sense
is that correct well first of
all our
convention has to happen
because we
are not officially nominating
joe biden
in order to take donald trump
so our
convention is happening there is
business that has to happen
now when it comes to um what our
convention is going to look like
i can guarantee you that our
convention
will ensure
that the safe that is safety
first
whether it is our delegates
the people of milwaukee or all
of those
involved in a convention
we will make sure that they are
safe
whatever that looks like and
that they
vote for our nominee now did
you catch
the beginning of how she
phrased that
i'll play it again i mean
there's a real
possibility of the convention
does not
happen or it happens in a
virtual sense
is that correct our convention
has to
happen because
we um are not officially
nominating joe
biden
in order to take donald trump i
like how
he
did notice that take donald
trump i
thought that was an interesting
use of words is that how they
see it to
take donald trump
well that's their only goal but
did you
listen to it carefully she says
our
convention is not to nominate
joe biden
is that correct as of today
well first
of all our convention has to
happen
because
we um are not officially
nominating joe
biden
in order to take donald trump
so our
convention is happening there is
business
we're not nominating joe biden
as what
she said i told you there's
something
weird in that clip and she
seems like she's not i know for
a comms
director i think she let out a
little
bit too much there
my personal personal opinion oh
yeah
they don't care about anything
but
donald trump
that's this you can't win
elections that
way
all right uh i i am very
excited to have
a second half of show coming up
for you
which uh is a send-in from one
of our
producers uh but first i think
we should
thank some more people who are
on the
spreadsheet for today
i'm gonna show my support by
donating to
no agenda imagine all the
people who
could do
that oh yeah that'd be fabulous
in the morning yeah we do have
some
people to think starting with
john
patrick
and he came in with a hundred
dollars
even
i had why don't you read a
couple of
these because i do have a
notes i do want to read
uh well we don't typically read
these
i'm not sure but okay
uh johnny get me down to where
it says i
got a note i got to go to the
desk and
get the note
oh you're just making me do it
okay john
patrick uh decatur illinois 100
much respect for you both for
covet
sanity
anonymous 100 has a douchebag
call out
and is from an anonymous
uh parts unknown don't mention
full name
location just well we're just
doing
anonymous
i'd like to call out oh my
goodness i'd
like to call out dame jennifer
as a
douchebag
for never sending an invoice
for some
voice over work she did
well how about that she's two
old
too good for this world too good
uh john cooper downers gay grove
illinois you have the notes
he has a note here's what he
was doing
uh
there's another note this is a
note
that's good and i want to read
it
i am new to your show after
hearing adam
on jre
another notch in your belt well
wait
until wait until you hear the
lights
more about that guy i gotta
tell you
joe and i were texting and joe
keeps
mentioning me
on his show i noticed a couple
of
mentions yeah
but here's the thing so tina
the other
night we're sitting on the couch
watching some tv shit and
i'm texting hey who are you
texting i
said my friend joe she says
she says she says joe de geneva
yeah that sounds about
classic
[Laughter]
yeah anyway onwards yes this
has done
well this is eight people so
far who
have uh
come over to our tribe from uh
jre i'm
very very pleased with that
john continues i've always
disliked the
media but in the last few years
the mask
has really come off
it is awesome finding
like-minded people
i look forward to joining the
meetup
once the not lockdown is lifted
thanks
for all you do
to keep people away from the
m5m fear
porn yes and keep amygdala
small i have
managed to figure out
most of the insider terminology
this is
always a problem with the
newbies
but i have a few questions okay
what is
the significance of the number
are you big fans of rolling
rock beer
well let him stew in this one
really well let me just say one
thing
we've noticed over time
that when the number 33 shows
up in news
reports
there's typically something
very fishy
going on with the report or
with the
situation now
of course we have uh it's we've
taken it
so far that and this has been
going on
since almost the first day we
did the
show
uh that people are noticing it
everywhere and during the uh
this rona
crisis it was everywhere 33
this 30
through that 33 people are sick
33 is
there
and we have a jingle for it
so that's it it's the magic
number
whenever we see 33 we pay
attention
we're never sure what it's
going to mean
but something always comes out
of it
yeah it's code it's code
it's and here's another one he
brings up
which i think should be this
i'm reading this because this
is good
stuff to reiterate for the
newcomers
it seems harsh to call people
douchebags
that have not donated but i
will not
become a douchebag if i've
included my
donation 100 but okay let's
start
let's start with that concept
this was
not
our idea no ever no
no we we also don't do it if
you realize
we are reading
the notes that people send in
we're not
calling them douchebags
uh anyway he goes on he says uh
he goes
on just
thanking us for the show
appreciate the
insights on audio production
and proper
microphone usage i
love benefiting from people's
expertise
in areas where i would
otherwise not get
it
my ear is now much more attuned
oh
excellent i thought you liked
that yeah
i did thank of course thank you
john
so anyway onward to uh forrest
morris
the fourth i love the name
forest forest
morris the fourth
horse another one another one
uh what well he's uh forced
yes this is the second note
it's right
behind this other one i think
no i don't
have enough force
no no no i'm going to read you
the note
when i say another one
it's something else forrest
morris iv
99.96
from murfreesboro tennessee
where we
have a lot of producers
uh forrest the mass barber here
listening since joe rogan
experience
withholding two cents for john's
opinions on barbers and
stylists not
listening and not needing any
time to
professionally handle health
and safety
and two cents for his mask as
he will
need to wear one at his haircut
keep up the great work would
like some
karma for tips
yeah we'll get we'll get some
karma for
the at the end of this
so he's cleve cabrell i think
at 800
boobs donation and this is a
first donation first donation
so he says
a d
d douching is in order
you've been deduced
got it lamb of the earl of
georgia sugar
hill
georgia 8008 ronald schull
came in with the pop money
donation joe
weiss in miami florida 77
77 he has the note that he
wrote this
check in and i this is another
note i
put aside for this reason
a quick message from miami
where they're
trying to move south florida
into a new
normal
this morning when i was taking
my daily
walk i was listening to
yesterday's
podcast 12 41
john just started to talk about
the
morons who are wearing masks
while
driving alone
and no sooner did that he make
that
statement within four minutes i
witnessed three separate mass
commandos
alone driving in their vehicles
fighting
off the corona
with the air conditioning off
and the
windows up uh
with your recommendation i also
listened
to two hour interview with the
jfk
junior interview
he said it was great treasure
trove of
good information and we do
recommend
that interview if you can find
it i
think there's
okay in the show notes it's rfk
junior
rfk what did i say oh jfkg
all right that's a mistake i
probably
did say jfk arnold
tyler arnold's next only 75
dollars
um he says he says he's sorry
is this
hate mail you're going your way
adam
well sure i just i just want to
you know
thank you but it's really it's
hate mail
for john that i
this gets sent to me and i don't
understand they keep doing it
tyler thanks well all hate mail
to john
should go to adam mccurry.com
sir
milkman in arcadia georgia 66-69
uh sir jake of the ip bogan
i.t bogan i'm sorry maury field
the
queensland australia 59-59
and he's got his old man jeff
uh on the
birthday list
you got that daniel mariano in
full
flugerville texas 55 10.
sir buck of the 11 of 21 12 55
yes another birthday needs
needs to be
stopped happy birthday from sir
buck of
2112 to my beautiful
caring talented pretty lady yes
it is dame jennifer of animated
no
agenda this is her husband
this is dame jennifer's show
pretty much
dame jennifer would you mind
doing the
show for us uh she used to be
smoking
hot and now she's beautiful
well he listened to the uh the
warning
that you gave we're not allowed
to
do that anymore you were very
very the
excited
darren has some good ones in
there yeah
classics i like the uh minecraft
washbish you know racine
wisconsin
55 his brother rick
is who hit him in the mouth i
know he's
listening but he has not done
it so he
donated so he needs to be
called out as
a douchebag
alana margoulis 51 carl vogler
fifty dollars and thirty three
cents or
dh slammer haven't heard from
him for a
couple of
weeks baron is central
california coast
venturi to santa cruz fifty
dollars and
thirty three cents
um circa and he's got a warning
for
cyrus sir christopher barron of
brown
county in green bay wisconsin
50 the
following people are all 50
donors name and location
beginning with
sir chris slowinski
well actually sir christopher
barron of
brown counties chris lewinsky
christopher muller in uh cedar
park
uh travis fricker in
philadelphia i got
a birthday elle
liebel in newark delaware
joseph harper
in arnold maryland
and john camp in antlers
oklahoma i want
to thank all these folks
listed us as producers of show
1243 and thanks for helping us
out yes
and also those who came in
under 50 for
anonymity
and we have a lot of these
programs
subscriptions that you can
participate
in and people actually get
pretty far
with those we have a lot of
knights and
dames
who have been on the longer
layaway
programs all of it is
appreciated
the value for value system is
real
simple whatever you think the
show is
worth
that's what you send us if it's
not
worth anything don't send us
anything
but what we see here today is
great
thank you so much and as we
said we'll
be back uh
on thursday you can support us
again all
you have to do is go to
[Music]
health and jobs karma jobs jobs
jobs and jobs let's vote for
jobs
you've got karma
[Music]
no title changes but birthdays
yes alana
margulis says happy birthday to
her harlan's uh harlan's father
zach
forrest martin celebrates the
day travis
fricker says happy birthday to
his
smoking hot wife becky she
turns 33 she
turned 33 on the 15th
sir buck of 2112. happy
birthday was
beautiful caring talented wife
dame
jennifer she is celebrating
today on the
17th
as is uh damien he is sir aaron
yoho's
son
uh he turns 11. dame jennifer
wieda
says happy birthday to sir greg
davies
now you know sir greg davies uh
was our our knights uh who
passed away
we miss him dearly he would
have been 44
years old tomorrow we celebrate
him
still of course sir
jake says happy birthday was
father jeff
canyon uh 59 on the 20th
and fred lybrand says happy
birthday to
his son fly not junior
who will be celebrating on the
25th and
fred himself will be
celebrating on the
31st happy birthday for
everybody here
at the best podcast in the
universe
yeah we actually we have a
meetup report
a very short one
i guess there was yeah some
people are
diehards
and i appreciate that this is
vernon
this is the may 16th marcellus
new york
nine mile creek
meetup report the adam there
were plenty
of people sitting around
maskless at the
picnic tables and benches near
the
baseball diamond at marcellus
park but
no one asked me about no agenda
people
did ask me about my white
uh cockapoo's red boots which
was the
indicator i was the meetup
leader
i guess not many people look at
the
website if no podcast meetup
announcement is made and there
you go
so i guess that was a
one-person meet-up
darn sorry vernon better luck
next time
when the rona is over
[Music]
like a party
so are you ready for um
sometimes i want to take before
you go
into no before you do that i
got a
little
uh on tremont okay
uh curiously this is 43 seconds
and it
look a little like the joe
biden stuff
which is really less than two
minutes
but it went on forever for some
unknown
reason
this isn't going to be another
one the
this is a apparently
all the virtue signaling uh
celebrities
mostly yeah are out there
showing uh
doing commencement speeches
yes yes including the president
right
they're all doing i didn't know
that he
was doing one but
he he'd go and do it oh no i'm
sorry uh
president obama i mean not the
president president obama has
been doing
commencement speech oh yes that
would be
true
uh but they're all doing them
virtually
and they're in a bucket they're
usually
in a bucket or they find a good
place to
put the mic
it's a little bucket on the
side and
they're all in a bucket and
they're all
giving these commencement
speeches that
are lame and they're terrible
but i've
decided i'm going to look for
the worst
oh yay so this is a short
snippet from tom hanks
uh giving a commencement speech
just to
some small
western case or something i get
the the
name of the school here
somewhere it's
uh
wright state you want your
rights and
never heard of him right stay
sorry
anybody writes state alums uh
so he's
giving this speech
he's reading it kind of but he
kind of
lost track and i think he
started off
with saying the wrong thing and
he's
tried to make up for it and and
he just
kid he never really caught up
to it so
the speech became this
discombubilated piece of crap
here it is
congratulations to you chosen
ones wow
stop right there this is i
i don't understand how they
allow this
to happen i i
this sound is just beyond me
beyond me
congratulations to you chosen
ones
and i am calling you the chosen
because you
have been chosen in many ways
you have not returned to the
starting
line like all of
us generations before you
you're just
approaching it now for the
first time
you've just arrived you are
chosen in
that way
to enter into the competition
of life
just when so
many have had to recover and
refresh and
restart
and reawaken and to retake up
the hard
work and the unshirkable
responsibilities
of making the world not only
our own
but of your own wow
talk about he start here's what
happened
he says congrats
i think he kind of ad libbed the
beginning thinking it was going
to be
cool and he
to said chosen ones and then he
thought
to himself right on the spot
wait a minute i'm not joking
i mean this is offensive what
i'm saying
here
and so he then goes and tries
to make up
for it and it says by what by
what i mean by chosen ones and
then
the whole thing falls apart and
it's
just an embarrassment
and he's in his home with a
brick wall
behind him and he's trying to
read off
his notes
this is just should not be
people should
not be doing this that was
pretty much
the definition of phoning it in
it was really bad from the
sound to the
copy
to everything and even the
intent even
the intent why does he why
why are they doing that very
odd and if
you're gonna do it do it do a
great
make it memorable not like oh
i'm tom
hanks in a bucket
yeah the other thing is these
guys all
know production values and
people like
tom
hanks is a good example he's
not like
he's a producer
yes he's a producer he could
produce a
video
and he could put the good sound
with it
he's got nothing else to do he's
he's holed up in his mansion he
could
put us he could put a track
behind
himself he could have a
green screen he could be in
paris i mean
there's a million things you
could do to
make it lively but no
he's just walks through a bucket
presentation
it's embarrassing these guys
are just
showing that they really
are they really producers or
are they
just front men that is
with no talent what uh what was
the
school he was doing this for as
it's
build by the way
on news sites as tom hanks
inspiring
2020 commencement address it's
inspiring inspiring who was it
for
though
wright state is that his alma
mater
i don't know i didn't go that
deep into
it
no they quote no one will be
more fresh
to the task of restarting our
measure of normalcy than you
you chosen
ones
oh brother all right fine all
right tom
hanks i'm so that is the worst
commencement speech i could find
[Music]
now entering second half of show
it's been a while it's been a
while
second half of show
i received multiple emails
uh this over the past few days
about the earthquakes in nevada
exactly i didn't know either
i'm like
there's earthquakes in nevada
what's
going on
it was i saw a couple of
headlines about
earthquakes in nevada
uh so we had dame angela who uh
said it but like 30 or 40 of
them it was
all day long and yeah and
people were a
little concerned
but now there's fracking going
on
somewhere well that's what you
think but
we have a boots on the
on the ground report from uh
sir joel so he's royalty you
know he's
legit
sir joel the skinny trucker
battle-born
black baron of the northern
nevada
certainly you've heard of him
here he is
with his earthquake report
hey adam and john this is joel
the
skinny trucker i'm also known as
sergio the battleborn black
baron of
northern nevada
just wanted to give you my
update on the
nevada earthquake that we had
early this morning on friday
may 15th
i was driving through pretty
much the
epicenter
exactly when it happened felt
the
truck shake a bit and i was
wondering
what's going on it's pretty
windy
but as i was going up the road
highway
95 there was one crack and i'm
like oh
that's strange that wasn't here
when i
drove down to tonopah from reno
and then
there was another crack
and then a third crack and i'm
like oh
there must have been an
earthquake and
lo and behold there was
but interesting thing that i
noticed
as this was happening i was
looking up
on the
the ridgeline of the mountains
to the
west and i saw this bright blue
light
behind the mountains and i'm
like i
wonder what that is because it
didn't
look like an
airplane or any kind of truck
light it
looked like something else so
if you guys know the area
middle nevada
western nevada it
is a lot of federal land
there's a huge
army depot
just north in hawthorne and
you know area 51 is not too far
away so
who knows maybe get the
theremin out
some tinfoil
and hopefully some other
producers have
some information that maybe can
shed
some light on the subject
but that's my take from
northern nevada
it's the battle born black baron
joel in the morning thank you
thank you
for your courage
in the morning thank you for
your
courage well northern nevada
and area 51
there's
not even close no i but i don't
think he
was insinuating was aliens
um i've been paying attention
to this
weird weather we have had
torrential downpour
literally just texas it's been
very
interesting
to see the weather patterns and
maybe uh
there's some
harp fire age going on who
knows i don't
know what's happening but the
blue light
out there
that's odd and these
earthquakes has
that happened before
like 30 40 earthquakes on a day
in
nevada maybe it has i don't know
there's an area in nevada where
they
have a lot of quakes it was a
but that was due to fracking
right
um well i don't know we'll keep
an eye
on it
i'm sure that we'll find out
nothing
oh you're so positive we'll
keep looking
we'll look and look we'll keep
looking
we're not going to get anywhere
with
this
all right any more screwball
reports
no i don't have that but i do
have an
update
on thousands of sealed
indictments yes
yes
yes i'm telling you everyone's
out on
the woodworks we've got
everyone talking
clappers on tv brennan's on tv
everyone's getting their points
in and i
think a good backgrounder is to
go
to the man who is the
mainstream gateway
for
thousands of sealed indictments
lou
dobbs on
fox uh business news and uh
here is uh
who i think is a good uh
journalist john solomon to
bring us the
lowdown
yeah everyone i've talked to
today has
been exasperated by the judge's
conduct
but at the end of the day it's
a lot of
show
for an inevitable conclusion at
the end
of the day
these charges are going to be
dismissed
against uh general flynn
because the law
requires it
when both parties go in as they
do in
this case and when there is a
preponderance of evidence as
there is in
this case of wrongdoing the
courts have
consistently allowed
a vacation or vacating of a
conviction like this it's just
going to
extend the drama a little
longer but
it's going to inevitably end up
whether
it's at the supreme court the
appellate
court
or the district court it's
going to end
up getting the the charges are
going to
be dismissed
finally and i do say finally uh
lindsey
graham has
scheduled a hearing to dig into
these
very serious issues i
i know his investigative staff
very well
they're very competent
they've been working very hard
behind
the scenes they're going to
have some
big
big revelations that are not
yet public
uh that will move this
narrative along
and show just how far reaching
the
corruption inside
the bureaucracy was uh as for
the issue
of president obama
you know there's gonna come a
moment
after that first evidence is
laid out in
his hearings
where people are going to
obviously say
hey this started at the top with
president obama
and then i think lindsey graham
will
have to face the music of his
own
evidence
and decide what he's going to
do and i
think that moment may you know
when the
evidence is all out there
there'll be an even more
poignant
question to the to the chairman
why aren't you talking to
president uh
obama and i think well you know
let's
see what the evidence comes out
but
keep in mind over the last few
months
there's been a lot of
information taken
from the national archives
from the obama administration
they lay
out a very powerful case
we're going to begin to see that
evidence over the next three
four weeks
and all i can say from what i
know from
my reporting is buckle your
seatbelt
buckle your seatbelt well well
first of all i am not buckling
my seat
belts
for starters uh-huh yeah no
kidding
because
nothing's coming up any of this
well i'm not so sure i think
that
something's going to happen we
you know
this flynn stuff
and the unmasking and fisa
court abuses
i i think
something will come of that but
we'll
well let me finish
it's easy to say i have i have
some some
i've received
have some backup um
there's a lot of running around
of
people coming out who haven't
spoken for
a long time and i think they're
all
jockeying and positioning
clapper seems
to be the the top guy
uh now this was cnn it was
uh people called this
differently than
it was
uh the way it was posted is oh
look he
asked him a tough question and
then the
connection breaks
but it actually you can hear a
little
truly an audio glitch
uh it froze right after the
first
question so he didn't he
probably didn't
even hear the second one but
that
doesn't mean that he wasn't
removed from
this
uh zoom call
uh so we could not answer
here's uh
clapper former director of
national
intelligence
uh and a liar uh a liar to
congress
uh but unindicted okay so
asking for
names
nothing wrong with that
unmasking in and
of itself nothing wrong with
that
leaking classified information
and by
definition these phone calls
were classified that's a
problem correct
uh absolutely it is um and if
anyone you
hear the little
that's when he cut out but
we'll do the
question anyway did leak
the contents of these
conversations with
or without the name
that would be a problem yes uh
we've
lost the shot i wonder if we
can at
least get him on the phone
to finish this let's try to get
director
clapper back all right we're
going to
work
we're going to work on getting
that shot
yeah so of course they did get
him back
later this question didn't come
up
but was he willing to testify
ah yeah
can you come in and testify
uh given my age demographic i'd
be happy
to come
uh after i've been vaccinated
for covert
19.
would you testify i could do it
remotely
as
the case with uh the faucet
hearing or
respond to questions or or or
that sort
of thing but
uh i don't particularly want to
put my
life or that on my
wife uh in life in jeopardy uh
for uh in pr in person testimony
yeah so basically not intending
to
testify to anything at all
because corona covid
the other guy out and about was
former
cia director
john brennan and uh have you
heard do
you know yet if his uh
clearance has been uh removed
no i just
got no information one way or
the other
we just don't know i'd like to
remind
you john brennan's uh stance
on uh the law and
when you are guilty or when you
should be sentenced or charged
it's very
short he's very clear
people are innocent until
alleged to be
involved in some type of
criminal
activity
so this would be guilty john
brennan who
was alleged to have some part in
criminal activity
and this is a longer clip uh
but it i
think it's
extra good because you can hear
well
we'll we'll discuss it
chris hayes and john brennan
there does
seem to be a bit of a shift
in the last several months with
william
barr at the department of
justice with
richard grinnell
at dni such that the actual
machinery
and tools of government are
being kind
of applied
along the lines of the rhetoric
of the
president how do you see things
right
now
well chris that's exactly why i
think
the recent developments are so
worrisome
because mr trump has removed
individuals
from the head of the intel's
community
as well as from the fbi as and
justice
and he's trying to put people
in who are
going to do his bidding
so we saw recently with the
acting
director of national
intelligence rich
purnell a hand-picked
individual who
i think has demonstrated his
loyalty to
mr trump over the years
um releasing uh declassifying
the names
of individuals who had
unmasked some names in
intelligence
reports
and with the implication that
that was
wrongdoing
well it wasn't carrying out our
responsibilities
incorrectly but then when i
look at the
attorney general mr barr
now so of course there's no
diving into
the fact that it was
39 people who were a
witness to or who had requested
and
received unmasking
but i guess that's just the job
carrying
out our responsibilities
correctly but then when i look
at the
attorney general mr barr
and how he has repeatedly
demonstrated
that his interest is being the
president's lawyer
as opposed to being the
people's lawyer
you need to get the updated
memo brennan
that's pretty old hat you're
repeating
there
uh and i'm very worried that the
instruments of governance
the instruments of intelligence
and law
enforcement and justice are now
being
exploited and manipulated in mr
trump's
hands and i think that's
something that
should worry all americans
it's one thing to have policy
differences and we can have
arguments in public about that
but if
he's going to try to bring
charges against individuals
trumped up
charges because of his political
interests
and he's going to have
individuals who
are going to help
make that happen that is
something that
i saw
overseas in my career my
national
security career
and i never thought i would see
that
happening here in the united
states
clearly back in the last
century in the
1970s
we had incidents where
president nixon
tried to use the fbi and cia
and others
for political purposes
and we had quite an uproar at
that time
and
president nixon was forced out
of office
sad to say that it sounds like
we are
now back in the same type of
environment
where an individual in the
white house
is now using
those organizations and using
people
in senior positions in
intelligence and
law enforcement for his
own purposes
that is the best example of
projection
i've heard from him
and says just like richard
nixon clearly
this president was using the
intelligence apparatus
to get at his enemies it's
exactly
what happened allegedly with
the whole
obama administration
if if that isn't rewriting the
history
the history of
nixon is also saying
out of the picture of these
guys oh this
guy is the worst
i think there's a fall guy the
cia
should be embarrassed that he
was ever
part of their operation yeah
there's one
little quick
thing a quick bite i got here
which may
be the fall guy because
someone's got to
go
i'm just hoping that
individuals like
chris ray who
is a remarkable public servant
will
continue to stay strong
in the face of this type of um
abominable
uh vulnerable uh
so chris ray's on the block
let's listen did he say obama
wow individuals like
chris ray who is a remarkable
public
servant
will continue to stay strong in
the face
of this type of
um abominable uh vulnerable
again abuse of authority oh man
obamable that's a great word
oh bombable but i think
christopher wray
is on the block
i think that may have been what
you just
heard there that clip
uh i think put put him on the
block
well that that would have been
part of
the part of the point
obamable.com registered done
i don't know why why but i need
it
and it's available right
obamable.com
that's right everybody i do a
podcast
you can find it at obamabull.com
yay and i think that uh
that's some other stuff um well
i got a
few things i want yeah
and we have our around the
around the
world
run around the world yeah you
want to
hear a few of those yeah run
around the
world
well let's start with the
funniest one
and i also have a sub clip for
it this
is covent new jersey
ah always a good time with
summer right
around the corner new jersey
announced
this week that beaches would be
open by
memorial day weekend with some
restrictions
the openings are weeks behind
other
coastal states like georgia and
florida
but as one of the state's
hardest hit by
the covet 19 pandemic
local officials say they are
proceeding
cautiously
at exactly 10 am yesterday
barriers that
had been blocking the boardwalk
and
beach in seaside heights new
jersey
were pushed aside an
announcement made
it official
these beaches are now
officially open
once again these beaches are now
officially open it's a sign
that things
are returning to normal in this
quintessential jersey shore town
sort of we're looking to see
how we do
with the social distance
and that's going to be our test
today
tony vaz is the mayor of
seaside heights
after nearly two months of
being closed
because of covet 19
visitors can now walk and ride
bikes on
the boardwalk
provided they heed the rule of
six feet
between groups of people
on the beach there's no
swimming or
sunbathing but the public can
walk
fish and even surf mayor vaz
says it's
just the first phase of seaside
heights
is reopening
i'm optimistic that this is a
good first
step
obviously i would love to see
everything
open i would love to see us
swimming
and so forth but we have to
recognize
that we have to take this in
steps
seaside heights is one of more
than
three dozen communities along
the jersey
shore
grappling with how best to
reopen in
neighboring seaside park
beaches are already open to
sunbathers
provided beachgoers keep their
distance
you know i was more interested
in this
this tony vaz
guy he sounds identical to joe
pesci
yeah it does a little bit
that's a
little bit a little bit i
actually have
a clip from further on in that
in that that presentation
and this is the 16 seconds of
him talk
this guy has a
voiceover gig anytime he wants
one then
he
by the way he's wearing a mask
so he's
kind of muffled but this is
tony vaz
talking a little bit more if we
just
obey the rules
you know you're going to stop
at a
stoplight yeah we gotta we
gotta whack
him
that's a rule so you know if
it's social
dissidency now social
distancing if you
know it's another
mandate follow it i'm not an
optimist it
has to get better i don't have
the
magical number when
it will get better yes
nailed it
we should find him and ask him
to do
some stuff for us i
i was thinking about it but
then again
i'm thinking i'm going to get a
call
back saying
you think i'm funny i can get a
visit
that's very good i like that
but sad man
what does new jersey become
i lived there for you know 12
years
jersey is
sad sad sad no i'm not 12. nine
years
just back back to the rundown
uh that
was jersey let's go to the
covet eu update with an
emphasis on
greece
covid eu a border
germany in switzerland was
dismantled
last night it's part of an
agreement by
those countries as well as
austria to
begin
opening borders again german
prime
minister angela merkel said
earlier this
week that she would like
all emergency border controls in
europe's 26th nation schengen
zone
removed by june 15th
also in germany the country's
premier
soccer league bundesliga
resumed play
today without
fans it is the world's first
major
soccer league to start up
following a
two-month pause due to the
coronavirus
pandemic
do they have fake fake
audiences i
have not heard i i have to
check that
out so far no
in greece more than 500 public
beaches
reopened today as the country
experienced its first heat wave
of
the year beachgoers were
required to
keep their distance as officials
stipulated how many people
could be on
the beach and exactly how far
apart
umbrellas needed to be
yes the beaches are back open
the
opening beaches is the first
major
easing of greece's coronavirus
lockdown
to date it has had just a
fraction of
the cases of many neighboring
countries
including turkey
starting tomorrow greeks will
be allowed
to attend church
and tourism officials hope to
welcome
back foreigners in july
no wow so they got nothing
going on it's
not is underreported nobody
wants to
talk about greece why they have
less
cases
maybe there's something they're
taking
they may be taking up a
prophylactic
like uh
hydroxychloroquine is it
possible nah
can't be could never that
doesn't work
the shit doesn't work you need
rem
disappear that's the one that
keeps you
alive somewhat longer i don't
know you
need the approved one
uh coved brazil pbs brazil we
are really
doing a run around brazil's
health
minister resigned last night
after just
one month on the job the
shake-up comes
as the number of coronavirus
infections in brazil continues
to rise
nelson taisha did not provide a
reason
for his resignation but it came
just a
day after brazilian president
jair
bolsonaro
pressured him to accept the use
of
chloroquine to treat coping 19
patients
the drug which is used to treat
malaria
has been praised as a
therapeutic for
the new disease by bolsonaro and
president trump
though it lacks scientific
support
bullshit
brazil has become an epicenter
of the
coronavirus outbreak setting
daily
records for infections each of
the last
three days
on friday the health ministry
confirmed
more than fifteen thousand new
infections
despite relatively low rates of
testing
if i may compliment you
it takes a real professional to
hold on
to a
surprise edit clip until the
very end of
the show i
i commend you sir that was well
done
very good
i got you off guard yes you did
not out
of it
you made me feel good overseas
in china
officials said they marked one
full
month with no new cova deaths
but vulnerable populations like
here in
bangladesh
are bracing for a blow in this
crowded
camp
home to one million rohingya
muslims the
first coronavirus case was
confirmed
just today
huh there you have it yeah
well i thought our boots on the
ground
from wuhan was better
well anything is better at
least we got
people on the ground in wuhan
well is that the same guy wrote
as the
note initially when this whole
thing
broke open yes yes yes yes
that's the
guy yeah
we're good we have some of the
best i
was let me just check and make
sure i
didn't miss any of these uh at
the
worsting home
nursing home the wuhan i want
to thank
dr disorder for uh
sending us our no agenda mask
not the
ones we ordered but he there
was a
cancellation so he sent
the keeper wants the 1984 mask
which is
coming i hope
she wants to proudly wear that
which is
a good one
um i think yeah
these are all be good i do i
could play
a little moro with the biden i
could
play the shields and brooks on
the pbh
resources
let's get out of here on
something happy
that's happy
okay what is it it's
just too depressing from the
same side
of the political agenda
standing in their in their
homes and one
of them worried sick the other
one too
old to care
let's listen to shields and
brooks uh
and it reveals that joe biden
is a very transparent person
the the
culture they describe is
certainly the
culture i knew when i was
covering senator biden and the
person i
know him to be and
it raises more skepticism about
the
claims
i would say this and in
addition there's
a politico report looking into
some of
terrorite's past allegations in
other
cases other parts of her life
and i think the bottom line is
if you
were a person who was
saying should this issue be a
problem
for me in voting
for joe biden i think the arrow
has
moved into less of a problem we
don't
know that it didn't happen
we we can't know that but
certainly the
um
the degree of skepticism has to
be a
little higher because of this
reporting
and mark i mean you're somebody
who's
covered the city for a long
time you've
walked the halls of the
the senate office buildings but
what do
you come away with here
well i come away first of all
with great
admiration for both police and
dan
i mean 74 people on the record
uh is
remarkable that
meant a couple hundred calls
they had to
make uh to get that
okay now what i wanted to while
i played
that clip because i was gonna
play a
series of clips where they pbs
i'll
play maybe play it next
thursday they
took their two lisa desjardins
some
other guy
and they went and they
investigated lisa
is not a yes
they spent a fortune um
investigating the tara reads
story by
talking to old staffers and
they talked
it they tried to
contact 200 people and they
contacted 75
and got
or got 75 on the record and
shields is impressive they got
75 people
on the record to
to do full interviews and i'm
as i'm
listening to the one overlooked
fact here is that the new york
times and
the washington post
do stories with nobody on the
record
they don't talk to 200 people
right
they don't talk to anybody and
they have
just as sources somebody thinks
that
somebody heard
somebody else said something
about
something no they talked to the
campaign
about it that
that's what they did and they
removed a
part of their reporting that
talked
about the pattern of him
fondling and touching people
which was
not a problem at all
so you end up with the anomaly
where pbs
just a tv show it's not even
any good
anymore
get 75 people to talk on their
record
about a specific thing
and the newspapers who have
people that
are supposed to be doing this
making a
lot of phone calls
they get nobody for anything
it's
unbelievable
well i just thought it was it
was
remarkable that then pbs they
why they have to do that many
people
what was that what are they
trying to
prove
and did they talk about any of
their
research or is that the series
of clips
you want to do that on
you want to do that now the
series of
clips well yeah we have time
i'll do the
series of clubs let's start
there's only
three of them okay
and the the longest one is the
first one
and we'll play that two months
ago
allegations arose accusing
former vice
president joe biden of sexual
assault
tara reid who in 1993 worked in
the
office of
then senator biden said that he
assaulted her
biden has categorically denied
the
allegations which now face
examination from the public our
own dan
bush and lisa desjardins
did extensive reporting talking
to 74
former biden staffers to learn
more
about the vice president
the culture in his offices and
their
thoughts on the allegations
the two join me now to share
what
they've learned hello to both
of you
and i'm going to turn to you
both but
lisa
to you to begin take us through
what you
did
and and what you learned in all
from
talking to all these people
yeah judy we reached out to uh
tried to
reach out to some 200 former
biden
staffers
of that we were able to have
in-depth
interviews with some 74 of them
now 62 of these former staffers
were
women
and to a person judy those
women told us
they had never had
any experience that was
uncomfortable
with the former vice president
or had
ever heard of any experience it
was
uncomfortable
or worse many of them said they
had
spent time with him alone
during work hours and that they
had they
wanted to say that they
most of them didn't want to
reflect on
whether what tara reed is
saying is true
or not
but they did say that it did
not reflect
their experiences at all
especially in a workplace that
dan and i
both heard from them
they felt empowered women
that's right
lisa i would add to that also
that a lot
of the former staffers
we spoke to said that while
they never
felt uncomfortable
they did confirm what we all
know about
joe biden which is
his history his habit of
reaching out
making physical contact with
people he
speaks to touching them we
spoke to
people who said at the time of
this it
was known about biden
that he would rub your
shoulders squeeze
your shoulders give people hugs
and kisses and again while the
people we
spoke to said that they
themselves
didn't feel uncomfortable
they did acknowledge that vice
former
vice president
biden doesn't seem to have
strong
a strong social signal in terms
of when
that kind of contact
is wanted or not that came up
last year
on the campaign trail
and now again here oh
man now they did dig up two
interesting little tidbits
which are i
don't know if they're important
or not
and they're trying to they're
really
going out of their way to
protect biden
so
is the candidate let's face it
no
kidding yeah let's listen to
clip two and lisa you also uh
uncovered
frankly
new details that reflect on
tara reed's
allegation that
she says she was forced out of
the
office because she
complained about uh being
uncomfortable
about this sexual
uh incident uh tell us exactly
what you
learned about that and why it
matters
well tara reid said that she
complained
about previous sexual harassment
in the office and that after she
complained
she says she was retaliated
against and
for in a couple of ways and
that that
eventually forced her out of
the office
we spoke to the man who shared
an office
with her
his name is ben savage they
worked
together on constituent
mail ben savage told us that
actually it was a performance
problem
with tara reid
that he himself raised two
supervisors
in some cases he said
she was throwing out constituent
important records of
constituent mail
and that the problem was bad
enough that
he raised it to supervisors
he believes that's why she left
and
here's some of the interview
that i had
with him over the phone
and of all the people who held
that
position she's the only one
during my
time there
who couldn't necessarily keep
up who
felt or who found it frustrating
we of course reached out to
tara reed
she declined our request for an
interview but her
attorney did give us detailed
responses
to our questions among them
to this exact issue he said
that story
is flat wrong
here is what doug wigtor wrote
us in
response he wrote miss reed
recalls that
there was a lot of nitpicking
regarding
her performance in the office
she was also very nervous at
that point
and distracted so it's possible
that
from time to time there was a
mistake
made
but her performance had nothing
to do
with her termination
and judy we do know that reed
worked in
that office for about nine
months
wait a minute she says she was
i thought
she left she was terminated
yeah um well then there's a
then there's
a termination letter and there's
something there that i have
somebody's to have some
documentation
for this and by the way
how what kind of a job are you
going
through mail
this is not a complicated job
that you
can't oh she can't keep up
come on with bull crap i worked
in the
government discussion
did they uh now how was this
report
presented this is it this is the
presentation of their findings
or they
have a package or
no no there's no package but
there's a
little bit of a package in this
last
clip where this guy goes on to
which i have to explain after
the
presentation this is the
part three and and dan you also
learned
uh
new information from reed's
attorney
about the location that tara
reid
says is where joe biden
assaulted her so
tell us about that
that's right judy reid's
attorney
provided us with new information
about this assault this alleged
assault
saying that reid claims that it
took
place somewhere between
the russell building where
biden had an
office at the time
and the u.s capitol building we
want to
show you
what these spaces look like so
this is
the hallway where biden's
office was
it's essentially unchanged to
now
to get to the capitol you go
down a
flight of stairs
and then take a tunnel where
there's a
subway that takes lawmakers to
the
capital
building now anybody who has
been to
this part of the capital knows
that
there are a lot of people
moving through
these spaces especially when
congress is
in session
lawmakers their aides reporters
there's
a police presence
as well and what a lot of these
former
biden staffers told us
is look these are public places
uh
if this allegation is true if
it took
place it would have been
extremely brazen judy because
the
likelihood
that it would have been seen by
someone
was very high
man if well i
gotta give you an explanation
of what
these showed first he showed
the big
long hallway
there was nobody there then he
showed a
spot where there's that little
little subway system and
there's a crowd
there and then he showed
another shot
there was
zero people he's going on and
on about
all the people
in these photos helping the
empty photo
empty empty corridors
well um i don't know what
happened we
we will not know we'll never
know
believe all women
whatever uh the fact of the
matter is
look here's the deal
joe biden is not qualified to
run for
anything
it's a sham i don't know what's
going on
i don't know why they're doing
this
it makes no sense and i would
hope that we remember the
people who
were speaking so
glowingly and lovingly about
joe biden
about his experience and what a
great
president he'll make
in these days specifically
because i'd
like to talk to those people
after whatever happens happens
because
it'll become apparent that this
was a
scam whether he gets in office
or not is
going to be a parent
yeah i don't get it personally
i don't
know what what's the point of it
unless it's just to put
somebody in the
vice president's slot that you
know you
can't get elected
uh amy klobuchar be a good
example no
one's voting for her she did
poorly in
all the
uh primaries uh but you can get
her in
as president and she'd be a good
bureaucrat
and as long as she's a
globalist it's
good to go
i mean they're trying to get a
globalist
back in the in the office and
get back
on track here of
turning the country over or
national
sovereignty should be turned
over to a
one-world government that's
obviously
what's going on
and there are people that
advocate for
that and that's the corona
thing is all
about that
well i i i think joe biden is
right i
think he's very smart he stays
in his
basement i think it's very
uh intelligent of his campaign
they do
not let
any outsiders in from comcast
or any
smart people who are going to
come in
and fix their sound
because the likelihood of him
being
killed is high right now
certainly in the corona period
we'd have
a great excuse
i i fear for joe's life at this
point
there's no way
anyone who was running any show
at the
democratic national party or the
democratic party
thinks that this guy is
actually going
to be something worth anything
as a
president
it's just i i i just totally
disagreement with you
you're speaking from a logical
perspective as if the democrats
are
logical i'm i'm waiting for you
i i just think they're
illogical i think
they're they're sincere
i think they sincerely think
this guy's
going to be a great president
they're keeping most of the
gaffes out
of the public eye so that so
the public
doesn't notice
and so we can get in they they
believe
their own publicity so when
they see a
washington
post poll that says that
biden's going
to beat trump by 10 points they
all
i think they believe it i don't
think
they they think that is bull
crap
i think well this guy's a
winner this
guy can beat trump that's all
we want
this guy can beat trump yeah
maybe he
won't be the best guy
but he can beat trump and he's
a good
guy he's one of ours he's one
of our
guys and he's next on the list
and he's
the guys
up next up the bat no matter
what
strategy you look at
it's apparent that uh people
are being
chosen around him
or so or selected or people are
getting
ready in case
he either dies in office and
okay we disagree on this but
the way
this is being run
and if you're telling me that
the people
who run the dnc i'm not talking
about
democrats i'm talking about the
the prostitutes on television
they're
just doing what they're told to
do i'm
sure they believe
but this to me sounds like a
setup for
someone who is not nominated
someone who
is not running
someone who is going to have to
come in
and save the day when something
bad
happens to joe
that is a scenario that has to
be looked
at well that brings hillary
back into
the mix
thank you very much that's all
i can
think of
and if if not that then yeah
then people
are just
delusional because this man is
not
appropriate
for any kind of public office
the right
word
any kind of public office well
hillary
again is the one that
could be targeting the whole
thing she
could be behind everything i
mean their
their machine still exists
and there's a lot of support
for it and
it i think the general public
in the
united states will get
extremely irked at this point
if hillary swoops in because i
i think
they're going to see
the whole thing was it was a
setup
what's the point what is that
what's
wrong with the democrats that
they can't
find anybody how about this
first
scenario wait a minute let me
she's flying over hold on you
got to be
careful once you
those low flyby she does are a
little
dangerous feel the flapping of
her wings
aiming for
trump's hair so how about this
how about we choose an
african-american
woman for vice president
joe croaks then we get hillary
as
president black hillary as vice
president
how does hillary get in well if
joe
croaks
is he going to crook before or
after no
no no before the nomination of
course
before yeah of course before the
announcement he's gonna have to
croak
within the next two months
and the clock is ticking the
biden
cro croak countdown clock has
started
t minus two months i hope not
but i don't know well i hope
not too i'd
rather see joe in it
much more entertaining much
more much
more entertaining
uh that is it for our
deconstruction for
today we have end of show mixes
uh
coming up
from jesse coy nelson we've got
us some
uh aaron uh aaron yoho who
supported uh the show earlier
today and
after this on no
agendastream.com
uh mo fax episode 37 a shell
game
hear more about that uh biden bp
scenario
until then i am coming to you
from
opportunity zone 33 here in
austin texas
capital of the drone star state
fema region number six on the
governmental maps if you're
looking for
my body bag
and please remember us at
dvorak.org
n a to support the no agenda
show after
all you're a producer too
in the morning everybody i'm
adam curry
and from northern silicon valley
where it rained again last
night which
is very screwy
uh maybe it's got something to
do with
something i don't know i'm john
cena
borax we return on thursday
right here
on no agenda until then adios
[Music]
so groups of people standing
outside an
ice cream parlor or
maybe they're playing pickup
basketball
sharing a sidewalk on a nice day
weeks ago these were everyday
activities
but the coronavirus
has changed everything if i see
something
that i don't think is right
especially
now i'm going to challenge it
social distancing complaints
are drawing
shame on social media
and calls to the police corona
corona corona virus corona virus
corona virus coronaviruses like
this
i don't know i don't know i
don't know
let's listen to the scientists
vaccine
vaccine or no vaccine with the
mask on
it's most dangerous
social distance it's contagious
don't be stupid or amazing
while driving entertain us
building gates crouching
focusing
quarantine ochioche
[Music]
don't be stupid
the neil ferguson imperial
college model
shacked up with his mistress
when he was
supposed to be yes
sheltered in place yeah that's
the one
and you recall that he built
these
models
not on rock and roll but on 13
year old
undocumented
don't you remember he built
his bottles he put
his bottles us
you know
[Music]
[Applause]
he
is
[Music]
[Applause]
someone in that troll room is
out of
[Music]
control
we're in the middle of a
pandemic