John C Dvorak: I buy a bar a
month.
Unknown: Adam curry, John C.
Dvorak.
Adam Curry: October 12 2023 This
Year Award winning give a nation
media assassination episode
1598.
Unknown: This is no agenda,
Adam Curry: penetrating the fog
of war and broadcasting live
from the heart of the country
near FEMA Region number six in
the morning, everybody. I'm Adam
curry,
John C Dvorak: from Northern
Silicon Valley where today's
theme is babies. I'm John C.
Dvorak.
Adam Curry: Kill. My goodness,
we're just going back in time.
Everything to read rerun. It's a
total rerun. I might as well I
got the clips, I might as well
run them. They're all pretty
short. Let's just go right for
it.
John C Dvorak: Well, before you
do that, I have a three clip set
disparate disparate clips that
I'd like to run first. Oh, no,
no, dog. No,
Adam Curry: Phoebe says. Daddy
slipped these clips. Phoebe. All
right.
John C Dvorak: Dose got a great
bark.
Adam Curry: I should run it
through the through the next
time she does that. I'll run it
through the sound effects. Well,
you should be recording
John C Dvorak: it up. There's
nothing a dog finds more
annoying than playing dog barks
back to them.
Adam Curry: Oh, yeah. I'm sure
this will drive the dog crazy.
All right. Well, well, you I
mean, this is what we call
John C Dvorak: this is just
theory. This reason is because
this is involving Chris Cuomo.
It's what we call an audible.
And here we go. This is
distarch. With this clip, which
is a Hannity show. He brings it
some Trumps to John, and it
begins with this. Joining us
now. former national security
adviser Robert O'Brien is with
us. When Bibi Netanyahu says
that they will strike with a
force that will be remembered
for generations. I've known
Prime Minister Netanyahu now for
almost three decades. I'm pretty
much 100% certain he means what
he says. He says the Middle East
will be reconfigured as a result
of this, you know, evil attack
on on their homeland. I believe
he means it.
Unknown: What are your thoughts?
Well, I know Bibi will also shot
and I think he means what he
says here and like he's got no
choice. I mean, if anyone who
wants to know that whether evil
exists in the world, just need
to look at the top of your
monologue and hear about the
babies being killed. I mean,
what kind of person goes house
to house and beheads babies and
these aren't civilians who were
killed collaterally in a in a
military attack. These were
civilians who are wanted they
slaughtered? This isn't war This
is barbarism?
Adam Curry: I think that's the
new thing to be able to say now
if you're on television, it's
like I know BB well.
John C Dvorak: I know BP Well. I
Adam Curry: know BB. I know.
Yeah, baby. You met baby.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, baby new
horse with the actress. Okay.
All right. Next up and you're
desperate Clint. Now we go to
Cuomo calling out Hamas.
Unknown: Nobody wants to see
pictures of mutilated children.
I promise you that
Adam Curry: well, that we
actually would like to see it
just to know that it's real.
Yeah, because it's only the news
guys
John C Dvorak: real pictures, of
course, not photoshopped ones.
But
Unknown: however, the reality
should not be shied away,
because it's what's driving the
understanding of this situation.
People in America especially
have a misguided connection
between the plight of
Palestinians, which is real, the
suffering there, which is real
and going on right now. People
are dying in Gaza because of
Israel's necessary retaliation.
I'm sure kids are involved there
too. In essence, you're involved
there too. You should be seeing
the pictures to drive the
intensity of the purpose here.
And we have to remember that our
urgency is on those who were
captured, not hostages, not
hostages. hostages are people
who are taken for security. And
they are negotiated. These
people were captured. They're
being mutilated. They're being
brutalized in ways that very few
people have seen in this region
in a long, long time. And
remember, it is on Hamas, to
counteract what I just said, it
is on Hamas to come forward and
say, No, we're holding them
humanely, because we want
protection against what Israel
is doing because we want to
negotiate because we want to be
taken seriously. This is on
Hamas, Hamas loves to talk
they're putting out videos all
over the internet of complete
barbarism and savagery. They
have said Not one word about
treating these people as human
beings. And they have given us
all the evidence and
understanding that they are
treating them worse than dogs.
Adam Curry: Okay, yes, let's
spin people up to school.
John C Dvorak: You know, it took
me all of five minutes to find
out that Hamas had said plenty I
guess He didn't have the time to
do it because he's flying over
there wants to hang out.
Adam Curry: He's played this
year in the region cromoz in the
region. Yes, he
John C Dvorak: went there
because it's in the region
thing.
Adam Curry: It's called in the
region. Yeah, he's
John C Dvorak: in the region. He
is in Israel, but it's Northern
Israel, it
Adam Curry: seems to be in the
region.
John C Dvorak: So region is the
region. So here's Hamas
Palestinian denials,
Unknown: because I'm brigades
has broadcast a video that shows
the release of three captives
that the video shows an Israeli
woman and two children near the
holiday kibbutz near Gaza. They
were said to have been released
shortly after being captured by
Hamas on Saturday. Hamas sources
say that video refutes what they
called false Israeli allegations
that Hamas fighters killed women
and children are the video
follows an earlier statements by
the group that said, Some
Western media outlets continue
to spread Zionist slander and
lies about our Palestinian
people and their resistance,
which falsely and slanderously
promoted allegations that
members of the Palestinian
resistance, beheaded children
and assaulted women without any
evidence to support their lives
and claims Hamas strongly
condemns the baseless
allegations
Adam Curry: and that's on Al
Jazeera so that's that's more
more official than it would be
on on x which is probably all
Cuomo is looking at. We want
everybody to
John C Dvorak: know what Cohen
was looking at took me five
minutes to find that clip. And
this is an Hamas had made these
statements earlier way before he
came off and you act in the act.
But this is the problem you have
is that our media is just not
good. No, and if you're right,
yes, you're right. And if you
listen to the I mean, I didn't
clip it because I got too many
clips already and this is cut
you can
Adam Curry: well let me let me
jump into into some beheaded
baby clips.
John C Dvorak: I want to mention
one thing to listen to judge
Jeanine and these others on the
five judge Jeanine is back to
her bomb them bomb them bomb
them again, don't really it's
it's fascinating. I didn't clip
it. I maybe I'll clip it for
Sunday, but she's just off the
rails.
Adam Curry: And but but is she
about bombing? Because back in
the day, that was
John C Dvorak: the Qaeda. Yes,
Unknown: bomb them, bomb them
and bomb them again.
John C Dvorak: Now, she made the
statement. And again, like I
said, I got too many clips
already. But I'll tell you what
she said. She said they're
coming here.
Adam Curry: Oh, yeah. Okay. Let
me that's you're moving too
fast. First, we got to know that
the bait the beheaded baby
story. Which has apparently
already been debunked by the
journalist who wrote about it
who said I didn't really write
about I want to clarify, I did
not tweet, which is by the way,
what journalism are we
performing here?
Unknown: Look at a journalism is
this I did not
Adam Curry: tweet 40 babies had
been beheaded. I tweeted that
form media had been told women
and children had been
decapitated. But we had not been
shown bodies, which was my
response to reports which had
gone viral about the 40 babies.
Also this number 40 is
interesting. I realized the way
my talk was, I don't know. 40
days. 40 Nights. It's all Oh,
John C Dvorak: Arabian Nights.
Yeah.
Adam Curry: Oh, yeah. Which is,
I realized, I realized the way
my tweet was written was too
short to explain the full
context. So I deleted it. All
right now, but this this went
quite viral. Of course. I mean,
we've seen this end of show make
sure even here. Some historical
examples we
John C Dvorak: have one of the
Indus show mixes is dynamite. We
had the
Adam Curry: babies on Bay Bay
and nets we had the babies and
incubators that they threw on
the floor. And this is just a
new twist. This is This is
Nicole Zedeck. From by the way,
John C Dvorak: the babies I'm
paying this I should go we
should mention this because I've
never mentioned the show before
but when you study world
history, there's this was the
same baby stories that were told
during the during the Vikings
invasions of northern Europe. It
was the day we're told that the
Vikings came in and grabbed the
babies and then threw them in
the air and then caught them
with their
Adam Curry: horns their horns,
their horns on their on their
John C Dvorak: doors, but the
spears they spear them. The
babies the babies flying through
the air. So this is not a new
No,
Adam Curry: it's late. It's a
true and tried tactic which
works incredibly well. So here's
the same Nicole Zedek who's who
tweeted X she slashed. Soldiers
told me they believe 40 Babies
slashed children were killed.
The exact death toll is still
unknown as the military
continues to go house to house
and find more Israeli
casualties. I 24 News. So Here's
her report,
Unknown: David, it's hard to
even explain exactly just the
mass casualties that happened
right here. In fact, the Israeli
Miller Jury says they still
don't have a clear number. But
I'm talking to some of the
soldiers and they say what
they've witnessed as they've
been walking through these
different houses, these
different communities, babies,
their heads caught off. That's
what they said, done down,
families completely gunned down
in their beds. You can see some
of these soldiers right now
comforting each other. Many of
them reserves who jumped into
action, leaving their own
families behind as well. Not
knowing the sheer horror that
they were about to come to. They
say they've never experienced
anything like this. This is
nothing that anyone could have
even imagined. When you're
walking through here, baby cribs
thrown to the side.
Adam Curry: There you go. So she
actually didn't say that she had
seen it herself. It's what
soldiers told her. But that was
enough. That was enough. And it
doesn't matter what Nicole's ex
says. Because our President saw
evidence proof he saw it with
his own eyes
Unknown: just came to basically
I really mean it from the bottom
of my heart. I give him my word
as a Biden. Thank you. There you
go.
Thank you for the intensity of
your support. It matters. It
matters in Americans see what's
happening. I have been doing
this a long time. I never really
thought that I would see
confirmed pictures of terrorist
behavior
Adam Curry: children. So we saw
it with his own eyes confirmed.
It's confirmed people. And then
he he goes into his tip when he
lies. He always goes into this.
Unknown: I never saw it ever.
Anyway.
Adam Curry: Anyway, anyway,
anyway, not to get the actual
report that you will probably,
uh, maybe maybe the five we'll
talk about it. But the White
House jumped into into immediate
crisis mode, because Oh, no, no,
no, he didn't quite mean that.
Unknown: Now. We have some
latest updates coming in from
the US a White House
spokesperson has given an
official clarification, as
reported by US media, that
neither President Joe Biden nor
the White House Administration
has seen any pictures or
verified any reports of children
beheaded by Hamas. Earlier
during a roundtable with leaders
from the Jewish community. Biden
had mentioned seeing the
confirmed pictures of militants
beheading children. The official
clarified though, that the
President's remarks were quote,
unquote, referring to public
comments from media outlets and
Israeli officials.
Adam Curry: Okay. All right,
please. He's an old, old man, he
senile, so don't you get it? And
at this point, I think the
international press is like,
yeah, we get it. Okay. Oh, you
made a mistake. Very, very,
very, very bad.
John C Dvorak: Mistake. I saw it
with my own eyes firmed
confirmed, confirmed.
Adam Curry: So this now. And let
me just as predicted, we got
some emails, and I just want to
reiterate that we're not I mean,
we don't really care one way or
the other, you know, about this
particular stuff. You know, it's
it's fun to fun to debunk it and
take a you know, a helicopter
view. But this is not about who
did what to whom, what we're
trained to do is to look at how
everybody is being spun up and
programmed against each other.
In fact, arguing against each
other is part of the point.
Distraction, which is beautiful,
because we don't hear about
Hunter don't hear about him
anymore. No hunters out of the
news. Look at the Gaza border,
not your border. We got a war
president now as good for
elections. You never want to
change a winning team. You know,
we've been spun up to believe
that tomorrow October the 13th
attacks in America attacks in
America. It's gonna happen
everywhere. This is where Judge
Jeanine gets it. She's probably
on the same hill country, Lady
text, text tree that I've been
seeing. But really it's all
recall. Then even just saying
911 That it doesn't matter who
you are even. Even the crackpot
in the buzzkill have oh, we get
you know, you get images, you
know where you were at that
moment? 911 911 911 This is the
Israel's 911 And so that means a
plan. What what?
John C Dvorak: Why is it January
6 Worse than 911
Adam Curry: It was funny the
last time and not
John C Dvorak: just my material
once in a while. You just
Adam Curry: spiking the ball
because it was genius. So it's
so the plan unfolds and in there
and reminder. After 911 on 911
Osama bin Laden Osama bin Laden
Osama bin Laden is Osama bin
Laden. Afghanistan Of course. I
mean no Iraq Iraq aluminum
tubes, yellowcake The New York
Times lied. The government lie
to get everyone agrees, I think
Now that we were lied to, to get
us into, of into Iraq, which is
not where Osama came from, but
of course, it was a genius
liquidity event of some $20
trillion, I think,
John C Dvorak: over 20 plus
years lot. Yeah, 20 trillion.
But
Adam Curry: I think if you look
it up, it may even be more than
20 trillion. I know. Okay, I'll
consult the book of knowledge
while we listen to the Israeli
ambassador to the UK, because
it's not just 911 Oh, no,
Unknown: this is our obligation,
our first obligation to fight
back and to make sure Hamas will
never have the ability to act
against Israelis,
Ambassador to totally How are
you at responding to the fact
that this is really creating a
whole host of tensions around
the world that have become sort
of ethnically focused on both
sides? It really has erupted
debates and protests and anger
on both sides. How would you
like to angle the conversation
to be able to foster something
more productive?
I think that this is time to
fight and to descend the people
of Israel. And I think whoever
saw the fact that 1000 Israelis
were killed in cold blood cannot
speak now about both sides.
There is one side here, who's
the side that wants freedom,
democracy, cares about human
rights, cares about people's
life, which is the Israeli side,
and there is the other side,
this is good versus evil, we
need to fight it. It's a terror
organization recognized in the
US and in the UK. And you know,
many people are comparing to
911. And I heard many people
that are making the equivalent
numbers with the proportion when
you think about Israel as a tiny
country, just 9 million people
to actually 10 times of 911.
This is the time to support
Israel, the international
community should understand.
Adam Curry: It's 10 times 911.
And then this comparison of
capita no but that came out
right away Sir Brian of London,
he immediately it was put into
his head and I'm not disputing
that this isn't you know that
this is the same vibe because
yeah, in in Israel, everybody
knows everybody. They're all
related. They as by their own
admission, but the 911 meme,
that's a good one. We got to
play that up. Let's bring in
James Stavridis. Admiral Joining
John C Dvorak: us now with more
is former Supreme Allied
Commander of NATO
Adam Curry: Supreme Allied
Commander, I'm sorry, Admiral,
James got his honorifics, right?
John C Dvorak: Staff Rita's know
where to start here. Admiral. It
take hostages, it's the
Adam Curry: same. It's exactly
the same tone as 911. They have
the the news media, which flips
right into it, no problem. And
it's it's normal, because
they've been told 10 times worse
than 911. Oh,
John C Dvorak: you bring them
back to Gaza. And you put them
in civilian areas, and you
surround yourself with
civilians, and then you threaten
Israelis. If there's any, any
bombing where civilians are
injured, you start executing
hostages, it's what is that you
know who's supposed to do when
you hear something like that?
Unknown: Well, you start by
calling all of this what it is,
which is terrorism. These are
acts of terror. This is akin to
the 911 attack. And just a lot
of people hear some of these
numbers. You know, there have
been hundreds of Israelis killed
and there are 150 hostages. To
put that in context. Joe, for an
American, you have to do the
math of the population adjust.
Here we go. If you have the
math, for example, 1000 Israelis
killed, I think it would be well
north of that. Ultimately,
that's like 35,000 Americans
killed on an equivalent 911 day.
And by the way on 911. There
weren't hostages. So let's say
there are 100 hostages that
would be 911 in the United
States with 3500 hostages. So
you're right.
John C Dvorak: That someone
yesterday said it was like
Nagasaki, I think it was
Jonathan Greenblatt on another
network. It wasn't like 911 It
was almost like if you do the
math,
Adam Curry: yeah. Do the math.
Okay. So the you know,
John C Dvorak: okay, I want to
say a couple of things. First of
all the 911 analogies bad. That
was four guys, they took this
store some planes and blew up
pretty much took out a building
one shot do they want people
industries, they weren't rating
a dance party and shooting up
the day did I mean, there was
that was a massacre where the
260 kids were killed. It's it
seems more like a extended
version of you know, that
shooter in Las Vegas where they
just started picking off poor
innocents that were at a dance,
country and western dance. The
911 thing just eludes me right
now is really
Adam Curry: an illusion
seriously,
John C Dvorak: there's
absolutely so little to do with
911 It's just the use of the
term and it the whole thing by
bothers me it's not as though a
number of people weren't killed.
And that's bad enough, John, why
are we going through the massive
trouble of equating it to this
and that and making stuff up and
making it worse than it already
is?
Adam Curry: Because it is. It's
beyond me what's not beyond me
and all it's clear as day. By
the way, Brown University says
the cost of the 20 year war was
$8 trillion. Okay, 8 trillion.
Now, the whole point is
playbook. That's the whole
point. We got to do it all over
again, we know where it leads.
We know it leads to Iran. That's
that's it's obvious that's
that's always been in play.
It'll probably go first to
Hezbollah. And we have which
would be Lebanon, and we have to
get everyone into that mode.
911 911 We need money. We need
money, money, money, money,
money, and we have a bad guy. We
have an Osama bin Laden. It is
so unbelievably close to the
original 911 story. It's crazy.
Unknown: This is one of the only
known photos of Muhammad if it
dates from 1989 when he was 24
years old years before he became
a massive military mastermind.
He lives in hiding in Gaza. His
face hasn't been seen publicly
in years. But according to
Israeli reports, he's been heard
speaking about the weekend
attacks on Israel in this video
Adam Curry: remember when we had
we only had cave audio from
Osama bin Laden? Remember that?
Oh, yes, we have audio from him
in the cave, giving the
instructions which had no idea
what he was saying, Oh, we only
have audio of Muhammad if he'd
seen publicly
Unknown: in years. But according
to Israeli reports he's been
heard and heard speaking about
the weekend attacks on Israel in
this video released by Hamas has
led her masters military wing
the Alka some brigades for two
decades, as seen in this 2003
report by French TV network
false television he was already
in hiding.
Why? We the fighters of the Alka
Sombra gates confirmed there
will be no negotiations with
Israel or the US whether
even before he commanded the
brigades de F led a wave of
suicide bombings that killed
dozens of Israelis than under
his leadership, Mr. switched its
primary tactic to cross border
raucous attacks from Gaza. ATF
has escalated these
indiscriminate attacks into a
multi pronged assault, directly
targeting Israeli civilians in
their own homes.
Easy to remember those
rhinoplasty were at an impasse.
They saw that the old methods
weren't working. And they also
realized that by doing this,
they succeeded in creating
terror, creating huge
psychological effects.
Over the years staff has
survived multiple attempts on
his life,
wait for the wounded in previous
Israeli assassination attempts
from 2001 onwards. There are
reports that he has lost an eye
there are reports that he has
lost at least one limb.
Earlier this week, Israeli
airstrikes hit Muhammad day of
his family home reportedly
killing several of his immediate
relatives. DFC exact location is
unknown.
Adam Curry: I'm gonna bet you he
shows up in Iran. I'm just I'm
just gonna guess that that might
be a good place for the this guy
is profile hasn't been spun up
enough yet. This is France 24.
But a one eyed one legged
bandit, like Osama bin Laden is
a step above. I mean, this is
this is really taking it all the
way you watch this guy be played
UPS exactly the same script as
911. And now we have to continue
to create strife inside our own
countries. We have to make sure
that we're all yelling, you
know, if you're not for this
group, You're horrible. If
you're not for that group,
You're horrible. Bring on the ad
L on MSNBC What a match made in
heaven.
Unknown: The thing that's so
challenging vexing about this is
people are saying well, could
this escalate into a wider war?
It is a water war. This is Al
Qaeda from from al Qaeda to ISIS
to Hamas. He says what Islamic
radicalism, jihadism looks like,
again, it doesn't seek a
peaceful resolution of a
conflict. This was not some
inevitable outcome. This was a
pre planned massacre, and how
did they send 1000s of missiles
into Israel? Because they were
supplied by Iran. And we'll ask
those questions. We will wonder
about
Adam Curry: houses Jonathan
Greenblatt, the CEO of the anti
Defamation League.
Unknown: Oh, that failure
happened that I saw David
Ignatius, who's journalism I so
deeply respect, and it was
reporting I appreciate and he
said, you know, they will look
at was this an intelligence
failure, a military failure.
Jonathan, same playbook. This
was the West's failure. This was
our failure for decades to allow
out Iran and its proxies to
dehumanize Zionists and Jews to
allow people to think on college
campuses at Harvard. To allow
anti Zionism to flourish.
Adam Curry: We say I'm sure you
saw the, the reports that that
all these billionaires and
business owners have said, Oh,
if you signed that note, at
Harvard, we're not we're never
gonna hire you. You're not
hireable you're a horrible
person saw this
Unknown: in the 30s legitimate
professors, students who came to
believe the poison of the Third
Reich, who came to think that in
the wake of World War One, the
Jews had literally abandoned
Germany. And remember what
history would Hitler said it's
the Jews who caused their own
misfortune. Now we have
Palestinian Hamas apologists and
their acolytes here in the West
are accomplices. Jonathan
saying, Israel broth is on
blaming the victim, while we're
still collecting the bodies is
as disgraceful and as
dishonorable thing as I could
ever imagine. The last thing
I'll say, and I'm so sorry, but
I don't ever remember feeling
like this before. Is that the
idea? The notion that somehow
this piece this rapprochement
with Saudi Arabia, they were
trying to disrupt it I think
there's some truth to that. But
let's be clear, that was a path
to peace working out a deal that
could have given the
Palestinians the end the
Israelis the confidence to make
a deal with the Palestinians.
Terror, reinforces terror
reinforces the conflict, because
that's what these these
barbarians want. We've got to
stand up against them every time
Adam Curry: so you know, it
doesn't matter what you say
you're gonna have someone yell
at you no matter who you are, we
might as well just not say
anything and even our very even
though I predicted these emails
would come in just two quick
ones that I'll just read your
take on Israel and the massacre
at the Music Festival being an
OP is disgusting longtime
listener I think I'm done now.
Here's my here's my favorite
what
John C Dvorak: was the first
line he said what he said was an
OP says
Adam Curry: Your take on Israel
and the massacre at the Music
Festival being an OP is
disgusting.
John C Dvorak: We never said it
was an OP No in fact that we
said it No. I never said was an
OS.
Adam Curry: It might have been
an inside job but not an OP.
John C Dvorak: Well, we fit we
fit well. In my the way I see it
is that this was allowed to take
place for some alternatives for
some for some reason, or other
because they there's no way that
this could have been a surprise.
That's all as far as I took it.
Yeah, those people were
genuinely killed. It wasn't an
OP.
Adam Curry: Well, you you.
You're like this next one?
John C Dvorak: I bet I will. And
by the way, we don't need people
like that in this audience.
Adam Curry: Now but it's
important to I think it's
important to just show this that
the strife is even within no
agenda nation.
John C Dvorak: And because we're
going to have new we had the
same thing with Ukraine. We lost
a lot of list.
Adam Curry: Oh, yeah. Would you
framework Oh, and guess what
turns out to be pretty spot on
about that one. But doesn't of
course, you sound like a neocon.
That's a subject from it's not a
real country to the nice Jews.
We're just going to pray in the
temple. You are Neo cons. Let's
just let me read it. Your Neo
cons. I'm gonna start I'm gonna
start over
John C Dvorak: it's over but I'm
just today. This is like is he
listening to our show
Adam Curry: yet? But this is
this is what happens when people
get infected by by the media
virus. It's a truth when when
people throw at you 911 The
first thing I think is dancing
Israelis or whatever. From it's
not a real country to the nice
Jews. We're just going to pray
in the temple. Your neocon
Zionist biases are becoming
obvious, and you sound like Dan
Vaughn Gino or your buddy Glenn
Beck, playing Wesley Clark's
clip and not connecting it to
the Zionist project and the
ancillary projects like mass
immigration, pornography, trans
attacks on free speech that they
do to us which they did to
Germany until they rose up
against jewelry and butthurt
bankers thus rallied the world
to destroy them. It is one
tribal group doing all these
things and you know it no matter
how hard your Jewish wife John
handpicks view it's going to do
your sole good to tell the truth
and connect the dots or are you
going to convert to take part in
the blood rituals the sick and
the interviews want to return to
and desecrate whole Muslim holy
sites? You are already halfway
there halfway there as a Christ
cook it said. So this is how
this this is Christ
John C Dvorak: cook him a
Christ. Wow,
Adam Curry: great show title.
Great.
John C Dvorak: Yes, a great
phrase Christ cook Okay.
Adam Curry: So a little a little
historical background. I like
doing this. Because this comes
for because we don't get any of
this in the United States. And
this, of course, is TRT Turkish
radio and television. And so
they come at it from a
perspective that they start off
by, I think, Miss misnomer of
Palestine, it used to be Syria
Palestina, but okay, they're
going to give us the history of
Britain's role. And
subsequently, the League of
Nations and the United Nations
in this entire thing, and you
just don't get any of these
perspectives. Forget about the
obvious slant, they're they're
putting on it, because you can,
you can refute a lot of what
they're saying. But I think some
of some of this is good to hear
for people who just have no
perspective, because as long as
I've been alive, and as long as
you've been alive, this crap has
been going on. I mean, ever
since you were a boy. I'm sure
you remember always
John C Dvorak: been going on. I
remember, just two quick
stories. One when I was at
Berkeley, it was every day there
was some Jewish guy and a
Palestinian guy yelling at each
other in the on the sprawl
Plaza, there was every day. And
then I went, I told him the
story about this before, which
is a three hour lecture I heard
at Wheeler auditorium with Phil
Spector. And this was very long
ago, and Phil Spector mentioned
in his speech, that when he was
a kid, this has been going on it
this is never ending,
Adam Curry: and, and just for a
biblical history, this goes back
to Isaac and Ishmael, briefly.
Abraham and Sarah were told they
were going to have a son, the
son would, you know, all the
tribes of Israel would come out
of this. And Sarah, and they
were like, 70, or something
like, okay, yeah, sure, God, and
Sarah's, like, this has taken
too long. So she brought her
handmade and Hagar and said,
Hey, Bran wants you to lay with
her, as they say, in biblical
terms. And out of that came
Ishmael. But that but you know,
she, she used to hope to God.
And so then eventually she had
Isaac miracle. And this
literally was the Jew and the
Arab who hate each other. This
is literally where it comes
from. This is why when I was in
Bangkok, with my friend Benco,
when Israeli who was an grew up
and and or lived in Amsterdam,
there were just two Arab guys
who came into this rest, I
think, was a McDonald's in
Bangkok of all things. And they
were just dressed in blue jeans,
he was anything. And he said,
Look at him, look them, they
hate me. They look at how they
hate me. And then meanwhile, I
could feel his hate. I'm like,
what what is your problem? It
goes back this far. So now we go
down go into the history of
Israel. This is that of course.
I mean, this goes back to the
Ottoman Empire. Do kids even
learn about the Ottoman Empire
in school anymore? Only 100
years ago, not that long ago.
John C Dvorak: taught any of
this? No,
Adam Curry: it's important.
Unknown: When you think
Palestine you may think
violence, land seizures, and a
decade's long Israeli
occupation. But what you might
not know is that another country
plays a driving role in causing
the region's conflict, Imperial
Britain. From 1516 to at least
1917, Palestine was under the
control of the Ottoman Empire, a
religiously diverse land where
Christians, Muslims and Jews
lived alongside one another at
peace for the most part. Then in
the early 1900s, a small number
of European Jews were trying to
drum up support for Zionism and
establishment of a Jewish
homeland just 20 years before in
1897, the movements led by
Theodore Hutsul, was initiated
at a conference in Switzerland,
they decided that they would
advocate for a Jewish homeland
in Palestine. But the movement
at the time didn't have much
support. And at the time, only
around 8% of the population of
Palestine was Jewish. At the
same time, Arab nationalism was
on the rise, and many
Palestinians wanted an
independent state, Imperial
Britain you have both ambitions
of Zionist and Palestinians and
use the situation to bolster
their own interests. In 1914,
amid World War One, Britain went
to war with the Ottoman Empire.
And in 1915, Henry McMahon,
Britain's representative in
Cairo that pushed Arab leaders
with a proposal, Britain was
agreed to Arab independence if
they helped fight against the
Ottomans. Then in 1917,
Britain's Foreign Secretary
wrote a one paragraph letter to
Walter Rothschild a leading
figure in the British Jewish
community. It's read His
Majesty's government's views
with favor the establishment in
Palestine have a national home
for the Jewish people, and will
use their best endeavours to
facilitate the achievement of
this object. This letter became
known as the Balfour
Declaration.
Adam Curry: This is important
because I think even today's
kids should at least learn about
the All for declaration. I mean,
it gives you a little more
context than this drivel. This
this, the absolute drivel that
is being seeped out of
television and people in watch
television. But all these clips
get onto social media and it's
in some ways, even taken up
context is just horrible how
over socialized and under
educated people are.
Unknown: And it was in stark
contrast to a declaration of the
British and French armies in
1918, which showed the people of
Syria Palestine and Mesopotamia
of autonomy. So what was going
on? Britain had promised
independence to the Arabs that
lived in Palestine, but then
also promised a homeland for
Jews on land that was already
inhabited was Britain just
transferring land that did not
belong to them to whoever they
liked. When the Ottoman Empire
collapsed in 1918, the League of
Nations gave Britain a mandate
or administrative control of
Palestine in 1920. It was a dual
mandate. On one hand, they were
to act on behalf of
Palestinians. But on the other
hand, they were to act on behalf
of the international community
of Jews who wanted to establish
a homeland, Britain and drew up
arbitrary borders, transferring
the eastern bank of the Jordan
River to the Hashemites. It was
under the British mandate that
Jews from Europe began to
emigrate to Palestine and buy up
land. The Jewish population in
Palestine grew tenfold, from
60,000 to more than 600,000.
Between 1918 and 1947. Many
Palestinians saw the mass influx
of Jews as a European colonial
movement.
Adam Curry: What's interesting
is the video that goes along
with this, you literally see
checkpoints with people on
horses. Yeah, it's the same
thing. It's been going on since
for a long time, the checkpoints
there were no cars, people on
horses,
Unknown: so as one might expect
it led to conflict. In 1929,
riots broke out at the Wailing
Wall in Jerusalem, with
Palestinians and Jews lost
lives. In 1936. After Jewish
emigration increased even more,
more riots broke out. This time
the British were heavy handed
and killed between 2005 1000
Palestinians. The Royal British
Commission concluded that
because Britain had allowed mass
emigration, Palestine had two
distinct societies that couldn't
be reconciled.
Adam Curry: I love how Britain
kind of no one really talks
about Britain being the the
actor behind the
John C Dvorak: whole thing.
That's the reason they're so
guilt ridden. And they're they
jumping in oh, we're gonna do
whatever we have to
Adam Curry: Yeah, it's 40
seconds left,
Unknown: they recommended a
partition of the land. The Arab
hire committee rejected this,
saying it was all their lands.
Britain then banned the Arab
higher commission. They
introduced the white paper of
1939 white paper stated that
Palestine should be a binational
states inhabited by Jews and
Palestinians, but that Jewish
immigration would be limited for
five years. But illegal
immigration still went on and
violates all immigration. And
when Britain couldn't handle the
mess, they had a part in
creating, they handed the
country back to the UN in 1948.
The UN then decided to partition
Palestine. The story gets a lot
more complicated after this, but
the British promising land which
already belongs to Palestinians,
to other people has played a
part in decades of conflict and
bloodshed.
Adam Curry: Alright, so the UN,
the UN is like, oh, we should
have a two state solution.
Another thing I've been hearing
all my life and here is our
current United Nations. What is
the Director General? Is it,
President, Chief, whatever the
group that has
Unknown: this most recent
violence does not come in a
vacuum back home. The reality is
that it grows out of a long
standing conflict with a 56 year
long occupation and no political
end in sight. I am deeply
distressed by today's
announcement that Israel will
initiate a complete seizure of
the Gaza Strip, nothing allowed
in no electricity, food or fuel.
Israel must see its legitimate
needs for security materialized,
and Palestinians must see a
clear perspective for the
establishment of their own state
realized only a negotiated peace
that fulfills the legitimate
national aspirations of
Palestinians and Israelis,
together with their security,
like the long held vision of a
two state solution in line with
the United Nations resolutions,
international law and previous
agreements can bring long term
stability to the people of these
lands and why the Middle East
region. Thank you.
Adam Curry: Yes, thank you very
much. Whatever same old sank you
saying that quick, biblical
reference. Matthew 24. This is
Jesus on the mound he says you
will hear of wars and rumors of
wars, but see to it that you are
not alarmed. Such things must
happen but the end is still to
come. Nation will rise against
nation and kingdom against
kingdom. So you know, as a as a
Christian, I'm like, Yeah, okay,
I guess maybe we're there. But
then comes this. There'll be
famines and earthquakes in
various places.
Unknown: There is another major
story developing overseas, at
least 2000 people have died. aid
after twin earthquakes in
Afghanistan near the border with
Iran, hundreds of people are
believed to be trapped in the
rubble. A lack of modern
equipment is hampering the
rescue efforts. No
Adam Curry: worries, all these
are the beginning of the birth
pains. Actually, it's
John C Dvorak: 3000
Adam Curry: years old report it
is at least two hours old. But
John C Dvorak: there's another
issue here that's not being
discussed in the West. And that
is war crimes which are apparent
by both sides.
Adam Curry: For me, it's just I
just want to say, war crimes to
me is the same as hate speech. I
mean, well, it's like, okay,
John C Dvorak: there are certain
specific things and I want to
play these three clips you got
it? Is War Crimes lead in Al
Jazeera.
Unknown: Petit Calhoun joins me
now from Washington, DC for more
on this and blinking on his way.
Now, what does the issue having
to achieve by going himself?
Well, first and foremost, it
sends the message, it backs up
with the President's words that
the US is fully behind Israel.
But there's going to be
discussions and one thing we've
noticed in the last 24 hours is
the US has really started to
shift focus to try and to get a
humanitarian corridor out of
Gaza. We he said on the tarmac,
that he's been speaking to
officials in Egypt. And in
Israel. He said it was
complicated. He didn't explain
exactly where the negotiations
were being held up. He wouldn't
answer that. But it is very
clear. And we're hearing this
from the White House from the
secretary of state that they are
pushing to have some way to get
civilians out of Gaza, get
Americans out, get civilians
out, they are working that and
they undoubtedly that is going
to be a huge part of the
conversation.
John C Dvorak: And that leads us
to the problem that that no one
wants to talk about in our
media. This is a clip to
Unknown: the end, Joe Biden has
just been holding a meeting with
Jewish leaders at the White
House. What did they have to
talk about? And did he make any
announcements off the back of
that?
Well, he actually moved the
needle a little bit. I watched
his speech just the other day.
And it was the full throated
angry, really emotional speech
from US President Joe Biden
about this. And some were
critical of him because he
didn't call for any sort of
restraint from Israel, it was a
full throated endorsement. We
were speaking to this group, he
told them he had spoken to
Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin
Netanyahu, and that he told them
that he had even though people
are very angry that they have to
follow the rules of war. And so
that's seems to me to be putting
a baseline on what they expect
from these really operation. One
critical thing is, that would be
the civilian quarter because it
is against the laws of war two,
that blood civilians escaped and
also might call into question
that total blockade blockade of
Gaza. That is a war crime
according to all rules of law,
the Geneva Convention, so he's
17, possibly a subtle message to
Israel, that there is a there
are things that the US will not
condone.
John C Dvorak: This is going to
be a problem. You can't cordon
off an entire area and just
pummel them, and not allowing
them to escape that is a war
crime by any standards. As far
as I'm concerned. I don't think
it's like hate speech is really,
you just can't put someone in a
cage and then just bomb the shit
out of them. Because it's fun. I
have a I have a fact there's a
third,
Adam Curry: I want to give you
24 seconds. Because this this is
of course the problem. This is
from last year. This is fun to
lie in talking about Russia.
Unknown: Yesterday, we saw
again, Russia's targeted attacks
against civilian infrastructure,
targeted attacks on civilian
infrastructure with a clear aim
to cut off men, women, children
of water, electricity and
heating with winter coming.
These are acts of pure terror.
And we have to call it as such.
Okay,
John C Dvorak: excellent.
Adam Curry: To pull out of a hat
you get to call it that
sometimes I guess not always.
John C Dvorak: That was a good
one. Yeah. Okay. Well, here's
the final for these this war
crime stuff,
Unknown: and petty, can you just
give us a bit more of an idea
about what sort of military aid
the US is actually sending
Israel?
They are being incredibly vague.
As you know, I'm the defense
correspondents, I've been
speaking to people at the
Pentagon. And there was concern
even before this happened in
Israel, that they were going to
run out of ammunition. They've
been giving incredible amounts
of ammunition to Ukraine.
They've been trying to ramp up
production, but it obviously
takes time. This officials told
me on background that basically
yes, we believe we can give
Israel some of what it needs
because we've got stockpiles all
over the globe.
Adam Curry: Hold on a second.
All that we had left was cluster
munitions. Is that what we're
sending over now?
John C Dvorak: Dado No, in fact,
you Only LG zeros mentioned this
because we talk about on the
army is oh, we're, you're giving
him a we're sending some, you
know, some chips down there to
block to block the
Mediterranean, we're there. But
they don't say what you're
saying when we're sending them
delta zero tried to dig into it.
And they can't find out that we
don't know if it's cluster
munitions or if it's, you know,
bubblegum we have, there's no
idea. That said
Unknown: they've been very
vague. They said, We want to
give them Munitions for the Iron
Dome defense system, obviously.
And then other than that, they
really haven't given very many
details. Now, if Israel is were
to launch a ground invasion, it
is by far the most challenging
type of war for warfare in
existence, it is exceptionally
dangerous and deadly. So if the
Israel has decided what they
would do, likely with Secretary
Blinken, they're going over some
of those plans, some of the
finding out where some of those
shortfalls are. If they are
going to do a ground incursion,
in an incredibly densely
populated area with very narrow
streets, they'll need things
like night vision goggles,
they'll need ammunition perhaps
better, but body armor. So
really, they're I think, part of
trying to get a sense of where
Israel is going to take this and
what the US can do to help them.
Okay, thank you so much. That is
Petit Kelheim for us. In
Washington DC
Adam Curry: TRT had a report
about what's being sent and the
and what the US is doing to
support Israel. Here it is
Unknown: US President Joe Biden
called Hamas his attack on
Israel and atrocity on an
appalling scale, promised that
the US has Israel's back and
then issued a warning.
Let me say again, any country,
any organization, anyone
thinking of taking advantage of
situation? I have one word,
don't. Don't
Adam Curry: that's actually a
contraction. It's actually two
words.
John C Dvorak: But even so, even
so he said it twice. I have one
word, don't don't.
Unknown: March may be broken.
But our resolve is clear. Biden
tried to separate the
Palestinian people from Hamas.
Hamas does not stand for the
Palestinian people, by
Adam Curry: the way. I'm sorry.
This is our president now.
Unknown: I have one word don't.
Adam Curry: And our president
then I have two words for you.
Predator drones. I mean, come
on. That was cool. Predator
drones. Two words
Unknown: don't. Our hearts may
be broken. But our resolve is
clear.
Biden tried to separate the
Palestinian people from Hamas.
Hamas does not stand for the
Palestinian people's right to
dignity and self determination.
Its stated purpose is
annihilation of the State of
Israel
on the murder of Jewish people.
National Security Adviser Jake
Sullivan says the death toll of
Americans killed in the Hamas
attack has grown to more than a
dozen with nearly two dozen
unaccounted for. But it's not
clear how many of those are
being held hostage by Hamas.
Sullivan said there are still no
plans to put US forces into the
conflicts and that for now, the
US is only helping Israel beef
up its Iron Dome defense shield
and providing expertise and
intelligence and sending a
flotilla of warships toward
Israel as a deterrent
Adam Curry: slay Flotilla. Isn't
a flotilla a certain amount.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, no.
Chicken. Nobody uses the term
flotilla they there's a term for
what they sent.
Adam Curry: Well, um, see
flotilla is like a bunch of
rafts. A small fleet of vessels
commercial or otherwise, he was
asked this
John C Dvorak: fleet, it's a big
fleet, aircraft carrier and a
bunch of destroyers small
Adam Curry: No, that's not a
flotilla. That's a fleet,
Unknown: but he was asked how
much of Israel's retaliation,
its destruction in Gaza is the
US willing to tolerate?
I don't think of this in terms
of retaliation. This is about
providing support to Israel as
it seeks to defend its territory
and deal with an ongoing
imminent threat from Hamas
terrorists.
Still, the Biden administration
is talking to officials in
Israel and Egypt, about
providing a safe passage to
Palestinians, perhaps through
Egypt, even though Egypt has
been reluctant in the past to
open up its Gaza border to them.
And that is sure to be one of
the topics when US Secretary of
State Antony Blinken arrives in
Israel later this week. Oh,
that's
Adam Curry: all you need. You
need Blinken that's just sent
Newland. That'll make it even
when they didn't
John C Dvorak: send that report.
What you you you falsely
promoted Oh, I had the floods.
They didn't say what they said
some some parts for that. No,
no, no. I
Adam Curry: said that. They
tried to get the answer to this.
So they also
John C Dvorak: can't get the
answer except the parts I
Raytheon. Apparently scutts
should send Some stuff. So that
part's at the further end,
because nobody else is using
this, you know, these patriots
Adam Curry: this is. So this is
how I'm going to view this
conflict and what happens for
the next period of time. I mean,
I, I do not think this is going
to end swiftly, it's going to
expand, just like COVID. Just
like 911. Really, this is a
liquid liquidity event. And
we're in more need of it than
ever, I would say, I don't know
much about the public markets.
But I see the issue with
everyone going into bonds. All
of a sudden, by on Friday,
everything reversed the dollar
started. This is before this
attack happened. The dollar
reversed, the bond yields
started to go down stocks were
looking more attractive. All the
Fed presidents were coming out
egg economy's great,
everything's good, then this
happens. And for that we had a
little blip there where Oh,
everyone's all our stocks are
gonna go up. And I think today
it's down again. So we need
money. The military industrial
complex needs money. Right now
we're in a shutdown situation.
So they couldn't get the 24
billion they want it for
Ukraine, then I'm I'm I mean,
it's so obvious. So so obvious
that that how much money is
going to be created for this? I
don't think we have a war chest
per se. I don't think we have
anything. I mean, what we have
stuff for everybody.
John C Dvorak: Like that one
report said they got stockpiles
all over the world. Yeah. Well,
Adam Curry: we didn't have it
for Ukraine. But I think I
think, you know, we're gonna go
into money printing mode. And
the markets needed the banks
need it. It's hard. I'm so
happy. We don't have a cap on on
our honored on our national
debt. With that, that's
convenient that there's no
statutory debt at the moment, as
you know, no ceiling. And then
of course, even though I truly
believe this, truly, here's some
here's some disinformation that
came out. But actually falls
right, it leads it folds into
this topic of money for the
military industrial complex. So
going on whenever you see a clip
that is 12 or 15 seconds long.
That is an oh my god, I can't
believe it. You shouldn't show
that. Oh, my God, I can't
believe it clip that's been
going around is a Rear Admiral
Kirby of the the National
Security Council. Say, here's,
here's the headline on the
tweet, we're leaving you we're
gonna we're gonna step away from
Ukraine. No more funding for
Ukraine. Look here. He said
anything
Unknown: funny. We're, we're
coming near to the end of the
rope. I mean, today we announced
$200 million. And we'll keep
that aid going as long as we
can. But it's it's not going to
be indefinite. So
Adam Curry: it's not going to be
indefinite. Oh, no, that's it.
We're ending? We're ending
support for Ukraine? No, no, it
is quite the opposite. He is
pleading for more money for
everything. Here's the full
minute,
Unknown: can you provide us
anything on a timeline or give
us a sense of how quickly the US
would exhaust what it can
provide to Israel before
congressional actions and
existing authorities and
appropriations to support Israel
in the near term? And I got
asked last time, you know, what
is near term? Or what's a bit
mean? I, I can't give you a date
calendar, because a lot of it's
going to depend on their
expenditure rate, and what the
replenishment ability is, what
the need is and what our ability
to do it is. But in the near
term, we've we've got
appropriations and authorities
for both Ukraine and for Israel.
For both, you don't want to be
trying to bake in long term
support. When you're at the end
of the rope and the in Ukraine,
on the Ukraine funding. We're,
we're coming near to the end of
the rope. I mean, today we
announced $200 million. And
we'll keep that aid going as
long as we can. But it's it's
not going to be indefinite. So
are we moving with a sense of
alacrity? Absolutely. I couldn't
give you a date certain on the
calendar.
Adam Curry: So no, no, what he's
saying is not worth stepping
away from Ukraine. No, we're
doubling down. We need more for
Ukraine. We Yes.
John C Dvorak: Actually, the
point you made about if you see
a 15 second clip going around, I
see these all the time, and I'm
always trying to find the
original. Yeah. Which is what we
both do. But when you see
something like that going
around, yeah, it's taken out of
context to fool you. Yes. And
all you have to do is do a
little digging, and I don't know
why nobody, nobody but this show
seems to do that. So now let's
head it's really remarkable to
me since we only had 41 people
out of the almost million people
that listen to the show that
even bothered to contribute over
$50 for this particular show,
Adam Curry: you know, we could
we could turn the cameras on,
boasted here with headphones,
and then talk about the outrage
of the babies. And we're going
to bomb them though. Yeah, we'd
make twice we make twice as much
money if not more. So, two
theaters we're going to add to
this. We don't have to go too
deep into it. But you probably
heard about the pipeline, the
Finland gas pipeline. Well, it
looks like that was some
terrorism. Someone blew up that
pipeline. Of course, Finland is
a brand new NATO member, what
are the chances? So outcomes?
Jens Stoltenberg, the head
honcho of NATO was the Lensky
literally standing next to him
like a little boy. And here's
what yen says
Unknown: we will also address
the incident in the Baltic Sea,
with the damage caused to
critical undersea
infrastructure. I spoke with
Preston Salvini minister and
Prime Minister Carlos yesterday,
and we are in close contact
important thing now is to
establish what happened and how
this could happen. If it is
proven to be a deliberate attack
on a NATO critical
infrastructure, then this will
be of course serious, but it
will also be met by a united and
determined response from NATO
Adam Curry: Article Five because
was Finland is now a NATO
country. So if someone did
anything to that pipeline, Putin
if anyone did some of that
pipeline Oh, Article Five
response so we have
John C Dvorak: all a different
idea. What if it was Lewinsky's
boys the Ukrainians who did
something to that pipeline just
to stir things up? And we find
out that it was them do it? Does
NATO attack them now?
Adam Curry: Dream on Dream?
Dream on? No, we want more wars.
War is good for business. It's
good for business. And now the
final frontier besides sadly, I
think Lebanon is there's not
much to realize in Lebanon
anymore. But you know, I it's on
the west Clarke seven lists so
we'll just we'll just add it
there. That wouldn't take much.
John C Dvorak: I do have
actually a couple of clips
regarding the Hezbollah attack
from Lebanon. Let's do that.
Let's do that. This is habitable
attack at this is not what you
hear from any of our media.
Again, I have to go to Al
Jazeera English for this. This
is Hezbollah attack one
Unknown: of the Israeli army is
trying to calm fears after a
false alarms and people
nationwide scrambling for
shelter.
warning sirens rang out across
northern Israel and flares were
fired at the border. As people
across the country were told to
seek shelter over a possible
aerial infiltration from
Lebanon. The army now says the
Panic was caused by human error.
Only Hashem is in the town of
Nakota human error and Lebanon
near the border with Israel.
Today was a very hectic day. It
started with Hezbollah attack on
Israeli troops on the borders,
mainly in the HERA village on
the border line. According to
the pictures we saw from
Hezbollah, it seems that there
was a direct hit with guided
missiles. Now following that
Israeli assaulted shelling, the
villages surrounding the
borders, and there were two
people injured. Now, later on,
this alarm came and there were
these reports about planes,
paragliders crossing towards the
border. However, there was no
genuine reason to understand why
this alarm is coming out because
none of these product gliders
were seen with eyes. Also, at
the same time, these product
gliders, the alleged panic
gliders did not engage in a
battle or in the fight on the
ground. So later on, it was
clarified that this is not
right.
Adam Curry: This is interesting.
This paraglider thing paramotor
ultralight everyone's using
different words for it. It's
it's also a 911 throwback to
these guys couldn't even fly a
Cessna. And they flew these
planes into buildings. Oh, look,
they're coming over a little
paragliders and they're causing
havoc. It's all a just a
different verse. It's like a
reboot of cheers.
John C Dvorak: Whatever the case
is, the non existent paragliders
that part clipped to indicate
that the Israelis are actually
pounding the southern border of
Lebanon as we speak.
Unknown: However, the Israeli
army continued to launch fleurs
in the skies of South Lebanon,
also burning the bushes around
the borders in order to deny any
fighters. Kind of a cover just
in case they're trying to
infiltrate the border. So it was
a it was a hectic day for
Israel. The troops on the
Lebanese side and this clarified
the situation whereas the
tension is mounting day after
day. So, in comparison with
yesterday when rockets were
launched and hummus, Al Qassam
brigades claimed responsibility
or the day before where a group
from Islamic Jihad infiltrated
the borders and engage in a
battle with Israelis. Today was
the bigger day. And it seems
that this tension is going to
continue. It's not going to
stop. And at least from what I
understand this is going to
continue as far as the campaign
on Gaza is going to continue to
continue.
Adam Curry: Oh, man, peanuts.
This is the peanuts part in the
background. We need to slowly
ramp up Iran. This is the prize.
This is the big one. This is
what and it would be would it be
any better to have Israel attack
Iran with our weapons? We wish
John C Dvorak: that that would
have to be what that would have
to be it
Adam Curry: and the Washington
Post Robo WaPo has Iran on their
mind. So we had Chuck Schumer,
Senator Schumer went to talk to
President GE, as the
representative of the United
States, our president can't get
a meeting with him. So send the
next best thing. And so here's a
question from WaPo. Journal. He
asked a question about GE. But
he also asked he slips into
question about Iran, the answer
is somewhat surprising.
Unknown: Thank you very much.
Just following up on what you
just said. How did they respond
specifically on the point of
Iran? How did President Xi
respond on that? And more
broadly, if I could just ask a
broader question? Many analysts
cite a lack of trust between the
US and China as one of the
biggest stumbling blocks to
better ties between the
countries after meeting with
President Xi today, do you trust
him more or less than
let me just say this, both
sides, the Chinese and us said,
unless we have sincere
conversations about our
differences, and not pull any
punches, that we would never
solve these problems. And the
thing that I think we respected
is the Chinese leadership from
President Xi on down understood
that we were going to be strong
understood that we're going to
be tough, but also understood
that's a necessity if we're ever
going to improve the
relationship. On the first
question he listened.
Adam Curry: Now listen to to
Schumer not having the answer,
but his handlers giving him the
answer.
Unknown: I don't recall him
saying anything specific on it,
but he listened several times
deliver the message. Go ahead.
They said they would deliver the
message to the Iranians. Yes.
Adam Curry: Okay. Okay. They
said they would deliver the
message to the Iranians. So WaPo
has Iran in their sights WaPo, I
would say is compromised. They
just fire they just fired 10% of
their workforce. They fired 200
people for whatever reason.
There is a scandal brewing. The
Special Envoy to Iran from the
US State Department, Robert
Malley has kind of disappeared.
He was supposed to show up in
some hearings, and you know, he
couldn't make it and now he's
gone away, and we don't know
where he is. And oh, WaPo has
intercepted some emails and
communications between him one
of his fellow State Department
or former State Department
workers now at the Pentagon with
Iran. It turns out, we had an
Iranian spy in the State
Department. Remember, now
there's all this noise about
Donald Trump leaking the plans
to attack Iran? No, that's then
he had it and then someone else
had it and who knows who had it,
but WaPo and this has been going
on for a few weeks. No one's
really talking about it. This is
Michael Christianson. He's he
he's on bitchute. So you're no,
you're no, it's good. And he
gives us a brief overview of
what's happening with the
special envoy. And the spies.
The Iranian spies in the State
Department. Iran is bad
Unknown: right about the same
time Malley was under suspicion.
Wow. Sensitive US government
documents started showing up in
Iran state media, so our top
Iran guide disappears for
mishandling classified
information and classified
information starts showing up in
Iranian government hands. It's
not hard to deduce what happened
here. But this new report adds
detail Robert Malley wasn't
really our top Iran guy. He was
actually a Ron's top America
guy. According to the report in
the emails It cites Robert
Malley was funding supporting
and directing an Iranian
intelligence operation designed
to influence the United States.
This project was called the
Iranian experts initiative. So
the experts strike again through
it. The Iranian government was
recruiting Western academics,
meeting them abroad to receive
their loyalty and issue
directions for how to influence
the US government. Though of
course eventually it wasn't just
influence that Robert Malley
achieved at the State
Department. It was a job at the
highest level crafting Iran
policy and Robert Malley brought
his Iranian experts initiative
friends to the administration to
so while Malley is now
officially out on leave, there's
still at least one more in a
high level position. Who isn't
the emails in the report show a
woman named Aryan Tabata by is
also a part of this Iranian
influence network who is Tabata
by Well, she's a person Robert
Malley, personally brought into
Biden's administration. She was
first at the State Department.
She was a diplomat on Melis iran
nuclear negotiation team under
Biden, and now she works at the
Pentagon, where she's currently
the Chief of Staff for the
Assistant Secretary of Defense
for special operations. So not
only did she negotiate with
hostels while being part of a
propaganda network for those
hostels, she's now working with
our SpecOps who of course,
handle our most risky and
difficult military operations
should any heightened conflict
arise, emails were covered by
the Wall Street Journal
reporters showed Tabata by
consulting with and seeking
advice from Iran's foreign
ministry before attending policy
events. Before she gave
congressional testimony in 2014.
She asked an Iranian official
for advice on how to deal with
other witnesses, who are Iran
critics, she sent in a run
sympathetic article she
published in The Boston Globe to
this Iranian official for praise
and recognition. And also in
these emails. The Iranian
government was very pleased with
the results of their project.
Adam Curry: So if you want
something to crack open view,
call your friends at WaPo it's
coming to the it's coming up.
It's gonna bubble up. We've got
Mohamed de F. I guarantee you
he'll show up in Iran. Oh, yeah.
We found him we are smoke them
out.
John C Dvorak: The whole thing
of these people go back to the
to the very middle east centric
Obama administration. And yeah,
this spy network is quite funny.
It's it was written up in a
couple of different places.
Nobody knows quite what to make
of it.
Adam Curry: Don't worry, it'll
it'll be twisted into something.
But it's Iran is bad. Iran,
Iran, Iran, Iran, Iran, let
Israel do it. It all has to
leave everyone saying it. Every
report. The anti Defamation
League, obviously Iran,
Hezbollah, Iran, Hamas. Iran is
all around. We've got to go out
we got to go with the route
swung out. The one eyed one
legged guy who planned it all
he's in Iran, you can just wait
for it.
John C Dvorak: Wait, if that
happens, I'm gonna give you 10
points because that would be
ideal. We should also meet the
whole thing's a scam.
Adam Curry: Well, this is what I
believe is it's a scam the
military industrial complex.
It's for politics. It's being
used for is getting all of the
bad news off of the front line.
Even the bad news about you the
Ukraine conflict. Everything is
just off the table. Don't worry
about it. I was
John C Dvorak: hooked by this by
the way. As you can tell by my
clips. There was no way of
getting any other news except
this story clip custodian
Adam Curry: sent me his normal
batch is like it's all Israel.
John C Dvorak: I did get some of
the stories. I mean, a few of
them here and there, but they're
all They're all minor. Well,
there's one. There's one other
thing about the hunter Biden's
This is the real kicker to me is
the hunter Biden's all of a
sudden completely opted out. Of
course,
Adam Curry: of course, you're
he's back to smoking crack and
hookers is all it was, Oh, good.
Good for him. So now this is
also a perfect opportunity to
enact and try out some of the
new regulation in the European
Union DSA, the digital services
agreement. Which Well, it's
actually in this report. But
spoiler alert, if if you find if
you're a platform and you find
hate speech, or disinformation,
you have to remove it
immediately. letters went out
letters went out to Elon Musk
letters went out to Mark
Zuckerberg there's bad things on
your platform that will not
stand in the European Union. As
violence
Unknown: rages in Israel and
Gaza sued as fake news on social
media. The US making urgent
appeal to big tech, in a letter
addressed and met a CEO Mark
Zuckerberg on Wednesday. Anyway,
it's on the blocks industry
chief urged the platform to do
more to curb disinformation or
face penalties curb it comes a
day after Viton made a similar
call to ex owner Elon Musk As
the source of the war social
media networks have been awash
with graphic images and
misinformation linked to the
violence, the fact checkers at
Frost 24 They've been debunking
some of the forces under the
aegis Digital Services Act, and
our social media platforms like
x are obliged to stop the spread
of harmful content, or face
fines of up to 6% of their
annual global revenue. Instead,
experts say that x is algorithm
is actively promoting
disinformation on the Israel
Hamas war. Favoring posts by
accounts that pay for its blue
check subscription service,
regardless of who runs them.
Users can receive payments under
the scheme, giving them more
incentive to publish posts that
are unlikely to elicit strong
reactions and go viral.
On a request for a comment made
by CNBC a meta spokesperson,
spokesperson said we quickly
established a special operations
center staffed with experts
including fluent Hebrew and
Arabic speakers to monitor and
respond to this rapidly evolving
situation. Our teams are working
around the clock to keep our
platforms safe, take action on
content that violates our
policies or local law and
coordinate with third party fact
checkers in the region factual
information. And there was also
a statement by ex CEO Linda
Yakko. Reno shortly just a few
minutes ago, saying that shortly
after the news broke about Hamas
attack X assembled leadership, a
leadership group to assess the
situation. Since the terrorist
attack on Israel, we've taken
action to remove or label 10s of
1000s of pieces of content. So
far since the start of the
conflicts ex says it has
identified and removed hundreds
of Hamas affiliated accounts
from their platform.
Adam Curry: Oh, of course, only
Hamas has disinformation, we go
to our DSA dashboard. Last time
we checked in with the DSA, the
Digital Services Act. We had
about 67,000 takedowns an hour.
Do you care to wager what it's
up to now? Joe? Quarter of a
million now not quite 137,630.
Now 137,630? Yes, there we go.
per hour, over five hour per
hour? Over 5 million takedowns a
day.
John C Dvorak: Others taking
everything down?
Adam Curry: My point? Exactly.
So what you are seeing is only
approved. It's only approved
narrative. I think we can we can
easily presume that. So you're
not getting anything from social
media.
John C Dvorak: You're getting
nothing from the sounds of it.
If you're taking down 100 A
quarter well, not a quarter of a
million to a million per hour.
That's a lot of posts. That
means every eight hours a
million posts are taken down.
It's a million posts a lot. It's
an it's an eight hours and yet
24 hours is three. That's you
know, it's 3 million a day. It's
ridiculous. Yeah. I know. So
there too, so it has to be willy
nilly. Your way? Well, no,
Adam Curry: it's it's it's
complaint from the government
take it down. Okay. Nothing has
changed. Nothing has changed.
The I just I'd say the the
agents are still inside of x.
And everywhere else. Platforms
are no good. Although I do like
kind of the insinuation that,
that x is the worst because they
pay people with blue checkmarks
for for posts. If you know
that's the Yeah, the Twitter X
John C Dvorak: payments, pave
eight bucks and you get a blue
checkmark.
Adam Curry: Yeah, but no, but
then you can join their
monetization program. And yeah,
if you get people commenting on
your post, and they're able to
sell ads, boom, you get some
money.
John C Dvorak: I'm doing it
Adam Curry: that tell me this
isn't an old story, just talking
about big tech for a second.
Somehow I feel like this story
we've heard I couldn't find a
clip but we've heard it before
Unknown: Amazon's Alexa has
apparently been claiming the
2020 presidential election was
stolen. The voice assistants
cites various sources when
answering questions about the
election, including from a video
streaming service popular with
conservatives called rumble.
multiple investigations
uncovered no evidence of
election fraud and Amazon says
for their part responses were
errors delivered a small number
of times and quickly
fixed.
Adam Curry: Why do I think I've
heard this
John C Dvorak: story before I
never heard this story before.
Adam Curry: I'm used to it must
be must be.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, you really
have a memory for this and so
you should Have it maybe it
floated arrive I was
Adam Curry: looking for a clip I
could not find a clip. I do have
a couple quick big tech things
unless you want to stay in in
the region.
John C Dvorak: We'll get to
Hizbollah tap run down
Adam Curry: the region are we
still stuck in the real region
the region in the region?
John C Dvorak: West Bank killing
so this is kind of interesting
here. There's a shooting people
in the West Bank, which got
nothing to do with Gaza. But
okay. Where is it? It's just
war. West Bank.
Unknown: More Israeli settlers
have killed at least four
Palestinians and attacks on the
village south of Nablus in the
occupied West Bank. The
Palestinian health ministry says
Israeli forces have also killed
a 16 year old boy near Hebron.
29 Palestinians have been killed
in the occupied West Bank since
the war began on Saturday.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, I was gonna
body. The other one as I want to
play this. This is a protest for
Palestinians in the EU and how
it kind of contrast with what
we're doing here in the United
States.
Unknown: But French police in
the city of Leon used force to
break up a demonstration in
support of Palestinians on
Wednesday. It comes after a
decision by city officials to
ban gatherings local activists
had planned for later in the
week. Authorities in Paris have
also imposed prohibitions on pro
Palestinian marches. French
President Emmanuel Macron has
condemned Hamas as attack on
Israel, but opposes stopping the
European Union's humanitarian
assistance to Palestinians. Pro
Palestinian demonstrations have
also been taking place in the
German capital Berlin with a
large police presence. Melissa
Chan has more.
Police have just told everyone
in the area to disperse they
have banned all Palestinian
solidarity protests over the
next few days. Particularly in
Germany, this is a touchy
subject because of the history
of the country, the history of
World War Two and the Nazis the
Holocaust, which means that the
German government and the German
people, many of them consider
something as simple as waving
the Palestinian flag as anti
semitic.
Just you know, this is always
the flag and all German
arguments to denounce and
actually persecute Palestinian
voices for the rights in
Palestine
also have the right to do
whatever they want. They have
been paying for 75 years and
that's not okay.
Now over the next few days,
emotions are going to run high.
There's also a big Israeli
community here. And police say
one reason why they're banning
protests is to prevent the two
sides from clashing. Melissa
Chan, Al Jazeera
Adam Curry: Berlin. It's all
it's all meant to Trump to
trigger trauma. And when
John C Dvorak: you're done that
was your basic thesis and I
think you're ready. One last
clip for this kind of thing.
There's the Democrats no support
for Israel. Just from New Tang
Dynasty,
Unknown: some Democrats for your
support for Israel among their
party might be waning. This
comes as some lawmakers voiced
support for Palestine while
others are distancing
themselves.
Some Democrats reportedly fear
that members of their party
might stop supporting Israel
sentiments in the US in the past
few days since the attacks were
mostly pro Israel, however, that
might change. One unnamed
Democratic lawmaker told
Politico for the last couple of
days, we've seen all the
pictures of girls who were
killed at this festival and the
children. The lawmaker says this
will change now as the counter
offensive begins.
Adam Curry: Have you actually
I've been honest, it is part of
research. I have looked Have you
seen a lot of people killed at
the festival? I'm not disputing
it. But have we actually seen
that I've seen
John C Dvorak: there's once
there's one telegraph telegram
site that has all these
pictures, it's it's pretty
elaborate, and it does hundreds
and hundreds of pictures. But
specifically from that festival
No, no, I've not seen anything
either.
Adam Curry: Because they just
reported that they've that
they've seen that. And it's you
know, it's like the base. Yeah,
I'm not disputing it, but but I
have not seen the pictures. And
you and the newsletter you sent
out was, but it was on point. It
will might
John C Dvorak: lie. I played up
to the bullshit pictures and
somebody sent me I did get a
note for somebody regarding that
girl that they kept showing over
and over and over again to being
taken out of the back of a jeep
and then being put in the front
of the Jeep
Adam Curry: which which which I
saw MSNBC claiming she was raped
and she was bleeding like you
have no evidence of that I when
I saw that first and I'm sorry
that you know to bring up this
is traumatic to see it. It to me
it looked like someone who
crapped their pants because they
were so terrified. That's what
it looked like to me or any
other many reasons but it was
presented as so
John C Dvorak: she could have
been sitting in blood to foil
you know, it was presented as
fact. No, and then they had this
guy who seemed to be in
blackface for some reason. He
shoots a gun in the air, pulls
her out of the back yells. Akbar
shoots a gun and then puts her
in the in the seat in the comfy
seat. I mean, what was the point
of this? And somebody sent a
note and saying this was a great
news. This is low budget
filmmaking. He says it only cost
them one bullet, you know, and a
day's pay for that a borrowed
jeep. I mean, it's just it was
really kind of crummy.
Adam Curry: I can hear keyboards
clicking don't send that email
to us. We're just we're just
we're just looking at media and
trying to understand what the
messaging is. Not we're not here
to bring you the truth of what
actually happened. We don't have
it. Nobody does. Exactly. That's
the point. But it's being
presented as fact. We'll
continue with your clip here.
Unknown: The only images we're
going to see for the next couple
of weeks are dead Palestinians.
Earlier this year, a Gallup poll
found that Democrats opinions on
Israel have changed
significantly. 49% of Democrats
now say they sympathize more
with Palestine, while only 38%
say they sympathize more with
Israel. That's the first time
more Democrats have said their
sympathies are more with
Palestine than with Israel. In
the 20 years the poll has been
conducted. Another Democratic
lawmaker told Politico the key
is making sure that the
sentiment doesn't grow and
metastasize. Meanwhile,
Democratic Representative
Rashida to leave is still flying
the Palestinian flag in front of
her office, Republican
Congressman Max Miller commented
on that saying the Palestinian
flag should not have a place
here. That's why I sponsored an
appropriations amendment to end
this silliness under the
amendment foreign flags couldn't
be displayed on Capitol Hill
Adam Curry: no only pride flags,
no problem with it the
John C Dvorak: same thing when I
heard that, but they you know,
there's a little element here
that was kind of not noticed by
anybody else, which is this this
idea that they've been pulling
Democrats, and now the sympathy
for the Israelis is down to 39%
and a sympathy for the
Palestinians up to 49% This is a
switcheroo. And this may be part
of the of the reason to do we're
going to bomb Iran. We got to do
it now. Because this is not
going to go the it's not going
to reverse direction. Yes, it's
clear trend.
Adam Curry: Yeah. That's, that's
a good. You know, what also is
interesting with all these
takedowns of misinformation. How
is it that I'm sure you've seen
her? I didn't clip her. There's
the Israeli blonde Israeli
woman, about 3540. Now must she
must be over 40 Who says 25
years ago, she was you know, in
service, she was specifically of
course, all young people go into
service in Israel. Then she was
in the intelligence division.
And she's just she's she's doing
video after video. After a video
about how this couldn't happen.
There's no way this was a setup.
This could never happen when she
brought in the cat thing again.
Like you can you can sense a
cat. You've got Brett Weinstein
interviewing her but yet she's
allowed to continue explain
that. If she knows this
information, why why is she
still on the air?
John C Dvorak: Just someone you
would take off just because
Adam Curry: so yeah, and so that
she just continues so you cannot
trust your social media.
John C Dvorak: Now the media
social media. Tell it that all
media Yeah,
Adam Curry: but but people often
are still like, oh, I can still
get all this on social media.
Look, I got the proof. Telegram.
Wow, it's proof do you remember
Yanis Varoufakis Oh, yeah,
whatever
John C Dvorak: happened to him?
Well, he has a really good to
tell you about bringing up an
old name yes. Yeah, it was one
of the first guys who was pushed
to the curb kicked to the curb.
So this is
Adam Curry: when Greece was
taken down by the US banks was a
Goldman and a couple others
John C Dvorak: Yeah, they the
guy in the motorcycle Yes.
Remember it's not to get it's
not the gay social media guy.
Another guy disappeared.
Unknown: You're thinking of the
case.
John C Dvorak: Was that guy's
name? It wasn't conservative
with the blonde Yeah, but social
media guy got kicked to the curb
that guy No, this is he was
rough and tumble leather wearing
bike riding American I think you
Adam Curry: know history. He's
Greek mile. You're thinking of
Yo yo,
John C Dvorak: Milo now that did
this. This great guy ended up at
the University of Texas I think
tape teaching economics, Disney
Adam Curry: while he's an
economics. He's an economist
economics. Feser and when Greek
Greece was being thrust into
austerity, and we covered all
this 2010, I want to say, so
it's quite a while ago. And the
Greeks, they, what happened is,
the bank said, Hey, we're
calling in our loan, how you can
pay for it, austerity for you.
And all of the Northern Europe
hated
John C Dvorak: this. This was
right after the Greeks decided
to join the Euros, which is
their biggest mistake.
Adam Curry: And people even go
into Greek restaurants in like
Holland and say, I'm not paying,
because you screwed us. You
stole our money. It was
horrible. So then this guy who
and he's a, he's a Marxist, he
admits his I'm a socialist, I'm
a Marxist. But he called he
says, in the traditional sense
of the word, whatever that
means, whatever that means. And
he became the minister of
finance for six months. And all
he did is he just said, no, no
more loans. We're not taking any
more loans, which was probably a
good thing for Greece. And then
his party got kicked out and he
got kicked out and get kicked
out. And, and now, you know, all
the wealth is in the north in
the south of Greece. They're
driving around and Lamborghinis.
And the rest of Greece is just
crap. What you get, that's how
it works. They are the ugly
stepchild. So Yiannis resurfaces
with a very interesting book
I've been reading called techno
feudalism. And it kind of folds
into, you know, these platforms.
And he says that capitalism is
in essence, over, because
capitalism is now slave to cloud
capitalism. And that is all
Silicon Valley based, that does
not exist anywhere else except
China. China does have WeChat,
that is the big, the big
competitor to the cloud
capitalists here in the US. And
he has a one minute. He's doing
interviews all over YouTube. And
I've been fascinated by a lot of
what he's saying, I don't agree
with all of it, of course. But
this idea, this concept was
something I think we should, we
should think about as we see the
world unfold, certainly with
secret meetings about AI and all
that crap.
Unknown: But what does happen
is, if you're Jeff Bezos, if you
are the owner of Google, of
Apple, of if you're Elon Musk,
then you own this new form of
cloud capital, which allows you
to extract from the rest of
society from proletarians. But
from everyone else, as well,
huge quantities of rents and
surpluses in a manner that
reconsidered is a form of
feudalism. The difference is
that instead of the original
feudalism, which is a system
based on private ownership of
land, which produces rent, now,
it's private ownership of the
clouds of cloud capital, because
the cloud is capital, right?
It's not some clouds up in the
sky in the sky, which yields
again, a form of rent every time
you buy something from
amazon.com 40% of what you pay,
doesn't go to the capitalist, we
selling you that stuff. It goes
to Jeff Bezos, that's a cloud
rent and he is a new form of
feudal lord.
I kind of agree with that. Yeah,
John C Dvorak: well, I sure
don't, you don't know. It all
goes to Jeff Bezos off.
Adam Curry: I mean, to me, of
course, is not the Bezos but he
said it's a public company. But
But Amazon, you know that people
have a very hard time really
making profit on Amazon. The
same thing for Apple, if you
want to sell an app 30% You want
a subscription of something? 30%
This is why you can't buy a
Kindle through the app. on
Apple, they are charging rents
for their platforms. It's true.
John C Dvorak: It's not saying
that that's not true.
Adam Curry: Forget about the
beat down. That's just it's like
John C Dvorak: minor. I mean,
it's like it's like one element
of the DIS stamp. So this whole
idea of what does he call it
kind of capitalism, techno
feudalism, techno feudalism that
this harkens back to the book
called surveillance capitalism
was different little different.
I don't think it's that much
different. It was it's the same
kind of condemnation of tech,
from a perspective of like,
well, these guys have made the
money that I didn't get to make.
It's just kind of a jealous
mode. Dang, I'm not buying any
of it.
Adam Curry: I think Spotify
tried to do this with
podcasting.
John C Dvorak: And that's where
they got so far they got, but
that's because of
Adam Curry: one special thing.
The ragtag band of developers at
podcast index. We wanted their
plan single.
John C Dvorak: How much effort
did it take to thwart their
plan? Not much.
Adam Curry: Work. Google
inherited
John C Dvorak: the billions that
those guys dropped. Google was
Not much. And
Adam Curry: that's only well,
because of RSS. Google is still
trying. They're trying to try
and keep trying to talk
everybody into into YouTube.
John C Dvorak: This is another
anti capitalist screed
definitely heard it before, from
a different angle.
Adam Curry: Anyway, just one
quick. So my feeling in general
is that this is what somebody
wants to try and do with AI. And
I've listened to the whole
interview with Sam Altman and
Joe Rogan. Sam Altman is full of
crap. All he says is just AGI it
will probably be about, you
know, three decades. Oh, okay.
Well, we're once Yeah, it's just
they'd be a 30 years we might
have autonomous generative AI,
you know, we'll have
John C Dvorak: getting closer to
the truth,
Adam Curry: but even then, I
mean, it's like, no, none of
this is happening now. It's all
bull.
John C Dvorak: Well, let me
bring us to real bullshit
artists. Please. You have to go
into the last week's archives to
get three clips.
Adam Curry: Is it under
bullshit? No,
John C Dvorak: this should be no
This is Maria. ReSSA
Adam Curry: okay. Oh, yes. on
PBS. Oh, you got a three parter.
I'm excited.
John C Dvorak: If you want to
hear somebody who doesn't know
what they're talking about,
Adam Curry: this is PBS. This is
great. I love the going on with
that
John C Dvorak: black the new
black anchor that's there who's
just seems like a dummy is this
seems I was gay or the guy.
Yeah, that guy seems like a dumb
gay guy to me.
Adam Curry: And I couldn't be
there the worst John said.
John C Dvorak: They're the
worst. It's a smart gay guys. So
this guy's lapping it up. And as
you can see it in his eyes. He's
got this look of Oh my God. Oh,
we're all gonna die.
Adam Curry: Oh, hold on. Let's
let's make sure we have America.
This is NPR or PBS
Unknown: veteran journalist and
past Nobel Peace Prize winner
Maria ReSSA has a dire warning
about the defense of truth in
the digital age. She says we
risk losing the information war
to adversarial artificial
intelligence and to
authoritarian governments who
can weaponize that technology.
And she's experienced it
firsthand. In 2021, she won the
Nobel Prize for fighting to
protect freedom of expression in
the Philippines under attack by
the regime of then President
Rodrigo de terre Tae Jeff
Bennett spoke with rest of this
week at the inaugural summit of
the newly launched Institute of
global politics at Columbia
University.
Reesa. Thank you so much for
speaking with us. I appreciate
it. Thanks for having you have
said the world faces a tech
enabled Armageddon turbocharged
by generative artificial
intelligence. Invoking
Armageddon sort of the final
battle between good and evil
might strike some people as a,
as an overreach, it might strike
some people as being hyperbolic.
But why in your view, is that an
accurate characterization?
I've lived through this. You
know, I never thought I would
get 10 Arrest warrants in a
little over a year, right? I
never thought I would have to go
to jail. I never thought that we
would tear apart our shared
reality and doubt facts, and the
lies could spread faster than
facts. MIT's 2018 Study shows
lie spread six times faster. And
that has turned everything
upside down. Tech enabled
Armageddon, and Rappler the
organization I read in the
Philippines we've been fighting
for our survival since 2016.
Adam Curry: Now Wayman, did she
get arrested by an AI that he
John C Dvorak: liked that make
you believe that no, she got
arrested because she was a
dissident in in the turkey under
the turret day when he was
running things and he was like,
putting everyone in jail and so
she got arrested and fought the
government or something and he
gets ended up here he's gone. So
she said okay, well Nobel Peace
Prize for being a do gooder. And
now she's an expert on AI with
no tech background whatsoever.
So what
Adam Curry: she's doing is she's
equating AI with a with a
dictator. Yeah, who makes
unintelligent decisions?
John C Dvorak: I guess.
Unknown: The fact that we were
still
John C Dvorak: not you brought
that up. Why is she on this
show? being interviewed by PBS
breathlessly that's what I'd
like to know. Oh, come on. An
expert.
Adam Curry: Doesn't matter. Who
isn't. Who is the expert on AI?
Elon, well, she's not they can't
get Elon Musk. Sam Altman. He's
boring. He's boring. Well, this
John C Dvorak: girl is kind of
boring.
Adam Curry: Oh, yeah. Yeah,
yeah, here we go.
Unknown: The fact that we were
still here shows you that doing
the right thing is the right
thing. But it's going to get
worse. So the first time that
you had,
Adam Curry: I'm sorry, the
revenue ation of doing the right
thing is the right thing. It is
the right
John C Dvorak: thing, and it's
gonna get worse. You bet
Unknown: it's going to get
worse. So the
John C Dvorak: not You bet.
Adam Curry: Oh, I cannot believe
it. The jury will disregard my
bet it's Yep. Yep, had
Unknown: humanity con. First
contact with AI is really
machine learning when everything
that you post on social media.
So this is social media, right?
Everything you post is pulled
together by machine learning.
And then that's used to build a
model of you that knows you
better than you know yourself.
Replace the word model with
clone. So we're cloned, then AI
comes in and takes all of our
clones, puts it together in a
mother lode database. That's
what's used to my does Oracle
Adam Curry: make that the mother
lode database is that I think
mother lode database
John C Dvorak: is a great name
for a product.
Adam Curry: You've heard of Ms.
SQL, this is the mother lode
database, puts it together
Unknown: in a mother lode
database, that's what's used to
micro target. micro targeting is
not the same as media
advertising,
Adam Curry: that she's literally
describing data brokers, it
already exists, lady, it's not
AI,
Unknown: media advertising, you
see the same things, right? But
micro targeting sells your
weakest moment to a message to
someone who will pay for it. And
that could be a company or that
could be a government. Right?
Right? That right? Not just you.
And when it becomes relentless,
it becomes Information
Operations. Those
vulnerabilities in the tech
platforms have been exploited by
geopolitical power your America
in 20 1600 26 million Americans
were impacted were touch by
Russia, Russia and information
works.
Adam Curry: Nice. Oh, my
goodness, this is all these
platforms are gonna suck.
Everything's gonna suck.
mastered
John C Dvorak: the idea of micro
targeting, which is you know,
targeted advertising. Hello, 98
Hello, right Hello 1970 For that
matter way I first
Adam Curry: I'm gonna get my
milk is going to be ordered the
minutes out in my fridge, it's
going to be so smart the world
would be groovy micro targeting.
John C Dvorak: So she's bringing
this back to the 2022 era. And
it's just unbelievable to me
that this is being played on.
PBS should be ashamed of itself.
For letting this woman ramble
like this. She's not saying
anything that means anything.
This is all bullshit.
Unknown: You know, there are US
officials, there are tech
leaders who have said that the
future of this country looks
fairly bleak if China finds a
way to develop AI technology
faster than we do. So how do we
on the one hand, continue to
innovate, but on the other hand,
implement solutions that don't
strangle the innovation that
we're trying to unleash.
Ironically, China, which is far
from Democratic, has put
guardrails in place around that.
Yes. And they're large language
models, right? Right. While
America says that
Adam Curry: just just to say, on
their large language models,
right, it's like telling me, we
all agree, China has large
language models, they put it
John C Dvorak: down and they put
guard rails around it in the
mother lode. Now, a journalist
would be sitting there would
say, Well, what specifically are
those guardrails and how do they
work?
Adam Curry: What are you You
don't think that that's going to
come out of PBS as a question to
you.
John C Dvorak: I think at some
in some future world maybe
Adam Curry: this we need to
write we asked world breed need
a list of all these AI bullcrap
words that Sam Alban,
guardrails, guardrails? Yeah,
like the guard rails guard
rails? Yeah, guard rails, they
really were. Yeah, that's a good
point. What are the guard rails?
John C Dvorak: Yeah, what are
they and how do they work?
Because it doesn't make sense to
even say that.
Unknown: has put guard rails in
place around that, right? Yes,
yeah. On their large language
models, right, right.
Adam Curry: No, no, no evidence,
no stories on or anything about
this guardrails around their
large language models right in
the mother lode database.
Unknown: While America says that
remember, these companies are
driven by profit, surveillance
capitalism. Large language
models will have the ability to
mimic you, it mimics humanity.
And when that happens, it also
doesn't tell you it lies. It
looks for patterns. It doesn't
necessarily find meaning. That's
what we've lost here. And if you
look at the two ways aI have
touched us, the first time it
exploited our fear, anger and
hate.
Adam Curry: I'm going to agree
It mimics humanity. It lies.
Yeah, cuz we're all liars. Of
course. This is no this is not
great, man.
John C Dvorak: Okay did lie
without having AI. Yeah.
Adam Curry: I was looking at
photos. Where's it here? I put
it in the show
John C Dvorak: notes at the end
of that clip.
Adam Curry: Yeah, that was the
other clip.
John C Dvorak: Yeah it went on
there was there was telling
people you want to go look it up
here.
Adam Curry: Let me see there's
this Associated Press Photo. Man
it was of a black lives matter.
protest. And it's completely AI
there's people with six fingers.
There's there's a guy in the
background whose eyes like
bulging and all blurred into his
Hey,
John C Dvorak: love the bulging
eyes, it's
Adam Curry: been, it's the six
finger thing. It's just it's not
going away. AI is just not
great. Show me a picture with
well, it should be four fingers
on the thumb. But you know what
I'm saying? It's not it's just
not great. It's people are
people fall for it. I'm telling
you that I am going to I'm going
to save the world for 3% of the
people will be saved by our
systems that we create with RSS.
Just 3% and everyone else is
going to be a bloody good number
that's about and that's about
what I think I can save. Is that
good enough for a Nobel Peace
Prize?
John C Dvorak: Well, we had to
exaggerate the lie. AI does have
to lie, to lie, but we can
manage it.
Adam Curry: Here's an example of
a human being lying. This is a
great example. This is again
Rear Admiral Kirby. And he is
asked a question about the
President's thinking. But he's
very clear in his obvious lie.
Unknown: I want to play this
soundbite for you that is just
last month and Vietnam and ask
you if this still holds for the
President watch. The only
existential
threat humanity faces even more
frightening than nuclear war. is
global warming going above 1.5
degrees in the next 2010 years.
Given all the nuclear players in
these two areas where we are now
engaged on does the President
stand by that comment?
Absolutely does climate change
is an existential threat, it
actually threatens and is
capable wiping out all human
life on Earth. Time. I mean,
that's
Adam Curry: global warming
climate change is in competition
with AI who's going to kill us
faster
Unknown: human life on earth
over time. I mean, that's I
don't know how more existential,
you get to that. But that
doesn't mean that we walk away
from our obligations, or our
national security interests in
very dangerous parts of the
time.
He said it was more frightening
than a nuclear war, is that it's
more frightening than a nuclear
war in this moment.
The President believes
wholeheartedly that climate
change is an existential threat
to the all human life on the
planet. That's just science.
That's a fact, Martha Beck on
the other challenges facing this
country and our allies and
partners around the world,
Adam Curry: that's just science
and focus,
John C Dvorak: tip of the day
for that peace.
Adam Curry: Just science, in
fact, Martha, that's all but it
is. I don't like that you
disparage my clip that way, but
I'll take the award. Thank you.
And the fact that her name is
Martha makes it better. That's
just science. In fact, Martha
John C Dvorak: teaches science
in fact, wrong. It's just
science, in fact that we're all
gonna die from global warming.
Adam Curry: We're not because
we're going to save the world.
No, we're gonna save the world
with carbon credits and right on
cue as predicted on the wait,
wait,
John C Dvorak: carbon credits,
does that change the mnemonic
carbon is released?
Adam Curry: Why are you trying
to be difficult? Just sit back
and relax and take the
propaganda. Do you remember I
had the clips from the big
climate change conference in in
Africa. And they were talking
about land being carbon sink. So
you know, if you own a piece of
land in Africa, you can turn
that into a carbon credit.
John C Dvorak: Yum. Well, what
is
Adam Curry: the United Arab
Emirates has inked a deal to buy
a fifth? That's 20% of
Zimbabwe's land, four carbon
credits. This is great. 7.5
million hectares
John C Dvorak: is one born every
minute.
Adam Curry: What is 7.5 million
hectares is a hectare. It's
John C Dvorak: about 14 acres.
14 acres and LinkedIn I think is
up to date tickets. It's like
for two acres proximately two a
hectare.
Adam Curry: So there it is. I'll
look it up. The flurry so it's
Oh, it's okay. The global $2
billion Voluntary Carbon Offset
market allows carbon emitters to
offset emissions by purchasing
credits from emission reducing
projects primarily in forest
conservation. So
John C Dvorak: I'm okay hectares
2.47 acres.
Adam Curry: So if I have three
acres here could I turn that
into a carbon credit? Yeah, how
much? Not much but I could Chem
bucks it's like a Bitcoin
John C Dvorak: I don't think
it's worth a Bitcoin No, but
Adam Curry: it's like a Bitcoin
you just you just say well, I do
I got this I got this stuff. Oh,
John C Dvorak: yeah, you make it
Yeah. But everyone get for it.
And if
Adam Curry: I plant a tree,
another carbon credit and your
gold we should have been doing
this a long time ago. We really
should have
John C Dvorak: the bank money in
the bank.
Adam Curry: So very sad isn't we
should take a break but very sad
for this next person. This
although, boy timing is
everything. This this 911 10
times worse than 911, which is
almost as bad as January 6 could
not have come at a worst time
for this announcement, a new
curveball
Unknown: in the race for
president to declare myself an
independent ganda. Robert F.
Kennedy Jr. Leaving the
Democratic Party to run as an
independent
Adam Curry: What are you
drinking?
John C Dvorak: It's the polar
just a plain polar seltzer get a
few more cans of this left
Adam Curry: because I opened one
earlier you didn't you didn't
mention here it oh, I'm drinking
a source Perrier lime. From the
camp
John C Dvorak: lime ladies and
gentlemen, very you know if
anyone can find a blue bottles
of Perrier lightly carbonated
tastes just like low bad to wipe
my favorite sparkling beverage?
Oh
Adam Curry: no Budweiser like
boudoir. Like big bad dua. No,
no be de Lobi day.
John C Dvorak: I don't want to
drink low bid day.
Adam Curry: The Democrats are
frightened that I'm gonna spoil
the election for President Biden
and the Republicans are
frightened that I'm gonna spoil
it for President Trump. The
truth is, they're both right.
Unknown: Back in April, he
launched a longshot bid for the
Democratic nomination. But his
position on vaccines and
abortion were out of the party's
mainstream his own siblings
denouncing his run as an
independent saying Bobby might
share the same name as our
father but he does not share the
same values vision or judgment.
We denounce his candidacy and
believe it to be perilous for
our country.
denounce him.
John C Dvorak: denounce your own
you know, what are your own
members of your own family? It's
disgusting
Adam Curry: was pretty bad. But
this is not good for it. I mean,
John C Dvorak: the timing sodomy
is horrible, but this is also
done this like a week ago or
maybe a month from now? It
wouldn't it wouldn't have
mattered by the way. I was gonna
say that report indicates that
he was thwarted. They did
without going into any details.
There hasn't even doesn't been
the Democratic Convention yet.
There hasn't been any primaries.
Adam Curry: Well, he he can't
get in. He can't he can't even
get in the primary lock
John C Dvorak: him out is what
she should what she should have
said yes, I locked him
Adam Curry: out. Eyes. I mean,
there's still a lot of time a
lot of things can happen. But I
see no reason why the military
industrial complex, the
financial, which is same as the
financial complex. Maybe this is
why Steve Steve Scalise Vegas
possibly can become the new
Speaker of the House.
John C Dvorak: We that was my
assertion to him was your
assertion. It was yours. But you
know, hey, you
Adam Curry: know he's got
cancer. Wow, we can't have that
guy with cancer. Well get rid of
Raskin then to come on. This is
what kind of acts we kind of
that's that's probably the one
of the most demoralizing things
you can say. Hey, ma'am. I'm
sorry. You can't run because you
got cancer. I mean, people
survive. People live with him.
Just an Marjorie Taylor Greene.
Notice my voice going up when I
say your name, Marjorie Taylor.
But you do that all the time
with Marjorie Taylor Greene why
she do it up? Oh, no, no, no,
he's got cancer. Oh, no, we
can't have him do he might die
before he can sign more money
for Ukraine and Israel?
John C Dvorak: Well, they have
to put him in my thesis because
he's all pro giving more money
to Ukraine. Yet while he was
marginally, Marjorie, Democrats
should put him in. I mean, it
just takes like 50 of them to
say yeah, and the whole thing
goes through
Adam Curry: how much do you
think? So I I think that 24
billion for Ukraine. I mean, the
public money, right? This is
just the stuff that they'll tell
us. I think that will now have
to move to 50 And I think
Israel, I think we go to 400
billion, just for starters.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, that's too
much. They don't need that much
money down there for Iran. Well,
no, Ron's different. If that
happens, then they have to start
putting money down there.
Adam Curry: Yeah, that's what
it's for. That'd be great. And
who do we actually need to take
out? What do we need to do in
Iran to
John C Dvorak: Toy need to low
flying jets and Hello, flying
jets and bombs and there's a
neighborhood where all the
mullahs live is known fact they
live in these mansions in some
kind of walled garden
neighborhood. And you just go in
there and bomb all their houses
and then fly back and say, I
don't know what happened. You
just
Adam Curry: hired you just got
us fired as the courier Devorah
Consulting Group. This is not
the right answer. How do we get
real money out of it? Some real
John C Dvorak: Whoa, yeah,
there's not real money to do
well. Yeah, good question. Good
point.
Adam Curry: It's not cheap to
send a aircraft carrier down
there.
John C Dvorak: No, that's
expensive. It's very expensive,
and they're gonna send another
group. I don't have the clip.
But somebody else came on one of
the shows another action arm. Of
course, he says, yeah, and they
got to another group going in
and reported jumped on him and
go, what this is news jet. Tell
me more. And they gave him no
bah bah, bah, bah, bah, bah.
That's good. That's good. It was
pretty funny.
Adam Curry: So the other scandal
what was the other scandal wiped
from the front pages? So many
people benefit from this? Never
let a crisis go to waste.
Menendez. Menendez don't even
Don't talk about him anymore.
Bob Menendez and his corruption
scandal,
John C Dvorak: though he's a
total criminal.
Adam Curry: Well, do you
remember what I said?
John C Dvorak: No, I do not.
Adam Curry: I said his wife is
the problem. Yes, you
John C Dvorak: did say that. I
remember that.
Unknown: This is the second time
he's been indicted in the last
eight years and report suggests
that Menendez his wife played a
major role in his murky deals.
Menendez med he's Armenian
American while studying
ARSLANIAN at a restaurant in
2018 and got married in 2020.
Prosecutors claim she played a
key role in collecting hundreds
of 1000s of dollars worth of
bribes from three New Jersey
businessmen seeking help from
the powerful lawmaker. Her role
was so vital that she was the
one who introduced Menendez to
parties connected to the
Egyptian government. According
to the indictment document. The
filing also states that Nadine
was unemployed before they met
but the following year, she
incorporated a new consulting
company strategic international
business consultants LLC. After
their marriage in 2020. She came
into possession of a large
amount of gold. She later sold
some of the bars for between
200,000 to $400,000, according
to the senators financial
disclosure reports. Now here's a
bit of context, Menendez was the
chairman of the Senate Foreign
Relations Committee until the
investigation became public.
That post gave him a lot of
influence in US foreign policy.
This is where wire Hannah comes
in. Nadine and Hannah were
friends for years before her
marriage to Menendez. According
to the indictment, Hannah helped
arrange meetings and dinners
between Menendez, Nadine and
Egyptian military and
intelligence officials. This was
part of a covert initiative
aimed at using the Senator's
influence to boost US aid to
Egypt. After one of these
meetings in 2018, Menendez
texted his wife telling her to
inform her that he would sign
off and a multimillion dollar
weapons sale to Egypt.
Adam Curry: Menendez should not
be impeached for corruption but
for being an idiot this woman
snookered him in
John C Dvorak: you know, I don't
know that this is really what
this sounds to me like you're
putting out a story that
parallels the Biden story with
his son you it's his fault. And
I think that's a judgment puts
in my mind I have a clip. New
bad stuff about Biden,
Adam Curry: Biden, hey, screw
the war in Israel. We've got the
Biden and Menendez stuff for you
right here.
Unknown: You record show that
President Biden was involved in
his son and brother's businesses
as vice president, America first
Lego published the records from
the National Archives following
a Freedom of Information Act
lawsuit. National Archives
Records show that then Vice
President Biden's office
exchanged over 19,000 emails
with Hunter Biden's is missed
confirm Rosemont Seneca over
4000 emails with Hunter Biden
himself over 1700 emails with
his brother James Biden, and
over 3700 emails was James
Biden's lie in whole group.
Biden has previously claimed he
was not involved in his son and
brothers business dealings.
America first legal said on X
today, quote, There was
extensive commingling between
them. The House Oversight
Committee which has been
investigating the Biden's family
business dealings is also
commented saying Biden's
statement quote doesn't match
his track record
Adam Curry: Oh, yes. You know, I
don't think anyone can say that
they don't feel much better
after just listening to this to
this hour and 50 minutes of the
no agenda show. I mean, you're
not I hope so you're not all
spun up you're not all worried
about tomorrow. Tomorrow all
it's gonna be attacks everywhere
in America tomorrow. Yeah,
John C Dvorak: we're going to be
attacked any minute today. These
guys are going to come in with
you know, somehow they're going
to swim over.
Adam Curry: Now they're coming
across the border. Coming right
up to
John C Dvorak: the Bahamas. How
do you get to Mexico without
swimming by
Adam Curry: coming right up
through Fredericksburg. No.
Stopping when you
John C Dvorak: see him? Yeah,
well, you mentioned that you
were we're talking about some
buddy wanted to send us some
clips from somebody we won't
even mentioned his name. A guy
who is a well respected or not
well respected but a well
followed. Guy as on the on the
YouTube and everyplace else and,
and I said that we don't play
this guy's clip. Charlie Kirk.
Oh, that's who it was Charlie
Kirk. And you said well, he just
came into Canterbury gave us
beach and they got all the local
women all jacked up.
Adam Curry: We were supposed to
go. But I don't it's something
that somehow that didn't happen.
And it was a I think it was to
raise money for the Tea Party,
which I guess still exist. And
brother, so I don't know. And I
have nothing against Charlie
Kirk. Personally, he's probably
John C Dvorak: he's he's a very
easy, very sharp, very sharp
guy.
Adam Curry: But everybody
everybody came back so riled up.
There's Oh, ha ha.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, I've heard
some of his stuff he gets it
says like he does it on purpose.
He gets people's like you said
spun up. Yeah. And this is not
this is not good. We're like
Xanax.
Unknown: Amen.
Adam Curry: With that, I'd like
to thank you for your courage in
the morning to you the man who
put the season in the Christ
caulk ladies and gentlemen say
hello to my friend on the other
end one only Mr. John Cena
John C Dvorak: Morning Mr.
Schiff see boots on the ground
feet in the air subs in the
water. And all the games and
nights out there in the morning
to
Unknown: the trolls and the
troll Joe can be counted around
Adam Curry: 2074 2000 Write that
down to 1000s I have a notebook
I
John C Dvorak: 2074. Yeah,
Adam Curry: 2074 Trolls. That's
up. And N and we're almost two
hours in. We know what it is.
This is what happens people like
man, I'm all spun up. Maybe the
boys will
John C Dvorak: spit me down this
slow you down a slow you down.
Adam Curry: I mean, there's
nothing like John saying that he
prefers the smart gay guys. I
mean, come on. That's common
people. That's the kind of
comedy The no agenda show
delivers to you.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, everybody
prefers the smart guys.
Adam Curry: Now, don't rely on
the platforms. If you want to
always know when the no agenda
show was on, if you want
reliable delivery of your
podcast within 90 seconds of
delivery, if you want the live
stream, because it's not just
podcasts on demand, you need a
modern podcast app, get that
from podcast app.com 3% of the
world will be saved by it. And
there's more coming. I promise
you. You can also follow us at
no agenda. social.com Oh, man,
people are mad at me. I'm afraid
to even mention anybody. Well,
the last show I said, this guy,
I'm not going to mention his
name because again, we all get
angry. Let's admit you
progressive nights sloughed and
sad, you know, he posted this
screenshot. And I said, Hey,
man, how about a link? This is
not helpful. And then Oh, yeah.
You
John C Dvorak: said you do that
which is common. You do that
constantly.
Adam Curry: And he's like, Well,
this is also the guy that claims
that we never talk about Julian
Assange and it's there's reasons
I find it interesting. You don't
talk about Julian Assange. Mm
Hmm Hmm. Hmm. It's one of these
guys. Then he and I will not
stop posting until you
apologize. I don't know what the
heck he was talking about. And I
didn't realize that we were here
to work for you. Said the man
with a free account. We don't
even run the thing. But you
know, it's like signaled noise
people see this, you know, even
this even Macedon is bumming me
out.
John C Dvorak: Really. bumming
you out. It's bumming me out. I
haven't heard that term for
While mountains go wow. Oh, wow.
Yep, yep.
Adam Curry: And then it was like
he's a great
John C Dvorak: guy. Oh, okay,
great guy this Assange
Adam Curry: partisan night slot.
John C Dvorak: Who says he's a
great guy,
Adam Curry: everybody. Oh,
you're wrong. He's a great guy.
I didn't say he wasn't a great
guy said he wasted my time with
a screenshot.
John C Dvorak: How does anybody
know where there's a great guy
or not? Nobody be intermingled
because the thing because
Adam Curry: he's onboarded so
many people. He's a great guy.
John C Dvorak: He's
unbelievable. Okay, well,
Adam Curry: I can't I can't how
I was going to bring my sister
in. But I can't now because you
said something about me. So I
can't ever let her hear that
because you'd be so
disappointed. No agenda is no
good with you.
John C Dvorak: On parents
getting kick him off, Master.
No,
Adam Curry: no, I'm kicking
myself off. It's annoying. I
just want to follow some blogs.
John C Dvorak: Well, there's no
such thing anymore. Yes, there
is.
Adam Curry: Bringing it back
baby. books, movies,
documentaries. It's all going to
be RSS and I'm gonna I'm gonna
the the army. The army will
create it. You watch. We start
with podcasts. No one has taken
down the podcast. No one has
taken on the podcast. They
tried. They couldn't they tried
to capture it. Couldn't
John C Dvorak: you couldn't make
it Adams RSS. No. Yeah, you
could be an arse okay.
Adam Curry: You can follow Adam
and origin the social.com I
won't post you follow Jhansi
Dvorak at norgine. The
social.com post something to him
and he'll say something grumpy
back. Everyone knows it.
Unknown: Everyone knows it.
We're no good. too rare.
Adam Curry: It's rare that you
say something grumpy? Yeah.
Where's the evidence? And stuff
like that? All right, then
that's just the voice I hear my
head. Value for value is the
reason why you have not heard
any advertisements you've not
heard anything about gold or
gold? Buy gold buy gold. Yeah.
And this is the reason what's
happening now is the reason you
want to secure your future. You
want to buy some gold? I have
gold bars. John, have you bought
any gold recently? Did you get
in?
John C Dvorak: I buy a bar a
month.
Adam Curry: Bar a month. Wow.
What that DHL plug must be doing
pretty well for you. Bar a
month. No, there's no no and no.
The only advertisements are the
things that we as products we'd
like or if someone slipped
something in a donation. We're
fine with that one moment you
will Finchy your your company
name I'm sure the door is being
burnt down with new clients
everywhere. Lena Lubetkin Yeah.
And so all we ask for is that
you return some value time,
talent or treasure. It saves us
enormous resources. It really
makes no agenda show and you
know agenda nation what it is by
the work that everyone else does
for each other. Like the
meetups. Oh man, the new being
at.io Sir sir de nonnamous. Is
he the upgrade is going to be
phenomenal. I this being a.io.
Man, I can I just give you an
example of how cool since we're
in the donation segment. How
cool bing.io is okay, I want a
second. Yeah. So I was looking
for something about a new story.
And this goes back to September
14. So we're almost one month
ago. And it only took me I want
to say 37 seconds to get exactly
what I wanted. And then and that
includes the editing of the harp
at the beginning of the listen
to this report from the show
1597 boots on the ground report
that is troubling from
Massachusetts. In the morning
boys quick update from the
horrible state of tax that UCITS
My cousin is set to get married
over Columbus Day weekend. The
groom's family is from out of
town and they rented two floors
of a hotel so they could all be
together for the weekend.
Governor Healy just seized the
hotel to house migrants so they
have lost their reservations.
There's nowhere else to say on
top of it. All the hotels that
are housing migrants are having
fires, assaults, etc. It's a
nightmare. So that is one month
ago. One month ago on your no
agenda show and what pops up
today.
Unknown: Early this year Travel
Agent Mark man's back booked 400
rooms for clients to stay near
Foxborough for the big Army Navy
game. Most of his clients are
veterans and plan to stay in
hotels like Comfort Inn and Best
Western only recently being told
up to 70 of those rooms were
canceled to make room for
migrants now staying there was a
done deal. I mean, they'd
already started taking in
migrants.
I was very concerned and
troubled to hear that any
veteran may have had their rooms
canceled.
Go to Bora Healy has directed
her Secretary of Veterans
Affairs to help those veterans
but for many the damage is
already done
as I understand it, those were
decisions made by area hotels.
Oh yeah, so management confirms
they are providing shelter and
support to refugees, saying we
consider it a privilege to offer
a safe haven to those who have
been forced to flee their homes
due to challenging
circumstances.
Adam Curry: We know that's code
for man the government gave us a
lot more money than those two
John C Dvorak: new vets are
gonna give us for these
veterans. That's
Adam Curry: no good. We don't
care about them. twice as
John C Dvorak: much money from
my for housing and migrant we
get straight from the government
checks cash and the
Adam Curry: governor's like, oh,
no, what I can't believe that.
That's crazy. I had no idea this
was happening. So that's what
being a doctor that's just one
of the many beautiful things
that we receive as gifts and
value from our producers all
around the world all around no
agenda nation. We also have
artists and the artists ever
since we started ragging on
their AI have been doing a lot
better. The artwork for episode
1597 Was I mean, we had some
choices to make. But this was so
perfect because it was the
Fibonacci episode than our last
probably the last one. Well,
considering it'll be another
1000 episodes before we get to
one. Yeah, I think I think
John C Dvorak: we're gonna do
2500 And
Adam Curry: fo Diddley, also
known as Sir Schouwburg did a
just a wonderful piece of
Fibonacci art with no agenda on
top of it. If you haven't seen
it, then that mean, you missed
out? Because man, this is good.
John C Dvorak: Yes, it was. It
was. It wasn't we looked and
looked and looked. And I mean,
we both kind of liked the war
calendar. We liked it a lot. by
Sir shooting. Yeah, it's
dynamite.
Adam Curry: We figured we could
use it any time because
John C Dvorak: we never do that.
By the way. We always talk a big
game about it.
Adam Curry: I use it for the for
the bad signal today. Oh, good.
Yeah.
John C Dvorak: Well, well, then.
That's something Yeah. We talk a
big game about that. I also
liked comic strip, strip
bloggers Air Force, the
parachute. It was la I
obviously. But the no agenda
thing. We looked and looked at
it. And it's just like it was it
just a good looking piece.
Adam Curry: It actually probably
wasn't a Fibonacci, golden ratio
because of the square size of
the of the art.
Unknown: So it felt it felt a
little off. I don't know.
John C Dvorak: I think it looks
pretty legit to me. But whatever
the case, it was dynamite. And
it just worked out. Yeah. As a
pretty piece. And then it's a
little different. It was great.
So
Adam Curry: what else did we
John C Dvorak: look at? There
wasn't really much. I mean,
there's a lot of stuff that
could be used
Adam Curry: Biden kicking the
dog, but the Biden wasn't good.
Yeah, we
John C Dvorak: didn't talk
enough about Biden kicking the
dog anyway.
Adam Curry: Now. What else was
there?
John C Dvorak: Biden kicks dogs.
Okay, well, good to know.
Adam Curry: Yes, not really
wasn't that much. I mean, in
hindsight, I think that lather
rinse repeat by the spook was
kind of nice. to two different
versions. But still, it just
didn't compare to the
John C Dvorak: Fibonacci was an
artistic enough. Yeah, it did.
Adam Curry: The calendar of
ripping off the Ukrainian flag,
revealing the Israeli flag
underneath. It was just a great
concert. It was the same guy. He
was competing against himself.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, you get
that a lot with somebody who's
on a roll. They got some good
ideas in their head and they do
a couple art pieces or three
sometimes and they're all in the
same guy that it was we look at
Adam Curry: and looking at
what's coming in so far. We'll
have to see. I don't know. Step
it up people. It looks like some
more AI stuff has slipped in.
John C Dvorak: Oh, yeah,
definitely. Yeah, definitely.
Definitely.
Adam Curry: Thank you very much.
To fo Diddley, fo diddley for
the artwork for 1598 Oh man. No.
1597 I'm sorry, what? 15 man
we're also almost at 1600 Yeah.
And the 16th anniversary is on
the 26th I believe
John C Dvorak: it's right the
next week we go to 1600 then we
hit the anniversary show and
we're not doing a two for one
kind of thing because that was
for 15 and Tana do was he's just
not going to keep doing that
now. But I do have a special
offer which I will roll Oh,
Adam Curry: yes special offer.
John C Dvorak: I've been working
on how to do it. Workout. It'll
be a start out I'll it'll be
revealed in the next newsletter.
Because it is going to start
it's gonna go it's only going to
be a three week there's a
special promotion. Yes, a
special promotion is only a
three week deal is ends. It's
not going to be going on
forever, because it takes work.
It takes J doing a lot of work.
Adam Curry: I was gonna say you
read really you're gonna do some
work
John C Dvorak: out for jobs
gonna be doing good work. And
it'll be a roll it out. It'll
roll out this Sunday. Oh, man,
I'm excited. And then it'll be
continued right through the 1600
and the anniversary show and to
the end of the month, and
probably one extra week.
Adam Curry: But we have to use
that promo code.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, and then
you get a mattress in a box.
Adam Curry: Then, of course, we
have the producers, really only
two executives and a handful of
associate executives for today.
This is all the way value for
value works. Whatever you get
out of the show, send it back to
us. It doesn't matter if it's $1
if it's $1,000 I mean it
obviously it matters to us but
the whole point is you valuated
what is valuable to you. We
can't look into your into your
finances. We all we ask is that
you send something back time
talent treasure, and about 3%
does. That's the those are the
people are gonna get saved by
the way. No one else is gonna
get saved. With my RSS
extravagance degree. We kick it
off with our top executive
producer Dame shell who's in
Millington, Tennessee Shelly
John C Dvorak: I think it's
pronounced Shelly
Adam Curry: I'm sorry. Usually I
probably met her. Dame Shelly
I'm thinking in Tennessee 333 33
Hey fellas been seeing lots of
30 threes lately and realize
it's been too long karma for all
and a little yay much love from
Dame Shelley.
Unknown: You've got karma
Adam Curry: your name Shelly
John C Dvorak: Vandenberg is
next season Provan Sol Louisiana
or they pronounce it 30 threes
kept showing up you're right
that's the signal it's time to
donate yeah Carmen health karma
for all please love you both.
And all you do to keep critical
thinking and humor alive. Semper
Fi ret
Unknown: you've got Harma
Adam Curry: simplified interview
right. And then we hit our first
Associate Executive Producer
with a row of ducks Benjamin
greasy from Overland Park Kansas
222 dot 22 When he says Zippy
rules Thank you
John C Dvorak: Eric Levin Berg
in Los Angeles, California. And
he is in for $201 and he says I
do believe 100% that you are the
best podcast in the universe.
I'd like to request jobs karma
health karma and relationship
karma shout out to my brother
sir Turkey, who I hope to follow
as Knight of the Round Table
Unknown: jobs, jobs, jobs and
jobs for jobs.
Adam Curry: Then here's your
health karma. Karma. We just
take it all in. Oh, John. You've
got to do this one.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, Linda Lou
Potkins up is she's in Lakewood,
Colorado. Jobs karma for a
resume that gets the results go
to Image makers inc.com For all
your executive resume and job
search needs. That's image
makers Inc with a k.com but just
find Linda Potkin under the show
producers list. This is a
showdown between the show and
Linda Lou Pak and who keeps
donating $200 a show to see how
long she can hold out. It
shouldn't be staring. Shouldn't
she be a dame? Tell she's a dame
maybe even a VI Countess. She
doesn't want to she don't want
to interrupt the flow job who at
the end when she gives up any
minute. Then she'll be a witness
which you have the totals and
we'll give her what she needs.
It'll
Unknown: be queen jobs, jobs,
jobs and jobs for jobs. Pharma.
Adam Curry: Sean Macross. In is
in tager kit take a que South
Carolina to want to dollars. He
says appreciate what you guys
do. Well, thank you. Thank you
very much.
John C Dvorak: You can get the
next one because you have the
notes open.
Adam Curry: I don't actually but
it won't take me long to open.
Sorry. That's okay. This is from
surfer, surfer, surfer, surfer.
And the services which Rudy
sends in a note which you will
read $200 In the morning, ITM
John Adams switcheroo. Please
credit this Associate Executive
Producer ship to His Excellency
Mr. Dana Brunetti governor of
Eldorado. That's his honorifics.
It's
John C Dvorak: very suspicious.
Adam Curry: These donations will
continue until John gets a big
part yet karma for all producers
please love is lit, sir for
black Baron of the i Four
corridor. All right.
Unknown: You've got
Adam Curry: karma, by the way, I
fully expect Brunetti to come
through one day.
John C Dvorak: He's out of the
business. Now he's not.
Adam Curry: He's not Hey,
John C Dvorak: thank you
bringing me back in.
Adam Curry: I just like to be
killed in something of a
gruesome death. I
John C Dvorak: think a lot of
people feel that.
Adam Curry: Go ahead, you get to
read this long one. Oh,
actually, that's it. Those that
were done those of the executive
and Associate Executive
producers for episode 1598 Thank
you all so very much. We highly
appreciate what you do for us.
These credits are Real you
John C Dvorak: can actually stop
stop. This next one is 159 and
Australian dollars which bumps
I'll read it. Yeah, this is Dean
from Melbourne, Victoria,
Australia. 159 70 or 200.
Something in American dollars is
dollar Rhett's? Which we made a
deal. It's kind of an agreement
bad,
Adam Curry: bad deal in
John C Dvorak: a bad deal for
us. First of all, you need to de
douchey
Unknown: you've been de deuced
John C Dvorak: and it's 159 70
is also the golden is the
Fibonacci number is a numbers
guy was pleasantly stirred by
the call for the golden mean
show. Unfortunately, my donation
might have arrived and the
cutoff time after the cutoff
time was at last when I missed
the donor segment and it'd be
who's both John and you given
the rare nature of the episode
indeed, that would be possible
for a golden mean credit award
in post. I would definitely make
my day okay,
Adam Curry: you gotta you got it
man. My
John C Dvorak: initial note was
to highlight I got hit in the
mouth off a sweet treat in early
2018 from Uncle Hotep. co host
of the Hotep Ben told you with
Hotep Jesus when his followers
does the only Hotep donation
ever have as far as anyone
listen to the show, and you got
to do somebody wants to do
Unknown: bad deed deuced
John C Dvorak: Big shout out to
the low tech community and all
the no agenda producers thank
you both for the invaluable
insights of deconstructions a
once a karma and verbalize your
33 Thank you for you service.
That's our pleasure. In the
standby 3333 33 out you've got
karma. And
Adam Curry: definitely concludes
our executive and Associate
Executive Producers credits are
Real you can use them anywhere
credits are recognized. Be like
Dana Brunetti and put it on
imdb.com Then you can say hey,
look at my credits. Look at this
guy. You heard this guy house of
cards with 50 Shades of Grey
GranTurismo do it to people,
it's good for your resume. It's
good for conversation. And you
might even pick up another
listener along the way. Thank
you again for supporting the no
agenda show if you'd like to
become a producer. Here's where
Unknown: you go. vote.org/n A
Adam Curry: or no agenda show
dotnet John is going to take us
through to the 50s won't take
very long and then Bruce
John C Dvorak: Schwalm starts us
off from Harrisburg,
Pennsylvania. $133. And it says
David poeple poeple and
curiously, Australia 12863. And
this is a switcheroo for his
lovely wife Liz's birthday. It
needs a de douching
Unknown: you've been de deuced
John C Dvorak: Yeah, Australians
can get a biscuit for their
birthday if you can hit that
button.
Adam Curry: Sorry. I should that
shouldn't be a button. Hold on.
You asked for it.
John C Dvorak: They always give
me a biscuit on my birthday God
and His Pull, pull. Pull pull is
how you pronounce it. I speak of
the devil. There's Dana Brunetti
from Golden cloud ranch in
California. That's his ranch. I
will read some of this because
of the nature of possibly
getting a big part. Monday is a
Stella's 11th birthday. She's on
the list. The only show episode
she ever wants to hear while I'm
driving her to school is the
episode last year where she got
a birthday shout out. Yeah,
mentioned her every show and I
can listen with her in the car.
Also, there's a good Fibonacci
reference in my movie 21 about
the MIT car card counters. He
comes in with a with a 112 30
fives like I discerned two
things from this to 112 a Senate
becoming an executive producer.
He comes in with just a low
level. He's running out of
money. He's and he's talks about
one of his old movies. He's
going back into the business of
being a producer.
Adam Curry: Oh yeah. Oh yeah.
It's gonna be 500 Shades of
Grey. It's got a big part
John C Dvorak: about that. Be
the guy handing out the whips in
the office. That's Andrew Kelly
in Los Angeles, California
$100.33. We give you some grad
school admissions karma at the
end anonymity and lien,
Netherlands
Adam Curry: Lena Lena Lena Lena
Lena lane, Lane, that lane.
John C Dvorak: Lane that lane
that $100. Katie in Bozeman,
Montana $100 Nisa de douching.
Unknown: De deuced.
John C Dvorak: Sir Ty Joker that
he is in Queen Creek, Arizona.
Eight, the 888 lot of eights
happy 10 by 10 by 10 day 1010
day which was just the other day
it was Tuesday.
Adam Curry: It was last week as
well. Yeah, it was two weeks in
a row
John C Dvorak: is the best
China. We'll get a note from the
Chinese Embassy because of that.
Kevin McLaughlin the Duke Aluna
Concord North Carolina 808.
Breast Cancer Awareness Month.
Save the JUGS getting getting to
the end of this. Josh urban
David German and North Tura Mora
New South Wales $77. This is
under 2556 and dollar ruse.
Kevin McLaughlin is back with
606 breast cancer awareness
month save the Sugar Plum. Okay,
Sir Don in Chandler, Arizona.
606 Dave gainer in Melrose
Florida 606 small boobs in
regards to recent news from the
curry house. We don't know about
on this show.
Adam Curry: Now you got to
listen to Korean the keeper if
you want to know about that and
less
John C Dvorak: Tara kowski in
Kingman Arizona 57 Oliver Reich
I should have called him by his
current name. But I won't and I
want to I just want to say where
he's from he goes with an
anonymous name now 5150 Thank
you. Christine Heinz and
Manchester New Hampshire 5123
Bad Ideas supply Bad Idea supply
5050. And now we got the $50
donors with few there are
there's actually more of these
than anything else as a matter
of fact that the natty a Borg
and San Marcos California oh my
god he said ended hood in orange
Vale California Michelle petty
in Grand Forks, North Dakota,
Tim del Vecchio and blend in
Pennsylvania. John spade in
Edmond Oklahoma, Andrew lasso in
Mineola, New York Cory
Cunningham in Warrenton,
Virginia Alex, Alexis Earl bliss
are Robles in Chula Vista.
Michael Vendel in Matawan, New
Jersey Gary Mao in Woodland
Hills California Stephen in, in
Bucks elder South Dakota.
Kimberly de in Holly Springs,
North Carolina, Erin Joyce in
New York, Pennsylvania, William
dole gay in Bristol Ville, Ohio,
Carrie Jackson and Watertown,
Tennessee and last on the list
from Miami Beach we have Jason
to luzio want to thank all these
people for making a show 1598 to
two away a reality
Adam Curry: and thank you
everyone who came in under 50
For real reasons of anonymity
that's the best way to stay
anonymous 4999 People do that a
lot also thank you for being on
those sustaining donations they
they come back monthly you can
make your own What do you got a
cool numbers 30 threes elevens
12 Even threes if you want all
of its there, and as always we
thank our executive and
Associate Executive producers
for being here producing episode
Unknown: this we go out but yet
people in the mouth
Adam Curry: and we kick it off
with the governor of El Dorado
Dana Brunetti, wishing Estella
Happy birthday she turned to
Lebanon October 9 Happy Birthday
Estella in the car. From uncle
Adam and Uncle John. Sir
protector. Sir Bob protector of
Western foco wishes his sister
Pam and son Andrew a happy
birthday. Born on the 11th So
that was all yesterday Tim de
vecchio celebrates today and
David poeple wishes his wife Liz
a very happy birthday as we say
happy birthday from everybody
here in the best podcast in the
unit. ours. Now before we we
have won one podium, one podium
person today for a Daming. This
is the dame note from Kara
parallel. And on last Thursday's
episode My smokin hot husband
Walker Phillips made a generous
switcheroo donation to make me a
dame or at least Dame adjacent
for my birthday. That's right.
We waited for you at the
roundtable. I would like a
bottle of 2017 cost of brown
Cerise, Pinot Noir and a vegan
gluten free pizza with
mushrooms, olives and onions.
But well, you know, how about
this wine? What's that? The 2017
COSTA brown Cerise Pinot Noir.
Is that any good? Yeah, I don't
I've never had it. My day name
shall be deemed windchimes
portraits of the Partridge
Family temple. Oh man, they must
be fun to hang out with thanks
so much for everything. And we
will bring you right in fact,
let's get our blades out. Here
we go.
John C Dvorak: Got it right here
ready to go.
Adam Curry: All right, here we
go. Kara power about up on the
podium you go. Thanks for your
hobby. He loves you very, very
much. I'm very proud to
pronounce the K the same wind
chimes Partridge of the
Partridge Family temple for you
we have well Brent boys and
Chardonnay. I don't think you
need any hookers and blow. We
also have that 27 custom brown
Cerise, Pinot Noir and a vegan
gluten free pizza with
mushrooms, olives and onions
delectable. I tell you, along
with that just in case you don't
have enough of that pizza. We
got some vodka but Ellis and
buckets and bourbon, some ginger
ale and Jerboas we got some
breast milk and pablum. And, of
course, the always effervescent
mutton and meat. Enjoy that
while you surf over to no agenda
rings.com Check out all the
rings that are available for
Knights and Dames. There's
really only one but it's a cool
one because it's a ring that is
a signet ring. You can use it
with the wax that we will
provide to seal your important
correspondence. And as always,
they come with a certificate of
authenticity signed by yours
truly. crackpot and buzzkill
Thank you very much to your
husband, thank you for being a
day. We'd love having you here.
And again, thank you to everyone
who supported no agenda on this
episode.
Unknown: No one said
Adam Curry: well, not only do we
have no meetup reports. There's
also no meetups on Friday the
13th Interestingly enough, there
is one today
John C Dvorak: me found that
quite peculiar.
Adam Curry: You'd think I was
afraid, you know.
John C Dvorak: There's also no
meetups on Halloween.
Adam Curry: Well, now is
Halloween. You gotta do
something else with your time
you
John C Dvorak: got to take the
kids. Take the kids know
meetups, the Mile
Adam Curry: High meetup kicks
off today at 630 at Lincoln's
Roadhouse in Denver, Colorado
then on Saturday, the North
Carolina triad two o'clock at
Kernersville Brewing Company in
North Carolina in Kernersville.
Obviously, the mutton and Mead
meet up Alaska and it'll be a
two o'clock at Parker Ranch.
That's in Palmer Alaska. So you
have to RSVP it's a private home
now that sounds like a lot of
fun. Lake chapel a muster that
chapel and next time will be 330
for you. That's Mexico. American
Legion choppa la Shapleigh Is
that how you pronounce it? Chapa
la central Mexico. Damn kicking
and screaming organizing that
for you can't wait to hear a
meet up report from there. The
spot the spook casual pint is
where you will meet up in
Huntsville, Alabama on Saturday.
The second Saturday slave soiree
at Dick's primal burger in
Portland, Oregon. Also on
Saturday five o'clock we have
the Northeast Houston meetup
3040 Farm to Market bogeys
billiard that'll be at five
o'clock on Sunday next showed a
505 ITM that's in sawmill.
Albuquerque, New Mexico. This is
Jeff tobique. Sir, sir Jeff,
please people go visit him. He's
been kind of low on the on the
attendance like couple people
only so and he's a cool Do you
really is asking Him to show you
his scars. Cast casting for
Gaston. That'll be at two
o'clock on Sunday at Gaston
manor in Charleston South
Carolina Dame Jennifer's
organizing all that sounds like
something good. Gaston Manor,
private residence like a Bruce
Wayne type of thing like Wayne
Manor Naik, EB Dame Jennifer
I'll be looking for a report
from you. And finally also on
Sunday the spooky October meet
up three o'clock at prodigy
Burger Bar in Indianapolis,
Indiana and Indy we're coming
December 4 to keep an eye coming
for for a meet up so everybody
get ready for that. It's gonna
be a lot of fun. I'm very
excited about it. Since we'll
have direct flights. Teams like
we can fly through Atlanta But
nope, nope, nope, nope, nope. So
we'll be arriving right around
seven o'clock to get everything
going and we're leaving that
we're staying at the airport
hotel people just say no, we're
in and out in and out but we're
coming for you because we love
you These are the no agenda
meetups, they're very important
for your psyche. You know,
whereas we act as the Xanax. You
really want, you know, the full
on ludes that's what you get
from the meetup you hang out
with people who you probably
wouldn't expect to hang out
with. But it turns out we're all
members of Gitmo nation and have
like a companion to the show.
You'll have great conversations
it's always fun. There's always
a little of alcohol involved and
you get connection which is
ultimate protection no agenda
meetups.com If you can't find
one near you start one yourself
will tell everybody all about
Unknown: everybody feels the
same
Okay,
Adam Curry: I'm back. I'm back.
I have two to two ISOs to I
think one of them's the winner.
Do you want to do yours first?
Are you always how you
John C Dvorak: did mine first
lesson?
Adam Curry: You love it? You're
wanted for Christmas? That's one
second I got a boost this next
one this is the winner Houma
This is the winner. Me just
looks at the volume sometimes
these aren't good. Okay, here we
go. This is the winner there is
just not enough of Taylor Swift
Come on. Come on. That's the
winner right there.
John C Dvorak: I like it. I like
it. I may have beat her when it
means now I have a couple here
that I thought I could fit that
I only I actually have one and
that one the other ones I have
are just an example of using the
Adobe thing and having it come
out cleaner but using but
changing some word now listen to
I get to I so big win and then I
so big win fix the play. I saw
big win and this is the clip I
wanted to fix.
Unknown: So a big way. Okay, so
a
John C Dvorak: big win. Yeah. So
a big win. big wig almost it was
so nice. But that's the problem
I have Adobe couldn't understand
it either. But he's but it was
big win.
Adam Curry: Okay, so here's the
Adobe product. Fixed Here we go.
Unknown: So I may weigh between
John C Dvorak: the big one a big
win big wing, the big wing
thanks to Adobe change when to
Wing Wing for nothing that's AI
for you. So now let's go to my
other one which is fact check
true
Unknown: fact check true
Adam Curry: na na na na nah,
this beats it. I mean, this is
just not enough of Taylor Swift
Come on. That's just that's the
that wins.
John C Dvorak: So I did a little
digging in this Taylor Swift
story.
Adam Curry: Why?
John C Dvorak: Because I'm
because this seems to me to be a
play by one public relations
firm to get NFL as one of their
clients because they have a
bunch of players and Taylor
Swift for some unknown reason is
probably write this up in the
newsletter. She is managed
publicity wise by us sports
management company that manages
athletes. Yeah. And she's there
among the athletes and this
makes nothing but sense that
they set her up with his a phony
boyfriend story, which is
Hollywood does all the time, of
course, but let's do it for the
NFL and get the numbers up. She
didn't show up in the last game.
We will never hear from her
again in the football era. And
she never was boyfriend
girlfriend bowl crap. But people
lapped it up.
Adam Curry: Do you have a clip
to go along with this or?
John C Dvorak: No, I use his
brother because you brought that
clip and I had to say something,
Adam Curry: just all your
assertions.
John C Dvorak: Alright, so I got
some I have some offbeat clips.
Adam Curry: Before we do
offbeat. Let's end with that. So
I can just depress everybody.
Well,
John C Dvorak: they're not
offbeat in that way. They're
their news clips that include
this one, which is Holland
climate change. Oh, here we go.
Unknown: And the Netherlands.
climate activists are
celebrating after lawmakers
Tuesday approved a motion
requiring the Dutch cabinet to
come up with a plan to phase out
fossil fuel subsidies. This
comes after a sustained campaign
by activists including a nearly
month long blockade of a major
highway this Lucas phenotypes of
extinction rebellion
Netherlands,
after a month long of daily
protests and more than 9000
arrests. The Dutch parliament
asked the Cabinet to come up
with scenarios for phase out of
fossil fuel subsidies during
this campaign we achieved
transformation I think of Dutch
society, with three quarters of
the people now wanting a phase
out of fossil fuel subsidies.
And even a third of the people
want immediate stuff out All
fossil fuel subsidies that is
the extinction rebellion demand.
So a big way. Yes.
Adam Curry: Let me tell you this
is some bull crap from the from
this ditch guy and I tell you
why. Okay, you ready for this?
This cabinet this cabinet fell a
while ago, so they cannot make
any laws or anything Intel
there's a new cabinet after
elections in November. So he is
full of vasavi coward. We call
it cow crap in Holland.
John C Dvorak: Well, the other
thing about that clip is that
they want to end fossil fuel
subsidies. What what is that?
It's not about ending fossil
fuel.
Adam Curry: It doesn't matter.
We got those idiots off of the
aid valve. It was annoying. We
couldn't shoot them with water
cannons because they were crying
all the time about it. So we
just say okay, you get something
from us go value children's cast
was actually pretty good. I
think I think I nailed that guy.
John C Dvorak: Nailed it. You
nailed it. You nailed it. You
will get nasty notes from some
of your Dutch. Oh,
Adam Curry: no, they agree. They
think they think it's all
annoying. Let's do something
depressing for a moment. And
then we'll do something funny.
You recall the well, actually,
you had the clips of the DNA
gene jock from the South
Carolina. What was it it was a
special hearing about COVID
About the vaccines about DNA
being in the
John C Dvorak: DNA being in the
vaccines and going into your
system as you know, recombinant
and putting it into your your
genetic material?
Adam Curry: Yes, none of this
seems to be doing very well for
a lot of people. And this same
ad hoc committee on the health.
Department of
John C Dvorak: Health seems to
be making a lot of people sick.
Adam Curry: Well, here is Dr.
Karen DeVore. She's a
dermatologist. Nice lady. two
parter.
Unknown: In the last two and a
half years since a vaccine has
been widely promoted. And many
patients have taken it out of
fear and isolation. The patients
who took the vaccine still get
COVID. And now I see patients
and I could not believe the
attorney whose spokesman said he
had heard the same thing because
in 30 years of practicing
dermatology, I've never heard
people describe their symptoms
this way. I am itching from my
bones out. I am on fire from the
inside. I see the most unusual
rashes and they don't respond
well to treatment. And they last
for months or years. I see
previously well controlled
autoimmune diseases like
psoriasis and eczema and lupus
now totally out of control. I
see your see aggressive, severe
shingles, it is more painful, it
is lasting longer. And this is
even in those who've had the
shingles vaccine. I see rapidly
growing skin cancers, including
basal cells that are just
supposed to be traditionally
very slow growing. I see
squamous cells, cutaneous
squamous cells that are
metastasizing much more often
than they ever did before. And
melanomas have become so unusual
and much harder to diagnose.
They are much more advanced at
presentation, and I have to
biopsy more and more things. And
it's all in vaccinated patients.
Adam Curry: So that's her
professional in her profession
in her field in the medical
profession. And he or she's
talking about just some other
ancillary things she has
noticed.
Unknown: And then beyond my
field, patients that I have seen
regularly for six to 12 months,
every six to 12 months for 30
years. They're aging more
rapidly. They've got unhealthy
weight loss, they keep their
balances bad, they're falling,
they're black and blue. They
can't get on an exam table. And
you see their medical updates as
they were in and they've had
atrial fibrillation, pacemakers,
heart attack strokes, blood
clots, pulmonary embolism,
Parkinsonism, ALS, tremors,
nerve policies, miscarriages,
infertility, did I mention
aggressive new ones that
cancers, recurrent stage four
cancers after 20 years of
remission? I know for people in
one small zip code in
Spartanburg that have rare
leukemias, three or four of them
are dead now, in over 30 years
of medical practice. I've
probably only known one or two
people who had Lou Gehrig's, or
ALS disease, and they were
distant and not really you know,
third or fourth contacts I now
know three people in my
immediate range of contact
Adam Curry: you know what's to
blame
John C Dvorak: Putin okay with
that, you're right. That was a
depressing clip. But
Adam Curry: now Now I'm going to
take you out of it. I'm taking
this
John C Dvorak: lie I still have
another news clip before you
take us out I was something
Adam Curry: no no because I want
you to end with something like
I'm going I don't have
John C Dvorak: something like I
have I have a what what clip
Adam Curry: Okay, do we want it
shouldn't that be the last clip
the what what clip?
John C Dvorak: Okay it's it's
actually a good last clip
because you go what
Adam Curry: will go what what
yep, yep. Here is Dr. Osterholm
that you know he has he has long
COVID Yes long COVID Yeah
John C Dvorak: the guy would
they got sick? Yeah right sick
as
Adam Curry: a dog. He was he was
the OG we're all gonna die. We
need to get vaccinated. met him
at Joe Rogan first time I went
on 3 million people gonna die.
Oh gee, he has a podcast. And oh
man COVID is it's all COVID.
Unknown: The researchers found
the SARS cov to can infect and
replicate and white blood cells,
leading to an inflammatory
response that is known to
increase the risk of heart
attacks and stroke. And this
elevated risk can last up to a
year after infection. In
additional research that has
been done, it has been
demonstrated that individuals up
to one year after their COVID
case, have an increased risk for
cardiovascular events,
cardiovascular events, as
specifically that is at least
seven times higher for COVID
related infections and for
influenza. We have been
observing an increase in heart
attacks and stroke with COVID 19
infections throughout the
pandemic. But until now, there
was no concrete biologic
evidence linking COVID-19 to
this increase, as the authors of
the paper explain their findings
provide for the first time a
direct mechanistic link between
COVID 19 infection and the heart
complications that provokes
Adam Curry: vascular problems.
We knew this, we knew this a
year of more than a year ago.
And we got it from these two
women. Do you know anything
about COVID Dix shrinkage?
Unknown: Yeah, okay, so remember
that it's proof it's COVID COVID
David dish rendering
John C Dvorak: that was I think
that was his shows off the rails
at that mark
Adam Curry: that's why I stopped
it all right. What give me some
light yeah
John C Dvorak: over the over
that guy over hold whatever the
hell is poster home Oh, Mr.
White He's making himself sick
at this point. I think you're
right that's a very good you
know how you can just get
yourself again using that term
spun up yeah, he's just doing it
to himself the poor guy I feel
sorry for him okay, this is this
is the update on Niger this our
African story right at the end
of the show, so people can't
complain you know, you can't is
it Niger on the show and we got
the funny stuff coming up after
this is Nigeria or nice air.
Nice air. Okay. So this is the
nice air clip and it just the
update and it's interesting
because of the very ending the
little ending at the end make
sure go what, here we go
Unknown: share, the first set of
French soldiers have started to
withdraw from the country after
orders by nushares military
junta following their July
takeover in the capital in the
AMA. Residents welcomed the
French soldiers departure
event today this batch of French
soldiers who arrived in who will
God willing shortly be taking to
the role to return home and is
only the culmination of a
struggle that the people have
engaged in. People are on their
feet to demand the departure of
the French soldiers from Niger
soil, because one thing is
certain Niger remains for the
people love Niger.
This comes as the US formally
designated the ouster of
President Mohammed Bazoom and
military takeover as a coup
suspending a two new Share. But
US officials say they do not
plan to remove any of its 1000
military personnel from new
Share.
John C Dvorak: What what I said?
What are we doing? We have we're
just so the French are rousted
and we still have our troops
there. And we don't plan to move
anything. Yeah, screw you. We
got our place and then we're
still you know, we're a kick ass
country. It's unbelievable.
Adam Curry: You know, they say
that the Empire is in decline,
and sometimes it kind of feels
like see
John C Dvorak: no evidence of
this.
Adam Curry: Well, maybe for you
in California, everything's all
hunky dory. I don't know. It's
not it's not feeling so great.
Unknown: But okay,
Adam Curry: there's no real
empire that EU they're in
decline. They're They're up
shits Creek. The EU has
reopened. I know. That's the
funny thing about it. Thanks to
us. Was that it? Was that was
that your end? That's the final
one. We'll do it.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, that's an
Africa clips. So there you go.
Adam Curry: Good work. Well, I
don't think we have anything
else that I think we've we've
kind of covered it all. For
today as best we can as best we
can. Well, that's good news
because We're going to end
everything with oh man some end
of show mixes and we got
John C Dvorak: these are
beauties by the way for people
out there don't hang up I'm
going to do
Adam Curry: the bomb them again
mix those throw that in there
since it was topical. We got
Maddie J miracle wolf it's a
brand new ones. Up next I know
AGENDA stream.com We have let me
see. ABS and a six pack with Sir
seat sitter and special guests
midnight Mike from OB Diem.
Whoa, you do not want to miss
that. at all, no agenda
stream.com With that modern
podcast app I know that you are
using for podcast apps.com More
deconstruction on Sunday coming
to you from the heart of the
Texas hill country here in FEMA
Region number six in the
morning, everybody. I am Adam
curry,
John C Dvorak: from Northern
Silicon Valley where I think
we'd kind of get our summer
Finally, I'm John C. Dvorak.
Adam Curry: We return on
Unknown: Sunday. Right here.
Adam Curry: Please remember us
at devora.org/na Until then,
adios mofos who we who he adds
Unknown: I'm gonna I'm gonna
bomb bomb. I'm gonna I'm gonna
I'm gonna bomb bomb out of I'm
gonna. I'm gonna I'm gonna bomb
bomb. I'm gonna I'm gonna I'm
gonna.
You 30 to 50% of the population
had relations back to Germany.
So there had to be this very
clever propaganda campaign. It's
known today as babies on
bayonets.
I can think of my nephew
gathered in the mud, the bodies
of lifeless children suspected
of being poisoned in a chemical
attack, allegedly orchestrated
by their own government. We have
all seen
the reports of the terrible
chemical weapons attack in
Syria. They took the babies out
of incubators, and let the
children to
the incubators. And they were
thrown out of the incubators so
that Kuwait could be
systematically dismantled 14
babies and young children babies
being bathed in kill to even
beheaded
babies and toddlers were found
babies and young children with
their heads copper children with
their head
deep headed. Babies found
dead next to that carts that has
been
through for civilized countries
of this world to do everything
within their power to remove
this scourge. From the face of
our Earth,
emotions drive wars, not facts.
It is sort of evil that it's
beyond comprehension. Beyond the
Leon the lake.
It took the babies and
incubators
is a bomb.
This is a fuse. This bomb has to
be filled.
Thomas is the original snack.
Pay attention please. It's a
classic tale of an authoritarian
and this little tale of
extremism. And sadly, so many of
those extremists are determined
to return to a place where you
know people could be in charge
of their lives feel empowered,
say what they want. So it is
like a tautology.
In order to try to end our
democracy, there needs to be
more multiprogramming of the
cult members gun control and
climate change in the economy
and taxes. What is it you want
to make America great again?
Tonight don't say that
oppo vora.org/in A
there is just not enough of
Taylor Swift