Adam Curry: Spread invading Adam
curry Jhansi Devorah for 1520 23
This is your award winning
combination media assassination
episode 1599 This
Unknown: is no agenda and we're
Adam Curry: partying like it's
1599 and broadcasting live from
the heart of the country here in
FEMA Region number six in the
morning, everybody. I'm Adam
curry
John C Dvorak: in from Northern
Silicon Valley where we're all
wondering where How and why did
Pete Davidson become a sex
symbol? Jhansi Dvorak?
Adam Curry: Wow, man, you guys
in California preoccupied with
the wrong things? Nobody cares
about Pete Davidson anymore.
John C Dvorak: Taco Bell does.
Adam Curry: Really? Is his air
commercial.
John C Dvorak: Oh, a.
Adam Curry: How do you How are
you? What are you watching that?
You get Taco Bell commercial? I
haven't seen Washington
television
John C Dvorak: to look for
Eclipse. Mm hmm.
Adam Curry: So we had to
speaking of Eclipse we had the
Eclipse yesterday. Yeah, we had
John C Dvorak: it too, though.
You had it too. Oh, yeah. We had
the was the 95% It wasn't full
like yours down there. But, boy,
I know your show isn't quite
100% full but you got one coming
in April. That's 100% And it's
gonna be in Texas. Yes.
Adam Curry: Yes. The 1% 100%
Well, the one yesterday was a
was judgeship was a total Jip
John C Dvorak: wasn't cool. No,
no, it wasn't cool. You know
what Chip is?
Adam Curry: Now we gotta we
gotta Ring of Fire. Okay, now,
that arc was what what, what,
what? What are you What are you
hiding from, but we had
John C Dvorak: cloud cover
through a bunch of fog. You got
to read it not only didn't get
dark, you wouldn't know it
didn't even happened.
Adam Curry: So Fredericksburg
was full. It wasn't like what we
expect for the full eclipse in
April. But it was full. And I
know it was full because we had
dinner with some new friends.
Remember, I told you I had my
birthday dinner? And this guy
bought us bought our dinner?
John C Dvorak: Yeah, the guy
from across the room. It won't
get Yeah.
Adam Curry: Oh, yeah. Anyway, so
they had they he has a ranch
like in Midland or something.
And he lives in Austin, but they
always come to Fredericksburg on
their way to the ranch. And, and
that's how we how we met them.
And they could they had to stay
at the Comfort Inn and we're
lucky to get a comfort in room,
which is almost a step below
LaQuinta everything was full,
but it wasn't over full crazy.
And you know, but people all I
ever do
Unknown: all. Ah ha. Ah,
Adam Curry: I just don't get it.
Why are people so fascinated by
it? By the Eclipse? What is it
that
John C Dvorak: the knives I've
seen a couple of them? I've seen
a lot of debate boys, and moon
and sun. And I did fun. It's
interesting. It was always
interesting. When you have a
full Eclipse, it actually
literally gets about 10 degrees
colder. Right on the spot. Yeah,
that didn't happen yesterday,
either. No, it didn't happen
here either. But normally, you
get this and as you can feel
it's like Oh, and by the way,
when that happens when everyone
out there gets to experience
this, like 10 degree drop in
temperature when the sun gets
fullest Eclipse for just a few
seconds. Thank yourself. Ah, the
sun has nothing to do with
global warming.
Adam Curry: Sure. Okay, well
speaking of that. So this new
friend, we're gonna call him
Paul, the tycoon oil tycoon.
John C Dvorak: So we had this
new friend of yours, it has to
be named in code.
Adam Curry: B, I haven't
discussed with him yet. And I
don't want to ruin my new
friendship just yet. So he had a
very successful Oil Company,
which he took public, and then
they sold it. And then he had a
year that he couldn't do
anything. They started a new
one. So it was no new oil
companies worth one and a half
billion dollars. You wouldn't
know looking at the guy. So this
is like, Oh, how interesting.
John C Dvorak: Texas
billionaires. They're all like
that. Yeah, exactly.
Adam Curry: And it's real. Like
he's a guy that has, you know,
like drills on the ground and
oil comes out. Yes. He's not a
wildcatter.
John C Dvorak: So wildcatters
Adam Curry: And he says, and so
we're, you know, we're yapping
away and ESG comes up, he says,
ah, oh, gotta tell you about ESG
All right, says Guess who the
and this company is not yet
public. Guess what the number
one investor is in my in my my
company my oil spurting out of
the ground company. You get one
guest jump
John C Dvorak: I wouldn't have a
clue of what who to guess. I
mean, yeah. Microsoft I mean, I
don't know
Adam Curry: No, no. Did you talk
by in the troll room got it
right right off the bat,
BlackRock, BlackRock,
John C Dvorak: 50, blank row.
They're interested in everything
and it will count down, but
Adam Curry: they're the guys who
started the ESG program. This is
This is Larry Fink's baby. And
it's like all we owe, you know,
if you're, if you don't have a
high ESG score, then you're on
investable. And so he explained
the mechanics, he said, he
backed off on it, by the way
recently, yeah, a little bit,
but the ESG score hasn't gone
away. And if you have a low and
environmental, social government
governance, if you don't have
oh,
John C Dvorak: yeah, he's an oil
company. You should be low
score, you should
Adam Curry: be zero negative
score. So 50 million already in
another 50 million coming from
BlackRock. And my new friend
Paul, the oil tycoon says, the
ESG is phenomenal. It's great.
Because whenever they tell us
all bow climate change,
whatever, you got to close it,
well, boom, price goes up, we
make out like bandits. He says
it's a whole the whole thing.
It's a scam. He says when we had
the public company, it was
phenomenal. Oh, boy, we have to
close it well, oh, it's a
problem. Boom, stock price
rockets. To this whole thing is
a scapegoat. When
John C Dvorak: I look at the
evidence of this, take a look at
the chart for Exxon. And first
look at where Joe Biden was
elected and look at the stock
price then and look at it. He
also said
Adam Curry: specifically, he
says look, I don't like it for
our country in the world. But
Democrats are good for business
use. Whenever a Democrat in the
White House is good for us.
John C Dvorak: Tell it tell it
to the 90s that's when Clinton
was in Iraq and
Adam Curry: yeah, why don't you
soak in that for a bit? I love
saying that marinate in that
once you put that in your pipe
and smoke it I don't know about
you but there's nothing but
disinformation everywhere. The
whole world is full of
disinformation so all
disinformation everywhere.
disinformation. Now we have
reports about disinformation.
Just disinformation. It's crazy.
It's happening everywhere.
Hallie Jackson has to
John C Dvorak: report this
information. Miss Sally jelly
Adam Curry: who has all kinds of
weird sound effects on her show.
New into
Unknown: NBC tonight research.
And by the way at work
John C Dvorak: she mugs she has
a weird mugging face she's
mugging cow it constantly. She's
getting she's I don't know. I
find her annoying. Uh, well,
Adam Curry: hello is joined the
Halle annoying club. Yeah. And
this one her eyes roll. She's
all bug eyed. Because Whoa,
misinformation is a huge
problem.
Unknown: This new into NBC
tonight a research group
uncovering a network of dozens
of accounts, formerly known as
spread.
Adam Curry: Did you know that x
is formerly known as Twitter?
This, you know be outlawed this?
Why do they keep saying this?
When is it just going to be x?
John C Dvorak: But you can do
what I do. I don't use x I say
twitter.com. No,
Adam Curry: I'm just I'm just
saying x still twitter.com
Unknown: and dozens of accounts
on apps formerly known as
Twitter. spreading, spreading,
Adam Curry: spreading dating.
Oh, this is cool. What how did
she do that? How do you come up
with spreading?
John C Dvorak: Spreading dating?
Adam Curry: She said spread
dating. What is that all of us
spread what disseminating and
spreading? That's okay.
Spreading dating. I think it
should be it should be entered
into the dictionary. I like it.
It's
Unknown: of accounts on apps
formerly known as Twitter spread
knitting was spreading rather
which believed to be coordinated
posts with distinct,
Adam Curry: coordinated. Oh,
it's believed to be coordinated
posts and videos
Unknown: that have been viewed
millions of times. X started
suspending some of the accounts
after they were contacted by NBC
News but didn't otherwise have
any comment. It's something
we've seen a lot of over the
past few days. Oh, yeah.
Militants started a new
airstrike on Israel. You see
that? That's that video that is
actually from a video game. No,
no, that's not even really to
the exact same video posted to
YouTube hear you
Adam Curry: there's an obvious
conclusion to what they're doing
here. You and you know what's
coming.
Unknown: And there was this post
claiming Israel bombed and
destroyed an old Greek Orthodox
Church in Gaza. It has something
like 3 million views.
Adam Curry: It has something
like 3 million. What kind of
news report is that? And how
many views that it have not
something like that's something
like
John C Dvorak: $3 million. The
number is right there. You can
read it.
Adam Curry: Now she sounded like
a high school girl. It's
something that had something
like 3000 3 Million Likes now.
Unknown: And there was this post
claiming Israel bombed and
destroyed an old Greek Orthodox
Church in Gaza. It has something
like 3 million views, but the
church itself said it hasn't
been touched that any other news
is false. Now have disclaimers
on the bottom if you go to F and
look at the posts, but they're
not taken down and some of them
are posted from verified users,
making it harder for people to
know what's real. NBC News tech
correspondent Jake Ward Joining
us now and Jake these are just a
couple of examples of this these
posts containing misinformation
disinformation very difficult
especially in a moment like this
when people are frankly
desperate for information
turning to social media
platforms just there's not a
clear cut picture that
desperately is
not a clear cut picture Holly
the past few days, this vivid
lesson in the fact that you
literally cannot trust what
social media is. Even more
difficult is the surprise turn
of events which means that
legitimate sources of
information are slow to react
because they were taking just as
surprised as so many people were
across Israel. So a very, very
difficult moment but as you look
for raishin of of misleading
content, and when it's not just
made up as in the case of the
video game clip you're showing
there a middle it's out of
context or out of time Oh, it
trust us legitimate sources.
It's even hard for us people
trust legitimate sources.
John C Dvorak: And when you're
going on this route, because I
have a series of misleading
clips from provided by PBS I
love that which is beyond like
misinformation. It's a it's a
it's a lie.
Adam Curry: Well, let me set it
up. Let
John C Dvorak: me set it up with
keep no I want to hear more of
this.
Adam Curry: Yeah, another
misinformation clip. This is
from CBS a term fake
Unknown: news is a controversial
one controversial. It's often
used to falsely claim that the
facts someone doesn't like or
just made up. But actual fake
news takes on a new tone when
it's used as a weapon of war
when misinformation has already
cropped up in abundance in the
current conflict in the Middle
East. Jolene Kent has the story
Adam Curry: you see a similarity
here the M five and what they're
saying.
Unknown: Oh, as the wound was
real in Gaza
good start
John C Dvorak: there trying to
use misinformation and a random
explosion Yeah, how
Adam Curry: should we start this
report about misinformation? I
don't know blow something up.
Good one
Unknown: as the war in Israel in
Gaza plays out in real time on
social media. Experts say bad
information and propaganda are
spreading on X formally, Twitter
Oh,
Adam Curry: it's x again.
Formerly known as Twitter I
there's a pattern here it's
group
Unknown: aleafia detected a
network of at least 67 accounts
that posted false content about
the war faulty Russians millions
of views by now. excluding these
mistranslated videos of Russian
President Vladimir Putin and
Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov,
you manipulated to falsely say
that Russia will support
Palestine if the US supports
Israel. Why are 67 accounts so
powerful in their influence? And
why do they not
Adam Curry: know they are? No
they are they're very powerful.
This is Elon his home business
model is now being attacked.
This is this is the point of
this
Unknown: and why do they matter?
It matters whether or not people
believe that and the more times
that people are able to view
content of a similarly, the more
opportunities an actor has to
convince somebody of something
that may or may not be for
Adam Curry: an actor George
Clooney was doing this. What
actor actor Brad Pitt This
Unknown: comes after Elon Musk,
the owner of X laid off much of
the team responsible for
monitoring. The European Union
sent this letter to the
billionaire asking Musk to
immediately remove illegal
content and disinformation.
Adam Curry: My name is God but
at all I have a habit bug it in
my book.
Unknown: Otherwise, penalties
can be imposed. How does this
disinformation impact the war?
And what we know about it
when we flood people with this
sea of unvetted information,
much of it deceptive, is we're
throwing away the goodwill of
our citizens. And we're opening
the door to a variety of people
that want to manipulate their
goodwill.
Do you anticipate seeing more of
this kind of activity as the war
continues? Oh, yes,
Adam Curry: of course. Yes.
Unknown: We do anticipate that
in the coming days that this
information sphere is going to
get updated and that more actors
will be weaponizing information.
Adam Curry: More and more
actors.
Unknown: What our history as
Adam Curry: she did it again,
did she just do again x formerly
known Twitter
Unknown: X. Formerly Twitter has
said as of Monday, they've
already removed several 100
accounts, including those that
are Hamas affiliated. Meantime,
we've been pressing the other
social media companies about
this. And Snapchat, Tik Tok and
Facebook all say they've
increased their resources to
fight disinformation.
John C Dvorak: Oh, please.
Adam Curry: So before, before we
get to your clips, I'm very
interested in those two things.
One, this is confirmed all right
now I don't have I don't have to
have the TIC tock app. People
send me tic TOCs all the time
and I open them in the browser.
And so what I do then every
single time after that tick tock
is done that one video, the
same. Horrific, violent clip
pops up from some Israeli kid
being killed at the at the at
the at the rave and my my buddy
Dave
John C Dvorak: he says it must
be your cookies
Adam Curry: no he didn't get it
well okay but I'm two people in
two different states are seeing
the same thing so I there's
those misinformation different
from from different from
Michigan now before we get
before we get into it before we
go any further with this talking
about this conflict what's
happening in the Middle East
John C Dvorak: Adams gonna read
his email by area fine there's
the old clip
Adam Curry: it's called a
cigales from the gym
Unknown: who's gonna read his
email
Adam Curry: on the no agenda.
That's not tedious. I want to
remind everybody that when we
deconstruct these things, same
with COVID lockdowns you,
Ukraine. It is it is masks, it
is bad for business. It is not a
great business model that we
have. It's not like people go
oh, yeah, this is great. No,
people walk away from the show.
They go,
John C Dvorak: Oh, I've been I
bought in hook line and sinker
and they're telling me I'm
wrong. You guys suck.
Adam Curry: I has been listening
to your show no agenda for two
to four years. That's Wait, wait
John C Dvorak: two to four
years.
Adam Curry: That's an interest.
Very interesting range. Never
heard to two to four years and
I've always enjoyed it. However,
your coverage of the atrocities
by the monstrous Hamas,
including the beheading of
innocent babies, babies torn
from their mother's bellies is
so appalling. So I, I don't
recall babies torn from their
mother's bellies to new one.
There is indeed ample footage
pictures to prove what happened.
And your glib laughter was one
your glib laughter with John,
well, there are no words, you're
excused that you're just
evaluating the media coverage is
cheap, and not even believable.
To say I'm disappointed and
disgusted would be an
understatement.
John C Dvorak: I want to remind
people out there who have these
kinds of complaints, send them
to Adam because he'll read him
on the air.
Adam Curry: You know, it's it's
taken on a whole new level, you
know, the mid curry.com. You
know, the, you know, that dude
who was so mad about when we
started talking about trans
Maoism.
John C Dvorak: Tim Poole now?
No,
Adam Curry: I iron iron hide.
1970 Mike Ironhide 1972 He was
it was he was putting pictures
up on Norwegian art generator
that we suck. It was your post?
Oh,
John C Dvorak: yeah, we I think
we bounced him that way.
Adam Curry: I died. I mean,
Paul, pocket two are bouncing
from that. But they showed up in
the troll room last show. So now
I get an email from one of our
producers who happens to also
own the venue where he's
organizing the a meet up. It's a
burger joint. And the email he
received which I'm sure many
John C Dvorak: the hater, you're
talking about organizing a
meeting? No, no, no, no.
Adam Curry: One of our producers
who's organizing a meetup who
organizes one regularly who has
a venue he owns the venue in
this case, as the venue owner,
he received an email from the
hater. Okay, letting you know
that a group from the no agenda
podcast will be at your
establishment on October 14 at
5pm this group follows a very
homophobic and transphobic
podcast. I would use all caution
when serving these people.
John C Dvorak: Wow.
Adam Curry: That was a good wow.
That was a very good wow,
John C Dvorak: that's a very
good while because that's a wow
moment. Yeah, so this prick
that's calm where he is.
Besides, he doesn't like to show
for whatever reason. Oh, noes
are after the venue for the
meetup. But coincidentally, the
venue is owned by the guy
organizing the meetup. So he
sends the mail right on to us,
which you just read. That is
unbelievable. That guy is a true
a whole I wish these people
wouldn't even listen to the
show. They get better things to
do. There's other shows that can
go to well, this I harass us,
because they're white trying to
ruin a good meet up. I mean,
come on. That's sick. I actually
Adam Curry: tried to talk him
off the ledge when this first
started and I was emailing him
personally and then he decided
that the prick Yeah, then he
then he published all my emails.
I'm like, Dude, I pray for him.
I go, I forgive him. I forgive
him. He has issues I forgive
him. I hope it works out for
him. All right now won't now on
to your your disinfo clips from
NPR which I'm very excited for
PBS it was our I'm sorry I mean
NPR PBS I mean
John C Dvorak: yeah what diverse
is a second let's
Adam Curry: do it let's do it
right
Unknown: elitist voices of
America this is NPR or PBS
Adam Curry: doesn't matter
John C Dvorak: so a couple of
these I got some intro ones that
we can go into which is the
Brooks and K part.
Adam Curry: Oh Mike you know,
I'm gonna have to start banning
these these these clips because
I'll blame me Oh, but nobody
watches this anymore. They have
zero traction. They don't they
still think it's Brooks and Dunn
Unknown: never was Brooks.
Adam Curry: That's a country
duo. What's what's Brooks
John C Dvorak: Garth Brooks?
What's the other guy? A key part
before before
Adam Curry: before K part who
was at the shields? Oh, Brooks
and shields see we don't even
remember the old guys
John C Dvorak: I remember.
Adam Curry: Oh, okay. Okay some
point all right, let's go but
what are we
John C Dvorak: examples I'm
gonna lead into the into the to
the egregious re edited clip.
I'm sorry. They used to become a
gassed and pissed off. And it's
ridiculous. But let's firstly
get us in the mood by listening
to these two boneheads in the
mood in the mood. This is start
I'm gonna start with Brooks
Putin Hamas.
Unknown: For I thought this was
one of Joe Biden's best weeks as
president. You know, he was a
was a moral clarity.
Adam Curry: That's great. Right
there. He's better. He said,
Hey, I've seen proof of the
babies decapitated. It's true.
It's right. It's certified
verify? Oh, I'm sorry. No, the
President was confused.
Unknown: He was one of the early
voices to remind everybody that
what Hamas has become looks like
ISIS sort of a death cult. He
did in the face of divisions on
the left. There are a lot of
mainstream liberals who are
appalled by what happened there
more progressive voices, many
who think this is a legitimate
part of decolonization. And
yeah, Joe Biden has knows
Israeli history. He knows the
Palestinians. He's been doing
this for a long time. And he
knows that this is a case of
someone who wants to have a
group that wants to destroy
Israel and push the Jews into
the sea. And so he said that it
is also making the case which I
think Solinsky is a little ahead
of him on Ukraine and Israel,
the Morgans Tomas and against
Putin are joined their wars
against barbarism.
Adam Curry: What? Yeah. What did
he say
John C Dvorak: that Putin in
Hamas are the same? Ukraine and
Israel is the same. Wow. Wow.
Okay. Yeah.
Adam Curry: It's the same. It's
the same except the reverse, but
John C Dvorak: we can't actually
say it's the same. It's the same
Hello. So
Adam Curry: you have a big
country like Russia is just like
Hamas? The big country and the
big country, the big the big
elephant in the fight? Okay. All
right. Okay, good.
John C Dvorak: Let's go Brooks
to K part two.
Unknown: And I think he sees
that clearly. And so I just
think it was it was just a
marvelous display, moral
clarity, and real storytelling.
For a guy who stories grand
narrative storytelling, and
rhetoric is not always the great
gift, but I just thought
magnificent
moral clarity and grand
storytelling. What's your
assessment of the
administration's response?
I agree with with David 100%.
President, it's the Secretary of
State who spoke from the heart
next to Prime Minister Netanyahu
and Secretary of Defense Lloyd
Austin being there earlier in
the day today also showing
solidarity but i What happened a
week ago, tonight or tomorrow is
really it's beyond disturbing.
And I I just feel compelled. You
know, as an African American, I
understand the ancestral pain
and terror felt by my Jewish
friends and Jews around the
world by what happened this was
not what Hamas did was not the
usual Middle East back and
forth. This was barbaric.
Adam Curry: This is literally
what you get called out for. If
you say I have a black friend.
You know, that's, that's a raw
take. No, but you can see I have
a Jewish friend but oh, that's
Dr. Jewish friend. Okay.
John C Dvorak: Another Jewish
friend.
Adam Curry: I got Jewish friend.
Oh, man. That's not so
John C Dvorak: they're pushing
this barbaric thing. So, of
course, so they are building up
to this and now I'm going to
take us into the to the
egregious editing of a Trump
clip to make him say stuff he
didn't say and I have the
original clips. I dug them up.
Okay, the way we do Yes, and I
want to compare one to the other
but let's start but it's also
the reaction first they edit it
clip, and then they react to it
even though the clips of fake If
they react to it and they go
out, they go off the rails with
how bad Trump is as a person.
This is the the intro to this
clip and this is Brooks Trump
edit intro as we
Unknown: talk about the Biden
administration's response and
response his predecessor Donald
Trump drew why criticism and
condemnation this past week for
faulting Netanyahu for calling
Hezbollah very smart in his
remarks.
Adam Curry: Oh, it's another
it's a new very fine people is
the very smart people. Now this
is good. This is good. Okay,
where do we go now?
John C Dvorak: Okay, so first of
all, he makes a mention he that
that's the host guy, the black
guy, postgame he mentions the
Netanyahu and then he mentioned
that, that Trump says Hezbollah
is very smart. And now we go to
they take the clip of a butcher
a clip, and they don't even have
it from the same feed. So it's a
mess. And I tried to even clean
it up with Adobe. But to hell
with it. Let's leave the mess
with the way it is because Adobe
actually doesn't work on Trump.
No interest. Very, I've noticed
this before. Adobe does not work
on Trump. They hate Trump. He
must. So they probably do.
Silicon Valley. So let's go to
this is the Brooks Trump and
this got the edited clip this is
to Okay,
Unknown: I'll never forget that
Bibi Netanyahu let us down. That
was a very terrible thing. I
will say that it is a GI Oh, PES
Villa desert attacks on the
north, because that's the most
vulnerable status.
And we can contrast that to what
Ron DeSantis and Nikki Haley had
to say,
Israel has a right to defend
itself. And that means do that
to the hilt. You have to uproot
the terrorist infrastructure,
these networks, and Hamas needs
to be no more this is sick, and
we
have to treat sick people the
way they deserve to be treated
and eliminate them.
Your response to what Donald
Trump had to say.
The clip you showed is exhibit
number, whatever it is, of why
he should never ever again be
entrusted with the power and
responsibility that comes with
sitting in the Oval Office. I am
happy to be wrong about the
reaction from the Republican
presidential field. I thought
they would follow form and not
criticize Trump at all for fear
of engendering rage of their
base. But Governor Haley,
Governor DeSantis, Governor
Christie, former Vice President
Mike Pence, most of them
criticize Trump, and I applaud
them for that. But there's no
way that guy should be President
of the United States, again, by
back clip alone.
Adam Curry: So you know, when we
deconstruct clips, and we're
looking at the media and we get
another kind of feedback I read
earlier, these a holes are just
politicizing it for their own
for their own ego, whatever it
is, oh, whatever it is, let's
keep Trump out. That's That's
disgusting.
John C Dvorak: waiting to hear
their original Trump clips. I
can't wait. We can also play I
think Brookes reaction to this
same edited little clip where he
says Netanyahu, first Trump
brings in Netanyahu then he says
Hezbollah smart. And this says
they're gonna attack from the
north or something. It's a very
confused, it's a really screwed
up edit. And then they bring in,
as you heard DeSantis talking
about a Hamas, which is not what
Trump was talking about. And
then Nikki Haley saying it's
these people are sick, kind of
indicating that Trump
Adam Curry: is sick, which is
not what that was about at
John C Dvorak: all. That was not
what that was about. So this is
a real real hack job hack job.
Exactly. And here's the follow
up by Brooks.
Unknown: It's also a reminder of
how Donald Trump's isolationist
views have really realigned the
Republicans approach to foreign
policy.
It's stunning. I mean, it well,
first that Donald Trump clip,
everything is about Donald
Trump, like 1000 People get
murdered, and it's all about
Donald Trump. And the party has
you know, it was the party of,
of anti communism. It was the
party of American led world
order. It was the party of
containment against Russia
against the Soviet Union. And
now it's very much the opposite.
And as I look at the Republican
Party, I just want to make sure
they're gonna fund Ukraine
John C Dvorak: so now, these are
two guys that are supposed to be
arguing with each other to give
people perspective when they
watch the PBS NewsHour, right.
And but no, there are two guys
that are in total agreement.
Neither one of them are
representative of anything other
than one lone pro Ukraine view,
but just go back to that clip
that they butchered and listen
to Trump's actually this is a
long clip, but you need to hear
the whole thing in context. The
six This is actually a good
sorry, this isn't good. This is
good quality. This is the Trump
unedited comments regarding
Hezbollah being smart
Unknown: for $6 billion was a
tremendous amount of money, but
nothing compared to the hundreds
of billions of dollars that
Biden allowed them to make and
oil and other things, hundreds
of billions that became a rich
nation in three years. That's
why they're doing this f so much
money. They don't know what to
do with it. They had no money,
they were broke. And then there
was the inevitable attack four
days later, which I predicted.
And then two nights ago, I read
all of Biden security people,
can you imagine National Defense
people? And they said, Gee, I
hope Hezbollah doesn't attack
from the north. Because that's
the most vulnerable spot. I
said, Wait a minute. You know,
Hezbollah is very smart. They're
all very smart depressant, like
when they say, you know, I said
that President Xi of China, 1.4
billion people, he controls it
with an iron fist. He said he's
a very smart man. They killed me
the next day. I said he was
smart whenever I get a say. But
his was diverse. And they have a
national defense minister or
somebody saying I hope Hezbollah
doesn't attack us from the
north. So the following morning,
they attacked, they might not
have been doing it. But if you
listen to this jerk, you would
attack from the north because he
said that's our weak spot.
Whoever heard of official saying
on television that they hope the
enemy doesn't attack in a
certain area. Now unless it's a
con job. But you know what a con
job is you're waiting. They're
ready. You want them if you want
to, but they weren't ready. They
weren't ready. You know, say
what you want. Israel was not
ready. This was a big surprise.
This was a terrible thing that
happened. They weren't ready.
But if you wanted them to attack
because you've got a million
people there with guns and
you're gonna blast to hell, then
you do exactly, but they didn't
have that. They didn't have that
Biden's National Security
Adviser Jake Sullivan, even
bragged just days before the
attack that the Middle East
seems to be quite quiet. That
was good. They really, they
really, honestly what they've
done. It's a shame.
John C Dvorak: Yeah. Okay, now,
what couple of things about
that, oh, this is all in
context. It's fine. What he
said, Whoa, he's not
complimenting Hezbollah, like
they also like to imagine, but
what did you notice? There was
no mention of Netanyahu in that
entire
Adam Curry: letter. They edited
that together. So that and it
was in the intro piece. It was
two different pieces of audio.
That's the first thing I
noticed. Yeah,
John C Dvorak: it was they did a
botch job. I mean, they could
have had good quality because it
was all from the same speech. In
fact, I have the Netanyahu
piece, and the Netanyahu piece,
which they just pulled out of
context and dropped it in as a
cheat as a as a sleazy lowest
form of journalism thing you
could possibly do, which they
did on PBS. I have the Netanyahu
piece, which actually stand
alone is very interesting and
could have been used as a
jumping off point for a big
discussion. And I'm surprised
that they didn't do that because
it's more interesting than what
they did, which was just Trump
batch. But listen to this. This
is Trump on on Netanyahu. It's a
backgrounder. That's kind of
interesting.
Unknown: The savage attacks on
Israel happened for three
reasons Biden loosen might
Adam Curry: not the grudge clip.
This is the regular live show. I
John C Dvorak: used to grudge
clip.
Unknown: I did have a bad
experience with Israel, though.
When we took out Soleimani. It
was us at Israel working as a
group. And we knew where he was.
We knew how he was coming in. We
knew the plane. We knew
everything. We worked on it for
weeks for months, actually. But
we worked on it for weeks. The
night before? Nope, I didn't I
don't think this has ever been
told. They'll say oh, it's
classified information. Well,
maybe it is. But I don't think
so. Israel was going to do this
with us. And it was being
planned and working on it for
months. And now we had
everything all set to go. And
the night before it happened. I
got a call that Israel will not
be participating in this attack.
Let's do it. And he came on the
plane and we follow them right
from the Situation Room. We
followed the whole thing and
about 15 seconds later it was
all over. And we did it but I'll
never forget. I'll never forget
that Bibi Netanyahu let us down
that was a very terrible thing.
I will say that we were
disappointed by that very
disappointed but we did the job
ourselves and it was absolute
precision. magnificent,
beautiful. And then maybe tried
to take credit for it. That
didn't make me feel too good but
that's all right. So they gotta
strengthen themselves up.
Adam Curry: Wow, that's that is
a little piece of info we didn't
know about.
John C Dvorak: We had no idea
but he noticed a little part in
that clip versus BB let us down
is the little piece they took
out They chopped it from that
and put it on the front end of
the other.
Adam Curry: Let's play that
intro again,
Unknown: as we talk about the
Biden administration's response
response, his predecessor Donald
Trump drew wide criticism and
condemnation this past week for
actually the beginning because
it's too hard to
Adam Curry: I'm sorry. Yeah,
Unknown: I'll never forget that
Bibi Netanyahu let us down. That
was a very terrible thing. I
will say that and they said gee,
I hope Hezbollah doesn't attack
from the north.
Adam Curry: Wow, that I mean,
you should you should be fired
from journalism for doing that.
John C Dvorak: They should all
be fired from PBS should PBS
should take a knee for for this
is the one of the most egregious
examples of editing. And false
it's this is misinformation,
misinformation.
Adam Curry: Yes. Blatant,
blatant on your national
treasure PBS or NPR. So I'm one
of those two, same thing.
John C Dvorak: So those are the
original clips and you can see
that they they totally, this is
a lie. And Brooks and K part
should be ashamed of themselves
for going along with it. And
then making a big fuss about
what a jerk Trump is.
Adam Curry: Unbelievable. It's
not unbelievable. It's
believable. It's totally booked.
No, it's
John C Dvorak: not unbelievable,
because it's happened
believable. Yeah. So that's
good. Good presentation.
Adam Curry: I like it. I like
it. Well, of course, we were
told
John C Dvorak: and I want to say
it again. Do not send your money
to these people send it to us.
Yes,
Adam Curry: we don't have tote
bags, but we can use the money,
that's for sure. So of course
everybody was all riled up about
the Day of Rage this
Unknown: morning law enforcement
officers across the country on
heightened alert after Hamas has
called for a Global Day of Rage.
The Los Angeles County Sheriff's
Office is pulling personnel from
specialized units to increase
visibility. In New York
congregates from dozens of
synagogues prayed for peace as
helicopters watch for suspicious
vehicles from above
and boats with radiation
detectors patrolled the waters.
The NYPD telling its officers to
prepare for 12 hour shifts.
We have directed the NYPD to
surge additional resources to
schools houses of worship to
assure that they are safe.
John C Dvorak: So as far as I
know, they got some day I got a
Day of Rage clip. Okay. What's
his? Well,
Adam Curry: there's always
something going on in the world.
Yeah, there's something
John C Dvorak: that's why I
think this is a good example.
This is the various 13th which
is the de river Okay, right.
stabbings.
Unknown: A Jewish teacher in
France is reportedly dead after
a knife attack to others have
been injured and asylum seeker
reportedly went on a stabbing
spree attacking various people
screaming
Adam Curry: alone notice notice
we've gone to asylum seekers now
which is the it's the word they
use in Europe. We're going to
use it everywhere. It does be
using this for years asylum
seeker. Asylum Seeker
Unknown: reportedly went on a
stabbing spree attacking various
people screaming Allahu Akbar,
France's President Emmanuel
Macron visited the school on
Friday afternoon. Also a staffer
at the Israeli embassy in China
was stabbed on the sidewalk in
Beijing for the chose the
diplomat being stabbed multiple
times by a man and white
Adam Curry: so that was your Day
of Rage not very successful, but
they got us all riled up I think
kind of everybody
John C Dvorak: get me riled up.
Somebody riled up didn't get
riled Oh, would you must have a
clip
Adam Curry: no agenda, people
don't know no agenda. People
don't get riled up. We just
don't get riled up. We don't
because we know we know what
they're doing to us. Now, I want
to talk about the military
industrial complex. A lot of
people benefit from this, this
crisis in the Middle East. I
just got an A message, I should
say, from Sir Brian of London,
boots on the ground. Who, you
know, there's this funerals this
guy's attending. He is right in
the middle of it, though, and
I've been back and forth with
him for days and he's having a
rough go of what's happening.
And, and he sent a video and he
has on his and I take his
credibility quite high. He's
He's a night that Israel is now
using the laser iron beam. Not
Iron Dome, but the iron beam.
And it's cool that they have a
laser now shooting things out of
the sky. Yep, yep.
John C Dvorak: Okay, there's a
couple of things before you go
into these clips. Did you see
the Richard angle clip that's
going around showing how the
Iron Dome supposedly works? You
see these missiles flying into
the air and then they're taking
a right turn and going in the
opposite direction. Have you
seen those clips? Well, I've
Adam Curry: seen it I don't know
if it's the one you're talking
about. I've seen
John C Dvorak: similar probably.
I just don't understand what's
going on with these clips
because there was always the
iron Iron Dome at work. Missile
going up and then turning around
Ronnie going the other way I
thought the Iron Dome was was
Patriot missiles that were
shooting these things out of the
sky.
Adam Curry: That's what I
thought, well not but now they
have, you can see laser beams.
In fact, Jewish laser beams. I
mean, it's a little crazy. But
I'm sure they're ours. But these
have directed energy weapons now
they're using which is it's
quite like whoa, okay, I didn't
expect to see that. Anyway, we
need to go to the military
industrial complex, which the
both of these people are part of
it in some way. Catherine
herridge, of course, the pixie
girl who was read in on all
things, military and
intelligence and John Bolton who
is just a huge moustache aihole.
And just a quick couple of clips
here because you know, you don't
hear from this guy for years,
and he's off the stage. But he's
back
Unknown: earlier today I spoke
with former national security
adviser to President Trump
Ambassador John Bolton about the
situation in the Middle East. As
we head into the weekend as a
former national security
adviser, what indicators are you
going to be watching?
Well, I think the big unknown
question at this point is what
happens with Hezbollah in the
north? I think the evidence is
clear beyond real dispute here
that the signal caller in this
operation is Iran. They armed
and prepared Hamas. I think they
unleashed him at a time they
thought it would be beneficial
to Iran in the Iran issue is Rod
part of the strategy that
they're following is to get the
Israelis sucked into Gaza in a
very heavy way, militarily, and
then to unleash Hezbollah from
the North. I think there are
some signs along the northern
border. Nothing conclusive, but
I think that's the main point of
danger at this point. Yes. Okay.
Adam Curry: Um, thanks. I mean,
my my sister in Italy could have
gone on on your show and said
that. Let's go a little deeper
into that.
John C Dvorak: Bring her on next
time. She's,
Adam Curry: yeah, get on
Catherine herridge. Let's get
this. Let's get John Bolton,
you're so interesting.
Unknown: Let's take that a step
further. Given the scope and the
sophistication of the Hamas
attack. Do you believe that
another shoe is going to drop
Adam Curry: Oh, another shoe is
gonna drop?
Unknown: I think it's very
likely. And I think Hezbollah is
the most likely implementer of
that. But there may be terrorist
attacks around the region.
Friday has been declared a day
of jihad in the region and
around the world. And so this
this really could be the
beginning of a much longer
process here. What that will
entail, but I think anybody who
thinks hold on to the over in a
few days, unfortunately,
mistaken nothing happened.
Bolton
Adam Curry: Yeah, nothing. He's
such a prognosticator
John C Dvorak: genius. Oh, as a
jihad day. Yeah.
Adam Curry: Take a long time.
We're gonna need some money and
start printing some money. We
need money. We mean money.
Unknown: What does it mean here
at home, law enforcement
officials have been telling CBS
News and other media outlets
that they're seeing no signs of
a specific or credible threat.
Adam Curry: This is so much fun
to play that after the global
day at rage.
Unknown: I think at the moment
the main threat area is in the
Middle East. I think it's
Israel. It's the target, but I
think it's almost certain that
having wow wow,
John C Dvorak: wow, what a
genius.
Unknown: Look at my moustache. I
think it's almost certain that
having missed this attack to
begin with, not just Israeli
intelligence. But but our own
intelligence community, whatever
evidence there was, they didn't
draw the right conclusions. You
know, the next question you
should ask is What else have we
missed? What
Adam Curry: else have we missed?
Oh, we need more spy gear was
not good. You know, I just as a
as a little side note here. This
is fantastic story which checks
out and I'm not gonna say it's
related to it per se. But you've
heard of Pegasus. The spyware
Pegasus, the company Pegasus? I
think so. So Pegasus was, you
know, that's the Israeli spyware
that's on everybody's phone and
they've sold it all around the
world. Our our US agencies were
using a Pegasus is great. You
can be track everybody. You got
to phone Pegasus is on it. So
when, when Trump came in, and
the Obama Biden administration
left the Blinken and who is the
assistant deputy director of CIA
Avril Haines, I think is her
name Haidee something could be
they all started a lobbying firm
called West executive. And they
started lobbying for a competing
firm. And that firm was also
with a P. O a second
John C Dvorak: that Palantir
Adam Curry: No, no, no, no, no,
no, this is all follow up
topology Palantir now they
started lobbying of course it's
great when when you lobby you
know, as a former
administration, prepare Gone
Paragon was was call and they
started loving all Paragon we
gotta get you got to have
Paragon and and you know this is
no good this this Pegasus
software. And coincidentally, if
you recall the big stink about
Khashoggi was that it was
Pegasus software that the
Israeli Pegasus company had sold
to Saudi Arabia that got him
killed. You remember that?
Remember that?
John C Dvorak: Vaguely remembers
it?
Adam Curry: Yeah. So that was
probably planted by these guys
because they get back in with
Biden. And in March of this
year, Biden writes up this huge
executive order on prohibition
on use by the United States
government of certain commercial
spyware that poses risks to
national security. And when you
know, that was written precisely
to outlaw Pegasus, and have this
other software be the software
and they haven't sold it to
Saudi Arabia. So it's just a
little side note. But when you
have the Israeli government
highly relying on one software,
for spying on anybody with a
phone, and that's Pegasus, and
all of a sudden, it's no good
and everyone has to have Paragon
and that company starts to bleed
employees bloat bleed clients,
that may have contributed in
some way to some lapses in
security. I have no proof for
that. But I just thought that
was interesting that Sullivan
and all these eight holes,
including Ehud Barak, they were
all involved in in this lobbying
firm, and then they get in and
boom, there you go. They get rid
of that company. And this new
company is supposed to be it and
I don't even know if the
Israelis are using it. Now, just
a little side note. So when
Bolton says, oh, yeah, baby
lapse and security, maybe our
lap, maybe it was a shitty
software you brought in
Unknown: why are the
John C Dvorak: US or no lapse in
security? That also possible?
Unknown: What are the US
government's best options to
secure the release of the
hostages bomb Iran?
Well, I think at this point,
unfortunately, given how caught
by surprise we were, that it's
going to take rescue efforts
under extraordinary
extraordinarily difficult
circumstances. I mean, I think
the administration is correct to
seek a diplomatic approach
they're in gutter today. I just
don't think Hamas is in a mood
to bargain I think they've got
a gutter he said gutter he
didn't say cutter
which they're in gutter today.
Yeah, gutter is in a mood to
bargain. I think they've got
very valuable bargaining chips
that they're going to get a much
higher price for at least that's
what they think. I think the
hostages are in grave danger and
I think therefore any further
time that goes by before rescue
efforts begin puts their lives
in even greater danger than it
is already All
Adam Curry: right. So Bolton is
that just asking anybody to come
on who's connected to anything
Think Tank anything money
anything hateful, these are all
just horrible people who would
just talk him out of there but
but the best by far the best
person the best representative
of the military industrial
complex on mainstream M five M.
Television is definitely Lindsey
Graham. Lindsey Graham is
rocking it. And he is making
very sure we understand that
Iran is in our sights, boss
Unknown: in the last hour
announcing it's going to begin
to execute hostages and post
video evidence online for every
Israeli airstrike. your sights
on this moment, Senator?
Well, for every Israeli or
American hostage executed by
Hamas, we should take down and
Iranian oil refinery. All the
way you got to keep this for
from escalating is to hold Iran
accountable.
Adam Curry: The only way you
keep the war from escalating is
by bombing another country? Yes.
How
Unknown: much more death and
destruction do we have to take
Adam Curry: by creating more
Lindsey
Unknown: from the Iranian
regime? I am confident this was
planned and funded by the
Iranians. Hamas is a bunch of
animals who deserve to be
treated like animals. So if I
was Israel, I would go in on the
ground. There is no truce to be
had here. I would dismantle
Hamas. This is the best
opportunity Israel has to
destroy Hamas. Take it to the
Iranians. If you harm one
American in Syria by using your
Iranian militia against us in
Syria, to escalate an area
urging Hezbollah to attack
Israel in the north, if Hamas
kills one American Israeli
hostage, we're going to blow up
your oil refineries and put you
out of business. It is now time
to take the war to the
ayatollahs backyard.
Adam Curry: I mean, he's
channeling Bush now.
John C Dvorak: They know he made
handling McCain.
Adam Curry: Well, but yeah, of
John C Dvorak: course if and if
you remember, I wish we could
find a clip where we can. Of
course, of course We have
Barbara and sewing as bom bom
bom bom bom Irfan
Adam Curry: I'm sure we have it
John C Dvorak: we do have it is
this God knows what it's called.
Yeah no this is all
Unknown: bomb bomb Iran bom bom
bom bom bom I
Adam Curry: think it's our own
version. I like it.
Unknown: Bom bom bom bom bom
Moran. Yeah.
John C Dvorak: So the ghost of
John McCain.
Adam Curry: He's still with us.
He's
John C Dvorak: still with us.
And he's being channeled through
Lindsey Graham now if you
Adam Curry: think that was good
and who is his buddy and just as
an aside, this is exactly what
we talked about this has always
been on the radar. This is pure
evil that exists in the West,
not even one group of people is
just evil that is taken over.
And they these people don't
actually care about dead
Israelis or dead Palestinians.
They don't care about any of
that. They don't care about you.
They don't care about me. They
just care about the programming
they have in their brain to just
bomb stuff more money getting
into the markets, we need stuff
to happen. This is what we live
for.
Unknown: What I would do is I
would bomb a Ron's all
infrastructure, the money
financing terrorism. This is on
CNN now comes from Iran. It's
time for this terrorist state to
pay a price for financing and
supporting all this chaos. Yes,
if you're the Iranians, if we're
up to me, this war escalates.
I'm coming after you.
I think this is what I'm trying
to clarify here. Because I'm
wondering, listen,
Israel, US and Israel, is
the United States. Crystal clear
The United States. Let me just
let me just understand you.
John C Dvorak: What was the
point of that he
Adam Curry: has no he he's
telegraphing that we aren't
going to do it. It's US and
Israel, Israel, Israel, but
okay. And the telegraphing is
we're going to give them all the
stuff, Bibi is going to pull the
trigger, someone's going to pull
there's not going to be us. Now
we want Israel
John C Dvorak: to throw that in
because he forgot to do that
earlier. Yes. You
Unknown: forgot, drill us in
Israel, the United States.
Crystal clear in the United.
Adam Curry: Let me just let me
join operations. That was
exactly what Trump was talking
about when when Bibi pulled out
of the joint operation. Isn't
that interesting. But he's
clear. It's clear. Now I
Unknown: understand you. Just to
be clear, you're saying that you
would want the United States and
Israel to bomb Iran, even in the
absence of direct evidence of
their involvement in this
attack? Hey, yeah, so
Adam Curry: what evidence,
evidence Come on? Everybody
knows this. Yeah.
Unknown: If there's an
escalation, Abby, there's
people's throats being cut on
television, as Israel goes into
Gaza.
Adam Curry: She's already
telling us what the what the
nightly programming is going to
be. It's as if he knows Oh, if
we start seeing people's throats
getting slit on television, wow,
tick tock, maybe television
really, really, they haven't
shown much on television, or
shown anything. Please don't
email us. We've seen that we've
seen
John C Dvorak: Okay, now we got
to telegraph account. Don't
worry about we have a telegraph
but
Adam Curry: he is telegraphing.
He is telegraphing what we're
going to see.
Unknown: Yeah. So if there's an
escalation, Abby, if there's
pappy throats being cut until
How is
Adam Curry: people's throat
being cut on television
escalation of anything, but the
mainstream media is not an
escalation of the atrocities?
No, I mean,
John C Dvorak: no, I know
exactly what you mean. He's
just, he's gotta be he's got a
script. He's going by I don't
know where it came from who's
delivered it? But it's always
well, of course, again, I like
I'll say it again, it came.
We're behind. we're way behind
on that. On that on the west
Clarke seven. Yep. And things
are time is running out on this
Iran deal. So they're either
going to have to do they got to
take action now because this is
the last bit and if Trump comes
back in office, which is
possible, not gonna happen,
won't happen. Not gonna happen.
So they mean something will
happen. But we will be that
which
Adam Curry: is exactly why
Brooks and Dawn are over there
saying, oh, it'd be horrible if
Trump came back in Oh, no,
because then we won't be able to
bomb Iran. So I know Iranians,
by Iranian friends.
Unknown: If there's an
escalation Abby, if there's Pam
throats being cut on television,
as Israel goes in Gaza, and
they're threatening to kill the
hostages of Hezbollah, As
unleashed on Israel in the
north, it will be because Iran
is supporting that. If you don't
get the connection between Iran
and this terrorist activity by
Hamas and Hezbollah, you're
missing a lot. This is a
terrorist state that has
American blood on its hands. It
is now time to dismantle the
financing system of terrorism.
If this war escalates, yes, I
would do to joint military
operation joint I tell the
Iranians today, if the war
escalates, you will pay a price
you will be out of that all
business want to be crystal
clear? And if we don't,
Adam Curry: that's interesting.
You'll be out of the oil
business, the oil before
business, are they still in the
oil business?
John C Dvorak: Or did they trip
up, though tripped the clip by
played from Trump starts off
with him talking about the fact
that they went from nothing to
let allowing him to produce oil
to the tune of 80 to $100
billion in profits war in Iran.
All day, I would like you to
play the just the beginning of
this again, because this is the
Adam Curry: which one is that
which is the clip.
John C Dvorak: I think it's the
BB background. But no, it's the
unedited comments just right.
The very beginning. He's talking
about Iran
Unknown: for $6 billion was a
tremendous amount of money, but
nothing compared to the hundreds
of billions of dollars that
Biden allowed them to make and
oil and other things hundreds
and 1000s it became a rich
nation.
Adam Curry: Oh, yes. Yes, yes.
Yes. Yes. Good catch. Trump's
John C Dvorak: blaming it on
Biden. Yeah. More because they
loosened up some restrictions,
of course, sanctions.
Unknown: If the war escalation
will pay a price, you will be
either all of this.
Adam Curry: Do we? Did we ever
get those hostages back, by the
way, which was the ones that we
paid $6 billion for? Have they
been interviewed? Or have they
been on 60 minutes have been
this would be a big deal? I
mean, these are each person's
about a billion bucks. Should we
be talking to them
John C Dvorak: to remember there
was hostages involved in this
deal? Yeah, that's
Adam Curry: guess the $6 billion
was to get hostages back from
Iran.
John C Dvorak: Iran? Oh, that's
right. There was a few
prisoners. Yeah,
Adam Curry: prisoners. Alright.
Do we do we? Do we know even who
that what their names are? If
they'd been on television? I
mean,
John C Dvorak: their names or
their CIA names? Thank you.
Unknown: If the war escalates,
you will pay a price you will be
either or business. Want to be
crystal clear on that? And if we
don't do that, what do you
expect to happen in the future?
Do you expect Israel to forgive
and forget? Biden did mention
one word about Iran today and I
want to support the president.
I'm supporting the Saudi Israel
peace deal. Israel made peaceful
several Arab countries through
their Abraham Rickroll course. I
want to help the Palestinians we
can do business with as part of
a Saudi Israel peace deal, but
I'm tired of letting Iran I
think they did this to stop the
Saudi Arab peace negotiations.
The Iranians, I don't want to
reward them I want to punish
them.
Adam Curry: Now that he says
that I think that's bull crap,
too. But this month Oh, they did
this to stop the peace
negotiations really? Really
think that Iran just I mean, is
it true Iran just wants death
and destruction?
John C Dvorak: Bring back a
tweet I mentioned in the
newsletter somebody posted which
was about it seems a little
weird. That on the 50th
anniversary of the famous Yamba
Kapoor award, the 50th
anniversary debt the debt Israel
let down their guard.
Adam Curry: Yes, see? Seems like
we you know, did you remember
odd? Did you read Seymour Hersh
his
John C Dvorak: piece? No, no, I
didn't know what he did. What'd
he say this time so
Adam Curry: it was also the
Sukkot celebration. But yeah, so
I'm gonna reading verbatim from
his just reading a paragraph or
two. The so called celebration
near Palestinian village, known
in Hebrew is how it should need
would need extra ordinary
protection given the tension
over the latest violence and the
local Israeli military
authorities with the approval of
Netanyahu ordered two of the
three army battalions each with
about 800 soldiers that
protected the border with Gaza
to shift their focus to the so
called festival that left only
800 soldiers the insider told me
to be responsible for guarding
the 51 kilometer border between
the Gaza Strip and southern
Israel. That meant the Israeli
citizens in the South were left
without an Israeli military
military presence for 10 to 12
hours. They were left to fend
for themselves. And that is why
Bibi is finished. It may take a
few months but he's over. Now.
I'm jumping ahead because I want
to get to that because I have
some other things that play into
that. But first we need to
listen to Lindsey Graham. He's
just I mean, you could do a
super In fact, I'll probably get
a super cut. So now he got I was
done with crystal meth and he
lays out this plan.
Unknown: Listen to me now and
listen to me good. We should,
without lubricant, go into Gaza
from behind. I know it sounds
brutal, but we need to penetrate
them blow our loads. And then
subsequently Plowshares ai i
love it. Actually, if we stay
inside for an extended period of
time because we need to make
sure that the deed is done. I
have been an expert on this
subject for many years. And I
think now is the time to act.
Adam Curry: That's AI obviously,
but I thought it was fun fun to
play.
John C Dvorak: It is was the AI
is getting funnier. Yeah. The
problem, of course, is that if
you don't listen to our show,
and you don't know or super
skeptical about everything, you
will be susceptible to some AI
shenanigans. But
Adam Curry: the whole point of
good AI is that you catch on and
it's funny. I mean, otherwise it
just no good.
John C Dvorak: Most people can't
do that and lizard kind of
training. You have trained ears.
I don't believe that 90% of the
people that would hear that 90
wouldn't buy into it.
Adam Curry: No, come on. It's
like yeah, we gotta
John C Dvorak: say that, but
Adam Curry: that's fine. That's
fine. Now before I get to the
Netanyahu bid, just one more
just as its global, the whole
Iran focus, as we suspected, yea
perhaps predicted is everywhere
as let's go to the European arm
of the CIA propaganda machine
toyed chavalla with some think
tank aihole
Unknown: for its incursion,
Hamas has used 1000s of drones
and rockets and carried out
cyber attacks. The conflict has
raised questions as to how the
group is able to finance these
complex attacks.
Adam Curry: They've done cyber
attacks. This is news to me.
Every cyber attack is always
Russia. Now Hamas has done North
Korea. Now Hamas has done cyber
attacks, very complex seems
unlikely. Well, it's the CIA
come on these or whatever
Unknown: questions as to how the
group is able to finance these
complex attacks. Israeli
retaliation also has enormous
costs for the economy of the
Gaza Strip, which is under Hamas
rule. Joining me for this
conversation is Matthew Levitt.
He's the director of the program
on counterterrorism and
intelligence at the Washington
Institute for Near East Policy.
Adam Curry: Oh, goodness, I
mean, you know exactly what this
is. We need a gig like that. I
want to be at the National
Institute for terror Near East
Institute,
John C Dvorak: something up like
that, and probably do as well as
we're doing for the show, or
better
Unknown: East policy, has been
using drones, cyber attacks and
rockets against Israel. Where is
it getting the funding for these
weapons from
Adam Curry: a where's it
getting? Hello, hello, Think
Tank guy, Hamas and Hezbollah
things in the background? Why
what I'm just out of curiosity,
do you have any idea where
they're getting the funding for
these cyber attacks? Could you
Could I'm at a loss, what could
it be
Unknown: moss is funding streams
have changed over the years in
particular, in 2007, when Hamas
took over the Gaza Strip by
force of arms, pointing its guns
not at Israel In that instance,
Israel had already withdrawn but
against Palestinians, once it
controlled territory, it was
able to tax some might say
extort the local population. And
that is its primary source of
income right now. The second
most important source of income
and this is something that has
been consistent over decades
since the founding of Hamas in
the late 1980s. US government
estimates that Iran provides
some us somewhere between 70 and
$100 million a year, probably
additional funds and moments of
crisis like this. And that has
been constant. That is money
that is in kind that is weapons
there is on top of that
training, intelligence support,
etc.
Adam Curry: Okay, so it's clear
who we need to go after because
Iran is the problem. It's not a
bunch of nut jobs known as
Hamas, who are just blood
thirsty. We don't even have to
talk about the genesis of that.
We've done that. But it's all
her right. It's all about Iran.
It's all about Iran. Now. We get
to Bibi Netanyahu and another
player that we haven't really we
haven't played paid any
attention to this woman. So my
initial and I think yours will
be one of the initial who
benefits from this. Well, you
know, Biden benefits as a war
president Hunter Biden benefits
the NGOs who are flowing asylum
seekers into every Western
country in the world. They
benefit don't look at our
border. Look at that one. Look
at that. 51 kilometer. Now, look
at that board. That board over
there that board, don't look at
Ukraine. Don't look at any of
this stuff. So a whole bunch of
people the end machinery
benefits and the military
industrial comp everyone
benefits benefits benefits Wall
Street's gonna benefit everybody
the oil guys are gonna benefit
are benefiting my friend paid
for dinner so I know he's
benefiting but but Netanyahu had
this huge problem and I think we
need to revisit this it's
controversial because we have
understood this from many people
boots on the ground no agenda
producers that the Supreme Court
I'm just I'm just gonna use the
simple version Supreme Court of
Israel, Israel Israel they have
precedence over the parliament
but over the government they can
say, you know, we don't like
this law or this run of the
blue, they can do it whenever
they
John C Dvorak: will slightly
different than our Supreme Court
which has to have it presented
to them through the court
system.
Adam Curry: Yes. And then here,
it's just um, yeah, we don't
like what you did.
John C Dvorak: Key Exactly.
Yeah, it's pretty. And it's
really
Adam Curry: also filled with an
app going on a limb because I'm
not really schooled in it. But
in Israel, you have Ashkenazi
Jews and Sarfati I think is
Sephardi Jews, which would be
like my 40 Sephardic, like my
buddy Benco Han, who wouldn't go
dark all have dark skin, then
and in the Supreme Court is
pretty much all the white Jews,
the Ashkenazi Jews and their
leaders and their woke stirs.
And they're just like, the
liberal, the nut jobs here in
the United States.
John C Dvorak: Yeah. And,
Adam Curry: you know, they're
like, Yeah, you know, everything
LGBTQ, you know, everything's
all good. It's all beautiful.
You know, we could you know, you
know, don't just the whole
thing, everything is It's
identical. And Bibi Netanyahu,
who I've always considered to be
very sketchy guy, I said, sketch
them very sketch says, I'm gonna
retract that. I'm both. I've
always been skeptical about the
guy. He's like, Yeah, go it. But
we've been programmed to think
he's a criminal. He's a
gangster, he's no good. He's a
war monger. He was voted in by
Democratic vote, if you trust
elections, to change with one
mandate to change the judicial
system, so that the people of
Israel would feel like they
actually have a say, and not
just this star pushed around by
the judiciary. Yes, this
Starfleet Command. And so what
happened was, and this is Sir
Brian of London has said these
riots that were ongoing that had
been going on since his
election, and all of these, all
of the accusations and their,
they hate gays, and they're
corrupt, and they're horrible
people, he says is pretty much
identical to Trump and Black
Lives Matter. And that these
protests are, you know, and so
all professional signs and
people are getting riled up and
the military is getting
involved. But it was it's been
led by a very interesting woman
named Sheikh my Bressler thinks
she's 4142. Good looking. She
actually started the Black Flag
protest earlier, which is much
more black lives matter related,
but she led this protest. She's
a physical that a particle
physicist from CERN. But somehow
she got drafted into the to
being the leader of this
protest. And I could not find
it. But she apparently somewhere
along the line said, you know,
this Netanyahu, you better give
it up. Something bad's gonna
happen. end of September, I've
been looking for that quote.
Because that would kind of that
would close the loop. But she
was interviewed by The Times of
Israel. And I just pulled a
couple of clips because I have a
feeling that this protest cannot
be isolated from what happened
by the lapse in security, as
certainly maybe the lack of
response from the military. And
the fact that Seymour Hersh, who
we I hold him pretty in high
regard. Seymour Hersh says this
guy's finished, he's done. This
might have been a plan to get
rid of Netanyahu that perhaps
they misjudged, and it went too
far. Here's a little bit of this
interview with Schick, my
Bressler so she come
Unknown: I asked you What
matters now. Maybe it will sound
a bit dramatic. But what matters
now is really to
Adam Curry: say I'm sorry, I
should say this interview is
from March of this year. Just
coincidentally, the same time
Biden did that executive order
with the security change, but
I'm not necessarily connecting
those two, it'd be actually
Unknown: sound a bit dramatic.
But what matters now is really
to save the Israeli democracy to
save the state and nation of
Israel. I as part of my duties
and job in Weitzman and being
part of a huge international
collaboration. I do talk to many
people from abroad. And what is
clear to me is that people do
not aware of the dramatic things
that are happening these days in
Israel. And the fact that if we
will discuss it in a month from
now we could be already beyond
the point of no return for What
people need to take away out of
this conversation and not wait
to the end of it is to
understand that we are now these
days facing a yield curve in the
sense that if we are not able to
stop what is going on at the
moment, in a couple of weeks,
days, maybe Israeli will no
longer be a democracy. And then
once the point of no return has
passed, it will take decades to
get back from this point. And
maybe it will not even be
possible. And I know it sounds
dramatic, but it is dramatic.
But this is the circumstances,
this is what matters now. I
think that people are not really
digesting, fully digesting what
is going on. And it is dramatic.
And it's happening now.
Adam Curry: The only thing she
didn't say was existential
crisis. That's the only thing
that was missing from that. And
by the way, it's
John C Dvorak: very similar to
the Trump is a threat to
democracy somehow.
Adam Curry: Yes. And I realized
that my sources are limited. But
I'm just giving you this. My
view may be different. On
Thursday, it'll
John C Dvorak: develop Don't
Adam Curry: worry, yeah. But
people like
John C Dvorak: that kind of same
guy.
Adam Curry: So. So then, in this
next bit from the interview, she
says something that catches my
ear, and my ears perk up,
because I've heard this
somewhere else, listen to this.
Unknown: How could you just to
play devil's advocate? How could
you possibly when the government
coalition will pass the overhaul
builds? Because it can, it's in
power, it will do that? So what
is a win for you? So first of
all, some extent we are already
a winning maybe we are winning a
battle, but not the entire
world. But you have to
understand it's a try. If you
look at the the changes that
opened in Hungary in the last
decade, and you when you make
the new when you compare it to
what is being done here, they
try to do what Obama did in a
decade in Hungary to do here in
two months. As I said, it's not
just one law that they are
trying to pass, but it's more
than 120 loads that are being
really ambushed on on us. And
this will probably not happen
the way that they want they
start to tell going to you know,
to do this legislation and they
will be done with it in no time.
No no defense. And then now they
need to change that. So they're
calling back a lot of they're
seeing and only focusing on this
committee for the election of
judges, which is the core thing
if you go back again to hunger
you will see is that this is how
all been started by taking
control over the judicial the
courts and the judges so they
are focusing on that. So when
Adam Curry: I heard this I'm
like what Orban committed a coup
in Hungary and overthrew the
judiciary and the country's calm
and orderly and people seem to
be happy there. Did I miss
something that he's a dictator
John C Dvorak: may have been
pushing the Orban being a
dictator the left has for at
least the entire
Adam Curry: or ban the guy who
would not mandate vaccines who
would not eat
John C Dvorak: or Bond started
the problem by blocking the
didn't do initial wave of
refugees from the Middle East.
Yeah, back 10 years ago yes. Or
Bond threw up defenses and said
no.
Adam Curry: And the people of
Hungary have seem to be happy
with him. I have seen protests.
John C Dvorak: I don't want to
say you know, bring this guy
into the picture but it's as you
recall, Tucker went there and
hung out with him and Jed tried
to look around for some sort of
problem and could find nothing
Orban did take on the judiciary
which did have an issue that
with the I don't know this is
like nuts. Okay,
Adam Curry: so when this
triggered me I went whoa, hold
on a second hold on
John C Dvorak: or bonds anti
globalist Yeah, obviously this
woman is globalist and this is
the word this what we're dealing
with now somehow.
Adam Curry: So now three weeks
ago, 60 minutes does an
interview with three Israeli IDF
soldiers they're in uniform. One
is a helicopter pilot one is and
that's the she was always sexy.
female combat chopper pilot
lesbian. Does it get any better
than that? The other one is
special forces. And I forget
what the third was. And they're
just talking about how horrible
Netanyahu is. It's the same
topic three weeks ago. Listen to
this
Unknown: head of national
security has had multiple
convictions, including
supporting terrorism against
Arabs. The finance minister is a
self described fascist.
homophobe. As for Netanyahu, he
is in the midst of three
separate trials on charges of
corruption. The protesters say
that laws his government has
introduced over 200 of them
would not only weaken the
courts, but control the press
and diminish individual rights.
And that this is how democracies
like Hungary became autocratic.
What's happened in Hungary and
Poland will not happen here.
There is a trend and it's going
against you. Around the World.
We'll be the first to stop it.
You're all determined.
We are not joking. We are really
trying to stop it and we will
succeed.
One of the big worries is that
without a strong Supreme Court,
the ultra orthodox block and the
government could turn Israel
into a theocracy where biblical
laws prevail.
Our Supreme Court is our last
line of defense. And this is our
last safeguard. We need them
empowered. We need them
independent, that what we fight
for
what is at stake for women,
Shira,
that will be sitting in the back
of the bus. Literally,
literally. Are you married? I'm
married to a woman, a doctor. We
have a daughter, she's one year
and eight months.
Her fear of an assault on
women's and gay rights is well
founded. A government member
said the gay community is more
dangerous than ISIS and
Hezbollah.
Adam Curry: Oh crap. For some
reason. I must have cut out the
bit worse. They talk about
Poland Hungary. No, I heard it.
Oh, it was in there. I
completely missed it. Hello.
Sorry. I just thought it came.
You know,
John C Dvorak: they mentioned
both countries as as autocratic
countries. Yes. Polar. I'm
giving you a clip of the day for
digging that baby out of the
woods.
Unknown: ever done? Oh, no,
Adam Curry: no, no. This is by
this is truly mine. It's not
coincidence. I know who gave it
to me. I know who does this.
It's It's Supernatural. So I get
this clip. And I'm like, Whoa,
this is the same talking point.
Poland Poland. same
John C Dvorak: talking points. I
exactly. And it's interesting,
because it kind of parallels the
queers for Palestine movement.
Yep. Which I, which I
highlighted in the newsletter,
and people should go read the
newsletter and click on the
link, or just go to Google or
duck duck go, which is what I
use at queers for Palestine and
start reading what's going on in
Israel with the game movement
there. And the symbiosis with
Palace Steen and the fact that
they're all you know, they, it's
just very strange. And I think
it's part of that I think with a
clip you just played is part of
queers for Palestine.
Adam Curry: So the problem is
that they said, We're not going
to let it happen, we will do
what it takes. And then here go,
but going back to schema, the
leader of this movement,
Unknown: so I think that if, as
I said, if this laws will pass,
by definition, the Israeli court
system will be underneath the
political system, the
government, by definition, it's
not a Democratic democracy
anymore. And then we'll have to
you know, we will wake up one
day for something completely
different than what we were used
to, I think that then then what
we will see here is that the
country conditions fall, you
know, goes down quickly, you you
we heard yesterday, large groups
from the reserve army unit
saying that if this happens,
they will not they will not they
will not serve a dictatorship,
they will only that we are here
we all took our oath to protect
the democratic a Jewish
democratic country and not a
dictator. I think that we see it
already we will be affected
economically, very dramatically
will be affected basically, in
every aspect, it may not be
happening in one day, but But
again, if you look at countries
that went down the throats or
condition, and then it will be a
huge and a long battle, which
will which you know, we will all
be losing, but but it will be it
will be awful, to be awful.
Adam Curry: So she says right
there, that reservists army will
not defend a dictator. They will
not defend, I presume Israel.
And I'm just putting a couple
things together here. It was
like, Do you think it's possible
that that they thought, well,
you know, we'll let some we'll
let some terrorists come in and
do a little
John C Dvorak: one. They tore
down that fence with bulldozers
and nobody did anything or even
took a shot at them. That was
extremely suspicious if you
asked me They bring bulldozers
up to the fence, and just night
the fence over when nobody does
it. And when you have
Adam Curry: when you have the
crowd, just like Black Lives
Matter when you have the crowd
program, this is an existential
crisis. You don't know what
people are capable of doing or
not doing. So if everyone's been
this, I mean, you don't see it
much on M five M here. But in
this research, I've been looking
at some of the video these
protests, you know, getting
pretty rowdy.
John C Dvorak: So there are and
monstrous or monstrous protests.
Adam Curry: And so if if there's
like, Okay, this is existential
to the democracy and the
survival of us here in Israel,
Israel L, then it's, it's not
unthinkable that this could have
been, at, at minimum, just let
go. And then they underestimated
how ready or how bad it would be
Hamas was or how bad it would
be. I mean,
John C Dvorak: they could have
estimated how they
underestimated how bad would be,
which but if we take this line
of thinking, which nobody wants
to do, no, because it's very
unpopular and very busy gonna
get more letters to Adam, that
he has to read on the next show.
Horrible letters. But if you
take that line of thinking and
take it to its logical extreme,
Iran is not involved.
Adam Curry: Very possible, very
possible, and Hezbollah
John C Dvorak: won't come down.
I mean, we already played the
clips from the last show on that
on the Hezbollah's as presented
by LG zero, which is a
representative cutter. So you're
gonna get something that's, you
know, cutter, and these other
Arab niches don't want to make
this into a big deal because
they're gonna get killed. And so
the Israelis have shot into
Lebanon from that area where
Hezbollah would come in, and
there's no evidence that they're
going to come in and they
probably won't.
Adam Curry: They don't have to,
for us to go bomb them.
John C Dvorak: Don't have to not
if you got Lindsey Graham,
Adam Curry: that's you got him
on your side. So I my my eyes
are on schema Bresler. She's,
it's baffling, baffling, that
they pull this physical partisan
particle physicist from CERN
into this and she becomes this
hero. I mean, I'm almost
thinking, Is she going to be the
next prime minister? Do we have
a new goldmine? Err on our
hands?
John C Dvorak: Who is this
woman? I'm looking at her wiki
page. I've looked at looked her
up. Who is she? Who is behind
her? You don't she didn't do
this on her own. I don't care
what anybody would like to
think.
Adam Curry: Well, she's at the
Weitzman Institute of Science.
And I've been searching to find
out I mean, she was married to
the guide died. Eight ton vert
Heimer, which I haven't, it's
very hard to find information on
her. She's in that regard. It
was a little like, huh, let me
see. You billionaire
businessman. Okay. He was one of
Israel's wealthiest men. Okay,
here we go. He died in 2022. Did
he? Seven years old. One of
Israel's wealthiest men after us
tycoon Warren Buffett bought a
controlling share in his
company. Oh, now this makes for
a little more interesting.
John C Dvorak: Read on
Adam Curry: as a philanthropist
Wertheimer was an ardent
supporter of Israeli Palestinian
businesses and peace
initiatives. He founded Erez
college in the northern town of
Shlomi and the experimental
school of toughen industrial
park that's all I have on this
particular article. So she is a
probably loaded and she comes
from the fear in urine you're on
that level. Then you know you've
got you're connected. She just
connected she's connected. Me
see this car metalworking sold
it to Buffett for 6 billion.
Hmm, I don't know. What is this?
Oh, he was an IDF. I know that.
I mean, this is where I got
stuck. This is this is what you
look at Chick Ma. M she's got
leader written all over her. Neo
lib tard leader but she's got
leader
John C Dvorak: reminding me
because of the nature of the
jobs woman.
Adam Curry: Oh, yeah. Yeah.
John C Dvorak: You know, he's
got a wife and Lauren. Lauren.
Adam Curry: Lauren. What's
John C Dvorak: your jobs?
Adam Curry: Lawrence? Their
middle name. That's important.
We
John C Dvorak: forgot anyway,
she ends up inheriting Disney.
She basically runs she owns the
Disney Corporation for all
practical purposes, the major
shareholder, and all this other
end Just nothing but money and
and stock. And she's I don't
know what her background is but
she was she Powell Jobs Lauren
Powell Yeah. Lauren Lauren
Powell Jobs. She was she's super
ultra super, I would say naive
liberal. And she puts all her
money toward liberal causes and
pushes things in that direction,
which is nothing jobs would have
done this is interesting.
Adam Curry: March 23 2020, stays
around the same time this
interview the same month of the
change of the technology
Bressler was detained by police
during one of the many Dave
disruption protests held across
Israel, Israel. She was later
released former minute Prime
Minister and protest leader Ehud
Barak, part of the West exec
lobbying firm that brought in
the new software tweeted the
Breathless arrest was
dictatorship and action. There's
too many connections here. I
mean, I'm just I need some red
yarn, people. I need to connect
this on my wall.
John C Dvorak: So we've got
plenty of Arabs that listen to
the show. There are plenty of
spooks that listen to the show.
I'm sure plenty of military guys
to listen to the show. Can
someone share? Share besides
Seymour Hersh, who probably is
digging into his into this as we
speak? Yeah, I think there's
something going on. As
Adam Curry: as usual. As usual,
yes. Then, of course, here in
the United States, everyone
loses their crap. And it's very
similar. What happened here,
particularly amongst the
universities was interesting.
There is such a I mean, everyone
jumping on the end, it's all
around the world actually.
Jumping on the pro Palestine
where is Roger Waters I keep
waiting for him to leave. He's
the guy that's always been anti
Israel Pro. You know, boycott
divest and been another be Meo.
Why Why don't the interview him?
It's the guy I want to hear from
right now. I want to hear what
he thinks.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, well, it'd
be nice. I have two clips I want
to play. This is about US
citizens stuck in Gaza. And the
reason I want to play these two
clips because there's a kicker
at the end a clip to
Unknown: the State Department
says the number of US citizens
killed in the Hamas attack on
Israel has risen to at least 29
with 15 people listed as
missing. This is Israel prepares
for unexpected ground incursion
into Gaza, as dozens of
Americans there are trying to
get out. They had hoped to
evacuate today, but they along
with more than 2 million Gazans
without us passports remain
trapped. Israel has imposed a
complete siege on Gaza, meaning
no people, supplies or food are
allowed to come in or out. And
here's Nina krupinski, has more.
Massachusetts resident of Budo
Cole and his family waited at
the Rafah border crossing for
hours Saturday hoping Egyptian
authorities would open the gate
to let them out. He and other US
citizens trapped in Gaza were
told by the US State Department
that the gate may open between
noon and 5pm local time that
window has passed and the
crossing remains closed. It's
just extremely frustrating. Oh
call his wife and their one year
old baby will spend another
night in Gaza
Adam Curry: was interesting
little
John C Dvorak: sound. This is
not about Americans in Israel.
This is about him. This whole
piece was about his buck from
NPR by the way. This whole piece
is about Americans in Gaza. Yes.
It was. I guess there's a ton of
them there. And there's a kicker
at the end of this one which had
me somewhat baffled
Unknown: US officials had been
negotiating with Israel and
Egypt to open the border for
Americans.
John C Dvorak: For Americans
Adam Curry: Yeah, screw the
screw the power to everybody
John C Dvorak: else, which which
is a sign of our as a nation of
our empire. And our empathy. The
well they empathy screw that we
have empire and it's like you
got that border down there. Open
it up for Americans Yeah. You
can be sure that we're putting
pressure on the Egyptian
Government to open that Southern
crossing that southern accent
from Gaza for Americans let them
get let our Americans get out
and then you get bombed you
humbled Hold on.
Adam Curry: That will in fact
well as we heard from Lindsey
Graham is going to be slitting
throats. Americans throats will
be slit an escalation of the
violence and escalation anyway
so back back at home man you
probably people in America
probably heard about the
university signing statements
and me oh we hate Israel. We're
all pro pro Palestinian cuz it's
crazy. Here's something from ABC
Mrs. from Boston
Unknown: digital billboard
parked right outside Harvard
University is attracting a lot
of attention. The names and
faces of Harvard students, which
we have blurred are displayed
under the title Harvard's
leading anti Semites. The
students are allegedly those who
signed on to a statement by the
student group Palestine
Solidarity Committee, which read
in part, we hold the Israeli
regime entirely responsible for
all unfolding violence, we're
merely amplifying their message.
The man claiming responsibility
for the truck says the Harvard
community should know who the
students are, if
they're ashamed of what they did
and want to apologize, we'll
remove them. If they're proud of
what they did. They should thank
us don't
put these people on this screen
because it puts them in danger.
But students like Jeremy
Ornstein believe the trucks
message is only Adding to the
tension on campus, Harvard Hillo
has already condemned this, the
Jews of Harvard have already
condemned this and make clear it
doesn't bring anything to the
discussion. And it actually
brings greater harm and danger
to a lot of human beings who
are here at Harvard University
increasing patrols in light of
the divide in an email to
students, the school says we do
not condone or ignore
intimidation, we do not condone
or ignore threats or acts of
harassment or violence.
I know some of the fellow
students on this camp on this
campus. And it just hurts my
heart. Just see my fellow
friends going through this when
they're just standing up for
what they believe that
this issue is very sensitive.
And this is a very insensitive
way to portray these Harvard
students.
Adam Curry: I don't believe I
don't believe this for a second
that these people these anybody
certainly in the United States,
certainly not at University has
any context any knowledge, any
historical background in in what
is happening.
John C Dvorak: Yes, particularly
that particular group was
exposed by a couple of
documentaries that there's two
groups and they're in they're
paid directly from that 100
million dollar slush fund from
Iran. And they are I think
there's 300 of them in the
country at different
universities including Cal
Berkeley, and it they I don't
know whether they know anything
or not but they are paid to do
this and that's what they're
doing
Adam Curry: and what happens is
just like Black Lives Matter
without thought without
investigation without any
critical analysis. Oh, I better
do it. I better do what everyone
else is doing. You know, I bet
this is the problem. Oh Rob, you
know it looks like everyone is
off I bet I don't want to be the
guy on the on the wrong side of
this argument then everyone's Oh
yeah. No classes let's go No,
but that's that's really what's
happened these are sadly our our
higher education institutions
have become a
John C Dvorak: well it's a
higher educate the higher
educated you get the more
boosters you get to so I don't
know if that tells you anything.
Yeah, I do have one more
Palestine clip. I want to play
more boosters, more boosters
more as you get a PhD, you get
all of them. Okay. Speaking of
PhDs, but first let's play
Palestine update. Okay.
Unknown: The day old truce
between Israel and Hamas
militants appears to be holding
after 11 days of fighting. Egypt
has provided a delegation to
Israel in an effort to shore up
the truce. Martin Indyk is a
former US Special Envoy for
Israeli Palestinian
negotiations. Now with the
Council on Foreign Relations.
He's not sure either
Adam Curry: party really wants
Oh, did you edit that in?
Unknown: Now with the Council on
Foreign Relations, he's not sure
either party really wants a
peace deal.
on the Palestinian side. It's
very hard to see how we could
work towards a final status
agreement and on the Israeli
side. There looks like they're
going into a fifth election.
They have a caretaker
government. Netanyahu was trying
to
John C Dvorak: stop the clip.
Oh, I'm sorry. This is a two
year old. I accidentally got put
into my pile.
Adam Curry: An old classic no
agenda gag. You got me. You got
me. You got me. You got me.
John C Dvorak: All right. Yes,
this is from May 2020. Yeah, I'm
sorry. I apologize.
Adam Curry: In an odd way. I
just want to play two more clips
and then we need to talk about
higher education and PhDs.
There's this woman Esther
Perell. And she is she has an
actual title here homeless
seconds. She is here we go. Also
younger than she sounds that
she's Belgian American
psychotherapist known for her
work on human relationships. And
she sounds kind of like a woowoo
person you have to Oprah. Oprah
loves her. But she attended the
Hebrew University in Jerusalem.
And she's another cutie she
could also have she could be in
that in that girl.
John C Dvorak: Amen. You're on
to the Jewish cuties today,
Adam Curry: well she's not who
she Jewish. Yes. Oh, she's the
daughter of two Polish Jewish
Holocaust survivors. I must have
been. Okay. All right. So she
shows up on my favorite hate
lists and pivot,
John C Dvorak: which she lists
her name again.
Adam Curry: Esther Perell, p e r
e, l, okay. And she shows up on
Pivot, my favorite hate listen.
And she has a concept which I
kind of like, which is AI is
artificial intimacy. Which I
liked, I liked I thought it was
it was a good guy. And so I want
to first a minute on the
artificial intimacy. And then
the clip that I think is
pertinent to what's happening in
the universities and
Unknown: modern loneliness. The
masks itself has hyper
connectivity. And so people have
easily 1000 virtual friends that
no one can ask to feed their
cat. And that loneliness that is
really a kind of depletion of
the social capital is extremely
powerful. It's more to men than
to women, but it's quite
generous. It's very important.
I've been very interested in
talking about modern loneliness
as it connects to the rise of
the other AI, artificial
intimacy. How often do you find
yourself working the whole day
on your laptop, then you can't
wait to close the screen, then
you go home, but you're too
tired. And all you do is watch
TV. Then while you watch TV,
you're also scrolling on your
phone. Then while you're
scrolling on your phone, you
lift your head and you see that
two people in the room are doing
the exact same thing. This is
modern loneliness. This is
artificial intimacy. I am there
but I am not present. And then I
talk to you about something that
really matters to me. And your
answer goes.
Adam Curry: Uh huh. Uh huh. All
right. So again, you don't
criticize don't criticize yet
because it's
John C Dvorak: your lead me and
you're leading me into two
clips.
Adam Curry: Good. We'll get to
that in a moment. So this is the
second and only other clip. So
as it pertains to what by
John C Dvorak: the way, stop.
She's You said she sounds
younger. Yo, sounds good. She's
65 She's not a young woman.
Adam Curry: Really? And the
unreal wiki page she she doesn't
I didn't look at her age really?
Now, let me say she is it right.
Now. She looks good. Then for 60
Oh, I just zoomed in okay to now
she looks like Victoria knew she
looks
John C Dvorak: like she's 65 It
looks like
Adam Curry: I really need to
click on those pictures. You
gotta
John C Dvorak: yet get
Adam Curry: busted. Okay.
Anyway. So this next clip, this
whole the whole thing was
because Kara and Scott, you
know, it's so difficult to talk
about the conflict and and she
brings in a little bit here
about you know, because of
course, you know, no one can
sleep you're scrolling all these
pictures is very bad for you
artificial and intimacy. And
then she drops this little
nugget, which to me explains
exactly why you're seeing
protests, which I think are
completely disingenuous. It's
just, let's just be for
something that everybody else is
for the new new things
Unknown: is changing something
in the world, not just in the
Middle East, the 10, it's not
sure that the image is really
the right image. And it really
tells the story that it pretends
to tell it's a total mindfuck.
There is, it's a little bit like
911, with 10 people titrate,
don't just watch it over and
over again, you will not sleep,
you literally will not sleep, I
am not sleeping. And I didn't
watch much. I just talked to
people. And that's enough. So
what you do after that, when you
feel like the tide is rising
inside of you. And you just feel
like you don't know what to do
with all of this is the most
important thing is to come
together with others to
experience collective trauma
collectively, to understand that
this is changing something in
the world, not just in the
Middle East, and to read poetry,
to talk about what's happened to
ask people where they are. I
think ally ship is extremely
important in a moment like this.
And all of those who missed the
ally ship of Black Lives Matter
will understand it even more. So
now that when somebody writes to
you just to say, I know you have
an attachment to that place, or
I know you know people there or
I know you know if you were
there recently or something that
says I know I see you there's
nothing else for me to say and
you answer this means a lot you
thought of me I exist in your
collective awareness and that is
a lot
Adam Curry: over socialized
under under educated ally ship
needing nut jobs.
John C Dvorak: That's what I
think you've been on that for a
while. I think you're right but
where did you get This
Adam Curry: Pro I told you from
pivot when? Friday
John C Dvorak: this is an up so
why do I say that?
Adam Curry: Why do Why do you
say that? What do you say? It's
not because
John C Dvorak: they just ran it
lowliness bit. Yeah, you know a
complete feature on NPR.
Loneliness. Yeah, I just picked
it up on Friday.
Adam Curry: Ah another up
uncovered. Wow. Okay, is I
played these clips.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, let's go
loneliness one NPR, the United
States is experiencing an
epidemic of loneliness WoW
Report from the US Surgeon
General says about half of
adults claim they have
experienced loneliness.
Unknown: So for some advice on
how to make friends, we turn to
some young experts.
I make friends by sitting next
to them at lunch or in a class.
Adam Curry: Where is this person
12.
John C Dvorak: More like eight,
Unknown: it's a little hard in a
little easy. You could play with
them or they can play with you
John C Dvorak: stop right there.
You know, now, as you mentioned
that they use these kids as
foils for this for this feature
that they're doing on
loneliness. And I'm thinking
that they're kind of put in the
position where they have to do
this because there's some op
going on about loneliness, John,
we get
Adam Curry: our producers to
have their children say the most
horrible things I know. I mean,
you can get the kids to say
anything.
John C Dvorak: Right. But so
they put these kids because I
think they're trying to push
back against the app. But oh,
let's continue
Unknown: friends by sitting next
to them at lunch or in a class.
It's a little hard and a little
easy. You could play with them
or they can play with you.
Adam Curry: According to the
troll room. Bill Maher also
talked about loneliness epidemic
on his show on Friday on Friday.
Hey, everybody, we dropped the
OP on Friday.
John C Dvorak: And Friday was
the day of the of the 13th the
raid global day every day. Ah,
Unknown: so you should ask them
nicely. Try to be nice, because
usually people don't want to be
your friends. If you're mean to
them. Oh, that's
Liliana Beckwith Collins a dusky
and Liliana is brother, Owen
Beckwith. The fear of rejection
sometimes holds people back from
making friends.
When you assume people like you,
you are friendlier, you are
warmer, you're more open, you
take more initiative,
that is University of Maryland
psychologist Marisa Franco.
She's the author of Platonic how
the science of attachment can
help you make and keep friends.
And she says, paying attention
to people can help you connect
with them.
Adam Curry: Wow, do they at any
point say if an older person
comes to you, you can trust them
to be your friend.
John C Dvorak: No idea what the
point of this op is. But the
fact that we have three things
going on simultaneously on the
same day, which you'd think
they'd spread it out a little
bit. I know, it's very
suspicious. Now that they kind
of demeaned the whole thing here
on this NPR report. But in the
second half, it's kind of the
second clip. It's kind of funny
because the woman who's doing
the Who's, who's the presenter
has to demean herself I think at
the very end and the whole thing
I believe falls apart, but you
know, it continues.
Unknown: If you're just like,
present, and you're just like
interested in people like That's
enough, you don't have to charm
people.
Having someone to confide in can
also affect the way your body
deals with stressful situations.
Research shows strong social
connections can reduce the risk
of heart disease dementia and
improve your overall well being.
Yeah, just as four year old
Edith wintech when I'm with my
friend and makes me feel happy.
Okay, so a you don't have any
trouble making friends. Am I
right?
No, I do because I don't want
any new friends. I describe
myself as friendly not social.
So in order to make new friends
you kind of have to be social
and I don't want to do that.
So can I be your friend?
I thought we were what do you do
audition now is
just checking I was just making
sure because you know we're all
we're both nice
Adam Curry: this is this has got
to be binary is this something
else coming to this
John C Dvorak: I believe I
believe you're right something's
up there How about a new dr.
strange and by the way I was
gonna be a good lead into the no
agenda meetup section because
into this a you have you have
you start making new friends you
you're happier. This
Adam Curry: is correct. And I
was planning on doing that
because well I will do it again.
But before we even get to the
meet up section, we need to talk
about the PhD.
John C Dvorak: Yes, here's my
here's what we're doing for the
CIT show. 16 103 Through the
16th anniversary, and probably
and I
Adam Curry: don't even know the
entire deal here. So this is new
for me is we're gonna you
John C Dvorak: know, most you
know, 99% of it,
Adam Curry: I'd say 80%
John C Dvorak: We're going to do
a no agenda is going to be
certificated and recorded, put
on a website, and we're not
going to do it forever, we're
going to do it for a month, at
most, because this work that Jay
is going to have to do.
Adam Curry: Talking about
getting your kids to do
something nice, and
John C Dvorak: she's going to
charge us for it. So it's gonna
be Oh, it's not frozen. So not
so funny is so we're going to
grant the show itself is going
to grant a PhD in media
deconstruction. And we're going
to do it in a in a in a, in a
way it's done it. Everyone does
it the same way by charging you
money.
Adam Curry: Just like a reel of
institutions, just like a real
college, will it be $500,000 for
a four year education, which
John C Dvorak: is by is a
bargain by comparison is going
to be $1,000. It's not a
cumulative bull thing. It's
$1,000. Straight up, you will
get a knighthood and an
executive producer, but it's not
that you can say well, I've
already contributed 500 to my
knighthood, here's 500 Give
Adam Curry: me let me let me ask
you a question. Can you name
your doc Can you say I'm now a
doctor of deconstruction? Or can
you say I'm a Doctor of
something else? Do you get to
name your your PhD or your
field?
John C Dvorak: You You can do
whatever you want. Now, on the
PhD it says Doctor philosophy
for Media Studies. Exactly. You
would if you put it on the wall,
it would pass by and say
Adam Curry: you have oh, you
have a you have a p at European
HD? Yeah. Is it just as valid as
any other PhD?
John C Dvorak: depends on your
perspective?
Adam Curry: Okay, like, like a
knighthood or an executive
producer ship?
John C Dvorak: Yeah, was
definitely as valuable as a
knighthood. Is it as $1,000
Straight up, that's it. It's not
$1,000 plus or minus anything?
$1,000 or more, you get a
knighthood, a PhD and an
executive producer ship all in
one.
Adam Curry: Let's put this just
as valid as Joe Biden's PhD. Am
I right?
John C Dvorak: As far as I'm
concerned.
Adam Curry: All right. And when
we kick this off on the next
show on 1600 are on Yeah, we
kick
John C Dvorak: it off, or you
can kick it off. Now actually,
today, we have a high donation
of 3000. And this person will
retroactively if he wants the,
if he wants to PhD, we'll give
it to him because it would be
unfair to not give it to
somebody who donated that much
the day before we announced the
donations. So that's a
retroactive when we can do that.
But from from now on, it's
$1,000 that's what it's gonna
cost we figure I figure we'll
get 10 or 20 people to do
Adam Curry: i mean i i spent
three months in college I have
nothing to show for it. It's you
will have a PhD and a hoodie and
I will not have a PhD you know
what I'm gonna
John C Dvorak: wait wait if you
give $1,000
Adam Curry: DON I want
John C Dvorak: you get a PhD as
because you're signing the beard
your signatures on
Adam Curry: that I'd like to
thank you for your courage in
the morning to the man who put
the seeds in the Doctor of
deconstruction by this gentleman
Hello my friend Mr. Johnson
John C Dvorak: in the morning,
do you miss random cranium
O'Neill's chips and see boots on
the ground feed yourselves in
the water names and nights out
there
Adam Curry: hello trolls in the
room if you don't mind would you
please put your hands up I want
to I want to catch that
people are interested in us 2381
Trolls listening live right now.
That's not That's okay. It's low
no it's not
John C Dvorak: low would be 2400
Sunday.
Adam Curry: Yeah, but that was
Sunday. Sunday and I just Sunday
night your low some of you
leaked out some of you some you
crept out what are you doing?
Anyway we need more trolls
trolls if you want to join us I
you know who you are. You know
you're a trophy or troll you
know who you are. Join us a
troll room.io Or get a modern
podcast app. Trust me you're
gonna want one of these. When
when the fake news is
everything's coming down.
Everything's gonna
John C Dvorak: stay good. Yeah.
Yeah, that guy has sent a note
to the hamburger place owners
gonna have to meet up Yeah. Do
you have his email? Should we
Doc's him?
Adam Curry: No, no, in fact, I
emailed him you want to know
what to email me? Yeah. Second.
Yeah. Because I he's because it
came through an email to him.
Where is it here? I think I have
it here. Not going to Doc's.
Anybody you kidding me? Susan
idea. No, you are you're a
troll. Get in the troll room
right away. Here it is. I said.
So I forwarded the email that I
got from the burger joint guy.
And I said to this, Troy said, I
forgive you for doing this. AC
and he replied, Go fuck
yourself. Okay? That was
basically it. I'm like, No, man,
I forgive me. You
John C Dvorak: don't want to
Daxing me or use email. No, I've
Adam Curry: when I forgive. I
forgive. It's done. It's um, I'm
not keeping that on me. It's
fine. I'm okay. It's all right.
We know that our bad guy
John C Dvorak: is a real creep
is really amazing that they find
our show.
Adam Curry: Well, he's, he's got
something stuck in his craw
about that. What can I tell you?
Anyway? Because I'm sure he'll
be emailing apple and in every
other place like oh, what get
these guys off there homophobes
at transphobes. So that's why
you want a modern app from
podcast apps.com. And these apps
also alert us
John C Dvorak: in the guy had
his nuts cut off.
Adam Curry: When we go live, you
get an alert, you can listen to
the stream live. It's really
It's quite amazing what we're
doing over there to podcasting.
2.0 So do that, or just follow
us? By no agenda. social.com
John C. Dvorak. No agenda
social.com. Adam at no agenda
social icon. Well, no, I'm not
posting anymore. I'm kind of
done. I'm reading I am reading
but I'm not posting I'll repost
something. Now it's too
polarized. Everyone's got an
opinion. Everyone's I got no
time for it. It's just as bad as
any other social network that
you started it. I did. And now
it's like, it's our home curry.
What do you think you are? It's
our home. Anything it's becoming
it's becoming like no agenda
forums?
John C Dvorak: No, nothing. When
they start starting their own?
No idea. What's it no agenda
social podcast, then? Yeah.
Okay, then you got some.
Adam Curry: Now see, that never
works. Because people quickly we
saw that we saw that when it was
like the kind of the anti no
agenda podcast and they couldn't
keep up because it takes a lot
of work and dedication to do a
show twice a week. And they
couldn't even deconstruct our
deconstruction, they got tired
of it. Like
Unknown: it's too much work too
much
Adam Curry: work to keep up with
these guys. Now. One of the main
reasons we're still here 16
years you heard it right there.
Almost 1600 episodes a very
interesting confluence of, of
numbers that cross this month is
because we haven't relied on
advertising. If we relied on
advertising, sponsorship,
underwriting, whatever you want
to call it, we would have been
long gone, because it wouldn't
have wouldn't have been able to
sustain ourselves with it, which
we need, then we can't do this
work as everything full. It's a
full time job. You're always all
everything we do is prep. Yeah,
go out to dinner with a friend
show prep. Yeah. There's a
there's a, I'm here in
Fredericksburg, there's an
eclipse show prep. Everything is
show prep. And then just the
incoming I've been busy, at
least after filtering the 115
emails in the morning. And then
throughout the day, another 100.
And I read it all I read it all
I have to, because there's
always going to be that one gem
that you miss if you don't feel
like hey, man, can your
assistant reply to me? No,
there's no assistant. Donations
are not that good. I wish. I
wish. So we all we asked for his
time, talent, treasure, and we
so appreciate the talent and the
time that people put into making
the show great, such as our
night Daniel, who does no agenda
meet ups.com now more important
than ever, as we just heard,
because you need to get rid of
the artificial intimacy and get
some real intimacy. Look in
people's eyes when you talk to
them and not have to be worried.
Because even if you have a
completely different opinion
from another no agenda producer,
no one's going to vilify you say
well, I don't agree with you.
Because we're normal amygdalas
here, normal size. One of the
great talents that we receive,
every single show is from our no
agenda artists, we appreciate
them so much. They do such great
work. And the artwork we had for
episode 1598 titled that one
guardrails was an anomaly and
people notice it right away.
They said, Oh my God is like an
upside down stamp. Curry Dvorak
is not on the artwork, which is
a pretty much a prerequisite.
But we laughed so hard when we
saw this from Matt Boisvert. We
just had to chuckle when, when
we saw the terror leader one leg
one I missing right here living
in a cave answer to the name of
Lucky foundries.
John C Dvorak: It's an old guy,
right? Have an old joke.
Adam Curry: It was great. And it
was. I mean, there was one other
stuff that we Well, I kind of
John C Dvorak: I want to mention
somebody. We noticed that was
No, I did that there was no
curry Devorah icon there. So it
wasn't like it slipped by us. It
was one of those artworks that
we made an exception.
Adam Curry: Yeah, it happens.
Yeah, we make it we make
exceptions. We do the I like the
The Spy Who Loved Iran and which
I thought was a pretty piece and
you correctly said and by the
way you can follow along no
agenda art generator.com Dred
Scott also puts these pieces of
artwork into the show notes so
you can see what we're talking
about. If you look at your
modern app right now you can see
it in the chapters. And you said
correctly Well, if you don't
really know what's going on just
looks like a James Bond on LSD.
I'm like, Yeah, okay. It was
pretty though. But it wasn't as
funny as the terror leader. You
know, we're not going to do
Stars of David you know, what
else the you use it for the
newsletter the peanuts
John C Dvorak: that I did? I
thought you did. Yeah. Yeah, I
didn't use that penis. Ah, why
do I have the newsletter? I
think I can tell you what I use.
No, I use the the
Adam Curry: the yes, the P of
war calendar. You laugh? Yes.
Yeah. But I look at that and
like that's it was commerce or
blog or AI generated so not
stolen? Totally stolen. That
I've seen that from that's
John C Dvorak: totally stolen. I
don't care if it's aaj if you
can generate Peanuts characters.
That's a copyright viral
violation. I don't care if it's
done by AI. But it's that stolen
art that is never going to get
used You thief.
Adam Curry: Oh, the so the the
faux diddly had a do the math.
And I actually sat with a
calculator and we're trying to
figure out
John C Dvorak: like oh no, we
gave up after two rounds.
Attempts. It's like
Adam Curry: I can't this what is
this artwork about what? I'm
hoping 33 pops out somewhere but
no.
John C Dvorak: So that was my if
you do do whatever he wants to
do, I'm
Adam Curry: not sure I don't
know how to do
John C Dvorak: it. Right
numerological tricks
Adam Curry: every odd it didn't
work at all for us the math yeah
so and there were other good
looking pieces for sure. Good
looking pieces. But nothing
quite like the terror leader who
we have who has not emerged as a
meme yet so maybe
John C Dvorak: we it's possible
that you're all you're going to
be wrong on this one I might be
Adam Curry: Yeah, Muhammad de F
it's the right kind of guy but
now
John C Dvorak: he's got all the
he's got the all the elements
Adam Curry: He's got everything
we need he's we don't know where
he lives. Got one I missing a
leg. I am this perfect. But no.
So far no good.
John C Dvorak: Again, we're so
far ahead of the game on this
deconstruction stuff that we can
do
Adam Curry: months from now does
happen it does happen so thank
you very much. Matt for Matt
boys word for boys. Ver I wonder
how you pronounce it. We really
appreciate the work of all of
the nogen artists we get such a
kick out of it every single time
and we just love that we're
arguing over real work real
input from people and remember
you're not doing it for us
you're doing it for no agenda
nation you do it for your
brothers and sisters. That's
what's going on here. I mean in
that regard, yes. No agenda
socialists also that's you're
doing all that for each other.
That's That's all fine. So
that's your time and talent. The
treasure portion is of course
critical to keeping the show
going. Then the good showing
today in no small part thanks to
our top executive producer I
didn't even see this I mean, I'm
really look at the I have no
time in the morning to read the
whole the whole spreadsheet but
this is from some earthling in
Houston in Woodlands Texas
$3,000 Now I'm blown away I'm
blown away by this Adam leaves
the note Adam and John thank you
for not only wading through the
much each week to the I think it
means the muck each week to
provide us with much NO I may be
much might be too much to
provide us with the treasure you
find but for truly doing it with
your independent approach the NA
ecosystem and culture rocks and
we cannot thank you enough for
creating it. Thank you again for
truly helping us scour so many
sources searching for the truth
Yes you do. You do. Clips, boots
on the ground all kinds of great
your own personal experiences
all part of the system. That's
why you're all producers, not
listeners or fans. Most of all,
thank you for being such an
inspirational example of
independence, the V four v and
other things y'all do, to remain
free of influence etc is
incredible. Honestly, I want to
write a novel to you both just
exploring these two principles
but I will refrain for now thank
you. Simply put, what you do and
have done is appreciated more
than you can know your prayers
karma in Sudha insert how you
view it will be appreciated as
well. You got it. I'll give that
to you. I would love to pick
your brains with either if you'd
be open to a short interview I
may be in I may even be in order
to come to Fredericksburg. If
that's In the cards, I'll meet
you, brother, or sister, or
sling, some Earthlink, or sling
or sling. You can't use the
actual alien, you come to
Fredericksburg. Of course, Dad,
I'll take you out to lunch.
John C Dvorak: He's the
woodlands. So it's
Adam Curry: not. It's not just a
drive. It's a couple of drive to
a couple of thank you so much.
And, and congratulations on now.
Are these PhDs numbered?
John C Dvorak: No, but they're
listed they're going to be
listed in a an archive.
Adam Curry: Okay, they will be
an online Well, you were the
first one to receive
John C Dvorak: like, an official
like, well, you actually think
about it, you know, that would
be the number and number them
one slash 100 It would be more
of an artwork you're getting but
no, we're not doing that.
Adam Curry: You could have just
said no, but thanks for the long
day.
John C Dvorak: Thinking about
it. The problem is you got to be
thinking about it.
Adam Curry: Some earthling Thank
you very much. Here's the karma
your requests I shall pray for
you. You've got karma.
John C Dvorak: He well. Was good
news from the no agenda shop in
Fayetteville, Georgia. They have
our cut of the action $14.18
Since ITM guys the shop is still
alive as the shop you should go
visit because they got cool
stuff to do. And here although I
think is I think the website it
could be easier to find some of
the cool stuff. Here's your cut
artists have been paid as well.
If anyone is looking for
recommendations check out my
tequila review podcast at still
chillin.com and wherever find
podcasts are heard, take you for
encouragement all you do.
Adam Curry: And again this is a
perfect example of time talent
and treasure no agenda shop they
can do whatever they want to do
we have no agreements no
contracts, run with it. And we
have we have one restriction
don't put our heads on anything.
They work out a deal with the
artists who are all nodes in our
generator and then whenever
there's something leftover
whenever they feel this right
that send a donation. And there
you go. And we've we've we've
never even met them in person.
John C Dvorak: And what's cool
is that we don't do shirts they
do. We don't do hats they do and
people that do shirts and hats
and all the rest that's a
business separate from
podcasting to an extreme. We'd
be losing $814.18 Euro
Adam Curry: Yes, we would
exactly what happened and we'd
have to have meetings. Oh god no
great lusty is in Tomahawk
Wisconsin. 477 dot 77
Interesting. Oh, I see driving
1077 miles from Tomahawk,
Wisconsin. For the thirsty Third
Thursday meet up in Charlotte,
North Carolina. See what well
with three douchebags in Tao in
tow. Wow, that's some
dedication. And yeah, and it
will pay off. You will love it.
Great, lusty? Send us a report.
Send this report.
John C Dvorak: Anonymous in
Biloxi, Mississippi. Four.
Three. Biloxi is a really nice
place. By the way. I've been
guys first time donating well
forgiving me pod father, but I
just wanted to express my
appreciation for the show,
especially during COVID. I was
an avid Joe Rogan listener when
COVID first started, and I
listened to the episode with
that lunatic Michael Osterholm
and him saying a million people
are gonna die
Adam Curry: 1,000,003 million.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, he says a
million in the note. Yeah, he
said 3 million. And it's going
to get really bad. Really bad it
actually had. Oh, it actually
had me freaking out a little
bit. And I consider myself a
very rational person. But I went
back and listened to Adams
episode. And luckily he plugged
the show that plugging the show
helps works, even though when
Adam was talking about people
getting rings and nice things so
it was a little weird at the
time, but I'll check it out. And
ever since I haven't missed an
episode. Yeah, I can see how by
not listening to the show and
only watching the M five M I
could have easily been one of
those people double masked up
driving around in my car by
myself and with my fifth jab by
now. But I just wanted to
express my sincere appreciation
for both you during that time
and today for keeping us sane
for two to three $3.33 I'm
Adam Curry: gonna give him a
deducing because didn't ask for
it. But it's the first donation
so
Unknown: you've been de Deus.
I'll do the next
Adam Curry: to him. Because Earl
Christopher in Marshfield,
Wisconsin out of Wisconsin today
for some reason. I've always
Wisconsin clip coming up later.
The huh Misko why you won't be
disappointed. Says No jingles no
karma 333 33 Thank you also 333
dot 33 from Josh Konings acre
Kooning's Ekor which will be
Konings acre I guess in Dutch
but he's not from Dutch land
he's from packet South Carolina
do i pronounce it that way?
Packet packet a packet it in the
morning idea there in the
morning Adam and John for many
months I've been a faithful
listener but a douchebag. With
this donation of 333 33 offer V
for B for the hours of
information and amusement you
offer me each week. I appreciate
your perspective and enjoy your
back and forth but my favorite
part is still Adams delivery of
your award winning Gitmo nation
media assassination. If I might
ask my ask for three things one
detachment if
Unknown: you've been de deuced
Adam Curry: was really easy to I
want to jobs karma for my
fledgling business. Bronze,
Bronze Age, ceviche Bronze Age
shaving code.com. Bronze Age
shaving koat.com. For fine
American made safety razors and
shave soaps, promo code no
agenda for 15% off. I might try.
What are you drinking?
John C Dvorak: My last can of
polar? Eileen seltzer since you
Adam Curry: never asked. I'm
drinking a Waterloo watermelon.
Huh? How is it? I don't taste
any watermelon at all. Could you
please give me my favorite
jingle rub Eliza thank you for
your courage. Josh Konings zikr
in piglet South Carolina
Unknown: in the standby 333 33
Eliezer our
jobs, jobs, jobs and jobs.
John C Dvorak: De Fuca zotoh Our
buddy in Gladstone, Missouri,
Dave and oh, they do go
everywhere.
Adam Curry: Duke of America's
heartland and the Arabian
Peninsula.
John C Dvorak: Happy 16 116
years getting in before the mad
rush. Here's hoping is a good
donation spree to keep you all
in the chatter. Please give my
pop a birthday shout out he's on
the list and a healthy healthy
dose of South Carolina scream
karma. Keep on keeping in.
Adam Curry: Dave scre Oh, South
Oh, hold on a second. I didn't
have that one lined up five.
Yes, we have it here. You've got
now this next one, I recognize
the name and I don't see a note
but I know that the note was
posted to my timeline. On no
agenda social. I do want to pull
this up for a second because
it's from Jason rich. And he's a
member of the beef initiative on
a second let me see if I could
find Yeah, and it was his first
time donating so I don't know
how we maybe thought by posting
it on the on the origin the
social that it Well, some
John C Dvorak: people I've seen
people do that. I have no idea
why they're doing that. Well,
Adam Curry: he's you know, it's
his first time so now I guess.
Oh, we go. Jason rich just
donate for the first time. It
was great to sit on the porch.
And by the way, what did he
donate? What was his amount
here? 33333. It was great to sit
on the porch with you and slim
at White Oak pastures. That was
Georgia when we actually did the
show from there. Thanks for
everything you've done for the
beef initiative for anyone in
Colorado looking for grass fed
and finished beef. We are the
hookup they can find us on
Twitter at Jason rich WR ich
this Monday the 16th will will
be my 45th trip around the sun.
My wife and I just purchased the
neighboring ranch and are fixing
it up for Airbnb and wedding or
conference venue. Yeah, all
right. So I gotta put Jason rich
on the on the Birthday Calendar
cause he's not there. Well,
thank you very much brother. It
was Believe me it was a lot of
fun hanging out with you there
as well. And I'll give you a DD
Unknown: D deuced.
John C Dvorak: Give me the put
some flank stakes aside, though
game Cheryl Wetzel in Pineville
Wyoming 33333 She sent an actual
physical note and check in and
you can tell because
Adam Curry: Yep, makes no no.
John C Dvorak: Oh Jensen
pintail, Wyoming happy 16 years
loving to show thank you for
highlighting the absurdity of
the world that we now live in.
So many discussions are so sad
but your voice has helped to
lighten the burden of the
insanity. I happen to have some
knowledge of rapid test kits and
it is beyond shocking. Beyond
Shocking. Shocking, that it is
now okay to willy nilly extended
an expiration date without going
back to the FDA to prove that it
gets still works absurd. Since I
do not believe that Cove to even
exist These kits are most
certainly crap. Even before
expert exploration. I would dare
say they are designed to be
designed to be an accurate Yes,
I suppose as long as the
internal control is working, the
test must be right. Right. The
promotion is that these kits
work best on the fourth day is
genius. Because of the dingbats
that I know, most of which are
no better good. We'll test all
four days because the primary
symptoms for COVID is now I
don't feel right.
Adam Curry: My nose is running.
John C Dvorak: The kiss must be
flying off the shelves. Final
note that recently a colleague
announced that she was COVID
positive at just after her
recent flu shot. Isn't that
interesting? She didn't have any
symptoms other than fatigue, you
know? She just didn't feel
right. She is waiting for PCR
confirmation can't do good work.
Good. Thank you for your courage
Dame Cheryl cowgirl of the Wind
River Range wa oming does she
want any? She wants the F 35
Scream? Oh, she also
Adam Curry: wants the F 35
scream Oh, one second. Sounds
like you got COVID
John C Dvorak: Yeah, I don't
feel right.
Unknown: Karma.
Adam Curry: Nothing is a winner.
That's a winner. Jennifer Davies
is in Bethlehem, Pennsylvania.
And she also has a note which he
sent in and I have that note
here. And Hi, John and Adam.
This executive producer donation
is in honor of my smokin hot
husband Oh switcheroo Jonathan's
50th birthday on October 16.
He's been listening to your show
for a long time. caps. And I
figured it was time to make an
honest podcast listeners out of
him. I can't think of a better
birthday gift for his 50th time
around the sun than an executive
producer credit for the best
podcast in the universe. Please
dee doo
Unknown: dee doo sched
Adam Curry: That is very cool.
It's a great birthday cake. You
should also probably just give
them a flame thrower or
something like that. It's also
cool 50 year old guys like that.
Jonathan is a hard working man,
faithful husband and amazing dad
to our for human resources. He
hit me in the mouth a few years
ago, and I have to be honest, at
first, I thought it was getting
corrupted by the show. Wow, was
the marriage on the rocks. But
when I actually started
listening, my eyes were opened
and my amygdala expanded. I'll
always be grateful. Thanks for
all you do. Please play China's
as Whoa, it's true. Oh, I didn't
get the it's true part. I missed
that. I just thought it's true.
That's true. Whereas it's
worthy. It's true ladies. And we
had no been asked for that one
in a while.
John C Dvorak: Because it's gone
out of favor.
Adam Curry: It's true. I got
Donald Trump it's true. What is
John C Dvorak: run into a number
of people who said that they
couldn't listen to the show
because they felt it was
corrupting them.
Adam Curry: Really? Really now?
Yeah. corrupting them in what
way? I don't know.
I can't find this anymore. What
is this? It's true. That's not
the right one. Where's the
ladies? It's true. Oh, it's not
it's true. It's That's true.
That's true. See? They messed me
up there you go. There you go.
Yes, I got you ladies right
here. Okay. Don't trust China.
China is as Hoh.
John C Dvorak: ESP ICT All
right, there you go. And I'm
gonna go to our Associate
Executive Producer Ryan de
Blasio in Fishers Indiana. To
2222 A row of ducks. From the
artwork to the end of the show
mixes and everything in between.
Show 1598 was superb. Thank you,
Ryan de Aza, Zo.
Adam Curry: Anna, you're
welcome. Anonymous is an
Amsterdam with a row of ducks.
two to two. Hi, John Adams has
been a while since I donated so
here take my money. I'm a
painter from Amsterdam who likes
to sneak his politics into his
paintings. Whoa. Ooh, I got Oh,
he was gonna
John C Dvorak: look him up. I
didn't. He has been he's
anonymous in he can't read the
name of his website because he's
not anonymous anymore. So we
can't plug his stuff.
Adam Curry: Well, really,
because it's just an Instagram.
It doesn't doesn't have his name
on there.
John C Dvorak: Well, it's up to
you if you want to violate his
desires to be anonymous. And he
says sometimes I know use it
into notes. So
Adam Curry: now I'm conflicted.
Some Well you tell me tell me if
it's worth showing first.
Sometimes the show inspires me
for a painting title like the
green leap forward. Thanks for
that one. Adam. Federal
listeners who like art from
outside of the lefty plantation
can find my He wants it can find
my work on my Instagram account
on the Insta pet Rex art p e t r
e x AR T pet Rex art. PS I made
that Grumpy Old Men artwork a
few shows ago of course. I know
you don't like your faces on
there the artwork was titled
Just for fun surprise. You
didn't catch that. Love the
show. No jingles no karma you
check it out.
John C Dvorak: It tried. I think
it's cut way back. What we do I
didn't know. I said I didn't
check it
Adam Curry: out. Oh, I'm
checking. Oh,
John C Dvorak: this is cool. See
you on his website.
Adam Curry: Yeah. On the on his
Insta. On his gram. Yeah, I can
see what he's doing here. Oh,
it's very, very, very different.
It's kind of cool. Kind of cool.
All right.
John C Dvorak: You got to say
good.
Adam Curry: I think so. Okay.
Yeah. I mean, I'd hang it on my
wall. Not the one with the
devil's horns. But the other
ones. Yeah, some good stuff. Oh,
John C Dvorak: yeah. James
Shea's up. Definitely. He's in
Brewster Mills, West Virginia,
to 1001 donation note email and
I do have it. Oh, good because I
forwarded I don't know why you
had to. Somehow so why didn't
didn't show up. I decided to
send a bank check this time
because John says that's the way
to go. So hopefully you can
match this note up with a check
when it comes in. And you find
out I saw this note too. I you
know, I didn't forward it to to
Jay though. I had to stop being
a freeloader. I hadn't donate in
a long time because the fuzzy
cows in the 10 for newsletter
got to me it was good. A lot of
people love those fuzzy cows I
love the cows. Your show
deserves more support. And we
know we need to recognize that
and step up Please play the
Emperor Hillary clip that I sent
you years ago that never gets
played No There you go. Oh I
have because I am holding on to
this dream that she will run
again solely for the value it
bring to the show. I would like
some goat karma please. Lastly,
I would like to change my night
name to sir. tip, tip theology
and certificate. Search Oh
certifiably insane, certifiably
got it is you can you put him on
the upgrade list is not on
there, I'm sure. Clear thanks,
fellas for the hard work you do
every week to bring us the best
podcast in the universe. Denise
goat Carmen and upbraiding name
Adam Curry: and this Hillary
Emperor clip from 2017 which I
found immediately
Unknown: by bidding my masters
this year on my birthday every
American gets a cupcake. Yes, my
master
you've got
Adam Curry: Sir Go T Fisher.
Winter Springs, Florida. 201 dot
33 Switcheroo okay. Hey John,
Adam, Adam and John. Actually, I
wore my no agenda University t
shirt out on the town Friday
13th And ended up at Ellen's
wine room in Sanford, Florida
and organically created a
fantastic impromptu meet up. We
had many people in the wine room
discussing no agenda after
sirloin and I hit people in the
mouth. The T shirt was an
amazing conversation piece.
Everyone should go to the no
agenda shop and buy their own T
shirts and enjoy the great
responses they create. Please de
Deus longtime listener Eric
Unknown: de Deus,
Adam Curry: owner of the wine
room Her name is Ellen
Unknown: de deuced
Adam Curry: please contribute
this donation to my keeper of 36
years and they never had a fight
Trish Holland do you do church
you've been de deuced and give
her and you know producer
credits that's the switcheroo
way I just did it to you got it.
I am also sending in a meet up
report as well. Yes received
gold scream love is lit karma.
Well, I'm not quite sure exactly
what that got goats Reman karma.
You got it man. Thank you very
much. You've got karma.
John C Dvorak: Mark Bognor, our
buddy in Los Angeles,
California. hudl Mark Bognor
$200.33. I humbly request to
John's my chair gently squeaks
jingle
Unknown: t shirt The
World Wide
Adam Curry: squeeze. It is a
classic from Darren O'Neal.
Beautiful. Glad we could play a
little bit of that. Earl Pennell
p&l is in Ohio Youngstown, Ohio
200 ollars Associate Executive
producer credits are real
people. ITM John Adam, new
listener spot on evaluation of
the war in Israel. Hopefully
this donation makes up for any
listener that was lost. Can I
get some good karma? Thank you,
you've got karma.
John C Dvorak: And finally, we
got Linda Lou patcon, who's in
Lakewood, Colorado, I'm gonna
give her a jet UniSA jobs Garma
I'm gonna give her a different
read this time for a resume that
gets results. I say go to Image
makers inc.com For all your
executive resume and job search
needs, that's image makers Inc
with a k.com. Or just find Queen
Linda Lubetkin under the show's
producer, list jobs,
Unknown: jobs, jobs and jobs,
for jobs.
Adam Curry: Thank you all very
much. All of you, our exec or
Associate Executive producers,
all of you receive a title one
that is completely real. It can
be used anywhere where the where
any type of title is recognized.
And we suggest you put on your
LinkedIn, your resume or go to
imdb.com. If you don't have an
account that you probably don't,
but you do now, you'll see lots
of heavy hitters in Hollywood
even who have credits. And I
would send you to our donation
page for other people to learn
how you can become an Executive
Associate Executive Producer, I
believe you you didn't demoed a
beta version of the new donation
page.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, no agenda
donations.com with a plural
plural.
Adam Curry: How are we going to
we ended up going to stop or
divorce act.org/and? A?
John C Dvorak: No, I'm keeping
the other one alive for a year.
Adam Curry: You don't have the
credentials to even do anything
with it. That's the problem.
Just do it.
John C Dvorak: Why don't you.org
I can take do anything I want. I
got a Why don't you? Why don't
you for ft. I will but I there's
a couple of things that need to
be done to it first. Yeah.
Adam Curry: Like like find the
password. I know what's going
on. You can't fool me. Keep it
alive for a year. You know, I'm
going to remember this.
John C Dvorak: I still have I
still have people using the the
legacy account, which is a
decade or maybe longer, too old.
And I've talked to pay pal about
this because we now have an
account executive because you
know, that calls once in a
while.
Adam Curry: Or they say like,
Hey, what's this weird donation?
Are you guys terrorists?
John C Dvorak: Now they never do
they have done that. Oh, and so
the guy calls and I said, you
know, and he says, Well, I don't
know what we need, because he
would they have programs, you
know what get you on this great
deal. It works. Yeah. So I said,
Well, you know, we don't need
that. Okay, well, I explained
the business model and
everything to the guy and I
said, but the one thing you guys
could help with? And he
certainly, you know, it's not
really my job to do this. But he
says I'll give it a shot and see
if I can get it done. Which is
to move the the legacy account
all the people over to the
regular account and then get rid
of that thing.
Adam Curry: No, they can't do
that. They're gonna try, they
can see, you know, a friend of
mine lost the email that he had
his ex account registered to
when it was still Twitter. That
email address went away and they
cannot reset your password. If
you don't if you don't believe
what they can't do. It's just
not possible. He was lucky
enough to buy the domain back
and set up an email address to
get it back. But it's it's
impossible. It's crazy. It's
unbelievable what they can't do
what they can't do. Thank you
all execs and Associate
Executive producers. We have
some meetups we've got I think
we have a 92 nice things coming
up. We got some birthdays and
John will take us through the
50s with people who came in and
just this week.
John C Dvorak: Phil Barnett
starts us off in Brentwood,
Tennessee 15999 Sir Gregory in
Cincinnati, Ohio 12121. Sir
Jonathan in St. Louis, Missouri
1010 170 threes que es zero IHT
70 threes, Julia Saavedra in
Madison Heights Virginia. 100.
Lucas Williams and Roswell guy
in Roswell. I think we have a
couple of people we
Adam Curry: got we got goodies
from Roswell. I got a flying
saucer. Do
John C Dvorak: you ever get the
driver's license from the alien
driver's license, dude? Sure.
Did. I use it? I use it all Last
time I gave it I was at the bank
and to do a no me No.
Adam Curry: Yeah. And they
accepted it. No.
John C Dvorak: But they get the
biggest kick out image. First
day look at it like it's real.
That's hilarious. They look at
it and they go and they look and
they have a big funnel look for
what and then they figure out
it's a big joke. So
Adam Curry: so and so when you
go to the bank, which is a small
little bank, and you know,
they're all sitting there. Tears
that old queued again. Borax
coming in with checks.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, pretty
much. But just so I throw this
I've used it a couple of times
and he's always gets a chuckle.
Lucas Williams in Roswell, New
Mexico comes with 100 Clara,
Sierra Clara, Sierra, Sierra,
and Charlotte, North Carolina
this year Morris 100 Happy
birthday to her talented, smokin
hot boyfriend. There we go. Got
him on the list? Yes
Adam Curry: Are SCOBY sure he's
been around. So Scott and
John C Dvorak: Clayton,
California 100 Nisa de douching.
Unknown: You've been de deuced
John C Dvorak: Stephen Shevlin.
And Southampton Massachusetts.
Nein. Nein, nein, nein. Kevin
McLaughlin. There he is.
Concord, North Carolina. Lover
American boobs. Duke of Luna 808
Breast Cancer Awareness save the
twins save the trends. Gary
blatten Wayne Pennsylvania 777.
David Jarman in North Turramurra
New South Wales Australia 75
Katyn Clifford. Bridge Ontario,
Canada 69 and 69 I got hairy
legs because what he says sure
did. Kevin McLaughlin in Concord
North Carolina 606 Again, Breast
Cancer Awareness Month save the
coconuts. Christopher dektor in
it 5678. Varun it and Dane and
the dame of Puget Sound and some
Manish buy for five forget a
birthday call out it's on the
list. Sir subterranean Shizen in
Saskatoon at the Paris of Canada
30 to 69. We put a birthday
biscuit because the birthday
here at the end. He also
Adam Curry: also wanted a
posthumous mothership boarding
pass for his friend Tanya's next
journey. All right, that's
virtual and you got it.
John C Dvorak: John Kraddick in
Stafford, Virginia 52 Sir
Kelsey, and he's on a birthday
list, sir recalcitrant crazy
Steve in Santa Rosa. 5150 get
John out of the house meet up
coming up on October 21. And
you'll be there. I will. I'll be
there. It'll be our it'll be the
prelude to the 16th anniversary
show. And if you're going to
donate to the show, bring an
envelope. Christopher Myers in
Dallas Texas 51 If you can even
see me in this dark bar. Will
Sherman in spring Texas 5033
Adam Curry: needs a D Do
Unknown: you have bad deed
deuced
John C Dvorak: economic sir.
barons are economic hitman and
Tomball, Texas 5001. And now we
got the $50 donors and I'll wrap
this up with starting with Jared
yaw in Nashville, Tennessee real
real deals now in San Antonio,
Texas. You want a real deal now.
Brandon Savoie in Port orchard,
Washington. Dane Patricia
Worthington in Miami. Thomas
fans low in Livonia. Christian
Christian Freeman in San Marcos,
Texas Kevin deals in
Huntersville, North Carolina
William McFarland in Manassas,
Virginia and that's a birthday
Anna de douching.
Unknown: You've been de deuced
John C Dvorak: Diane Shrawan it
back in johnsburg, Illinois, big
papa productions Minneapolis
Minnesota, Kelly MacDill and
Mission Hills Kansas. Easy
landscapes in North Stonington
Connecticut, easy peasy Philip
blue in Louisville Kentucky is
Michael Thompson in new brown
fells Texas. Chris Lewinsky sir
in Sherwood Park, Alberta,
Michael Pirot parrot in Salem,
Oregon, Michael wind down in
Matawan New Jersey James powers
in Carnegie, Oklahoma and last
on the listeners spot the mighty
in Marietta, Georgia plus, Sir
Jerry William Roth in Saugus,
California want to thank these
people for making the prelude to
Show 1600 Show 5099 success
thank you Oh
Adam Curry: yes thank you all
very much. Also if you came in
under $50 For reasons of
anonymity, I see you there 4999
Or if you're on one of our
sustaining donations we thank
you very much for those those
always get us through the
tougher times you can make one
up yourself we have a lot of
different ones and for a while
stocks last you can still find
all that information on this
website vorak.org/in A and thank
you once again for supporting
episode 1599 of the best podcast
in the universe
Unknown: formula is this. We go
out we had people in the mouth
Adam Curry: and we've got a list
that we will work through right
now Baron and dame of Puget
Sound was shut Tim White a happy
birthday turned 54 Yesterday,
John Craddick is turning 52
today Jason wrench will be 49
years old tomorrow. Jennifer
Davies says Happy Birthday to
her smokin hot husband Jonathan.
He turns 50 years old tomorrow,
William McFadden. Celebrating on
the 18th or subterranean
chitosan wishes Landon C.
Johnson Happy Birthday CR Morris
Happy Birthday to a smokin hot
boyfriend to SCOBY of the
Piedmont and Dave focus odo that
is our Duke of American
heartland and the Arabian
Peninsula wishes his pop a happy
birthday Happy birthday,
everybody. Here's the best
podcast in the universe. Two
night notes to read because they
came in at lower amounts but
they be they will be knighted
today and the first one is from
Kirk stroke or stroke. Since
he's from Iowa and not from
Holland, I'm a dude named Ben
named Kirk from whole Iowa I
decided to check my paypal
history today and took the
sustaining donation subscription
I've been on since at least
2018. To my surprise, I've
reached knighthood and a third
more please Knight me sir Kirk
of Su land protector of things
with power cords if I may,
please have protein bars and
Diet Mountain Dew with the
roundtable Ooh, breakfast of
champions. No jingle no karma
and no jingles no common unless
you have one for people who
found no agenda by searching for
what happened to cranky geeks.
It works Keep up the great work
and of course staining donation
to keep the show going Thank you
very much Kirk. You're on deck
for a knighting in a moment and
we have a note from Chris
gentleman It was a long haul but
please see the attached
accounting which allows me to
Don seriously uncomfortable body
armor while sipping something no
agenda social name the dangerous
clams at dangerous underscore
clams at no agenda social icon
please note me as sir Christo of
the Black Mountain roundtable
tacos and Diet Dr. Pepper Oh we
got some health nuts here today
thanks guys don't stop what
you're doing from Chris and both
of you can get ready because
here's a blade John has a sword
here you go oh nicely unsheath
car can Chris pop up on the
podium here both of yours long
row but doesn't matter it's just
as valid get him here by very
proud to pronounce the k d s sir
Kirk of Su land protector of
things with power cords and Sir
Christos a Black Mountain for
you we've got hookers and blow
for rent and rent boys and short
names. We have the protein bars
and Diet Mountain Dew and tacos
and Dr. Died pepper why? I don't
know because we also have cow
girls and coffin foreigners
Rubenesque woman and Rosae
geishas and sakeI vodka, Manila
buckets and bourbon, sparkling
cider escorts ginger ale and
gerbils, breast milk and pablum.
It is breast cancer awareness
month. But of course you will
always want to try out our
mutton and meat it's top notch
and you can surf on over to
norgine earrings.com checkout
are those beautiful night rings
you will be receiving one of
those along with wax to seal
your important correspondence
with because they are Signet
rings and you'll get a
certificate of authenticity just
send us your ring size and your
address which is all available
there in the handy form and
thank you so much for supporting
the no agenda show the best
podcast in the universe No one
don't fall into the trap of
artificial intimacy attend a no
agenda meetup you heard it you
heard it smart people are
telling you this is a real
thing. And we have a solution I
mean when I say we I mean the
producers have no agenda this is
an adjacent program adjacent to
the the podcast itself supported
by listeners just like you and
people like to send us meetup
reports. Here's that to Ellen's
wine room meet up report which
was impromptu
Unknown: Hey, no agenda nation.
This is Jeff sir goatee from
Fisher of the Space Coast here
at a impromptu meet up and
Ellen's wine room here in
Sanford Florida.
This is Tristan you You think
keeper, love it. Hey, this is LM
from Ellen's wine room in
Sanford, Florida. I just learned
about no agenda and Jeff and
John. Awesome. Love it.
Yeah, this is Eric soon to be ex
douchebag. It's Oviedo. They may
not be Oviedo although
follically perhaps it looks that
way but it's Obito. Danger out
here.
Certainly not New Smyrna Beach
circ shallows and surrounding
seashores cup of coffee in the
big turn boys. show better meat
lovers
Adam Curry: All right. Oh Vito
will never remember. But thank
you for for correcting us on
that Denver had a meet up every
day you're not
Unknown: at a meetup. You should
think of the old Dutch saying so
Noblesville tucked in on his Oh,
wow. So yeah, something else
we're arguing about who the
Three Musketeers were Jim from
Denver filling in for Rasputin
in the morning.
This is Sir our I think I'm
maybe dark Canyon. It's not the
bad guy.
All right. Love is lit. Come on
out.
Mile High meetups and we're out
Adam Curry: and that was not
even touch when he spoke that
was funny. I liked it. Right now
as we speak there is a meetup
underway at Sol mill in
Albuquerque New Mexico. That's
sir Jeff was out there. I told
you go go that meet up ask him
about his scars. Hopefully he'll
have report for us. Also today
casting for Gaston kicked off at
two o'clock and Charleston South
Carolina. That's a Gaston Manor.
Dame Jennifer organizing you
know there's going to be Drayton
Manor Gaston you know there's
gonna be an awesome meet up
report from that one. Especially
from Dame Jennifer. Dave
Jennifer just so much good
stuff. We have the spooky
October meetup, which kicks off
just started at prodigy Burger
Bar in Indianapolis, Indiana.
them tomorrow Oh Monday night
bowling night in the Ozarks
enterprise Park Lane
Springfield, Missouri seven
o'clock on Thursday. Our next
show day North Idaho Sandy
brigade they've been meeting for
years and years five o'clock at
Selkirk Abbey, and that's in
Post Falls, Idaho. North Georgia
monthly six o'clock at Cherry
Street brewing in Alpharetta,
Georgia on Thursday and finally
Charlotte's thirsty Third
Thursday seven o'clock at Ed's
tavern, Charlotte North Carolina
there's a ton of them the whole
calendar is filling up all the
way through December no agenda
meetups and we say connections
protection It's true you protect
yourself from artificial
intimacy if you have never been
to a meet up now is your time
you will notice the difference
it is good for your health you
heard it the OP has been dropped
no agenda meetup.com You can
find one near you start one
yourself some
Unknown: day days you won't be
triggered you wouldn't be saying
is like
Adam Curry: no, I know I did my
ISOs first last time so now you
have to start
John C Dvorak: you know I think
you're right about this binary
nature this loneliness up.
Adam Curry: Oh, there's
something come and maybe it's a
drug you think it's a drug?
Maybe? Or?
John C Dvorak: I don't know they
can do something that will be
Adam Curry: a new survey. How
about a government run social
network? That's better for your
health.
John C Dvorak: When it happens,
we'll be the first one we'll
Adam Curry: know. We'll know.
We'll know. Yeah,
John C Dvorak: I have to. To one
of his kind of funny I don't
know if it's a good enough
showcase but it's funny is ISO
8010 80%
Unknown: of structures have been
decimated.
John C Dvorak: So long, long 80%
of structures have been
decimated just Yeah.
Interesting. All right. Well, I
try this one dystopian
nightmare. Guess Tolkien
Adam Curry: nightmare. I like it
nothing like a good Amy I so let
me see what
John C Dvorak: I've got. She's
got vocal fry in it too. I get
bonus vocal fry. It is bonus
Adam Curry: Tolkien nightmare.
Yeah, yeah, it's a bonus. It's a
bonus. Let's see what I got. The
things I do for this show. is
too long is too long.
Unknown: It's funny though.
It feels wrong but it's actually
right.
Adam Curry: And then my favorite
here's the ringer. I swallowed a
bug Come on.
John C Dvorak: You know it's
really good. dystopian
nightmare, like reflects the
show. Yeah. But I would go with
that. But if you want to use
it's up to you, you just use
your choice are you because I
know you love I swallowed a bug.
Adam Curry: I'm gonna I'm gonna
look at the troll room. Alright
troll room. Here we go first one
I swallowed up. And the second
Unknown: limit trolls. Tolkien
nightmare.
John C Dvorak: They're going to
pick the bug because the troll
room now
Adam Curry: I get bug bug bug.
Bug bug bug Amy bug. Yes AMI AMI
AMI bug bug bug. Bug bug bug bug
bug bug bug bug bug? Nightmare
bug? Wow, no toss it. Let's do
that. I'm gonna do dystopian
nightmare. I'm with you. It's
it. It's reflects the show that
can always play the bug.
John C Dvorak: How about this?
Adam Curry: No, don't make me
combo it.
John C Dvorak: I swallowed a bug
followed by Nestopia. Now
Adam Curry: it has to be three
seconds or less. That is the
rule. That's the rule. That's
the rule. But because I give you
that I will get the next clip.
Did you know In the world of
podcasting that Rob Lowe has a
podcast
John C Dvorak: course why would
I know? I don't know that.
There's no way I would know
that. I didn't know it
Adam Curry: either. Rob Lowe has
a podcast. It's pretty
interesting. He had Arnold
Schwarzenegger on his podcast.
And this is a clip that's been
doing the rounds because it's
quite entertaining.
Unknown: Okay, let me ask you
this. And I asked people this
all the time. David Dreier, good
friend of ours. Yes. And good
man. served for many, many, many
years. He used to have the
greatest what makes me a
Republican and he had I think
four or five things I think was
in no particular strong
military, low taxes, less
government, more personal
freedoms. There might have been
one a COVID but it makes sense
to know strong law enforcement
strong law on the person and
then I'd like to know what the I
was asked Democrats what it
means to be a Democrat in that
way and I think whatever anybody
would say is boy that what this
what would they say
to this? What's that room you
sit on your city? Sob about
ruining the cities? You know,
the fuck up every city in
America? That's what seems to be
the theme right now. Why is
that? I have no idea. I
Adam Curry: thought that was
dynamite. is funny. You don't
hear Arnold dropped the F bomb.
Of course. He said screw your
freedom. We haven't forgotten
that you don't get a pass. You
don't get a pass because you're
funny here Arnold. But that was
funny. I thought that was pretty
good.
John C Dvorak: I want to give
ourselves some kudos for picking
up on something somebody
accidentally said. And here's
the kudos clip. Second carrier
group is on its way and
Secretary
Unknown: of Defense Lloyd Austin
says the US will send a second
carrier group will west as
Dwight D. Eisenhower to the
eastern Mediterranean to help to
tour the widening of the war
between Israel and Hamas. This
carrier joins the Gerald R Ford
Carrier Strike Group which
arrived earlier this week.
Adam Curry: You know, all the
vets are all worried about was
it the Phoenix that Israel
attacked?
John C Dvorak: Liberty back in
the day? No, it was at Liberty
at Liberty, the USS Liberty that
the Israelis killed a bunch of
American soldiers. They're
covered guys. Yeah.
Adam Curry: The Libya. Yeah.
They're all worried about it.
Like this is not good. This is
very dangerous.
John C Dvorak: Well, they still
don't trust anybody after that
Liberty experience. And that
thing is still been covered up.
It's it's been suppressed to
this day.
Adam Curry: Yeah. Yes. Yes.
Well, it's on the wiki but still
kind of not know. Alright, since
we're doing kudos, bow just give
kudos to myself for calling this
one a long time ago.
Unknown: The president is
expected to arrive later this
afternoon. We know among the
topics we'll be discussing is
the Mid Atlantic hydrogen hub,
which the White House expects
we'll bring about 40,000 jobs to
our region. Take a look at this.
Here's what we are expecting.
You know, the President will be
here with the energy secretary.
They're announcing seven
regional clean hydrogen hubs
that were selected to receive $7
billion in funding to accelerate
the domestic market for low cost
clean hydrogen. According to the
White House hydrogen, which is a
clean fuel helps the US reduce
emissions while creating jobs
and building healthier
communities. Now we know that
mid atlantic hub will be in
Pennsylvania, New Jersey and
Delaware again, creating 1000s
of jobs. We will have the latest
on that announcement when it
happens.
Adam Curry: Clean Energy clean
hydrogen. This scam is here now.
Clean hydrogen $7 billion
John C Dvorak: for good news
story. I didn't know this was
happening. You know they're
throwing money at this 7
Adam Curry: billion. Yeah,
that's a lot. $7 billion for
clean hydrogen. Crazy. All
right. I promised the story
about Wisconsin.
Unknown: Now is time for our
friends now. was initiated.
Adam Curry: Yes, trans Maoism
continues just because there's
that we do have a war and it's
covering up a lot and but we
still will stay on the stories
that matter. This is a video
that is from Canadian
Broadcasting Corporation kids
news, CBC kids news. Kids do
kid's news and it is being used
in Wisconsin schools for fourth
graders. It is animated kind of
like, no agenda animated, no
agenda, that style a little,
little more purposeful. Both
kids are brown. The mom looks
Asian, the dad looks Mexican or
Latin X. The baby in the story
is white. So it's a very, it's a
very polarizing visuals. And we
can stop it anytime you want.
But I think it's worth listening
to the entire thing again, this
is for children's CBC kids news.
You can find it right there on
YouTube. They broadcast it on
television, and now in Wisconsin
schools for fourth graders.
Unknown: Oh,
Hi, baby. Are you a boy or girl?
Funny you should ask Syd. One of
the first things they check when
a new baby is born is what kind
of body parts they have. They do
that to determine a baby sex.
Most of the time, it's easy to
determine. And sometimes it's
more complicated. This one has a
penis. Boy, this one has a
vulva. It's girls.
Adam Curry: I gotta stop it
right there. Why do they use
vulva instead of vagina? What is
the reasoning behind that?
John C Dvorak: Well that now
that you stopped it because I
would have said well I'm gonna
dumb thing to say. I have to.
I'm glad you stopped it because
now we have to discuss this.
Yes. Here's the reason there's
these things are not done
without
Adam Curry: cola troll room. Not
Volvo, Volvo Volvo I love being
childish. 15 forever, right? But
why? Why? Why? Why?
John C Dvorak: The vulva is the
global term that describes all
of the structures that make the
female external genitalia. The
components of the vulva, or the
mons pubis, labia majora, labia,
minerale, clitoris, okay, this
bigger vulva, Deborah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, whole bunch of
stuff and the and the vaginal
opening. So this is a new one
that they're trying to push.
Adam Curry: It's only the
external stuff. It's only the
stuff you can see on the outside
what it
John C Dvorak: says.
Interesting. Yeah, just the
external.
Unknown: It's more complicated.
This one has a penis. Boy, this
one has a MOBA girl.
Congratulations. Oh, let's hit
the brakes. People. The way your
body looks on the outside is
only part of the story. One,
stay with me gang. This is
important. I live. Your six
refers to your physical body
parts, remember, but there is
also something called Gender,
which is how you feel inside
your body and who you know
yourself to be and your gender.
How you feel on the inside.
doesn't always match the sex you
recalled when you were born.
Okay, let's say you were born
with a penis and you feel like a
boy inside. In that case, your
sex and your gender match? Well,
what if you were born with a
penis? And you know your girl
inside? It's not a boy, then
your sex and your gender don't
match? Wait, what's those know
your girl inside mean anyway?
Does that mean you have to love
pink things and princesses?
Nope. Sometimes people refer to
things as girl things and boy
things but this is just how
people sometimes classify
things, usually to make it
easier to sell stuff to kids and
their parents.
Adam Curry: So so the reason why
we call boys boys and girls
Girls is for people to ease make
it easier to sell stuff. That's
an interesting take.
John C Dvorak: It's just how
does that work in a communist
country? Or, or tribal
organization where this was
capitalism doesn't apply if
there's no capital. So are they
saying that? I'm just guessing
here? Are they saying that? It
this is the problem? Capitalism
is causing this issue? Because
if there was no capitalism, you
wouldn't have this? Yeah. Then
then we wouldn't have confusion
if there's no capitalism.
Correct. I don't see where
that's going.
Unknown: Close toys and games
are for everyone. You don't have
to be a boy or a girl to like a
certain thing. Said, has anyone
ever told you that you shouldn't
say with something or wear
something because you're a boy
will? Yes. The body parts you
were born with don't always
dictate who you are, how you
feel or what you like to play
with. That's such a relief
gender, how you feel? tells you
who you are. And there are a
whole bunch of possibilities.
Figuring out what feels right
for you is just part of growing
up. Fine little cutie. You might
want to change that diaper
sooner than later.
Adam Curry: Yeah, there you go.
Hello, Canada. Good work. Good
work up there. And of course
that that results and leads to
new stories like this to Italy
Unknown: now where a whole bunch
of transgender men are entering
the miss Italy pageant after a
pageant rep said transgender
women can't compete. Alright,
let me lay this out for you.
Here. It's a little complicated.
The organizer of the miss Italy
pageant said the pageant only
allows people who were assigned
a female gender at birth to be
in the competition, meaning
transgender women, men who
became women would be excluded.
One transgender man named
Frederico saw this and thought,
Well, hey, I was born female. So
he decided to enter the pageant
under his birth name Frederica,
even though he identifies as a
man now, that moment, then
turned into a movement. One
LGBTQ group shared his entry on
Facebook, encouraging other
transgender men to apply. And
now more than 100 trans men have
entered the pageant, with some
even being called to the next
stage of the competition.
Adam Curry: Jesus come quickly,
this world what I find
fascinating is that no point
does anyone state the obvious
that the whole idea of beauty
contests is is crazy. No, no,
they don't see they don't see
that.
John C Dvorak: Well, that used
to be the thing. Yeah, they use
all your beauty competitions.
And I mean, I'm sure you
remember, like 25 years ago? I
sure do. Let's say everyone's
bitching and moaning about
beauty contest. And we used to
do a review of all of them on
this show me you know, recently.
Oh, yes. Yeah. Real. Yeah, we
stopped doing it. Yeah. And the
main complaints, objectified
women and a lot of out of out of
a bag. And then that died down
for some unknown reason. Now we
got this. Yeah.
Adam Curry: It's, the whole
thing is sad. Alright, I have a
John C Dvorak: two parter. It
says you're on the transgender
thing that's played by visiting
me dragging along this tick tock
clip is called tock tock tick,
tock. transphobia, you have to
look it up from the last couple
of shows. Oh, hold
Adam Curry: on. Talk, yes, I got
it.
Unknown: If you are told that
something you're doing is
transphobic. It is not your job
to try to prove that it's not,
you are going to mess up. It is
guaranteed. If you are told
information and you immediately
reject and go, nope, that
doesn't fit my view of what
transmits means you're not going
to be able to show up as an
ally, because all you're worried
about is what you think and you
feel abundant experience that's
not yours, it's going to be
uncomfortable, it's going to be
confusing. And it's going to
mean that you are going to have
to evaluate how gender is seeped
into society, how it has
affected and shaped your life,
how sis heteronormativity has
affected your life. And just
because we're existing in front
of you does not mean that you
get to ask or say whatever you
want. And that's supposed to be
taken as a compliment. Questions
can be transphobic, compliments
can be transphobic. And so
that's where it comes in, where
a lot of the work with being an
ally, actually has to do with
our own individual reflections
on how transphobic society has
shaped the way that we think and
live and treat people. We don't
need allies who are trying to
prove how good they are or who
were asking for a pat on the
back or who are trying to seem
nice, or who are worried about
what they look like. We need
allies who are willing to stand
up for trans people and learn
how to do that the
best that they can.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, by shutting
up.
Adam Curry: You know, I gotta
mention this. Do you remember
the podcast conference that I
went to Podcast Movement? And I
do and they wanted? They wanted
me on a panel. I said Who else?
Oh, it's this one, this one. And
but you know, we can't have just
all white guys on the panel. So
we invited this woman who knows
nothing about the topic because
she's bipoc and that woman
because she's American
descendants, but they didn't
know anything about the topic.
And if they're not appropriate
for this topic here, we can't
have four white guys on the
panel. I said, Well, you know
what, you can have three because
I'm out. I'm not a part of this.
So those very same guys, one of
them had, like a a, like a mini
podcast conference, sold tickets
to it. It was in in Europe and
Um, they got canceled. I mean,
they the events still went on
but some black lesbians, who, as
it was described to me started
calling up speakers they had
contracted and saying, there's
no there's not enough black
people on this stage, not enough
LGBTQ, you shouldn't go there.
And these were people who work
for companies guess what, about
10% had to cancel. So the very
people who are trying to protect
the, you know, the, the
sensitivities of LGBTQ bipod
people were now being cancelled
by those very same people.
They're great. What this what
they never understand. It's like
it's going to be used against
you. So you might as well take a
stand now, because it's going to
come back to bite you in the ass
eventually. My final two Mom, I
have a funny one. But on my
final two clips are COVID.
Related, specifically,
vaccination, adverse events. Dr.
Drew, who I we've played Dr.
Drew throughout the COVID
period, the COVID years. I think
we both trust him. He's not
always been in line with our
thinking we still have always
played his his opinions because
he is a doctor. Well, boy, he
had there's a new study out that
he read and he's kind of upset
about it
Unknown: because the article
came out this week in
circulation, which is a very
fine high end. A cardiology
journal is called circulation.
I've been throwing I've been
sending it around to people. And
it showed it took my breath
away. I was I was shocked at how
how what an indictment it was.
It showed that myocarditis was
not that common and not that
uncommon in young males.
Certainly more common than
severe COVID in that group,
okay? So myocarditis more common
than severe COVID. So you're
putting people at risk and
taking away little problems,
okay? All right, the and then
you've heard all this it just
myocarditis, as you might use it
for itself limited somebody
myocarditis throughout my career
as a medical emergency. And now
this article showed for the
first time that about half of
the kids, these are adolescent
males who got myocarditis are
going to have lifelong cardiac
dysfunction, which means a
significant percentage are going
to end up in heart failure,
hopefully at an advanced age,
but if not, on the transplant
list.
Adam Curry: So this comes the
very same week that the Nobel
Prize for let me see what the
actual title is. Physiology and
Medicine is given to the
inventors of mRNA. Yeah. And so
there's a Chinese journalist at
this, this little event, asks a
question about long term effects
of mRNA. I'm going to tell you
what she said, because she's a
little difficult to hear, then
we will hear the answer from the
first scientists receiving this
Nobel Prize. And then the second
one
Unknown: was AC sizing media
from China, and waste the mRNA.
We don't know the long term
effect yet. So do we have any
concern over that?
Record? Would you like to
respond to that question?
Yes, of course, you know, mRNA
vaccines have only been given
for a certain amount of time,
which begs the question, having
said that, of course, the mRNA
vaccine that is given is very
transient, and the fact that 13
billion people have gotten the
virus, vaccine virus. And oops,
I mean, the the amount of side
effects noted today, it is
extremely limited. So I don't
think it's a it's a major
concern.
Adam Curry: So first, this guy
gaffes, it says, Oh, 13 billion
people have been known. What do
you say he's having with him
crazy amounts have been given. I
mean, given the virus, I mean,
virus, I mean, the vaccine,
let's ask the other guy. And
when asked to that, or that's
fine. Oh, yes. I think that's
yeah, say so.
Unknown: Well, it can't be
integrated into the nucleus into
the net. And that's, you know, a
safety precaution. The adverse
effects, that's been noted is
mostly mild. My court it is
apparent myocarditis, mainly
affecting young males. But that
normally resolves without any
short term effects.
Adam Curry: Oh. So these guys
are getting a Nobel Peace Prize
while the tonale a Nobel Prize.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Thank you for correcting me. The
outrage is still there. They're
getting a Nobel Prize for this
technology and they sit there
stone cold face and as just
limited. It resolves itself well
The top publication says this is
horrible. And Dr. Drew says this
is you're going to be in the
transplant list. What is wrong
with the world?
John C Dvorak: But there seems
to be a disconnect between
something and something. And I
think one of those symptoms is
money.
Adam Curry: Yeah, yeah.
Unfortunately for the love of
money is the root of all evil
does seem to hold true. Unless
you've got something,
John C Dvorak: let me take one
quick look and see if there's
anything that's is I got one
kind of an odd ball clip, which
maybe is worth playing. Gotta
military gotta synced Biden,
succinct comments on NPR is
always a good way to go out. And
then I have a weird Mexican
education deal, which is like
what
Adam Curry: what? Well, you tell
me which one you want.
John C Dvorak: I would say this
play the weird Mexican
educational deal. And you tell
me what's going on here.
Unknown: under a new law low
income mesco Mexican residents
living near the California
border can now go to some state
community colleges at in state
tuition levels. The law creates
a pilot program for some
Mexicans who want to attend
certain community colleges in
Southern California and we'll
run through 2029. The law is
designed to help low income
Mexicans who live within 45
miles of the California border
to get an education and prepare
for jobs. Under the new program
students would pay $46 A unit in
state as opposed to $307 a unit
out of state. That's according
to a legislative analysis.
Similar tuition programs are
available at least 24 states
including Texas, Arizona, and
New Mexico.
John C Dvorak: Due to literally
Mexicans, New Mexico.
Adam Curry: I don't know what's
going on. And meanwhile, do you
know what the most emailed clip
is that I've received this week?
Can you even it's 12 I don't
want to get 12 seconds of it.
It's a little longer but can you
just imagine what people are
asking me as an audio expert?
John C Dvorak: Oh, they're
asking you this AI are asking if
it's to be edited. Yep.
Adam Curry: And it's the same
clip. Do dude, listen to this?
Did AOC fart on camera
Unknown: and to ensure that
horrors do not happen in the
names of victims who do not want
their tragedy used to justify
further violence and injustice?
Adam Curry: Wow, she farted on
camera. This is the number one
email clip
John C Dvorak: guess what
everyone cares about
Adam Curry: them this is why
we're never going to be rich.
Ever, ever, ever ever. All
right. We got a little bit of
Iran stuffs ended up with we got
Billy Bones Billy Bones with a
live show mix. We got what else
we got here we got some C is
Donald Winkler as the other one.
And the classic classic that you
heard earlier in the show. If
you are listening that is you
might have heard that coming up
next on no agenda stream we've
got behind the scheme's always
special guests Graham from
primerica There you go. Keep it
here, draw room.io Or keep
listening in your brand spankin
new podcast and coming to you
from the heart of the Texas hill
country here in FEMA Region
number six in the morning,
everybody. I'm Adam curry.
John C Dvorak: And from Northern
Silicon Valley. I'm John
Cedarburg. We return
Adam Curry: on Thursday, which
will be episode 1600 get your
PhD until then remember us at
DeVore act.org/na We'll see you
then everybody adios mofos such
Unknown: we need to kill them we
need to kill them bomb them bomb
them bomb them and bomb them
again
we need to kill them we need to
kill them bomb then bomb them
and bomb them again a bomb them
again a bomb the bomb them and
bomb them again a bomb them
again. plomin
Kill them bomb them and kill
them bomb them again. on them
again we need to kill them off
them again on them again we need
to kill them and bomb them
again.
Thank you so much for being here
and please be safe
John C Dvorak: this is the stay
safe medley one of the I think
MSNBC host and this is what she
does.
Unknown: Thank you so much for
being here tonight. And please
stay safe
John C Dvorak: because it was
just a matter of course and
again I'm reminded of people's
reminding people to
Unknown: Colorado Secretary of
State Jennifer as well thank you
so much for being here tonight.
Please
John C Dvorak: think of miles
Gibbler
Unknown: NBC News correspondent
Thompson thank you so much for
being here tonight. And please
stay safe. Stay safe and
journalists out there. Thank you
so much for your time tonight.
Please stay safe. HMS was
Timothy O'Brien thank you so
much for being here tonight.
Please to save
John C Dvorak: life secret.
Representative Jeremy Gray. I
want to thank you for your time
tonight. And please stay safe
file handler Hitler enough John,
stay safe. Child Hitler. Hitler
and please
Adam Curry: stay safe.
John C Dvorak: Kyle Hitler
Unknown: bomb bomb bomb bom bom
bom Iran. Bom bom, bom
bom Mofo vorak.org/in. a
dystopian nightmare.