Unknown: I'm Adam curry Jhansi
Devorah
Adam Curry: we're 1920 23 this
is your award winning chemo
nation media assassination
episode 1600s This
Unknown: is no agenda,
celebrating
Adam Curry: sweet 16 and
broadcasting live from the heart
of the Texas Hill Country here.
Reason number six in the
morning, everybody. I'm Adam
curry
John C Dvorak: in from Northern
Silicon Valley where summer is
finally here in October. I'm
John C. Dvorak. Raglan Buzzkill.
Yeah,
Adam Curry: we did it once
again. Happy anniversary, John.
John C Dvorak: Happy Anniversary
Adam Curry: Happy anniversary to
all the producers. But it's not
really the interface to 1600
anniversary.
John C Dvorak: It's
Adam Curry: 1600 shows. It's our
anniversary week. Anniversary
week. And we celebrate with our
Oh, that's a really bad horn.
Something's wrong with that
horn. This is going off the
rails.
John C Dvorak: Do you remember a
real one here somewhere?
Adam Curry: Do you remember?
When I wanted to quit it
episode? 100.
John C Dvorak: Oh, yeah, yeah,
you was like this? Well, we got
to show 100 I think Greg was a
good run.
Adam Curry: We had a good run.
John C Dvorak: And then my
comment was What are you nuts?
Adam Curry: Now? You said, Come
on, son. Stick with it. I'll
make you rich. I'll make you
leave your wife rich. And I left
my wife but I didn't get rich.
Yeah. You remember you said
that?
John C Dvorak: The I don't
remember any of it. I just
remembered that it wasn't going
to happen. What wasn't going to
happen? That you're going to
quit and showed 100 now? No, you
wouldn't let me you wouldn't let
me then. You're a pushover you
Adam Curry: know you even got me
me on the phone and got her to
Candela?
Unknown: Yes, you do.
Adam Curry: What do you mean? I
remember.
John C Dvorak: You gotta keep
doing this show. I don't
Adam Curry: know. That's not the
way she said it. She said
Please, I gotta keep John busy.
Please keep
John C Dvorak: that's always
possible.
Adam Curry: And I realized, you
know, 1600 episodes and still
people just you know, we've
we've we've taught them nothing.
They're all spun up in the
world. Everybody's all crazy.
It's
John C Dvorak: 1500 or 1600
episodes of utility.
Adam Curry: It seems that there
you go. That is it. How utility
John C Dvorak: show title if
utility. Let me write that
utility.
Adam Curry: It's unbelievable.
It really is. You know, it's
like, I mean, we're all wars
bad. But we've been through so
many wars on this show. This one
seems particularly polarizing.
You know, you have to choose a
side. You got to have an
opinion. You got to let that
opinion be known. That's for
sure. Gotta let it be Buddha
daddy opinion be known. Actually
got a nice email from Tom.
John C Dvorak: I have an
opinion. What's your opinion?
And I have clips to go along
with my opinion.
Adam Curry: Because I read this
quick email from Tom. Yes. Read.
Tom says, you know, I started
listening. I started nafcu on
Glenn Beck. I
John C Dvorak: have a waiting
list. Stop, stop. But is this
nasty? Oh,
Adam Curry: no, it's not. No,
it's the opposite. It's
John C Dvorak: open for a nasty
Oh, no, it's
Adam Curry: sick. No, that
people stopped doing that. Like,
when my email right Oh,
John C Dvorak: you're gonna read
it. I know. I
Adam Curry: know. The One. The
One the one person who sent me
that short note like, Yeah, I'm
done. Now then comes back and
sends me did not everybody goes
Eric,
John C Dvorak: wasn't it? No.
Adam Curry: Did not everybody
get the 10 minute video of Hamas
violence? I mean, that thing
when that thing went viral has
been pushed real hard. People
just sending it to me. No
subject here. Have a look at
this. What do you call that?
Like, yeah, I see horrible
things. I see horrible things.
Although actually, before you
start before you start something
someone pointed something out in
that 10 minute video. This is
the video where ultimately I
think that one the guy who's
filming it gets shot and dies.
You've seen that one Haven't
you? That's part of this 10
minute Compendium.
John C Dvorak: I guess you have
to we know for a fact that he
got shot. You
Adam Curry: know, we don't know
anything. Of course. But in
this, we get that straight. We
don't know anything but in this
video. The filmer of the video
is holding an RPG at the
beginning and then funny Where
did that appear fell? Yeah, I
wonder where that RPG came from?
And he's playing a video game at
the beginning. It's totally look
like a video. All of these shots
with the GoPro cams look like a
first person shooter which, if
not intentional, certainly is
triggering a lot of gamers by A
cool game. So he's on the back
with his RPG. And one of our
military people pointed out that
there's a term used right after
the RPG guy jumps the fence. I
guess that would be part of the
security checkpoint. If you can
hear this at a certain point,
the word send it send it or used
to
send it. Send it send it. Yeah.
According to this, our military
person here, boots on the
ground, says that is completely
American terminology for firing
off the RPG send it send it. He
says there's no similar word in
Arabic. I think it sounds kind
of like an American accent when
you hear it. And his final, his
final quote was, well, we'll be
attacking Iran in five days.
This is us. I don't know about
that. But I just thought it was
interesting to send it send it
was in there.
John C Dvorak: Kind of it's just
part of the whole thing. Part of
the whole thing. Exactly. The
Iran thing was the is the right
is the right pick. Yeah.
Adam Curry: So here's just this
one line from Tom. I was
listening to Ben Shapiro every
day as well see, see, this is
what happens. Oh, my goodness.
Ben Shapiro. Shapiro needs to
listen to our show. He did a
week of obviously pro Israel,
Israel and reality on the ground
as he was receiving photos and
texts from friends of friends
and family who were there. I
have to admit, I was twisted
around the axle when you all
didn't take aside. But that's
not your gig. I stayed with you
through 1598 and then 1599 After
listening to John's gig on
Trump. Bibi hosed us and
Hezbollah ain't dummies and how
perverse and twisted day PBS NPR
reporting on Trump. I got up out
of the chair went to my 21 year
old daughter and told her don't
believe anything ever hits. So
we've saved not just this one
guy but his daughter as
John C Dvorak: well. So well we
saved him for the moment. Yes,
you're
Adam Curry: right momentarily.
There's so many good people who
who stuck with us through COVID
Even could handle Ukraine. And
then this one Oh, no. Now check
it out. Now. Check it out. You
guys are glib Cavalier laughing
at death and destruction. Well,
what can I say? What can I tell
you?
John C Dvorak: We're laughing at
the reportage.
Adam Curry: Exactly. The
reportage the teta Tet the real
professional. Sheesh, all of
this all of this stuff. And and
we are also here to calm you.
Right? We're calm where we we
intend to have a calming effect
on you to renovate what is
happening because you're in it.
You're affected. You're deeply
affected by these videos deeply.
Yes, it's rich. Now this I have
a lot of clips, I see that
there's overlap. So I'll just
let you go. If you
John C Dvorak: really I want to
do my may I'm gonna, I'm not
gonna, well, maybe we can start
with the summaries that are
NBFCs NBC, I gave Garrett top
summary NBC. Well, if you do a
summary, I want to jump right
from the summaries right to the
thesis that we're going to
Iran's a target onto
Adam Curry: proof proofs. Oh,
you bring Oh, you're like you
you got proofs
John C Dvorak: of proofs,
proofs. Let's stop, stop, stop.
Where do we stop the war word?
Yes. Where do we start? Let's
stop with this start with top
summary NBC one
Unknown: today President Biden
was here in Israel standing with
its people in the face of
tragedy while across the Arab
world anger rage protests from
the Middle East to Europe. Some
aimed at the US over the deadly
explosion that a Gaza hospital
that Palestinian health
authorities say killed hundreds
and Plame Israel is the culprit.
President Biden however coming
to Israel's defense
Adam Curry: just want to stop
here for one second. It's
amazing that even our own no
agenda nation are just going ape
crap over the hospital. Unto you
Nazis. The hospitals the whole
point is, is to divide up my
Lords This has got to be this
gotta be there's gotta be no
team, this team that team got to
this point. It's the whole point
of the thing people that's the
whole point is to get you to do
that. And we're falling for
John C Dvorak: it saying he was
I actually think it's got a
bigger point. And
Adam Curry: now I'm sure
President Biden
Unknown: however, coming to
Israel's defense, saying he was
deeply saddened and outraged by
the explosion, before declaring
it appears as though it was done
by the other team, blaming the
explosion on a failed rock It
launched by terror group Islamic
Jihad. Israel offering what it
says is evidence it was not
responsible. But pictures of
children in Gaza being rescued
from the rubble of airstrikes
only hardening positions, as the
American President sought to
calm tensions over the October 7
attacks here and avert a
humanitarian disaster in Gaza.
But the diplomatic ground
shifting beneath the President's
feet as he traveled here from
Washington to a war zone
overnight, as Arab leaders were
dropping out of a plan summit
meeting on the crisis. Here's
where we start tonight.
Adam Curry: I love I love all
the military industrial complex
dude showing up all gray hair.
You know, some of them in a
suit? Someone just probably put
on the uniform. An explicit
splaining okay, this is how a
rocket works. This is why it was
a rocket. It's like they just
Oh, no, no, no, no, no. Let me
explain how this works. People
we have proofs. Yeah, that
summit that kind of gets snowed
under that. Was Biden seriously
thinking that he would have some
kind of summit that wouldn't be
disturbed by I don't know a
rocket.
John C Dvorak: The rocket attack
took place. This is all very
convenient. By the way. Yeah.
The rocket attack took place
while he was in the air. Yeah,
he had already the summers were
all arranged. Yeah. So he's
gonna meet here and there's
gonna go to Jordan who's gonna
meet this guy and that guy. And
so do you ever?
Adam Curry: Ever somewhat clip?
John C Dvorak: No. Well, I don't
I haven't.
Adam Curry: I have an angle
somewhat clip. Just explain who
was supposed to be there. It
might be helpful.
John C Dvorak: Okay, because
because I got angle stuff. Yeah,
Adam Curry: I'm tied into my
thesis. You're driving, you're
driving. I just want I'm
John C Dvorak: only driving so
far, then you're gonna have to,
you are holding
Adam Curry: on to the wheel
right now. Do not take your
hands off at Stevie. Just Just a
little background, because I
thought this was this was not
well explained anywhere. But of
course, Richard Engel, did I
want to
Unknown: briefly turn to
Richard, is that along the west
bank there on this issue? That
was not because of this hospital
explosion at the complex, the
hospital complex in Gaza. This
this plan to meet with the
leaders of Egypt, the
Palestinian Authority, as well
as the King of Jordan fell
apart.
John C Dvorak: Do you notice
Hold on a second. Do you notice
they all call it an explosion?
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yes, instead of
attack or rocking?
Adam Curry: Because that's the
message they've been given.
They're totally see, by
John C Dvorak: the way, I should
mention as you play this clip,
I'm gonna have no I have backup
clip to prove it. NBC is all in
on the fact that Israel did the
bombing, oh, MSNBC is
Adam Curry: off the hook with us
Unknown: plan to meet with the
leaders of Egypt, the
Palestinian Authority, as well
as the King of Jordan fell
apart. And the art of that
meeting, Richard was to try to
stop this from becoming a wider
conflict in the middle of so we
have before the President
speaks. What are the prospects
of that now?
Well, now? Well, it
was a disaster. They were
supposed to be this peace summit
with US allies, Mahmoud Abbas,
the moderate leader of the
Palestinians, in contrast to
Hamas, the leader of Egypt, the
King of Jordan, but after this
hospital attack, the the those
in attendance decided, in their
words that it would not be
productive to to hold the
summit. But
Adam Curry: that's interesting,
because you hear you hear angle
clearly saying not explosion
after this hospital attack. So
he is definitely not leaving any
room for it to be a Hamas failed
rocket launch. So there's
backing up your NBC thesis,
Unknown: Palestinians felt that
they could not be there. We had
Mahmoud Abbas, walk out of this
meeting leave Jordan that they
could not be seen standing next
to President Biden, who's done
nothing but support Israel give
a full personal support
expressing support of the United
States is giving military
support to Israel sending
weapons here there are US
military advisors on the ground.
These leaders felt it this time
after this incident which as
Kelly was describing are under
disputed circumstances couldn't
be there sitting next to the
President.
Adam Curry: Hey man wasn't NBC
owned by GE at one point am I am
I am I mistaken that no you're
not mistaken at all. Yeah,
because they would not have done
this this report back when GE
owned them. I wouldn't think so.
No Military Industrial Complex
company Corporation. All right.
Back to your thesis I'm sorry I
just needed to
John C Dvorak: do you want to
interrupt all you can I just to
go and I did takes me a little
bit aside. I want to play I want
to jump to clips there and I'm
gonna go to this one because you
just play that clip jump. That
clip. Jump in the clip. This is
the hospital NBC take side with
Jordan.
Adam Curry: Yes, I got it here.
I got I got it
Unknown: today. And now let's
see Egypt's president will allow
20 trucks of aid into Gaza. What
he would do is open the gate The
plan summit with Arab leaders in
Jordan was scrapped after the
hospital explosion and the
announcement that Palestinian
leader Abbas would not attend.
Was there important work though
that didn't get done the fact
that summit didn't take place?
A lot of important work. I mean,
we all did. The only item in the
agenda right now is to stop this
this madness and stop the
killing that civilians are
paying the utmost price.
Tonight, I spoke with Jordans
Foreign Minister Ayman Safadi as
you know President Biden, the US
they take the position that this
was not an Israeli strike, but
the result of other Palestinian
militants. Do you believe that
to be the case?
Sir, nobody's buying that that
narrative in this part of the
world the the reality does
really harm us army is not very
credible in this part of the
world as well. The only way that
people would entertain a
different narrative is if there
is an independent international
inquiry into into into into the
tragedy that has happened with
impeccable evidence that it was
it was not Israel.
Adam Curry: Yes. And in the blue
helmets, we need an
investigation.
John C Dvorak: Go to this clip
now, which is hospital video
timestamp.
Adam Curry: Oh, yes. Oh, yeah.
Unknown: President Biden's in
Israel hours after Palestinian
officials accused Israel of
killing at least 500 people at
Gaza's athlete Baptist Hospital
and an airstrike. In addition to
treating sick and wounded
patients. The hospital was
acting as a refuge for displaced
Gazans fleeing Israel's
unrelenting attacks. This is
Mohammed Al Naka, a doctor at
the hospital.
lumea Munna Musa there was no
warning before the hospital was
targeted. There were about 3000
people who were taking shelter
here while we were working at
the hospital and without any
warning there on 6:30pm. The
hospital was targeted by
shelling. We didn't know what it
was, but we found out what it
can do after it targeted
children who were cut into
pieces.
guises Health Ministry said
Israel told the hospital that
had sent warning strikes one day
before the deadly explosion. The
UN has called for an immediate
humanitarian ceasefire amidst
international condemnation over
the attack. Israel's denied
responsibility blaming a
Palestinian Islamic Jihad
rocket. Israeli officials appear
to have deleted a video posted
on social media showing
Palestinian rockets being fired
after realizing the timestamp on
the footage did not match up
with the hospital attack.
Adam Curry: Again this whatever
you do, make sure you do
forensic investigations on this
hospital attack. Please, let's
keep that go on people. This is
good keep everybody occupied and
John C Dvorak: less billing on
this one more along this lines
along these lines and then I
want to add one comment and I
want to get to the
Adam Curry: clips. I'm ready.
I'm waiting for you. Hospital to
Biden
John C Dvorak: canceled opinion.
Unknown: A planned trip to
Jordan as part of President
Biden's visit to the Middle East
was cancelled in the wake of the
hospital bombing. Biden said he
was outraged by the attack which
constitutes a war crime but
sided with Israel as he made
remarks alongside Prime Minister
Benjamin Netanyahu earlier
today.
I'm deeply saddened and outraged
by the explosion at the hospital
and Gaza yesterday. And based on
what I've seen, it appears as
though it was done by the other
team not.
Many have pointed out that
militant groups and Palestine do
not have the firepower to level
a massive building. Israel has a
history of lying about its
responsibility against
Palestinian civilians, including
the murder of Palestinian
American journalist Shireen a
black lab last year, which it
initially blamed on
Palestinians. Israel apologized
a year after her death man did
Adam Curry: Amy just say those
Jews be lying? Is that what she
just said? Wow. Yeah,
John C Dvorak: well, he had
cutters lurking in that
operation
Adam Curry: gutter got her get
it right. Gutter gutter. Yeah.
All right. Take us back to the
Okay. So
John C Dvorak: let's go to now
want to go to let's go to that
this is my thesis is I've known
to begin with 12345 clips, which
kind of indicate that we are we
sent the two carrier groups
Strike Forces strike force to
the areas we are going to end
this the last two on the list of
the of the West Clarke seven are
Lebanon, Lebanon
Adam Curry: and Iran, Iran and
we have we have already prepared
everything else right. We've got
every other one including so
more
John C Dvorak: or less.
Adam Curry: Syria, Syria.
John C Dvorak: Come on, into
Syria. It which brings us back
to those hospitals for now. Who
benefited from the hospital
strike? Who bent up that's what
you maybe logically fear who did
the hospital strike by figuring
out who benefited okay. And and
on the surface it seems as if
the beneficiary what are the
Arabs because they get to use it
as a talking point? Yes,
Adam Curry: like they killed
children. Right.
John C Dvorak: But on the other
hand, if Israel doesn't want any
peace whatsoever, and they've
been talking about saber
rattling about Iran the whole
time, wouldn't it make more
sense for them to do it let the
Arabs you know chirp about it
and then meanwhile, plan to
trigger Iran into doing
something stupid. So we says we
got to strike forces there we
have to now we we the United
States now have to put boots on
the ground? Or is there anyone
into who would indicate this
kind of get me to give us a
heads up because we look for him
for kind of information that
comes from the sources? Let's go
to Richard Engel one Oh, I'm
Adam Curry: sorry. I was
starting with Richard angle one.
Yes. Here we go. spook a boy.
Unknown: Nice. The explosion
that has shaken the Middle East
New Video shows that deadly
explosion at a hospital in Gaza
City that reportedly killed
hundreds and sparked protests
from Iran to Yemen, to Lebanon,
where demonstrators directed
their anger against the United
States, Israel's main backer.
Security forces in Beirut used
water cannons and tear gas to
disperse crowds outside the US
Embassy. The United States
pulled out of it scores in the
Middle East, but now could be
heading back into work. In the
West Bank, Palestinians today
dragged out the barricades and
slung rocks at Israeli soldiers.
There weren't many, mostly
teenagers, Israeli troops kept
their distance. But when the
stone throwers got too close to
soldiers opened fire, sending
medical crews rushing in. And
here's one more injured being
taken away. Israelis are picking
them off with what appears to be
rubber bullets at this stage. No
one was seriously injured here
today. But a new generation of
Palestinians is taking to the
streets. While Israel and Hamas
are blaming each other for the
hospital explosion. A new
Palestinian uprising could be
starting today. Our crew filmed
at the Gaza hospital site. And
so families collecting what they
could from the debris.
Adam Curry: All right, you rang
your bell twice, a
John C Dvorak: couple of hints
there. There's going to be hit
there using rubber bullets. Now
was it for time being as a hint
before that was there's going to
be a wider war but he gets a
little more specific here and
clipped to
Unknown: Iran, which backs both
Hamas and Hezbollah is working
to fan the rage even further
Fanning. Ron's President calling
on Muslim nations to isolate
Israel, impose an oil embargo
and bring revenge.
Richer the size of those crowds
you're seeing does say something
about the impact of this
hospital explosion.
It may be that we're not
millions of people on the
streets across the Arab world.
But I can tell you, Lester,
there are real and growing
concerns here that this is
headed to the REIT toward a
regional war, Lester,
Adam Curry: regional war
John C Dvorak: in the region. So
now we go to we go to the clip
that's there. I have a bunch of
clips about all the protests all
over the place. Yes, he's the
one that relates to this this
thesis protests in Iran.
Adam Curry: Yes. And this has
been going on protests in Iran,
the whole country.
Unknown: Yes. So also protests
against Israel and the US in all
major cities across Iran.
President Abraham Lacey spoke at
a rally in Tehran, where he
warned the situation in Gaza
risks spiraling out of control,
and said aid must be allowed in
Tulsa Jabari, has there
been a day of solidarity with
the Palestinian people across
Iran as a number of rallies took
place in all the major cities
across the country. It was
declared a Day of Mourning by
the government and in the
demonstrations here taking place
in Tehran. The Iranian President
Ibrahim Bracy, made an
appearance and delivered a
speech during which he condemned
the Israeli aggression. And he
also blamed the United States.
Adam Curry: And they raised the
Black Flag, Black Flag but the
Black Flag
John C Dvorak: didn't get to
black.
Adam Curry: Oh, yeah, they
raised the Black Flag. Yeah,
that means it's time to go
crazy.
John C Dvorak: So they go crazy.
And they said that, you know,
they, they want they want us to
You know, the Palestinians have
got to get support, they gotta
get relief and stuff has got to
go in there. And so there's been
hemming and hawing and now
they're working on the road,
they still haven't gotten that
clear. And all of this is going
on. And it seems to be a very
triggering thing about the fact
that we're really not doing
anything for the Gaza people.
And we're maybe not doing it on
purpose just to get these
Iranians worked up. We really do
this is a war that's got to
happen have to happen. And
here's the unreported this story
is unreported in the mainstream
media. And it makes zero sense
unless you're trying to cause
trouble. This was the unreported
story about one of the vetoes
that we did, and you went away.
This was great,
Unknown: while insisting they
were working to get aid into
Gaza, those against the United
States standing alone blocked
the Security Council from
passing a resolution that would
do just that. And
Adam Curry: our ambassador to
the United Nations. I forget her
name. She's just sitting back
like, raise my hand. I got a
veto here going on. Did you see
that? She wasn't like engaged.
You're just leaning back? Yep,
I'm against and we got a veto.
Unknown: The US Ambassador
insisted that the draft was
incomplete.
The United States is
disappointed this resolution
made no mention of Israel's
rights of self defense, like
every nation in the world.
Israel has the inherent right of
self defense, as reflected in
article 51 of the UN Charter.
The resolution did condemn Hamas
as October 7 attack and the
taking of civilian hostages, as
well as demanding pauses in the
fighting for aid deliveries.
After several days of
negotiations, 12 council members
voted for it. Many pointing out
that civilians, humanitarian
workers and medical facilities
must be protected under
international humanitarian law.
John C Dvorak: You know, she
blocked it, because it's already
in the UN Charter that
everyone's has a right to self
defense. But it had to be
reiterated in this in this
proposal. Are you kidding me? So
for it's it's really it's a
technicality. Yes. So she puts a
veto in for that reason, right?
I don't have this clip. But
right afterwards, the British,
the Brazilian guy who put this
forward, he went on and on and
on about how well, you know,
this thing was researched this
this proposal. And the fact that
the United States is the United
States stood alone to veto it is
just a triggering mechanism.
Now, I do have the one, which
indicates to me that we're going
to war with Iran if we can,
Adam Curry: yes, we need now
some more. Well, we'll get to
that in a minute. Yes,
John C Dvorak: something more
has to happen. But it's
obviously in the cards. And this
brings us back to the west
Clarke seven, and the Trump
memo, where the preparation for
the Iranian attack has already
been in play. They did it took
place during the Trump
administration, and he has a
copy of
Adam Curry: it without his
knowledge.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, it was.
It's not like that. So the only
thing that's the kind of a
kicker is not much of a backup
of this, but the Russians caught
wind of what we're up to. And so
they tried, they're trying to
pull a kind of a fast one is the
way we do it. And this is the
unreported USA veto. A do this
clip, too.
Unknown: Many members of the
Security Council vowed to keep
working towards consensus and a
resolution. But Russia taking a
page from the west playbook
suggested they bring the issue
to the General Assembly instead
for a vote where no country has
veto power.
Adam Curry: All right. All
right. Cute. Way to go. Well,
I'm so not to move back a little
bit. Before the bumbling Biden
showed up the other team, which
the other team is very annoying,
I could probably obsess over
that choice of descriptor for a
long time. You know, what is it
red team? The blue team, you
know, what does that even mean?
Why'd you use that? What's wrong
with you? You Oh, man, this is
not sorry to be ageist. But
that's nuts. But last week on 60
minutes, our president was much
more coherent. They got him
jacked up. Maybe it was the
other guy, I don't know. But he
had a message for Iran last
week.
Unknown: Rarely does a president
confront so much peril, the
catastrophe in Israel, the war
in Ukraine and no help from a
paralyzed Congress. Mr. Biden
will be at one next month and he
has said just that when he's
tired, his lifelong stutter can
creep back in there about people
that gotcha President 2 million
people trapped about half of
them are children. Are you
asking Israel to To establish a
humanitarian corridor in that
area or get humanitarian
supplies, yes, our
team is talking to them about
that. And whether there can be a
safe zone. We're also talking
with the Egyptians, whether
there is an outlet to get these
children and and women out into
out of the hat area at this
moment that
you would like to see a
humanitarian corridor that
allows some of the 2 million
Gazans out of the area. Yes, you
would like to see humanitarian
supplies brought into Gaza? Yes.
So you do not agree with the
Israeli total siege of the Gaza
Strip.
I'm confident that Israel is
going to act under the major the
rules of war. There's a
standards that democratic
institutions and countries go
by. And so I'm, I'm confident
that there's going to be an
ability for the innocents in
Gaza to be able to have access
to medicine and food and water.
There's limited fighting already
on the northern Israeli border.
And I wonder what is your
message to Hezbollah, and its
backer Iran.
Adam Curry: Set up?
Unknown: Don't Don't Don't
Don't,
don't come across the border
don't escalate this war.
Adam Curry: All right. So when
you say don't that means Come
on, do it, do it. We want to go
we need that. We need it to
start. Come on, do it by saying
don't. And then the most
remarkable, most remarkable
statement from the President and
you say he's not that jacked up.
This is jacked up for this Joe
right now. I mean, the guy was
dead brain dead in Israel.
John C Dvorak: I have three
clips. I want to play Wait, let
me play this. No, not now. I
want to play the Biden in Israel
clips when we get the chance.
Unknown: Wow, yeah, we'll get
there are the wars in Israel and
Ukraine more than the United
States can
take on at the same time the
United States of America got the
most powerful nation in the
history of the world and the
history of the world?
Adam Curry: Oh, the history of
the world. Oh, part of these
Unknown: wars in Israel and
Ukraine relate to the safety of
the American people.
Overwhelmingly, they relate. For
example, in Ukraine, one of my
objectives was to prevent Putin
who has committed war crimes
himself, who, from being able to
occupy an independent country
that borders NATO allies, and is
on the Russian border. Imagine
what happens now, if he were
able to succeed. Have you ever
known a major war in Europe we
didn't get sucked into. We don't
want that to happen. We want to
make sure those democracies are
sustained. And Ukraine is
critical. And making sure that
happens.
Why do you feel so strongly?
What does Israel mean to you?
Adam Curry: It's almost like,
like you're asking a seven year
old What does Israel mean to
you? To me? Totally
Unknown: Jews have been
subjected to abuse, prejudice
and attempt to wipe them out for
over 1000 years. For me, it's
about decency, respect, honor,
dignity. It's just simply wrong.
Wrong, wrong. Wrong. It violates
every religious principle I have
in every way and every single
principle My father taught me.
Adam Curry: Yeah, bringing the
old dead. It's, this is what's
so interesting. We have a
situation now where we are
funding Nazis in Ukraine, and
we're caught. I mean, seriously,
yeah, that's it, you know, it's
like, it's the dichotomy is
crazy the way but what we're
seeing, and this is important in
light of him being at one
etcetera, and generally the
octogenarians in in our
government, and many older
people around the world. This is
generational. And I think Israel
has lost the moral war. I mean,
this is what you're seeing that
I'm not saying it's right or
wrong. But and this probably
comes back to the loneliness op
that we identified. Hey, man, I
got something like that. There's
more victims. I can go out on
the street and I can protest.
It's like Black Lives Matter all
over again. We go pro Palestine
because Screw you, Israel. This
is this is a problem that I
think the Biden administration
and probably all governments are
not identifying properly. Your
people do not agree with this
anymore. The vocal people, the
people that you sent out for
George Floyd it.
John C Dvorak: Yep. All over the
world. People all over it
exactly
Adam Curry: the same people.
Exactly the same people. Now on
top of that, I'm sorry. We do
not have the fighting force. I
don't even think you know, wo
IDF. They're the best effort.
No, I don't think so. They're
not used to this. What Hamas and
Hezbollah would they have they
have been training in real war
real they fearless killing for a
long time. We don't have
manpower. We don't we're AI come
on all of a sudden we have we
have ammunition. We didn't have
it for Ukraine. We don't have
it. The Israel wanted 3000 Iron
Dome 50k a pop rockets. Now we
got 300 We're out of ammo. We
don't have enough people. You
know, we may look badass. I
think you know, we got a couple
1000 people in Syria looks
great. But we really don't have
I don't think we don't have the
weaponry in place. And the
training in guerrilla warfare or
the urban warfare. I'm just not
so sure, Mr. President, that
we're irrational? I don't think
so. And I really doubt the
Israelis. capacity at this
point. I'm not so sure that we
can win anything. Yeah.
John C Dvorak: I think it's a
valid position.
Adam Curry: Yeah. What are you
going to do? Is Israel going to
drop a nuke? Well, that does not
going to work. You blow yourself
up. There's going to be no
nukes, I'll tell you that right
now. No nukes are going to
happen. So you can stop worrying
about that. But we need it then
the play is simple. We need
Hezbollah, Hezbollah to attack
in the north, then we can go
straight after Iran. And it'll
be interesting to see what we
do.
John C Dvorak: We some is going
to happen, at least from the
looks of things. I have liquid
Democracy Now clip, although I
prefer nothing, you know, and
Adam Curry: we don't want
anything happening. Of course,
we're anti war. This is
Professor Rashid Khalidi on
Democracy Now
Unknown: spawned to President
Biden sitting down with the
Prime Minister Netanyahu today
and saying the other team did it
attacking the hospital and go on
from there.
The President has bonded the
United States, Israel, the hip
since very soon after this
horrible escalation started. In
so doing, he's made the United
States responsible in the eyes
of the world for everything. And
this is the latest example of
that. He's basically read from
an Israeli teleprompter, as he
seems to do routinely, when
anything relating to the Middle
East comes up. It's almost as if
his lines are scripted in Tel
Aviv at the Israeli Defense
Ministry, where their
disinformation headquarters are
located.
Adam Curry: I should probably
add one more thing to this just
so people understand the
dynamics of Israel in the United
States, AIPAC. A AIPAC is what
is it the American Israeli?
Something? AIPAC is very
important and all
John C Dvorak: it's a big gun.
They have a big convention.
Adam Curry: And the convention
for Republicans specifically is
very
John C Dvorak: pretty No, it's
across the board who met Schumer
is always there speaking.
Adam Curry: So here's how it
works. AIPAC, very well funded
by Israel, Israel, that American
Jews or whatever people might
say is by Israel. And if you are
not all in with what a PACs
agenda is, they will primary
you. That's the threat. And
money drives all politics all
around the world, and certainly
in the United States. So, you
know, Biden has to do what the
AIPAC agenda is all politicians
have to do with it particularly,
it could not be a better time in
an election year coming up. You
better do it, otherwise you will
lose power. And that's what
they're all afraid of. They
don't really care about Israelis
or Palestinians or Americans or
Iranians. They're insane. All of
them. We've We've let a whole
politicians go insane and busy
work. And if they're not it only
take one year, one year in DC
and you're part of the gang
John C Dvorak: get more from
that guy. I had that clip.
Adam Curry: I do. I do. About
not that guy. I have. I think
actually this we've had NBC I
want to play a few CBS CIA
broadcasting systems. I have
three small trifecta. Regarding
this, this latest frack is
joining us
Unknown: at the table is
Margaret Brennan. She's chief
foreign affairs correspondent
and moderator of face nation.
Margaret really glad to have you
here today
Adam Curry: because she's an
expert at reading prompter.
John C Dvorak: So much to unpack
why she Yes, exactly
Adam Curry: what she's done.
expert because this is the
morning show. It's the morning
show. All right, let's get
really deep into it with
Margaret Brennan who read let's
talk journalists talking to
journalists. Yes. That's when
the messaging is always
considered
John C Dvorak: a faux pa in
journalism technically
considered a faux pas.
Adam Curry: Yes. You think this
is journalism? Margaret, really?
John C Dvorak: In this case?
Yes. That even that is the
newsreader talking to
newsreader. Yes, I'm
Adam Curry: going to introduce
you with the script. And you can
read the script. Go ahead.
Hello, Margaret. I'm so happy
you're here. You are the expert
here today. Yes. Glad to be here
to unpack
Unknown: on this. The blame game
is underway. Who was responsible
for the bombing of the hospital?
Oh, very
John C Dvorak: good. Get it got
me interrupting mode. Yes. Okay.
When an unpacked becomes such a
universal phrase. Have you
noticed that? It shows up all
the time? I was hearing it this
morning. Yeah. unpack what
you're on packet. I think we can
pack I think we
Adam Curry: should say unzip it.
You know, that would be much
cooler. We will use unzip it.
Unzip that archive for me. Do
you have winds are
Unknown: to hopefully bring
sides together? What challenges?
What additional problems? Does
this cause for the President of
the United States at this time?
Adam Curry: Oh, let's go
straight to politics.
Unknown: Whatever the facts are,
it's the perception that matters
and the perception in the
streets of Jordan in Egypt, I am
a journalist, facts don't
matter. West Bank, United States
saying it stands by his wife.
Adam Curry: She literally said
that look, but who cares? Who
cares? What facts are let's
listen to let's unpack that
again.
Unknown: This time, whatever the
facts are. It's the perception
that matters. And the perception
in the streets of Jordan and
Egypt in the West Bank is that
the United States saying it
stands by Israel without
question means that it is
allowing for continued civilian
casualties, not just with that
hospital bombing, but it is seen
in the broader context of this
bombardment. They talk about
bombing bombing that's been
going on for 11 days now. And
certainly it became politically
untenable for the King of
Jordan, to host the president,
the United States. And that's
pretty extraordinary. Given
Israel and Jordan and Egypt,
they have peace treaties. This
is one of our closest allies in
the Middle East. And because of
the uproar in the streets, it
just became impossible to host
the president. So that shows the
level of complexity that this
mistake perhaps was an errant
strike. Was it on whose part
exactly somebody military claims
it was Islamic Jihad, a militant
group that's smaller than Hamas,
but operative there?
Adam Curry: This is this Hello,
new player, new player, the
Palestinian Islamic Jihad new
player is being introduced by
CBS, which is not just No,
John C Dvorak: everybody's been
talking about that group. None.
Yes. I have the clip that I
played earlier, from NBC.
Unknown: But this is not present
this morning when he said the
other team is responsible. He
didn't say what that was based
on. Is that a US intelligence
assessment? Is that accepting
the Israeli military's version
of I love
Adam Curry: the guy in the
background? Oh, cool, cool.
whole
Unknown: team is responsible. He
didn't say what that was based
on. Is that a US intelligence
assessment? Is that accepting
the Israeli military's version
of events? And so could that
escalate things? Yes,
absolutely. And that is part of
the concern here is how do you
win back? The public? Holly's
piece was just showing her the
political problems that the
Prime Minister of Israel has his
people want retribution for this
horrific attack that happened.
But as you're seeing with the
president there with the
Secretary of State with the
Secretary of Defense, with all
these lawmakers going, there are
quiet questions being asked
behind closed doors to the
Israeli government saying Prime
Minister Netanyahu, what is your
plan for what comes next?
Adam Curry: Ah, okay. So CBS
knows that there's quiet
conversations and questions
going on in the background
behind closed doors. Do you
think it
Unknown: was necessary for
President Biden to be there at
this particular time? Well, I, I
was, you know, talking with
officials last night saying, Can
you call it off yet the planes
and road they were stuck. It had
already been announced, even
after the Arab summit was called
off because President Abbas had
to return to the West Bank,
there are protests against him.
And then in Jordan and Egypt,
you see these protests going to
Israel, for some will look like
the United States is standing by
even if this is an open question
of vulnerabilities, very
Adam Curry: serious problems
that were to be discussed at the
Arab summit involving
humanitarian aid and access to
each of those remain. Are they
being discussed on the
sidelines, any progress that can
be made?
Unknown: Well, the President
will be calling some of those
leaders as well. He can't be
seen standing beside them
because of their own political
issues. But you know, Secretary
Blinken spent the better part of
the last week shoveling around
the Middle East and came back to
Israel to pres Prime Minister
Netanyahu to get this agreement
to allow in any aid even though
it's very restricted, what is
being allowed in VA that we
vetoed, if any, is allowed. And
for some, it appears that this
visit was collateral for that,
because Tony Blinken and the
Secretary of State was by Behind
closed doors for nine hours,
with the Israeli government
trying to get this agreement to
allow in aid, but
Adam Curry: obviously we're the
most powerful country in the
world. We're the best. We
control everything except to Oh,
crap. We didn't control that
part. last clip.
Unknown: What if anything, can
you tell us about diplomatic
efforts to release the hostages,
we saw the mother with a picture
of her daughter who has now
become the face of the hostages,
he or Gail, I've been talking to
sources in the Middle East here
in the United States, people who
work with hostage families,
there had been some hope leading
up to this bombing. And this
morning I am told Hamas is
signaling that it is not
possible for them at this moment
to go through with any kind of
release. Now that's if you
believe that the diplomatic
efforts to date actually we're
going to be successful was
Adam Curry: this laugh for Moshe
was was just so funny, was so
fun to go through.
John C Dvorak: Where was that?
Where was that placed? Again,
Unknown: it's possible for them
at this moment to go through
with any kind of release. Now,
that's if you believe that the
diplomatic efforts to date
actually, we're going to be
successful. So this
John C Dvorak: diplomatic
efforts she thinks is bullcrap
we all we all know who she
talking to her sources? Yes, in
the Middle East is
Unknown: difficult. And it also
Carol's other diplomacy, very
complicated, very layered,
Adam Curry: very layered,
John C Dvorak: layered, very
Adam Curry: layered. Well,
that's why he had to unpack it
because it's layered. It's a tar
ball. All right, back to you,
Bob.
John C Dvorak: Let's go with a
couple of these protest clips
because there's one it might be
good, just world protests on Al
Jazeera.
Unknown: There have been
protests taking place around the
world in support of the
Palestinian people.
demonstrators gathered outside
the US Embassy in Tokyo in
Japan. They were chanting USA,
shame on you. In Tokyo, police
fired water cabinet protesters
on the streets of Istanbul 1000s
are gathered in front of the
Israeli consulate. Demonstrators
in India describe what's going
on in Palestine as a genocide.
And members of a Muslim
organization gathered in Chennai
and in the Philippines. People
carried Palestinian flags and
candles and protest the Israeli
airstrike on that hospital in
Gaza. Well, the bottom below is
that a demonstration in the
southern Philippines they're
John C Dvorak: talking about the
Philippines gas. It's
unbelievable. The guy pretty
good organizational skills
better than ours. Anyway,
onwards. Well,
Adam Curry: I mean, it's it's
that you know, this is I think
it's probably a lot of the trans
Maoism that has crept in every
way
John C Dvorak: I 100%.
Adam Curry: I get to see if you
say a for your one 100% I get to
say You bet.
John C Dvorak: I never finished
this. I never got to the tea.
Oh, okay. Mobilization
Unknown: gathered in Chennai.
And in the Philippines, people
carried Palestinian flags and
lit candles and protest at the
Israeli airstrike on that
hospital in Gaza. Well, Barnaby
Lowe is at a demonstration in
Marawi in the southern
Philippines and joins us live
Barnaby. So what are protesters
telling you? And why are they so
angry about events in Gaza?
It's definitely a huge anger
here as demonstrated by the huge
crowd right behind me. And it's
not just here all over Morocco
is city. There are banners and
posters saying Free Palestine
and Israeli occupation. This
protest, definitely primarily
sparked by that attack on the
hospital in Gaza on Tuesday, but
their calls their condemnation
go beyond that. Just just that
one incident. And in fact, they
go beyond this week long
hostilities in Gaza. atrocities
they say by Israeli forces. They
say they want an end to Israeli
occupation because they
understand that people in Gaza
have been living under constant
bombardment. And they have been
living under decades of blockade
by by Israel. And so they want a
free Palestine, not just in
Gaza, but also in the West Bank.
Adam Curry: All right. I have a
protest clip from ABC. This is
about protests across the Middle
East. And they all start off
perfectly fine.
Unknown: In Beirut today, we
witnessed protesters rushing the
American embassy security forces
pushing them back using tear
gas, water hoses and rubber
bullets. Amid the chaos we take
cover. As you can see protesters
pushing back against security
forces started by throwing rocks
launching fireworks. It's been a
constant push and pull here
between security forces and the
protesters who were trying to
push up against the American
Embassy. They say they're
outraged at Israel's bombardment
of Palestinian citizens and the
US support for it. Ross the
region fury drops Israeli
government and its ally the
United States now at a boiling
point from Iran to Jordan. A
deadly explosion at the hospital
in Gaza further and flaming
demonstrations, Israel insisting
it was not responsible. The US
saying intelligence backs that
up. But for protesters here,
that's evidence. The Israeli us
alliance is toxic. Because it's
supported in the West Bank, the
anger growing in Ramallah ABCs
Matt Gutman among the
protesters, downtown Ramallah
This is a protest of unity the
rallying in support of the
Moscow support Palestinian
fighters. People telling me here
that
those demonstrations quickly
spreading across the West Bank
protesters clashing with Israeli
soldiers as the region smolders.
Adam Curry: I mean, it's these
demonstrations are and these
people who go they have no
historical context, they really
don't. Maybe Muslims have some
built in historical context,
generational context that
they've been given throughout
the years and every everyone's
toxified their children. This
will come to a head one way or
another in the Netherlands. In
the Netherlands. The protests
have a slogan Hamas Hamas, the
Yoda on a cos which translates
to Hamas Hamas put the Jews on
the gas as in gas. I mean, this
is Oh, really? Oh, yeah. In
Holland. But okay, it's all
right. But let's bring in some
show. Hey, yeah. What are you
gonna do we need a show business
angle. All right. Let's
Unknown: switch gears now to
Alicia Keys, and the posts that
sparked a social media backlash.
Alicia was criticized for this
Instagram post asking quote,
what would you do if you weren't
afraid of anything? I've had my
eyes on paragliding Oh, many
user said the word paragliding
was both triggering sensitive
giving there used by Hamas
during the October 7 attack on
an Israeli Music Festival. The
massacre claimed nearly 300
innocent lives and led to the
capture of several hostages.
Some even accused Alisha of
showing sympathy toward the
terror organization by wearing
green the same color as the
Hamas flag. Someone who came to
Alisha is defense. Her former
manager guy Oseary the Israeli
American took to Instagram
saying quote I spoke to Alicia
and she was horrified to learn
what the word implied and
immediately took it down
Adam Curry: rather this is where
we're at this is where
John C Dvorak: the old brother
part of the show
Adam Curry: if I was President
right now I would have an
executive order shut off the
internet shut up
John C Dvorak: shop would have
done it years ago but that's
Shut up why
Adam Curry: was shut down social
media right now.
John C Dvorak: This was done
protests. Let's do this one. We
this one was poorly covered. I
thought by the American
president that a Al Jazeera did
a great job in the protest in
DC.
Adam Curry: Oh, yeah. This was
interesting. In
Unknown: Washington, DC
protesters from anti war group
Jewish Voice for Peace have
staged a sitting inside a
congressional building.
Adam Curry: This is what I mean
by generational this is exactly
what I mean. The demonstrators
are calling
Unknown: for an immediate
ceasefire amid the rising death
toll in Gaza. Some protesters
are wearing shirts with a word
not in our name. Tactical Hanes
sent us this report from Capitol
Hill.
Protesters are taking the pro
Palestinian cause to the US
Capitol here in the cannon House
Office Building. This is where
members of Congress and their
staff, many of them have their
offices. This happened earlier
in the day. I'd say about five
dozen maybe six dozen activists
wearing T shirts say not in our
name juice, a ceasefire now came
into cannon chanting, they knew
they would be arrested. Now this
all started at a protest just a
few blocks away earlier in the
day. More than 1000 people are
really all faiths came out. But
I did talk to one gentleman he
said his grant his grandparents
survived the Holocaust helped
build Israel. But now he says
you need to come out because he
does not believe the people, the
people of his own religion are
doing to the Palestinians.
I see my job as carrying on
their legacy as Jews who
fundamentally see their role as
standing up for stateless and
oppressed people all throughout
the world. And I see no better
way to do that than fighting for
peace and a ceasefire in Gaza
today.
Adam Curry: Yeah, this is
amazing what's going on? I mean,
even amongst the pro, you know,
the Save Palestine protests. If
you look at if you really look
at some of the pictures, there's
a lot of Jewish groups they're
Jews for Palestine, they got
signs they're intermingled. The
generational fact is that the
young people who have have no
context at
John C Dvorak: all they are no
because they weren't given a
decent education for starters,
and they but they
Adam Curry: also that people
don't want war anymore. The
people don't
John C Dvorak: just this if this
war cranks up the way they're
trying to do it with Iran, I
think the backlash is going to
be huge, unexpected, because if
you're a Democrat strategist,
you're thinking, what are we
going to do to keep Biden in
office because he's going to run
whether you like it or not. Well
make him a war president or
nobody ever votes a war
president out of office. George
W. Bush is a good example.
Adam Curry: You know, this. I
hate to say this, now would be a
perfect time for Biden to die.
That's, that's the only thing
left that would make this chaos
complete. Well, President
Kamala,
John C Dvorak: President Camela
Well, things aren't bad enough.
Why not? Part two, part two of
this clip is got an interesting
kicker.
Unknown: As we take one more
look is the crowd as they start
to get arrested one by one being
put in zip ties, this is going
to be a misdemeanor, they're
unlikely to face any sort of
jail time, they'll probably pay
a fine. Just to give you a sense
of how different this sentiment
is from those of the elected
officials in these buildings.
There was a resolution by one
representative tasking Joe
Biden, the US president to call
for a ceasefire in Gaza, in all
13 members of Congress agreed.
Al Jazeera at the US Capitol.
John C Dvorak: So call for a
ceasefire in Gaza, which would
be not a bad idea. Seems to me.
Adam Curry: I'm pretty I'm
pretty sure that Hamas in total
John C Dvorak: congressmen and
senators be agreed to this is
um, this is no, they're not
connected.
Adam Curry: There was a Hamas at
some point, I had the clips in
here somewhere, said, you know,
we'll let all the hostages go if
he just stopped firing rockets.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, I don't
believe that to be true. I
Adam Curry: don't believe it
either. But it was a talking
point for a moment there. I have
some some trigger clips. People
just do using triggering
triggering stuff. Sky News. This
is Sky News with former Israeli
Prime Minister Naftali Bennett.
And he goes straight for the
jugular.
Unknown: And what about those
Palestinians in hospital who are
on life support and babies and
incubators?
Adam Curry: Oh, hold on Sky
News. We've got babies and
incubators, turn them up, throw
them out
Unknown: whose life support an
incubator will have to be turned
off because these readings have
cut the power to Gaza?
Are you seriously keep on asking
me about Palestinian civilians?
What's What's wrong with you?
Have you not seen what happened?
We're fighting Nazis. We don't
target them. So the world can
come and bring them anything
they want. If you want to bring
them electricity, I'm not going
to feed electricity or water to
my enemies. If anyone else wants
that's fine. We're not
responsible for this is the
point of
Adam Curry: this is my show. And
I am asking questions your way.
So this is this goes on for
quite a while. But you know,
everything's everything's Nazi
now. Nazi Nazi Nazi. Let's go to
Piers Morgan. Piers Morgan, is
who's this guy by Sam Yousef. I
don't know if he mentions it.
But this is, you know, the
dichotomy between Russia,
Ukraine, ISRAEL PALESTINE,
Unknown: I would say I really
applaud Israel for doing one
thing that no military force in
the word does, because I heard I
heard Ben Shapiro and I heard
Ron DeSantis. And they said,
they said isn't amazing
Adam Curry: that Ben Shapiro is
now on the world stage. With Ron
DeSantis.
John C Dvorak: It doesn't
surprise me he's a hard worker.
He doesn't surprise me at all.
Unknown: Force in the word does,
because I heard I heard Ben
Shapiro and I heard Ron
DeSantis. And they said, they
said Israel is the only military
force in the world that wore
civilians before bombing them. I
mean, how fucking cute. That is
so nice to have them. Because
with this logic, if Russian
troops started warning
Ukrainians before bombing their
houses, were cool with Putin,
right? I mean, okay, habibi. You
have warned them go invade, it's
fine. You have done your job. I
mean, the thing is, and I
understand all and also heard
Ben Shapiro talking about, about
human shields. So you remember
my wife's family? They live in
Gaza. So I asked him, I told him
when Israel give you the nice
warning, the cute warning Does
Hamas force you to stay in your
home so you can be bombed and
use a as as human shields? Does
that mean that every single one
of those civilians will stand in
a obscuring a military target
behind them? Because that's a
lot of weapons. I mean,
harnesses packing? No, it
also doesn't.
Adam Curry: I love these
comparisons.
Unknown: I want to understand
what is the logic of Israel,
carpet bombing Gaza? I mean, if
there is a logic, if it is a
good if this will make Israel
safe, I want to hear the logic.
So if I can understand this
correctly, basically Israel is
doing this to pressure the
Palestinian community in Gaza,
to turn against Hamas. Is that
right? I'm sure that's part of
it. Yes, that's smarter. So this
is exactly what terrorist
organization do because there's
organizations would have no
chance beating the whole nation
in battle. So they terrorize and
they kill the civilians in order
to spread fear and terror so
they can turn against the
government to change their
policy or to resign, you have
just compared Israel with ISIS.
The thing is, this is the
problem. Israel always
victimizes itself. And I have
never seen a victim putting
their oppressor under siege and
bombed and 24/7 Israel wants you
to believe that they are the
victim is beginning with Israel
is so difficult. It's like being
in a relationship with a
narcissistic psychopath. He
fucks you up and then he makes
you think it's your fault.
John C Dvorak: Guys got
opinions. By the way, our
bombing firebombing of the
German cities, especially
Dresden was exactly this course.
Adam Curry: This, this is the
context that people don't have.
This has been going on forever,
all around the world all the
time. And we're being told this.
Now it's this is it. This is
where an End Times It's all over
now.
John C Dvorak: It's like the
hottest day. Yeah. The hottest
day, what a good day for 100
years. Because red hot, hot for
100 years. It's good. It must
have been global warming 100
years ago, what are you telling
me? So we've
Adam Curry: got to shore it all
up now and make sure everybody
understands particular financial
markets? Let's say it's okay.
Don't worry. We got it under
control. We can do this with the
best country in the world. Have
you ever have the history? Let's
bring out Janet Yellen. She is
after all, in charge of our
finances paid Janet, can we
really clean? Really? Can we
really do all this? I mean, we
do we have mass you? Do we have?
Do we have a war fund? Do we
have like a little piggy bank
are something that we can break
to open up for money? Do we have
that? Is there is there that I
know of? I don't think so either
Paul
Unknown: Tudor Jones, the famed
investor was on CNBC this week.
And he said, This is the most
threatening and challenging
geopolitical environment that
I've ever seen. At the same
time, the US is in its weakest
fiscal position since World War
Two, with debt to GDP at 122%.
Can America can the West afford
another war at this time?
I think the answer is
absolutely.
Adam Curry: Absolutely. Bring in
another one. Hey, how about
Taiwan?
Unknown: Can America can the
West afford another war at this
time?
I think the answer is
absolutely. America can
certainly afford to stand with
Israel and to support Israel's
military needs. And we also can
and must support Ukraine in its
struggle against Russia. The
American economy is doing
extremely well.
Adam Curry: I love this. It's
doing extremely well.
Unknown: Inflation has been high
and it's been a concern to
households.
Adam Curry: It's a concern to
households. It's just a little
concern. What's
Unknown: your problem come down
considerably. Oh, at the same
time, we may rise
John C Dvorak: has come down. It
hasn't reversed.
Adam Curry: It has come down
considerably. Look, I mean,
John C Dvorak: you're still
going up. It's cumulative. This
is the one thing that people
don't understand about
inflation. Please. Explain.
Well, if you have an inflation
rate of 10%, and then it drops
to 5%. It's five on top of the
10. It's not but you can say but
a politician was there? Well, we
had it it's gone down 50%
Inflation has gone down 50%.
It's gone down from 10% to 5%,
which means it was 10%, which
you've lost, you've already lost
10% of all your all your value
right there. And then it's
another 5% On top of that, on
top of that, on top of that,
it's
Adam Curry: just a concern. It's
a
John C Dvorak: scam.
Adam Curry: It's just it's just
a concern. It's what people are
talking about around the kitchen
table. It's just a slice
Unknown: of the price of
gasoline. The American economy
is doing extremely well.
Inflation has been high and it's
been a concern to have sold.
It's come down considerably. At
the same time. We As about the
strongest labor market, we've
seen,
Adam Curry: let's just re
explain the labor market, the
labor market and unemployment is
determined by those who have
registered and are willing to
work versus those who are
working. Not all the people who
have given up.
John C Dvorak: Give. The people
have given up as a huge number.
Adam Curry: A huge number shadow
stats.com 50 years.
John C Dvorak: Yes, Shadow
stats.com 3.8%
Unknown: unemployment. And at
the same time, America, the
Biden administration has passed
legislation that is
strengthening our economy in the
years to come. Okay, medium
term. What is it was we have
three historic pieces of
legislation,
Adam Curry: three historic
pieces of legislation, each
about a trillion dollars,
Unknown: bipartisan
infrastructure at the chips, and
some
John C Dvorak: one Republican
voted yes. bipartisan,
bipartisan bipartisan.
Adam Curry: Hey,
Unknown: hey, infrastructure
Adam Curry: is there. How are
the potholes?
John C Dvorak: I don't see. I
mean, they're, they did pave a
section of ADF, north of me, oh,
repaved it, but the reason they
stopped, I mean, it's still not
good to be infrastructure. And
there's all kinds of, you know,
if you want to drive drive
around Berkeley sometime, and I
should put a camera on one of
the cams, you know, is car cam
on my car, and I'll drive some
areas. And without the without
the image stabilization on
you'll see what I'm talking
about.
Adam Curry: I expect you
John C Dvorak: to do this. I'm
going to do it now.
Adam Curry: And make sure you
focus it on that dashboard,
which you claim after 25 years
has still not cracked.
John C Dvorak: Do I take some
photos for you
Adam Curry: know, that's okay.
Unknown: bipartisan
infrastructure at the chips and
science act in the inflation
Reduction Act. And
Adam Curry: the best the
inflation Reduction Act?
John C Dvorak: Yeah. Which is
also the green New Deal. So
that's bull crap.
Unknown: We've seen a burgeoning
of investment, especially in
manufacturing, we have
manufacturing.
Adam Curry: Oh, I'm sorry, I
must have missed all the
manufacturing going on. I
haven't seen any
John C Dvorak: factories go up
around here, of course,
Unknown: in industrial
renaissance in the
Adam Curry: industrial road
here,
Unknown: and we're creating good
jobs, good jobs, for people
who've been who have crossed the
border illegally, don't have a
college education have been
lifted out of Republicans really
economic progress in the United
States. So the United States,
Adam Curry: you know what, those
jobs aren't serving other people
in restaurants,
Unknown: a economy is in a good
place. In terms of the fiscal
situation, I don't know where
122 comes from the US federal
debt to GDP ratio is about 98%
At this point,
Adam Curry: okay. Do you know
that that's, I've heard anything
but a number under 100% debt to
GDP. She's claiming it's 98%. I
thought it was like 110. I've
heard what the guy said 120.
I've heard 160. And she said, I
don't know where that number
comes from. It's about 98%. But
she did say federal, probably
plan some words, got
John C Dvorak: some debts,
weasels, there's something
Weasley about what she said,
yeah,
Unknown: just the fiscal
situation. I don't know where
122 comes from the US federal
debt to federal ratio is about a
percent at this point. And the
interest expense, which is a
more relevant statistic still
remains manageable. Now. It is
true with higher interest rates,
and those higher interest rates
may persist, although that's not
clear.
Adam Curry: Yeah, it's not
clear. Well, it is clear,
because they're gonna go higher.
Powell just had his little chat
today. And it was like, okay,
that's not working. We need to
start print. The President has
an announcement tonight.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, no. show
now. Of course.
Adam Curry: I think it will be
the let's print some money
night. Yes, you're
John C Dvorak: gonna have to
jack him up tonight. There's no
doubt about it. He's going to be
pumped. So he'll be screaming
about dignity.
Adam Curry: I don't think they
you know, he's over jacked. I
don't think they can do it
anymore. It's not working.
John C Dvorak: Well, we're gonna
find out tonight because tonight
tonight if they're going to jack
him with a hotshot, tonight's
the night.
Adam Curry: Tonight's the night.
We're gonna jack him to Jack
him. Well, this I mean, this
will be the speech of his life.
What can he possibly say?
John C Dvorak: Well, I have some
fun Oops, I might have a couple
of clips.
Adam Curry: Do you have him
talking about Golden my hair?
John C Dvorak: Yes, I have that
Adam Curry: clip because I
looked that up. Let's can do you
mind if we play this one first?
John C Dvorak: Well, I will one
is the kicker.
Adam Curry: Okay. We'll do it in
order whatever you want.
John C Dvorak: Let's just go
first, the rambling about peace
Unknown: doctors, too to be
light into the world as though
we're about. What are
Adam Curry: we about?
John C Dvorak: But darkness into
the light? Oh, oh,
Adam Curry: I thought we were
the Doctors of the World. This
into the light into the world
darkness into the light of the
world, the darkness
Unknown: to be light into the
world as it were about,
Adam Curry: oh, we are the
light, the shining light on the
hill. You inspire
Unknown: hope and light for so
many around the world. That's
what the terrorists seek to
destroy.
John C Dvorak: As he noticed a
protests about all these were
inspiring people.
Adam Curry: Yes. Well, he's not.
He's correct. We're inspiring
people to protest. It's all
going according to plan.
Unknown: That's what the
terrorists seek to destroy.
That's what they seek to
destroy. Because they live in
darkness. But not you, not
Israel. Nations of conscious
like the United States and
Israel are not measured solely
by example, or power. were
measured by the power of our
example. That's why it's hard.
Adam Curry: Oh, wow, who wrote
that one? Chat GPT. We're not
measured by our examples of
power. No, we're measured by our
powers of example. This is
unconscious,
Unknown: it United States in
Israel are not measured solely
by the example or power. And
were measured by the power of
our example. And that's why as
hard as it is, must keep
pursuing peace. Must keep
pursuing a path. So that Israel,
the Palestinian people can both
live safely. Is security and
dignity in peace?
Adam Curry: No, that's never
going to happen. Dignity, isn't
it? I mean, every single time
remember president, Bill
Clinton? Oh, yeah. Oh, it's
gonna be great to have peace.
He's gonna be peace. And all we
used to see on television back
in the 70s. Was kids with Sling
shots, but they weren't the
sling shots we had really cool.
Well, yeah, the cool ones like
and they were good at it with
the, you know, like the, the
David's sling shots with. And
that's what we were looking at.
And I always thought, why don't
we give them some good
slingshots. How does that really
work? But those things are cool.
They they and that's all
John C Dvorak: you get a lot of
velocity off of one of those.
Yeah,
Adam Curry: yeah, that's, it's
as far back as I can remember.
John C Dvorak: Well, I'm older
than you. And I can say the same
exact words for 3d
Unknown: the story of Moses
death.
Adam Curry: We're gonna go
biblical here for a second.
John C Dvorak: That's it. That's
why I have to set this up, if
you listen carefully. Key
claims, I think, yes, to have
done something that very few
people have ever done. Read the
Torah. Now why a Catholic boy
would read the Torah is beyond
me. But I think that's what he
says in this clip
Unknown: country, the story of
Moses death. Those who observe
the holiday began reading the
Torah, from the very beginning.
A story of creation reminds us
of two things. First, we get
knocked down, we get back up
again. And we begin to new. And
second, when we're faced with
tragedy and loss, we must go
back to the beginning to
remember who we are who we are,
we are all human beings, created
an image of God with dignity,
humanity, the purpose?
Adam Curry: No, but the Torah is
the Old Testament.
John C Dvorak: Dignity, the
tourism. Dettori is bigger than
the Old Testament is more to
attend just the Old Testament.
Notice was taken from the Torah,
as far as I know, I'm not
Jewish. Right? So let's go to
the clip. You are so anxious,
Adam Curry: but it's Hold on a
second. It's it's a cup. It's
several. It's like four or five
books from the Old Testament.
And I don't know if it's bigger.
I mean, it may be bigger to the
Jews. Don't believe in the New
Testament that Jesus was not the
savior. He was a prophet, not
the Son of God. Yeah. And they
still kind of stopped at an eye
for an eye, which is how they're
feeling right now. To all these
rays, like we're going to take
we're gonna gouge your eyes
because you gouges our eye and
it would be nice if everybody
had the love and peace of Jesus.
But okay, but that's neither
here nor there. He says that,
yes.
John C Dvorak: His column if,
let's say the Torah and the Old
Testament are exactly the same.
Why wouldn't he say as a good
Catholic boy that the Old
Testament is pandering,
patronizing. Patriots
patronizing the audience. Yeah.
Adam Curry: Well, he's also
lying. The guy lies about
everything. Yeah, he's a liar.
And this one is a whopper.
John C Dvorak: Okay, now this
was a whopper, you're gonna tell
us why it's a big lie. I looked
at it, as you'll will, you will
soon see as a shaggy dog story
the way he tells it. Let's go.
Unknown: I told the story before
and I'll tell it again. My first
BT was an Israeli Prime Minister
50 years ago as the young
senator sitting across from
golden years or desk in her
office, because she had a guy
named a guy who later became
prime minister sitting next to
me just before the 1973 Yom
Kippur war. As he flipped the
maps up and down, telling me how
bad things were out to me. They
were all of a sudden she looked
at me, she said, she'd like a
photograph. I looked at her. She
got up from her desk and walked
out into that hallway. I think
it's marble for walk down the
hallway. Walk down there, a
bunch of photographers stand in
front of us. We're standing
shoulder to shoulder without her
looking at me. She said to me
knowing I live here. Why do you
look so worried Senator Biden?
And I said worried? Like of
course I'm worried. And she
looked at me and she didn't look
she said we don't worry,
Senator. We Israelis have a
secret weapon. We have nowhere
else to go. Or today I said all
of Israel the United States is
going anywhere either.
Adam Curry: I didn't expect
that. He's been telling this
story throughout his career and
in this time, it was just before
the Yom Kippur War it's been
during the Six Day War in the
past CNN has a whole article on
this which is old missing one of
the one of this published from
CNN, this is from 2021. He keeps
telling this story about Golden
my air and like and then she I
want to take a picture. Now none
of this. It's a corn pop story.
Yeah, totally corn, corn pop
story. He's full of it. I don't
think I have the clip. But he
was I tried to run it through
Adobe No way. Could I get it to
work about him. Saying that.
Jews are not zombies. It's okay
to be a Zionist. Did you hear
that?
John C Dvorak: Yeah, I remember
something about this. I mean, it
is so here fumbling and mumbling
about Zionist. So here's
Adam Curry: the here's the raw
audio. I
Unknown: remember the first time
that I was in Israel with
Adam Curry: that's almost an
inaudible so I run it through
Adobe.
John C Dvorak: I can't I can
kind of hear it.
Adam Curry: Well listen to what
Adobe does to him.
Unknown: I remember the first
time that I was in Israel with
the coordinator and she was just
before with a 60 morning
Adam Curry: there he says Six
Day War. Yeah. And he just in
your clip. Did you say Six Day
War? He said no, no.
John C Dvorak: Yom Kippur war?
Yom Kippur war.
Adam Curry: This is great. He
confused it on the trip. I
didn't even I didn't even
realize he had confused it on
the trip. Let's do it and she
was telling me how weightless
let's use this
Unknown: was in Israel with me
here she was just before the Six
Day War and she was telling me
how terrible everything was. It
was she can flip the maps up and
down behind her and all of a
sudden she looked at me she said
would you like a photograph she
just got up and walked out
Adam Curry: outside her I'm so
we got we caught him in the lies
exactly the same story. Yeah,
except and that was before the
sixth day well, I didn't even
realize he had he had he had
Bumble bat on this trip. Let's
go to the Zionist part here
because the security and safety
of Jews right here somewhere
Unknown: that we're in Israel in
terms of the matter is that I
believe that
Adam Curry: I can't hear it
Unknown: terrible. Everything
was great if they were in
Israel,
Adam Curry: we'd have to admit
it. Why can't forget it? Forget
it. It's a I can't listen to it.
It's so bad as funny this is
that's crazy because when you
had that clip I'm like wow, you
found a clip of good audio I
couldn't find that story with
good audio which is why I didn't
clip it and now it turns out it
was before the the Yom Kippur
War on your clip before the Six
Day War on my clip Wow, our
president is a liar lost
John C Dvorak: it he's and he's
a liar. He's a liar.
Unbelievable liar.
Adam Curry: Yeah. Let's listen
to some hate from MSNBC that you
pointed out. NBC is all in on
hating Israel. Why? I don't
know. I don't know why either
other than they are the most
woke most leftist network.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, I think so.
Here is Mark
Adam Curry: Lamont Hill, Danny
Ireland. Thank
Unknown: you so much for joining
me on upfront with the former
Adam Curry: Israeli deputy
foreign minister.
Unknown: My pleasure.
The idea of collective
punishment is one of the things
that we're talking about here.
There are residential buildings
being hit, there are hospitals
being hit. This is a densely
populated area, the idea of
being able to run away or to
escape or go to a safe area
seems impossible. Also,
according to your own military
representatives, you've
abandoned the idea of knocking
on roofs that is safe to say
giving a warning of dropping a
non explosive munition on
buildings before people go so
people aren't getting a warning,
they have nowhere to go
residential building schools and
hospitals are being hit. How is
this not again, an act of
collective punishment? And how
is this not a target of civilian
unless of course you're
regarding everybody in Gaza as
an enemy combatant.
Until you in a practical manner,
what we should do and what we
can do create like in the past
in history, a humanitarian
corridor when there is a
humanitarian corridor and we
have been discussing this with
the United States then we can
guarantee in this corridor that
nobody will get hurt. Now again,
I say there is a way to receive
them all on the other side for
temporary time on site because
what did her master and on the
other side, we talked about
Rafa, are you saying the other
side that go to
Egypt? Yes, absolutely.
Absolutely. And Egypt will have
to play ball because this is
human life is at stake.
Human life is at stake because
you're cutting off power. You're
shutting down hospitals, you're
bombing residential buildings.
Right now there is a hospital
that has not does not have
sufficient power. There is a
hospital where people are
literally going to die and
Israelis Energy Minister Israel
Katz said no electrical switch
will be turned on no hydrant
will be open no fuel trickle
enter until the Israeli
abductees are returned home
Adam Curry: goes on and on and
on and on want to play the rest
of that it's just it's it's just
yeah, now but of course we need
to bring it home we need to
bring the fear and the terror
home.
Unknown: ABC tonight a warning
the war between Israel and Hamas
is increasing the chances of
violence in the United States. A
new intelligence bulletin says
potential targets include
individuals and institutions
Andrew Horowitz This is for you
perceived as symbolic of or tied
to the conflict. There are
stepped up patrols at synagogues
in Los Angeles, more crowd
control in Washington DC and in
New York, the nation's largest
police force has called in
reinforcements instructing all
officers to prepare to work 12
hour shifts.
There's a lot of tension that's
taking place right now. And this
can play out on our streets.
The FBI is not aware of any
organized plots, but the fear is
someone acting alone. Like the
man charged in the murder of a
six year old boy near Chicago
and Walla dia Alfa Yun was
buried this week after police
said he was stabbed to death by
his landlord because he was
Muslim.
Adam Curry: Yeah, that makes
sense. That makes sense. I have
that story. I
John C Dvorak: want to play this
story. Just make one comment.
This is the this is the odd
riots and maniac war in this
again, NBC so
Unknown: in Washington, DC
dozens were arrested at the
Capitol during a rally of Jewish
Americans calling for a
ceasefire. And in suburban
Chicago last night, more than
1500 people packed a vigil for a
Palestinian American boy he was
a child. A child filled with
love. And not any hate
prosecutors saying six year old
one dia alpha you meet was
stabbed dozens of times by his
family's landlord who they say
was angry about the Hamas
attacks. Joseph zuba faces
murder and hate crime charges in
Illinois and has not yet entered
a plea. A child taken and a
country on edge as war wages on
a world away.
Adam Curry: That's exactly what
you want it I don't believe this
at all.
John C Dvorak: Well, I kind of
believe it. And I'll tell you
why. Again, it could be just
part of the hope thesis button.
So they show a picture the guy
yeah. That guy looks like a
lunatic. He's like I've got a
inexplicably homely looking old
man. That is just looks like
he's nuts. And I tried them to
kind of believe a lot of it
because it just seemed like you
got some screwball the guy just
looks the guy looks wrong. Okay,
so
Adam Curry: people are being
riled up and this is the result
of it. Yeah, yeah. Well, this is
this is what you get this is
this is what everybody is
John C Dvorak: to blame the
media as far as I'm concerned.
That's right. There's one more
Adam Curry: from NBC now
tonight,
John C Dvorak: by the way, by
the way, that last one was from
NBC that when you play before us
from NBC so NBC News playing
this story, that was ABC. Okay,
well, my last one
Adam Curry: was NBC. This is
NBC.
Unknown: Tonight, authorities in
the US ramping up security amid
warnings about potential
violence mounting nationwide
over the Israel Hamas war in New
York, the NYPD ordering officers
indefinitely to be uniformed and
ready to deploy. American
officials and private analysts
telling NBC News extremists are
flooding social media with calls
for attacks on Jewish
communities and other targets in
the US and Europe, with groups
linked to al Qaeda and American
Neo Nazis seeking to exploit the
war. According to intelligence
memos obtained by NBC News, a
Homeland Security Official
telling NBC News DHS is
monitoring a heightened threat
environment in
Adam Curry: now that a think
about it. How to think about it.
This is all intended these
reports about you know, ba so
dangerous for Jews in America.
This is being ramped up to make
sure that we hate Trump. Because
that's exactly the result. I
told you I heard from that from
my hairdresser that everyone is
freaking out in Austin. Oh, oh
no. If Trump if Trump becomes
president, all Jews will be
killed. What? Yes, yes. Where
does
John C Dvorak: that come from?
Do they know that his daughter's
Jewish and he might need to
Adam Curry: stop with your
logic. This is this is people
are not of sane mind anymore.
They're not of sound mind. I
should so tied
Unknown: up and American Neo
Nazis seeking to exploit the
war. According to intelligence
memos obtained by NBC News. A
Homeland Security Official
telling NBC News DHS is
monitoring a heightened threat
environment in the US
Adam Curry: heightened threat
environment. We have an HTTP
everybody.
Unknown: The FBI also by the
way,
John C Dvorak: this this is
mimicking the Bush
administration because it worked
so well to get him reelected.
You know, we
Adam Curry: need we need to
bring back the color code again.
John C Dvorak: I was thinking
the same thing.
Adam Curry: Orange orange threat
level orange everybody who's
Unknown: a Homeland Security
Official telling NBC News DHS is
monitoring a heightened threat
environment in the US. The FBI
also on high alert. We stay
laser
focused on mitigating those
threats. Tonight.
The NYPD is Hate Crimes Unit
asking for the public's help
finding this man who they say
punched a woman in a subway
station Saturday telling her he
did it quote because you are
Jewish. This as protests
continue across the country. In
Washington, DC dozens were
arrested at the Capitol during a
rally of Jewish Americans
calling for a ceasefire.
Adam Curry: I love how it's a
rally. Now. This rally. It used
to be insurrection. But now it's
a rally
Unknown: during a rally of
Jewish Americans calling for a
ceasefire. And in suburban
Chicago last night, more than
1500 people packed a vigil for a
Palestinian American boy
he was a child a child filled
with love. And not any hate
prosecutor saying six year old
one dia alpha you meet was
stabbed dozens of times by his
family's landlord who they say
was angry about the Hamas
attacks Joseph zuba faces murder
and hate crime charges in
Illinois and has not yet entered
a plea a child taken and a
country on edge as war wages on
a world away
Adam Curry: country on edge
country on edge be on edge
people be on edge be afraid be
worried go outside. Do you
please go outside if you can
afford to go outside and tell me
if you if there's war all around
you? Is there someone right
there ready to punch you in the
face strike you right your face
right? You I listened to DHL
unplug it you I mean you kind of
glossed over it but Horowitz
said I'm a little worried about
it.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, I try to
calm him down. Good job Lord and
for God's sake. That's
Adam Curry: that was that was
your way if you're in Florida,
what are you talking about?
Andrew Wallace is a very is he's
a solid guy. And he's worried
he's getting spun up.
John C Dvorak: The course he's
get everybody gets spun up. Do
you got to stop? Two of us now.
Did you see clarify? podcasters
Adam Curry: podcasters save the
day. Did you catch Claire daily?
John C Dvorak: No, I do have one
more clip before we play Claire.
Adam Curry: Okay. All right.
John C Dvorak: Good work. All
right. This is the actually two
more first of all since we've
been playing all these clips. I
want to just play this six
second little short clip Which
to me epitomizes all the
reporting on all the all the
Middle Eastern media and this is
from Al Jazeera and the way they
just do the matter of fact about
the hospital goes like this. I O
matter of fact, I got it
Unknown: have taken to the
streets after the Israeli attack
on an utterly Baptist Hospital
in Gaza, which killed hundreds
of people
John C Dvorak: said, That's it.
After the Israeli attack. That's
all they say. They don't say
don't say what could have been
but just allegedly No way.
Adam Curry: Did he just say this
was a Baptist Hospital. I think
it's called that Yeah.
Interesting.
John C Dvorak: That's another
little tidbit they leave out of
our coverage. That's very
interesting. Yeah. Baptist I
think it Yeah, no, I
Unknown: think it was taken to
the streets after the Israeli
attack on an utterly Baptist
Hospital in Gaza which killed
Adam Curry: was the guy's name
Allah He Baptiste maybe that's
there's no
John C Dvorak: I think it's a
Baptist. I know. There's a
Christian we will look into it
Adam Curry: as a Christian
Hospital in in Gaza Strip. Why
not? believable,
John C Dvorak: where else would
you put them? So they have this
is a report on again from
Democracy Now. War journalists
dead.
Unknown: Israel's reportedly set
to ban Al Jazeera as operations
in the country over its coverage
of the war. Al Jazeera is one of
the few global media networks
that has reporters on the ground
in Gaza. In related news, the
Committee to Protect Journalists
that at least 17 media workers
had been killed since the start
of the war. 13 of them
Palestinian, three Israeli and
one Lebanese.
Adam Curry: What I can't believe
that those big flak jackets with
huge words press didn't save
their lives.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, they're the
newer ones. They shoot me.
Adam Curry: I saw Richard angle.
He says media.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, and he's
got a dumb helmet on.
Adam Curry: Yeah. But it's his
Flak Jacket is huge words media.
Yeah, I saw that. Do they
seriously think that? I mean, it
used to be Red Cross. Don't
shoot him. Yeah. Now he's media.
He's helpful.
John C Dvorak: He's Elbit us.
Adam Curry: So Claire Daly Irish
representative in the European
Union,
John C Dvorak: who we follow
closely with Yes, we this is our
favorite socialist chick. She's
a socialist
Adam Curry: and man. Something
happened this was not a good
look for her. I mean, she looks
Claire Daly usually looks you
know she's a Birkenstock with
your with her dress type lady
kind of in general.
John C Dvorak: She's kind of a
she looks
Adam Curry: Jaggard Chuck
haggard in this she. She
John C Dvorak: I think most of
the time she's pretty haggard.
Adam Curry: No, no, no, no, not
like this one that she had a
sweatshirt on and I don't know
what happened. But she anyway,
she was pretty angry. At Queen
Ursula. Queen or slow who went
right away with her Flak Jacket
and you see her whether she must
be three feet tall. This Ursula
John C Dvorak: she has. She's
she's a little shorty this you
get a little petite
Adam Curry: little a little flak
jacket on that said queen. Don't
hit don't. Queen. Claire Dana
was pretty angry about this.
Unknown: I've been involved in
politics for 40 years, but I
have never seen anything like
what is being unleashed in Gaza
in full public view. While the
world watches it unfold 10 days
of relentless airstrikes. One in
1000 people murdered by the
Israeli government in a week,
open declarations of siege 24
hours of fuel, electricity and
water left collective punishment
on innocent people, all illegal,
all war crimes. And when the EU
should have been arguing for a
ceasefire for the upholding of
international law for the
protection of civilians, Ursula
von der Leyen torches down in
Tel Aviv to photo up the
preparation of a genocide and
says your upstands when Israel
now and in the days to come, how
dare she she has no authority in
foreign affairs matter. She does
not speak for me. She does not
speak for Ireland, and she does
not speak for the citizens of
Europe. We stand for peace. We
stand for justice for the people
of Palestine and for the
upholding of international law.
It's long past the time that
this woman exited the stage.
It's time for her to go.
Adam Curry: It makes a good
point that Ursula von der Leyen
pretends to be speak for the
year like she's the president,
the queen of Europe.
John C Dvorak: She's not the
only one of Claire's not the
only one who has made this
commentary. They're getting a
little annoyed with her going
around things. She's like the
foreign secretary of the EU or
whatever she thinks she is the
Queen Queen, and it's getting
done. on people's nerves.
Adam Curry: Europe is I hate to
say it but Europe is done for
you're done for Yeah, you're
done for that, of course, you
know, hey Europe while we have
no money at the moment, but that
may change tonight we'll see
what the President says. You've
got to remember to keep funding
Ukraine keep funding them keep
fun. I'm hearing noise that
Ukrainians are pretty sick and
tired of Zelinsky now they were
supposed to have an election
which is obviously
John C Dvorak: not canceled
elections so you'd be king
Adam Curry: any a also just
outlawed the Christian Orthodox
Church,
John C Dvorak: right, the
opposition parties. A democracy
we gotta
Adam Curry: fight for its
democracy. But the most well, I
play one more clip and the and
then I think we were all clipped
out on this. I mean, we've
played clips from all sides. And
there's a point to it, these
ladies would say we're looking
at which is BBC with. Hold on a
second. This is the BBC was this
without? Oh, this is Daniel
Levy. He is the former Israeli
peace negotiator,
Unknown: the Israelis would say
we're looking at we are
defending ourselves, we are
targeting Hamas targets in Gaza,
we are trying to put an end to
what we believe is a terrorist
organization once and for all.
Adam Curry: Let me think about
that.
Unknown: Do you really keep a
straight face? When you say
that? Do you think terrorist
organizations embedded in
populations who are denied their
most basic rights are ended once
and for all in a military
campaign? Does that happen in
history? Can someone credibly
tell me that when the leadership
of a country says we are cutting
off food, electricity, water all
supplies to an entire civilian
population, that they're
targeting militants? I'm sorry,
these kinds of lies can't be
allowed to pass. And when you
tell yourself the lie, it leads
to the wrong policy. If anyone
told me that what the militants
did on the weekend was a
legitimate response to years and
years of occupation, I would say
no, you're wrong headed. You've
lost sight of humanity and
reality. And if anyone tells me
that what Israel is doing in
Gaza today is a legitimate
response to what happened on the
weekend. It's exactly the same.
And yet they are saying it and
yet the international community
is saying
people need to challenge them on
it, because it's a lie. And
we're war mongering, if we allow
them to get away with it.
Adam Curry: What team is he on?
The other team, according to the
president, whatever team so I
think we should just all remind
ourselves, that war is a racket
is very good for business. Once
the money printer starts going,
war always has to be funded by
borrowing or printing and
borrowing is kind of two sides
of the same thing. There's a lot
of a lot of financial markets
are waiting there. They'll
benefit from it. Everybody wants
this. This is what it's about.
It has really very little to do
with Israel and Palestine,
Hamas, Jews Muslim, it's all
just yeah,
John C Dvorak: we weren't
spending enough money. Nope. On
Ukraine, we're trying to
Adam Curry: well, we get we're
gonna we think somehow they've
already approved the four bagger
the 100 billion is already in
the pocket somehow. For Israel,
it's well, it's for Israel and
Ukraine. And what I'm hearing
now is that the President
tonight will ask Congress for
more, in addition to that 100
billion, which I'm sure probably
he's coming from an accounting
error inside the Pentagon.
John C Dvorak: Well, he is he is
going to be jacked up.
Adam Curry: I think you have
claimed he's talking about
John C Dvorak: it and about
where America we're America and
there's nothing we can't do. And
he's gonna yell at yell at, he's
gonna yell all that stuff that
if he's jacked up, and he's
going to ask for a lot of money.
And as we heard from the LG
Azuro report, where that woman
was in the rotunda where they
were having the protests she
said they asked for a ceasefire
and the Congress and nobody's
now No, so it's everyone's gonna
be behind this at least our
legislator, people. We need war
you need we're all good. Good
for it. And so except for Rand
Paul, probably two other guys.
Adam Curry: Rand Paul be like,
it came from the Wuhan lab. Rand
Paul, wrong talking point.
Goodbye. So
John C Dvorak: Rand Paul say no
throw Fauci in jail. Yeah, yeah.
And that'll be that and David,
we're gonna end up with this
mess and, okay, I don't know how
they're gonna do it. Deal with
it, but I think they're gonna
maybe we'll go boots on the
ground would just pummel I still
think it would probably be. You
can find the neighborhoods that
everyone knows where they are
where the mall is live. You rock
hound them to oblivion in that
area. Those
Adam Curry: Will that and will
that settle Muslims around the
world? Will that make them feel
boy? Yeah,
John C Dvorak: everyone's good.
Well, you know, the she, she as
Sunni thing is still a little
thing. Yes. About time you got
those guys? Yeah. You know, no,
you have no idea.
Adam Curry: No one has an idea
other than
John C Dvorak: good for
business, it's
Adam Curry: good for business.
Now I'm so worried about all
these groups and people and you
remember the intellectual dark
web? Vaguely the intellectual
dark web? Yeah, it was the
intellectuals. Well, now we have
something called the Westminster
declaration. And I'm surprised
you were not asked to sign this.
What is it? The Westminster
declaration? Quote, open
discourse is the central pillar
of a free society.
John C Dvorak: Rather, yeah. So
this is twice as my second
brother for the day.
Adam Curry: Yeah. Westminster
declaration.org. And I and I'll
just read a little bit because
this just came to my attention.
I think it's relatively new. We
write as journalists, artists,
authors, activist technologists,
and academics to warn of
increasing international
censorship that threatens to
erode centuries old democratic
norms,
John C Dvorak: no.
Adam Curry: New you'd love it.
Coming from the left, right and
center, we are united by our
commitment to universal human
rights and freedom of speech.
And we are all deeply concerned
about attempts to label
protected speech as
misinformation, disinformation,
and other ill defined terms. The
abuse of these terms has
resulted in the censorship of
ordinary people, journalists and
dissidents in countries all over
the world. Across the globe,
government actors, social media,
companies, universities and NGOs
are increasingly working to
monitor citizens and rob them of
their voices. These large scale
coordinated efforts are
sometimes referred to as the
censorship industrial complex. I
never heard that one. It's
what's only sometimes I do have
to write that down the
censorship industrial complex.
So and they don't
John C Dvorak: think about oh,
yeah,
Adam Curry: they go on and on
and on. About. Let's see,
John C Dvorak: what's it got to
do with West minister? I don't
know. What's the connection to
West ministry, Twitter
Adam Curry: files revealed tech
five tech companies are often
performing since Oreo content
moderation in coordination with
God. So this is a bunch of
Yahoo's who are pissed off that
they don't control Twitter.
John C Dvorak: So you see,
there's a bunch of lefties. So
I'm gonna, I'm gonna tell you
Adam Curry: who it is. But let
me first tell you what they what
they for the sake of human
welfare and flourishing, we make
the following three calls to
action. We call on governments
and international organizations
to fulfill their
responsibilities to the people
and uphold article 19 of the
Universal Declaration of Human
Rights. I don't even know what
there's
John C Dvorak: a copy of that.
Adam Curry: Look up a copy. We
call on tech corporations to
undertake to protect the Digital
Public Square Twitter, as
defined in article 19 of the
Universal Declaration on Human
Rights and refrain from
politically motivated
censorship, the censorship of
Dissident Voices and censorship
of political opinion. These are
people who are so misguided.
They think that social media is
the Digital Public Square. And
finally, we call on the general
public to join us in the fight
to preserve the people's
democratic rights. legislative
changes are not enough. We must
also build an atmosphere of free
speech from the ground up by
rejecting the climate of
intolerance that encourages self
censorship and creates
unnecessary personal Strife for
many, instead of fear and
dogmatism. We must embrace
inquiry and debate. Who do you
think sign this? This is the
elite of the Twitterati ready?
I'm ready. Matt Taibbi
journalist us Michael
Shellenberger Jonathan Haidt.
Steven Pinker. Tim Robbins.
John C Dvorak: Tim Robbins,
actor, actor. Yes.
Adam Curry: Richard Dawkins,
John Cleese, Oliver Stone.
Edward Snowden, Glenn Greenwald,
Jordan, Dr. Jordan B. Peterson.
Barry Weiss, Peter Hitchens.
Niall Ferguson. Yamas viral
Varoufakis is your buddy yeah,
the guy who we talked about
Chris Hedges ah, ally here. She
Ayaan Hirsi Ali. Let me find
some more that we know here.
It's not a lot of people, Brett
Weinstein. People are
John C Dvorak: in there too,
Eric. No,
Adam Curry: he's not funny
enough. Is not let me see if
there's anyone else who has a
bunch of people I don't know.
It's nothing. It's all you know,
college people. But this is done
in order of appearance. So I'm
presuming this is a, you know, a
tie EB Greenwald type thing. And
we all got a promotion for them.
We all got together in
Westminster, then yeah, why is
John C Dvorak: the like, explain
it. Well, this is paralleling
the new FCC chairman who just
announced Yes, yeah, they're
pulling back they're pulling
back on all the Trump stuff net
neutrality net neutrality back
in play, which means of course
technically, net neutrality
means for example, I have one of
my connections is Sonic and they
have a gigabyte or gigabit
gigabit connection I can Yes.
And they have a two gigabit but
it seems to me if I read net
neutrality correctly you can't
do that
Adam Curry: no, you have to give
everybody equal gigabits
John C Dvorak: everybody has to
have the equal gigabits that
means instead of gay having the
opportunity to get two gigabits
and I gotta give everybody two
gigabit now we're cutting back
on your bits. So everything goes
down. So all it does is become a
good becomes, you know, we go
back down we go to the mean, we
go to the the we go, it
downgrades every that's what net
neutrality is meant to do. Yes.
Dialog. Raise the speeds will
slow down. I
Adam Curry: love for everybody.
Yes. No. We have looked at this
ad nauseam years ago during
Obama within the Obama
administration. And the main
sticking point for me because I
was I was walking the dog this
morning and reading this. I had
read this before I went out and
like, Oh, they're gonna bring
this back. The main sticking
point was equal equal traffic,
except illegal traffic. You
remember that?
John C Dvorak: Well, yeah,
they're just a way of getting
porn off the internet,
Adam Curry: no illegal traffic,
it has nothing to do with the
content. It is the protocol. So
Tor, and torrents would be seen
as illegal content.
John C Dvorak: Okay, that's
right. I'm trying to remember
the trick. That's the trick.
Yes, to get rid of movie
sharing, or
Adam Curry: you know, Tor is
good for you know, object
John C Dvorak: storage good for
a lot of stuff is a fantastic
product, a guy who did it is
something of a coding genius.
But if it's if deep packs, deep
packet sniffing is in play, you
can see as a Tor stream, and it
once you recognize it, it
becomes like, oh, no, you can't
do that. There goes all your
people who download movies,
which is about 70% of the net.
It'll free up some bandwidth,
that's for sure.
Adam Curry: I did want to play
one last Israel clip so
apparently, we got duped. The
clip of the laser dome was was a
hoax. The laser dome was a hoax.
That was supposedly footage from
a video game. And it was not
true. So clip did
John C Dvorak: we play that was
a hoax. We
Adam Curry: didn't play the
clip. I said that Sir Brian of
London who was very apologetic
about this.
John C Dvorak: He said, Oh, that
yeah, you read his note. I
didn't. Yeah, I looked into this
too. In the meantime, after we
win iced tea, but I made a
mistake. I've made a call bla
and this was I said, Why just
pay? I thought it was a Patriot
Missile system from Raytheon.
But no, it's developed by
Israel. Yes. And it's a
completely alien system that I
guess it works well.
Adam Curry: Okay. So what we
immediately got was, it's fake.
It's a hoax. It's from video
game footage. It's not true. But
then France. 24 does this.
Unknown: And now it's even more
tried to fill in the gaps, the
potential gaps in the Israeli
aerial system. The Israeli DOD
and the company have failed. The
Israeli company have been
developing this time a laser
based anti missile defense
system called the laser beam, as
you said, and according to some
sources, close to the Israeli
DOD, they could indeed decide to
deploy that system earlier than
what was expected. And one of
the reasons why is that this is
actually a very cost effective
system because it only cost
about $4 per launch compared to
$50,000. I was talking about
with the Iron Dome. Now how does
it work this is a mobile laser
cannon that can really turn to
here you can see these pictures
footage from the company have
failed trying out its system,
but it can really turn to dust
rockets, missiles, drones in a
split second, the laser beam is
of about 100 kilowatts.
Looking at some of the best
technology in the world at the
moment in terms of no defense
system, but the ion beam hasn't
been deployed yet.
No. And it's important to stress
that because on social media
networks, we've been seeing
videos that purported to show
this this this laser beam, but
it isn't actually this is a
fake. I want to show you those
pictures. These are a night
pictures of course. But this is
actually footage from Arma three
which is a video game that is
known because it's particularly
realistic with its realistic
graphics now, we are indeed when
we're talking about these laser
beams, we are talking about the
future of defense systems, many
countries around the world are
trying to develop their own
systems here in France. Albion
for instance, is developing
something called Alma P which
could actually be used by
security forces here in France
to secure the French capital for
instance during the 2024
Olympics. Now all of these
systems that we've been talking
about have also been purchased
by other countries Germany for
instance, recently purchased
arrow three and even Finland
purchase David slings anti
defense system
Adam Curry: I love it direct the
real fire ran
John C Dvorak: a TV station I
would give this report and then
I would have a video of an old
Apple two game called Missile
Command shooting the things out
of the air or and then cut the
Space Invaders Yeah, asteroids
asteroids because you have to
have you know you have to have
some Twitch skills to be able to
use these things although I'm
debt system I'm sure it's all
computerized you don't to do
anything. Push a button. Yeah,
this is bounded what eventually
that system has to go into play.
Adam Curry: Oh, yeah. Well, I
now the way she said this is
obviously night footage, but
it's from a game to me. They
were using it to testing it out.
But what better opportunity to
test it out right now. As he
goes over there, they're
accelerating it why wouldn't you
just use it? The French are
going to be frying people during
the Olympics. I don't know why.
I can just see them using it.
Now where am I not what a world
we're in man. What a world we
got lasers that are the gist.
And if you see the video, it
doesn't burn them up. It turns
them to dust. Well, Dad, I don't
believe well, that's what that
was the demo was that that's
that's in the sales brochure. I
think it's just disabled in the
brochure. Not Freising.
Freising, Miss cool. Very cool.
Okay, well, all this is going on
with everyone's focuses and
attention is on the Middle East
and on Biden and Ben, just
everything. We're not even
talking about Ukraine anymore.
Funny how that works. China that
you go on, they're doing their
own thing.
Unknown: Morning Stewart. It was
launched in 2013. And he's one
of Sujan pings a signature
signature policies. And as we're
about to see, it's really
undergone a Trump's
transformation in the last 10
years. Beijing now says it has
inked Oh, close to $2 trillion
in contracts around the world
contracts that cover a wide
array of different investments,
roads, high speed rail, ports,
energy infrastructure, among
others. Over the course of 10
years, the number of signatories
to the project has gone from
eight members in 2013 to now
150. And this is the
Adam Curry: Belt and Road
Initiative and they had a big
meeting in China. Everyone
showed up Hey,
John C Dvorak: Putin was there I
believe,
Adam Curry: Putin, he's like,
Hey, let's do our own thing.
Unknown: Representatives from
about 130 countries are
gathering at this year's summit
in the Chinese capital many
arguments are made for and
against the Belton Road
initiative. On the plus side,
it's been a much needed vector
for investments, development and
economic growth for global south
countries on the downside, it
has saddled many nations with
huge levels of external debt
while in many instances also
causing environment
environmental harm and inviting
opportunities for corruption.
But the Belton Road initiative
today is not the same project it
was 10 years ago, in part
because of a response to these
criticisms. Researchers have
found that as China's economic
growth is slowing down the days
of seemingly seemingly unlimited
overseas borrowing are coming to
an end to China's total overseas
development finances only just
below $5 billion in 2021. And
far from the peak seen in In
2016, just under $90 billion for
that year, that's because
China's overseas investment
policy is now to try and focus
on smaller and greener projects.
Adam Curry: Is China getting
caught up in the in global and
climate change? Or they do more
green projects?
John C Dvorak: I don't know what
that's all about seems unlikely
to have avoided it like the
plague seems unlikely.
Adam Curry: I'm, I'm thinking we
delayed just a little bit
longer. We get everything in
because I think that donation
segmented being our 16 100th
episode will be a little longer
than normal.
John C Dvorak: It'll be long.
But I guess it might be my
favorite story. I will say this
at the end of the show. Kind of
just kind of a pathetic story. I
got an oddball story about
Venezuela that I thought was
like, where's just I haven't
heard.
Unknown: The government of
Venezuelan President Nicolas
Maduro and opposition leaders
have agreed to new rules ahead
of next year's presidential
election. The move is expected
to clear the way for the United
States to ease its harsh
sanctions on Venezuela, which
have wrecked the economy,
forcing millions to flay. As
part of the agreement, the
Venezuelan Government will allow
all political parties to choose
their candidates grant
permission to delegations from
the UN in the European Union to
observe elections and give equal
media access to all campaigns,
Adam Curry: there was some kind
of deal. This is why the
Venezuelans are getting
preferential treatment when they
show no
John C Dvorak: some deal went
down. Yeah, and this is just a
part of it. I don't know what
the whole thing is. But it has a
lot to do with getting oil back
on track, as we used to see, I
think the cynical or what they
said a guy who I forget which
company but there's one company
that was a major provider of
gasoline in the United States.
And they sit go, maybe Citko
Yeah, I think so go, and they
would bring this Venezuelan
crude and and refine it. And it
would be it's a big loss to us
not to have the Venezuelan crude
oil into our system for
gasoline. And I think that at
some point, we decided, you
know, it's better than we can
still talk a big game about not
drilling here, but we got to get
this Venezuelan oil on back
online. They're huge. They got a
monster field.
Adam Curry: Right. Is that the
right kind of crude? Is it the
the good stuff?
John C Dvorak: It's a good crude
for us? Yeah, yeah. It's not a
dirty crude. Well, we looked it
up. But my understanding is that
most of the South American crude
is pretty clean, but we've
Adam Curry: got a lot of
Venezuelans coming into the
United States. And oh, man, I
actually I should I should play.
I've got two migration
replacement clips. The first one
is an update from Chicago. Oh,
my goodness. It is not good in
Chicago, that there's like 40
buses a day showing up. And this
is a local Chicago report. The
Chicago ones are mad that
getting really mad now what's
happening. We are learning
Unknown: much more about the
migrant crisis here in Chicago.
I spoke to Christina Pacioli as
is the city's first Deputy Chief
of Staff. She gave me insight on
how the crisis is impacting the
city and state financially.
We have more people coming in
than we actually have
transitioning out of shelters.
Already this week. 41 buses have
rolled into Chicago that means
there are now 11,000 migrants
living in shelters. 4000 are
still sleeping on police station
floors and staying at the
airports. There have been calls
by city officials to close the
end of Chicago shelter site
after report.
Adam Curry: This is really
interesting. The enough Chicago
shelter site and they have this
picture in of Chicago Miracle
Mile. So this is on the Miracle
Mile which is the shopping
street.
John C Dvorak: Yes, the base.
The main part of this the best
part of town in of
Adam Curry: Chicago is is a kind
of a nice hotel. It's not a
shelter spot. They're paying
this hotel, and of course the
hotels like be as good. Bring
them all in here. But it's not
like the Roosevelt, New York.
This is a nice hotel, and the
website is up and this is like
no vacancies. Yeah. No kidding.
Here we go.
John C Dvorak: know, when I go
to the airport, I see a bunch of
people camped around in the
airport. And that's really
inexcusable.
Adam Curry: Oh, and you see it
upon arrival. It's in the
arrivals hall. But they have the
curtains around them and stuff,
which is that's very humane,
though. So humane. There have
Unknown: been calls by city
officials to close enough
Chicago shelter site after
reports of criminal behavior
including drug sales and
prostitution. Pasi Yonis. Is
says it's not shutting down.
We are in a lease. You know,
that's the other thing.
Adam Curry: We're in a lease. So
I guess they've leased the
entire Chicago Hotel. The city
has just leased it is crazy
paying top
John C Dvorak: dollar. Oh yeah.
Unknown: This chart shows the
number of migrant children now
enrolled. Within the Chicago
Public Schools 30% of migrants
here in Chicago are children.
That migrant crisis is straining
resources. The state is footing
the bill for what they call
temporary housing. The state is
paying on the high end $9,000 in
rental assistance over a six
month period of time with that
comes out moving in and a
starter kit to furnish the
apartment
Adam Curry: star kid. Here's a
vase for flowers
Unknown: that read last for six
months and ideally, people would
have started their legal
process, secured legal work
authorization and then be able
to sustain that apartment. The
city
put $4 million towards helping
migrants get temporary housing.
Right now there are just a
handful of case managers to
handle the load to get migrants
in temporary rentals. We did
reach out to see how many asylum
seekers are currently taking
advantage of the rental
assistance. We haven't heard
back from the city on that.
John C Dvorak: Well, that's got
to go over big with the
residents.
Adam Curry: Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
I'm sure Airbnb is in on it.
John C Dvorak: Oh, absolutely.
Adam Curry: They have to be so
in New York. Mayor Eric Adams.
To he up. This kind of shows you
how much bullcrap AI is. So they
use a robocall system, which
transmogrified the mayor's voice
into different languages.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, a couple of
two or three languages. Now.
Adam Curry: I mean, this is this
is the same as calling anything
blockchain. We have a pet store,
we use blockchain. Now we're
using AI says Mayor Adams AI is
here is hair, I'm using it. I'm
awesome. using
Unknown: AI to improve the
delivery of goods and services
is what we're going to do. And
we're going to all look back on
this one day and say, You know
what, this guy, Eric had it
right. I know we have a right
Adam Curry: from the future. And
Unknown: so those who sit on the
sidelines, wake up in the
morning, and say, let me see,
we're going to criticize Eric
about today. Jeff, we're going
to use it. It's not against the
law. So people want it.
John C Dvorak: Well, I was gonna
bring you down with a clip, I
have a question that more
generalized, but I'll ask it
now. Why not find a person
that's fluent in the language
and have them deliver the
messages over the phone, as
opposed to some bulky version of
that guy was can barely get a
sentence out without sounding
silly? And get you know, have
you flew? Hiring a fluent person
to do this? Why don't you do
that instead of this nonsense?
Well, obviously,
Adam Curry: there's some pay off
some some buddy of his has an AI
company. I mean, you know,
Spotify did a big announcement,
where Spotify. Now if you upload
your podcasts or Spotify, we
will translate your voice into
Portuguese into Spanish into
German into French into every
language imaginable. You know,
it's always interesting to me.
You never hear anyone promoting
the, the opposite direction. You
never hear someone saying, Wow,
we're now using this. So you can
listen in English to podcasts in
French. You know why? Because we
would only have to listen to
three seconds of it. And we'd be
laughing about how horrible it
is. Because you know, it sucks.
You know that it sucks. It just
John C Dvorak: gotta suck. Suck.
Unknown: Because what are your
voice? The people want to hear
that man's voice.
Adam Curry: It's also a bit of
ego, I think,
Unknown: tell me you do not
enjoy waking up in the morning.
You hear my voice? You know,
people think about the seat at
the money. The problems that we
have, is that those of us who
are able to enjoy life from our
normal space. We think everyone
feels that way.
Adam Curry: Well, because you
know, the we want to make
migrants feel comfortable when
they come here illegally. We
want their space to be
normalized. Do you know how
empowering it is? If you speak
or do or, or do you know how
empowering it is? If you can
speak Urdu? Yeah, I feel very
powerful.
Unknown: And all of a sudden you
hear in the voice of your
mayor's speaking your language.
Adam Curry: It's so empowering
Mayor Adams, it's really believe
me? The Venezuelans feel
empowered because of this.
That's empowering
Unknown: to people. And it's we
don't understand it because we
always hear English. Everyone is
talking in English, but this is
a city that's diverse. And you
know Uh, I know what I hear from
my constituents that speak
different language. Hey, I heard
that robo call from you. Thank
you understood it. And this is
the right thing to do and we're
gonna do it.
Adam Curry: Let me see. Do you
think that there's an example of
his robo call in Urdu? Do you
have one? Well I know that you
mentioned it let me see if
there's one available
John C Dvorak: there's got to be
viewed think so. I want to hit
the Chinese version.
Adam Curry: I'm I'm thinking now
I'm thinking like what companies
in on this?
John C Dvorak: Yeah, it's
definitely some operation
there's some corruption involves
New York. Yeah,
Adam Curry: let me see now
unfortunately, fortunately,
it'll come out Oh, come
John C Dvorak: on to wash. Yeah,
Adam Curry: I can't wait. I'm
very excited to hear to hear the
mayor in Urdu.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, or do
especially
Adam Curry: using AI to fake his
voice in always doing ads as
well not just robo calls.
Interesting. Yeah. Anything
else? Well,
John C Dvorak: are we gonna
Hallows or segment going to be
at the end? Probably not too
long. So we should probably get
this out of the way. Okay. This
is the I think is pathetic
stories played. In an
unfortunate way. There's the
black man story.
Adam Curry: I'm gonna have to do
this morning. AMY GOODMAN
flippin bound. I'm sorry.
Everybody is a lot of people got
triggered in the troll room
since we've been playing AMI
clip after AMI clip after Yeah,
John C Dvorak: well, I got a lot
of AMI clips today.
Unknown: Back in the US in
Georgia. A man who was
wrongfully imprisoned for 16
years for a crime he didn't
commit was killed by police
Monday, Leonard Allen cure a
black man was driving on a
highway in Camden County near
the Georgia Florida State Line
when a sheriff's deputy pulled
them over reportedly for
speeding the officer notified
him he'd be arrested before
shocking him with a taser at
least twice speeding him with a
baton then fatally shooting him.
The 53 year old man was released
from a Florida prison in 2020.
After he was exonerated for an
armed robbery conviction from
2004. Since his release, he
often gave inspirational talks
to high school students and it
plans to go to college.
John C Dvorak: I just don't
believe this story is giving us
all the details now.
Adam Curry: I'm sure it's not
John C Dvorak: bad cop, I guess
pulled over for speeding and
killed him. But it sounds like
because he's black. So and he
wanted to go to college.
Adam Curry: That's Amy. I mean,
you know, how can you even play
her anymore?
John C Dvorak: I love it.
Adam Curry: All right. Let me I
need to do this, I need to do
this. Now it's time for our
friends malice to self destruct
initiated trans mouse update,
which as you know, contains a
lot of different things. And the
first one is just I have to read
this. This is what this from
this was a owe them.us is a
great publication. And I'll just
I'll just read this. I'm an
Israeli trans woman who
desperately needs Palestine to
be free. I need this because I
refuse to accept that the
massacres peaceful protesters in
Gaza is something that my people
keep doing. I need this because
I understand that trans
liberation and Palestinian
Liberation are linked. You
starting to figure out how this
all works. This is why people
are on the street. But also it's
another flag is another cool
flag we can fly. About 10 months
ago, I figured out the flag yes
new flag. That's a good title to
a new flag. About 10 months ago,
I figured out that I wanted to
start hormone replacement
therapy and in that way
medically transition. There were
many reasons for this decision.
But one of them was the
realization that growing up
Israeli and trans in Jerusalem,
while being expected to become a
Zionist man left an aftermath in
my body. Wow, I needed help to
heal and since the growing
around her more tender body
would help me connect with the
justice loving feminine child
inside of me. And having such a
body would help me grow from
that soft place. Anyway, so that
goes on and on and on and on.
And then so I waited until the
Jewish new year to go to my
pharmacy and start that phase in
my transition. I imagine the
little ritual I will do while
taking that first teal colored
pill New Year New Jew new me.
But when the pharmacy handed me
the bottles with my medication,
I looked at the label that read
produced by Teva
Pharmaceuticals, and my heart
stopped. Teva or Teva? I guess,
a word meaning nature and Hebrew
is an Israeli owned
pharmaceutical company that I
have vaguely heard about as a
participant in the economy of
the occupation. This must be a
mistake, I thought, excuse me, I
said when I went back to the
pharmacist This estrogen is
produced by an Israeli company.
I'm a supporter of BDS. Could I
please have a prescription from
a different manufacturer? No,
we're sorry. That's the only
manufacturer we carry. The
pharmacist quickly replied. I
was in shock. How could this?
How could this be? I texted all
my medicalized trans sisters on
my way home and asked the simple
question, who makes your
hormones? Many of them didn't
know offhand. It takes a great
deal of struggle and an intense
amount of questioning for many
trans folks to get their hands
on this life saving medication.
And once we do, we want to start
immediately and experience and
enter questions regarding the
validity of identity and our
choices. But my sisters heard
the urgency you might call and
checked in, and the responses
came every single one was either
Teva, or company that a quick
Google search listed as linked
to them. How did this one
Israeli company play such a
large role in the cross gender
hormone market? How did my body
once again find itself as a
battleground? A settlement, an
ongoing pawn in this Zionist
game? I feel so bad for these
people.
John C Dvorak: So we need to get
a jingle for these reads.
Adam Curry: Oh, what would you
call them?
John C Dvorak: Well, they're
they're they're interesting. I
don't know yet. I can come up
with a name
Adam Curry: for it. Pearl clutch
kind of in a way. It's the
John C Dvorak: pearl clutching
with Adam curry.
Adam Curry: Let's let's all
clutch our pearls.
John C Dvorak: All right, that's
not a bad name. Pearl.
Adam Curry: It's a new podcast,
Pearl clutching podcast. And
then one final clip just to make
sure that we all know exactly
what the agenda is. This is from
I believe the Canada's new
Democrat Party. Isn't that to
dos party?
John C Dvorak: You see that he's
he's he's a liberal I Liberal
Party. Isn't the liberals?
Adam Curry: Who's In Who's the
liberal? Oh, okay. Well, he
shouldn't be with this one. This
is the new Democrat party's
convention. And before they
started off first everybody a
few ground rules,
Unknown: a reminder that we will
enforce gender parity at the
mics and a julienne explain the
process with the yellow card as
well. So please remember to give
space to those who face systemic
barriers and discrimination
including women, black,
indigenous and racialized folk
in particular, people living
with disabilities and to LGBTQIA
plus folk. Our convention has
special speaker priority for
gender equity if you identify
with a gender other than men for
the purpose of the equity
speaking rule, you will have
received a piece of yellow
cardstock during the
registration process so please
raise this piece of yellow
cardstock when you arrive at the
mic so that myself and Adrian as
chairs can identify you easily
fit on hive one there will be
additional cards available at
the mics as always if you
require support please flag a
volunteer and they will be happy
to assist you. As New Democrats
we strive to create inclusive
spaces where everyone gets a
voice at the table
Adam Curry: except for men
except for white men keep leaves
us Yeah, I can believe
John C Dvorak: it the only thing
that she doesn't go on and on
about enforcing pronouns
Adam Curry: well I don't miss
you might have what I'm
surprised I mean they're only
one step away from taking those
yellow cards and cutting them
into stars you're almost there
lady keep it up. Yeah
John C Dvorak: he's on the back.
Adam Curry: And with that, I
would like to thank you for your
courage say in the morning to
you the man who for 1600
episodes is putting the sea and
things today the sea in the
center strip industrial complex
ladies and gentlemen say hello
to my still friend on the other
end the one and only Mr. John
Cena
John C Dvorak: in the morning to
you Mr. Adam Korean and Maria
all ships of sea boots on the
ground feet in the air subs in
the water and Allah deems a nice
out there
Adam Curry: and we celebrate
with our we we celebrate with
our trolls today. We always in
fact the trolls have been
celebrating with the trolls for
well over 14 years I think
thanks to void zero who has
always kindly gave up his his
chat room has made that the no
agenda troll room. Sir bemrose
running the no agenda stream. We
have so many people to thank for
all these episodes that we have
been beaming to you particularly
on the live shows on the
Thursdays and Sundays and why
don't we just joke funny What
does A normal count for a
Thursday
John C Dvorak: 1800
Adam Curry: Oh, okay well even
to weld two hours and 15 minutes
into it 1977
John C Dvorak: Good. Oh guys
Yeah,
Adam Curry: that's very nice.
John C Dvorak: Hello trolls here
for port port 1970s
Adam Curry: Well, the trolls are
up they come back they'll run
away the scurry whenever I try
to count them. It's a good year
for the trolls as well. The
trolls troll room.io Or if you
prefer, you can get a modern
podcast that podcast apps.com
You'll need it believe me
eventually you're gonna need it
because things are gonna get
start to platforms as it's
already happening to many
podcasts. So get one a podcast
John C Dvorak: crew. Well What
have you heard?
Adam Curry: Well, they the
platform stuff every week. Every
week conspiracy disinformation
misinformation. Oh, yeah. It's
gone all the time. Can you get
Alex Jones on Apple podcasts?
You see? Oh, that's
John C Dvorak: been for years.
You're
Adam Curry: horribly dangerous
man.
John C Dvorak: Not by my
standard. You
Adam Curry: get monkey works on
Apple podcasts. Never heard of
it. Monkey works. Yeah, we've
talked about monkey works. Yeah,
no, you can't get any of that
stuff. Oh, no. And it's not just
that. This is all this is
happens all the time. I'd say
they remove on average eight to
10 podcasts a week. And I'll get
I'll get a list. I will gladly
get a list for you. Oh, yeah, we
should have a list. Yeah, yes,
it should be an honor roll. But
get one of those because it
alerts you when we go live and
as the bad signal has a live
stream that has the troll room
it's it's it's really It's good
stuff. You can also you can also
follow us at no agenda
social.com Which I'm not barely
active on it's got so bad on no
agenda social.
John C Dvorak: Okay, notice it
changing one iota one way or the
other. Well,
Adam Curry: I look at the look
at stuff that everyone's
posting, posting not just stuff
I follow. And all I see is you
know, anti Jew memes anti EU
Palestine anti Muslim, and it's
all all sides of it. Everyone's
all and it's all posting from
other places. Every link is to
something on Twitter or Reddit
or somewhere else is writtens
isn't almost no original
thought.
John C Dvorak: I guess that's
what social media I guess, the
point of
Adam Curry: social media. But I
would also like to thank Aaron
are for keeping that running out
of the goodness of his heart. He
took that over for me years ago.
I started that and it was about
a year and a half two years into
him like this is too much work.
There's too much to do. So he's
been an excellent steward of
that. Now he also posted about
about what I've been saying
about no agenda social he says
hey, you know everybody, it is
what you make out of it. Oh,
there you go. Yeah, I don't see
you posting that often. Post
John C Dvorak: constantly.
Adam Curry: What are you posting
memes
John C Dvorak: if I can find a
good meme I'll post it for sure.
Adam Curry: I love how this is
contingent on the origin of
social that things Adam hates
memes like oh you do no I don't
I hate
John C Dvorak: bad I'm in that
contingent by the way.
Adam Curry: I only hate bad
memes it stems from the
knowledge of how much storage
space that sucks up by everyone.
Oh, there you have it a posting
all of these pictures. The back
end? Yeah, the back end in the
back end suffers people. Hey,
you're not the boss of us.
John C Dvorak: They just say
that.
Adam Curry: Oh, yeah, many, many
I'm not. I'm becoming you. I'm
starting to block people's like,
I don't want to see you anymore.
I'm just not
John C Dvorak: there's always a
practical method was blocking P
No, but like you're becoming me
Adam Curry: know I'm becoming
you. I am I'm becoming you. And
you're becoming blocked and
you're becoming me. Because
people have noticed you're
cussing a lot more.
John C Dvorak: I've tried to
keep the cussing to zero. Yeah,
but that's failing. You're
failing is a lot of cussing. I
haven't cut today once
Adam Curry: True. True. But the
show's not over. Not on over No,
I love the memes that I'm in you
idiots. Now if you have a meme
about me I love them but then he
just was a narcissistic mean
yeah, they're rarely any good.
There's a couple of good ones
I've seen of you the one where
I'm all like on fire that one
John C Dvorak: I didn't see that
one that's probably good. I'd
like to challenge right
Adam Curry: like the ones where
I'm on fire. Now I just have
other things to do with my life
that's all this you know adhere
to here. There's no agenda
social use to make me smile used
to make me happy. But now it's
just memes do it's just but no,
it's doom and gloom. And then
it's like, everything sucks.
It's now it's not funny. I don't
know. I can't put my finger on
it. I guess But if it's good
enough for you, then you should
keep going there
John C Dvorak: I think is
terrific.
Adam Curry: You're just sucking
up to the trolls. Follow Adam
will follow to follow John C.
Dvorak had no agenda social.com
Posting memes He loves them.
John C Dvorak: He go follow I
also follow the real DeVore I
could Twitter please. Oh, I'm
down like, like the 1000 people.
Adam Curry: Oh no. That was
that's probably the real the
actual real people that followed
you
John C Dvorak: know, it's hard
to say. There's a lot of new
probably write it write this up
on substack there's a lot of new
types of fake accounts.
Adam Curry: I love that. I'm
just looking at the troll room.
Adam takes memes too seriously?
No, I don't. I'm just sour on
social media in general. He
John C Dvorak: sour sour don't
even put anything about it.
Adam Curry: Um, so our um, sour
What can I tell you?
John C Dvorak: I'm just sour.
Sour is from living in
Fredericksburg.
Adam Curry: Oh man. This
Fredericksburg is the best. What
are you talking about? See, I
know what you like you liked it
when I was divorced and
freewheeling and smoking weed
and all crazy. That's what you
liked. That's Adam. You like
Well, I'm sorry that Adam is no
longer here. I'm just you.
John C Dvorak: Adam was short
lived. And you were so mean not
too worried prior but that's
beside the point. But free
wheeling out there. Getting you
know, finding girls left and
right.
Adam Curry: Finding girls Hey.
Yeah, how many? How many did I
really find 10. Okay. Oh
goodness. So I just want to
continue thanking everybody
who's a part of no agenda nation
now which is all of the
producers of course, but we do
have so many people who have
participated specifically in the
time talent and treasure. We
have no agenda artwork generator
we have the no agenda meetups we
have Gitmo list that lists all
the all the so many different
websites the no agenda agenda
shop, no agenda shop, I mean,
this, it really has made no
agenda nation what it is today.
And I want you to take that
seriously. The time talent
treasure is real, that there's
no way we could come anywhere
near what we're doing without
without that selfless return of
value. And along with that comes
treasure as well. But we'll talk
about that in a moment. Because
people have just been so
gracious helping us throughout
all the all these years. Making
it possible. I think when When
did I really? When did we really
go full time? Was it around
episode? 200 I think
John C Dvorak: no. Way before
that. Was it it? It was sub 100?
Adam Curry: No, it wasn't sub
100? No, I think so. No, because
100 I was
John C Dvorak: fine. It was a
big deal, because that's what we
had to do club and the deuce
club. Really, it was a very
successful promotion. It was
like the most success promotion
we had and continue to be such,
probably for another three or
400 shows. We had the art to
deuce club art people join the
deuce club.
Adam Curry: Yeah. Yeah, the
deuce Club was Big. Huge was
huge. What was the was the one
episode that we keep? We kept
repeating is that the one 100.5?
John C Dvorak: I can't remember.
It's it's we kept just Yes, we
did a retrospective I can't
remember the number
retrospective show that we kept
repeating with layers and
layers, have more retrospection
until we kind of ran out of room
and this thing is floating
around. So I can't remember what
the show number is. Somebody in
the troll room will know exactly
what the show number is. Yeah, I
think we did the last one about
four years ago. And I wanted to
do another one but I think the
last one covered it covered it
all. I don't know. We can talk
much more about how we got the
jingles and how we went from
here to there and how who's
winning the but
Adam Curry: we need to but yeah,
that's right. I mean, do we even
need to do that anymore? We we
haven't done that in a while. I
don't know if we ever need to do
it again. Honestly.
John C Dvorak: No, I think that
one episode does the trick.
Yeah, yeah, it does.
Adam Curry: It does. So, I mean,
really, there's just too many
people to thank that. That's
that's the real problem. There's
too many people to thank for all
of the time and talent you've
put into it. But we do always
like to thank our artist. As we
have noted, an Art Generator
where artists upload art
sometimes Time's in droves just
amazing amounts I think every
show we have at least 10 pieces
to choose from if not more. So
we want to thank Matt boy there
I got an education blog where
I'm sorry blog air blog web it's
you spell it Boisvert but it's
Bob air is the Arleigh francais.
Matt. For the artwork for
episode 1599 We titled that one
drop the drop the OP
John C Dvorak: This is enough
Adam Curry: another uncovered
Yeah, we got a jingle for it
too. Now, this was an
interesting piece because I
don't think either of us noticed
when we first saw this. Israel,
Ukraine Hamas and NATO with the
IR and n of each of those
highlighted that Hamas was
misspelled. Di Yeah,
John C Dvorak: I'm noticing it
now. And I
Adam Curry: wonder if like Hamas
did that. Well, that's that's
what a lot of people thought
it's like, oh, wait a minute.
Was this a subtle dig at Hamas
by by putting to me love Hamas?
We do love Hamas.
John C Dvorak: Everybody loves
Hamas. If they've, you know, how
could you especially if you've
ever been to the Middle East,
where the old lady's go in the
basement. You always told this,
y'all. There's a couple old moms
down the basement grinding the
beans down, you know with a
pestle and they do it by hand
and the stuff is so peanut
butter, butter. creamy, smooth.
It's astonishing. It's good.
It's
Adam Curry: good. It's good.
Holy mackerel. Have you seen how
many pieces of art have been
submitted for today's show?
Quite a few. Wow. Well, let's
see what else there was. Dave
Jackson, you can fast forward
now. Dave Jackson says he hates
the art segment. For summary. He
listened to the donation
segment, but he hates the art.
So
John C Dvorak: he's going to
miss my story about how he got
to the PhD certificate diploma.
Adam Curry: This too. He's
already gone. So that's too bad.
First let's talk about the
options we had. We had none.
Well, I liked the spread inator
Yeah, you did by scaring. I kind
of like the spread nature we use
spread inator as the opening
clip though, which kind of audio
removes it from ruined. Ruined
did see. Was there anything else
that we liked
John C Dvorak: whether choose
lies which is spread Nadir was
the other? Okay, that one?
Adam Curry: I thought the red
yarn was okay though. Yeah, you
were onto the red
John C Dvorak: yarn. I thought
it was too boring.
Adam Curry: Well, yeah, I mean,
we both just agreed on on the
deficit of
John C Dvorak: fall back dos
that it was a fall back
agreement. What
Adam Curry: it was, yeah. Yeah,
it's hard. I mean, what is this
thing with? To Kenny? Damn Kenny
Ben man did she she's lost the
plot.
John C Dvorak: She when she
would when she had the stork?
Adam Curry: With a car that
looks nothing like a Volvo and
it was titled it's a Volvo we
had that Volvo Volvo the
John C Dvorak: Volvo thing Yeah.
Adam Curry: That was John I was
kind of weird. I expect better
from Dame Kenny Ben
John C Dvorak: Yes, she was she
wasn't you know she's one of
those artists that's not a
professional that I know of and
she needs right she really needs
to be inspired. Yeah,
Adam Curry: yeah. Boy Rivera has
been uploading a lot I see he
uploaded a lot of pieces ESG now
tank with laser beam no more
Volvo stuff no I guess sorry Joe
was kind of we didn't really
discuss it but
John C Dvorak: either way Yes.
Damn Kenny Ben stork with the
car yeah, that's not a Volvo
Adam Curry: that's what I just
said it's not a Volvo
John C Dvorak: Oh okay. That's
what your complaint was no it
that's a cooper it
Adam Curry: looks it looks like
a mini well not even a Mini
Cooper it looks doesn't it's not
it's not a recognizable it looks
like a almost like a suture when
John C Dvorak: it's a clipart
car
Adam Curry: clipart cars No.
Have no particular origins your
particular brand. Matt Boivin,
Baba, thank you very much for
providing us the artwork for
episode 1599. We appreciate that
as always. And let's thank some
people who brought us some
treasure for our six by the way,
John, congratulations. It's been
fun six cylinder episodes. I
think there you go. I think
we've we've we can stop now.
We've done we can quit. We can
quit. I think we're there. I
think we've we've done a good
job. How much longer we're gonna
go we've never escaped
John C Dvorak: that debt. Is it
some sort of a gag?
Adam Curry: How about for real?
John C Dvorak: I think we can go
to 2000 and quit
Adam Curry: 400 More episodes?
Yep. How many?
John C Dvorak: How many spit in
the bucket as
Adam Curry: two more years?
Yeah, it's about right. Yeah,
well 2025 Yeah, that was always
my bitcoin block one. 1 million
was always my target Yeah,
you'll
John C Dvorak: be a rich man you
won't even want to do the show
Adam Curry: and where am I
getting rich from?
John C Dvorak: You cash in your
gold bars?
Adam Curry: The gold bars are
longer I got some coins I got
some silver coins I got some
bitcoin well Bitcoin to 220,000
then yeah then I'll quit I'll
quit on a dime thanks to vorak
by
John C Dvorak: Yeah, that's okay
I can get mo facts to do the
show.
Adam Curry: Oh wait you think
you get to just take the name
you just
John C Dvorak: heal your team
Adam Curry: yeah and steal the
team and you're gonna produce it
John C Dvorak: simple effects
I'll teach you about it you need
to learn this skill
Adam Curry: it's funny because
he was my choice when you keel
over. It's interesting. We both
the same guy in mind about that.
Let's thank our executive and
Associate Executive producers
for episode 1600. And we start
with we got several nights we
got title changes we got some
Daily Show number members we do
have many show
John C Dvorak: we also
introduced the the ADHD
Adam Curry: explained the PhD
because we also
John C Dvorak: were giving out a
PhD and we got to we got 15 So
far people are getting them. Oh
wow. It's a natural it's a
video. It's from note that no
agenda show you'll be granted a
PhD Doctor of Philosophy PhD in
media deconstruction. Oh, like
one of oh, it's
Adam Curry: it's a PhD in
philosophy of media
deconstruction. Yeah,
John C Dvorak: that's what a PhD
is.
Adam Curry: Okay. All right. I
didn't leave there's always
John C Dvorak: been a POC, where
you get a I'm getting a doctor
of media and that's what I
thought there's no doctor of
English he there's no doctor.
Adam Curry: It's a real PhD of a
real subjects philosophy. Yeah.
Ah, okay. So
John C Dvorak: now I have to
tell the story. I
Adam Curry: saw the certificate
by the way, dynamite. I mean, it
I'm putting mine on my wall.
John C Dvorak: I'm putting mine
on my
Adam Curry: wall. Does it come
with a frame? Is it framed or
No, no,
John C Dvorak: it come now you
get your own damn frame. So get
your own damn frame. So I have
to tell the story about how I
came to this. Doing this idea as
an idea. It goes back to when I
was in college. I was a freshman
at Berkeley. And a friend of
mine and myself during the early
days of the Universal Life
Church. We actually got a hold
of Kirby Hensley.
Adam Curry: Yes, I have a huge
I'm a minister of the Universal
Life Church. I have one of
those.
John C Dvorak: But almost
everybody is I think there's 14
million or something like that a
huge number. And so we went to
it. This is the early days. So
we went to his house in Modesto.
It was we me and Andrew hood.
The my partner in crime he was
also a student at Cal is Andrew
still alive? Yeah, I don't know
where he is. Yeah, he doesn't
listen to the show. Okay, he
would have said some. So we go
to Modesto. He Kirby lived in a
little cottage kind of a farm
house and just an attract not a
tract of houses, but like on
some acreage. And so he went in
there and chatted with him. And
he told us what he was up to.
And so before I give give his
little spiel of the story, I
looked up the Wikipedia page on
the Universal Life Church and
Hensley. Unbelievable bullcrap.
So, you're gonna get the real
story here.
Adam Curry: But but the general
idea is, and this is why I got
my minister of the Universal
Life Church. It is, it is a
title that is so official, even
though it's just basically you,
you send the guy money, and he
sends back this ordain
certificate that I was able to
perform weddings. Yeah, I've
done it legally in as a top 40
DJ trick. I'm gonna do a mass
wedding.
John C Dvorak: It's a great bit
it's legal in all the states
except Virginia. Make note
interesting. So anyway, so we
went in there and we got to we
got our you know, our ministers
certificates and then he
mentioned you, would you like a
Doctor of Divinity? And I said,
Oh, yeah. Now in the in the new
in the wiki pages says you have
to get a bunch of training to be
how to start a church. Now. He
just gave us a couple of doctors
of divinity. Now, a couple of
things to note. One, he said he
was illiterate couldn't read,
but memorize the Bible by having
it read to him and he was a
Baptist minister. Oh, I didn't
know the reason he started. The
Universal Life Church, according
to him at the time, was very
similar to L. Ron Hubbard story,
which is that the government
taxes he thought it was a gyp
that, that these churches were
you are getting away with not
having to pay taxes and he
thought anyone who starts just a
one man church should be able to
not pay taxes. And that was the
whole reason for starting this.
He had some grudge against the
tax man. That is not what is
told in the wiki page. It's more
of all love and light. Just a
bunch of bullcrap story now and
it was kind of an interesting,
irascible guy was really a funny
guy, Alabama
Adam Curry: he'd become rich off
of this.
John C Dvorak: I don't know if
he did. He didn't seem like he
cared. He wasn't one of those
guys. He was just a nice guy.
very personable Alabama slight
accent. And so we're leaving and
this is what, to this day, the
sticks in my craw. And I don't
think they do this anymore. But
at the time, as we're two of us
really. We had a nice chat with
him. Probably an hour. And he
says, Hey, do you want a PhD?
And we're leaving and I said it
because I got the doctorate
divinity. I think that's pretty
cool. So then I said no,
Adam Curry: oh, no. And this is
your way of getting back at your
horrible faux pa your canard.
John C Dvorak: It was a complete
blunder looking back on it. I
don't even know if they do the
PhDs anymore. But he said, he
says you want a PhD? I'll give
it to you anything you want.
Adam Curry: Wow. Wow. No, no,
no.
John C Dvorak: So this has been
galling me forever. So I said
hell with it. We're gonna do it.
Adam Curry: All right. And this
is a promotion that lasts how
long? I think we're
John C Dvorak: gonna do it
probably halfway through
November maybe to the end. Okay,
it may be
Adam Curry: the 16th anniversary
promotion.
John C Dvorak: And yeah, 16th is
it 16 years 16th anniversary
promotion? Definitely continues
for the next couple of weeks.
Adam Curry: And it's on it's on
beautiful paper. Like real
diploma paper. Good
John C Dvorak: looks if you
looked at it from any more than
one foot away it looks like and
it's got to seal that whole
thing. We got some seals made no
agenda
Adam Curry: race you. Yes, the
stamp. Oh, wow.
John C Dvorak: We got to
establish has no agenda scholar.
Oh, wow.
Adam Curry: I love it. All
right.
John C Dvorak: Well, so those
are just a donation of $1,000 or
more. It can be added to
anything else you're doing. But
it's it can't be like you know,
you it's not an additive thing.
You know, you pay 10 bucks a
month for five years and get it?
Adam Curry: No, no. Typically,
you'd have to pay $50,000 per
year for four years.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, yeah, we're
saving money.
Adam Curry: Let's thank our
executive producers and Knights
and Dames who showed up for
episode 1600 with a lot of show
number donations. As John
alluded to Jonathan Poehler is
from Coors Ville, Virginia. Hey,
he can't be a minister of the
Universal Life Church. Sorry.
Well, you can but you just can't
marry anyone in Virginia. And he
says first heard Adam on Tom
woods in June of 2021. My full
my full conversion finally took
place 12 months later in June of
2022. With little help from my
friend, Chris some time. I'd
love to hear the full Adam dog
walking song. Well, I don't
think we really have time to
play to play. There wasn't a dog
walking. What was that about? I
can't remember dog walking now.
I think it was. Was that trapped
dog? I don't know. Oh, by the
way too many eggs.com it sir
Jonathan of the fan mountain.
Ugh knots and for supper. This
means that the round to table
he'd like to eat his connais
lays kinase Kenneally catalase.
What a catalase.
John C Dvorak: Cantlay is a
board dough desert at his killer
if you can find somebody knows
how to make them read. They're
kind of they have to be made in
a copper pan is that they're
cute little things you've
probably had when you don't even
Adam Curry: know them on fire.
Do you put them on fire? No.
Okay, and with that he wants a
small glass of colostrum.
John C Dvorak: Oh pool.
Adam Curry: What is colostrum?
John C Dvorak: Just a goop that
comes out of a woman after she
gives birth. Oh.
Adam Curry: Thanks. Thanks,
Jonathan. Good one, bro. Nice.
Okay. All right. As 16 133 top
executive producer and show
dough Norton Show number donor
donor. Thank you very much. And
we will have your request ready
at the roundtable?
John C Dvorak: Yeah. Yeah, put
some saran wrap over a dame CeCe
in Greensboro, Georgia. 1600
another one. Congratulations.
Here's the 1600 more the shown
number donation brings you up to
Baronet Tessa, other than that,
I have nothing clever to say
Thank you both for doing the
work so we don't have to no
jingles no karma. That's nice
name CC. And by the way, both
Jonathan and DMCC will get the
diplomas if they want them. And
those are you had to fill out
the form at the no agenda
rings.com site has got it we got
a link there.
Adam Curry: Okay, so then they
just send their address that
makes it very Yeah, just an
address for shipping. Dame Nancy
is in Waco, Texas 1600 And she
says congratulations and thank
you for 1600 episodes it's an
honor to earn or buy a PhD in
media deconstruction. That's
right Dr. Philosophy Be on the
lookout for the first don't
Austin my waco meetup coming
soon. Damn now Baronet s Nancy
the road trip girlfriend
excellent you get your upgrade
you get your and
John C Dvorak: there's Bruce
Shrum in Harrisburg Pennsylvania
was 1600 is a nice oh please oh
please my donation is small but
could you fake tonight at the
round table? Okay, I would like
to be I would like to be called
out I would like to be called
out in backwards if at all
possible I can't decipher what
Adam Curry: does it mean maybe
it means sir out in sir out in
backwards, sir. out backwards? I
think so.
John C Dvorak: Excuse my stroke.
I will be harder next. We'll try
harder next time sincere Bruce.
Okay.
Adam Curry: Right. Um, I love
that people are just donating
boom, in and out. One and done.
One dude named Ralph Miami,
Florida. John and Adam. Congrats
on reaching 1600 shows I look
forward to proudly displaying my
PhD in media deconstruction. I'd
like Cuban sandwiches and Kapha
CTOs. What are Kapha CTOs? I
have no idea when he wants that
at the roundtable. warmest
regards, dude named Ralph PS.
That's the title for now. Okay,
I'll title TBD for now. All
right.
John C Dvorak: Given that, all
right, that's our $1,600
superstars. Let's start with
those who are still here. Now we
got two donations for the
diploma circus media in Bozeman,
Montana. $1,000.01.
Congratulations on 1600 episodes
in 16 years of programming. I've
been listening since around 900.
And I've listened to every
episode prior to my discovering
the best podcast in universe
according to the Muller report,
thus, the honorific of a
doctorate immediate gets
deconstruction is too enticing
and offer to pass by and quite
arguably, well earned. I agree.
Please accept his binary
donation of 101 in exchange for
the value I've received since
episode 1500 1001 equals 33.
Well done gentlemen. Life is lit
circus media Baron of Bozeman
and greater good Loudoun
Gallatin Valley, Gallatin,
Gallatin dating karma
Unknown: you've got karma
Adam Curry: Nicolas Everts EB
four this is interesting. In
Gallatin, Tennessee, we just had
the greatest Valley All right.
$1,000, no jingles no karma S
and S l. One is SMSL.
John C Dvorak: This is I have no
idea.
Adam Curry: Now Baronet Nikko of
the hills with a PhD in media
dissection named change
appreciated health karma to all
members of the nation. You got
it health karma S and S l.
Unknown: Got karma
John C Dvorak: Stroh Rocha no
shung paying in. Li Lancaster UK
1000 And with his Chinese name,
he says how are all comrades? A
PhD for one kg is too good to
pass up. I'll be known his forte
for that as sir. Why you come
now. Okay. King Wong, please
prepare Chinese hotpot and some
Korean soju for me at the
roundtable. Love the show for
jingles. fisting nuts, then hot
on leg.
Adam Curry: Assisting nuts is
too long. It's not a jingle.
It's a minute long, but I'll
play a little bit of it and you
will get your hot on leg. Just
go for John, tell us your peeve
about the fisting method of
eating snacks.
John C Dvorak: I see this on the
airplane and it's very annoying
and I think it will result in in
fights breaking out as it just
so annoying to watch. guy takes
his bag of peanuts and throws a
pile of them into his palm of
his hand and then he makes a
fist around the nuts.
Adam Curry: I just felt
something hot on my legs. Yes,
you that worked out perfect.
That worked out. Jeff Anderson
is good for 1000 in the morning,
John and Adam, thank you for a
great show. I've been listening
for 15 years Just so have
absolutely earned my doctorate
by now. I will keep praying for
you both and all the producers
and he says go podcasting. Thank
you. Thank you so much brother.
Good to have you here.
John C Dvorak: Jeff Lightner in
Zionsville Pennsylvania 1000 ITM
doctors Oh, wow. And executive
producer knighthood and
doctorate all in one. How can
you resist de douche me please?
Unknown: You've been de deuced
John C Dvorak: I would like to
be knighted Suri. Suri. Yes,
sir. PhD of the south eastern
mountains of Pennsylvania. Give
me a seat at the corner of the
roundtable where the
paratroopers hang out. And I
requested grass fed ribeye and
Genis to celebrate. I'm a
kitchen and bath remodeling
contractor designer, I'd like to
give some bet something back by
offering 25% off to all
producers on kitchen and
bathroom cabinets. If you live
in Pennsylvania 33% off to no
agenda social members. I'm at J
light at no agenda. social.com
just put ITM on the subject line
and email. Jay Lightner J S JT
I'm sorry JTLI de que te l i g h
t any art co J Lightner. CO at
protonmail for the best price
Patriot karma please.
Unknown: You've got
Adam Curry: and we move on to
Thomas sneeze ik sneeze ik I
believe sneeze ik $1,000 Thank
you for your courage please do
Unknown: you've been de deuced
Adam Curry: to me Dr. Tom of
upstate New York F 35 Scream
karma you got it.
Unknown: You've got karma
John C Dvorak: sir otaku and
Flower Mound Texas 1000 years my
tuition for the PhD in media
deconstruction the best
university in the universe. It
comes from the no agenda show
yeah Congratula we have to make
that clear. But congratulations
on 16 years and 1600 episodes
can I get a JCD mac and cheese
with a little girl yay sir oh
taco the Duke of North East
Texas and the Red River Valley.
You slaves get get used to mac
and cheese macaroni and cheese
melted together
Adam Curry: mac and cheese mac
and cheese mac and cheese mac
and cheese everybody. Fan we
move from Sir otaku to Bessie
Tolbert foretold bear hey John
nada my husband hit me in the
mouth a few years ago she says
the T is silent Tober Tober
okay, my husband hit me in the
mouth a few years back it's been
a minute since we donated so
thanks for that reedy douchey
Unknown: you've been de deuced
Adam Curry: appreciate the show
and all the insights you provide
yet karma for everyone Dame
Bessie the T is silent friend to
all creatures great and small
roundtable Manhattan's with
river set right and medium rare
ribeye. Oh very nice. Jingles
resist we much W etc. Seven and
that's true and resist.
Unknown: We much. We must and we
will much about that. Be
committed
Adam Curry: Yes, true.
John C Dvorak: You know, when I
read her note, I looked at it
and she said that he is silent.
I say her How do you pronounce
it old Bert?
Adam Curry: Oh my, um, we better
get more warmed up in the
bullpen?
John C Dvorak: Sure. skywriting
Bethesda, Maryland $1,000 I've
been a producer since show 100
That's Adam quit I quit nice. I
think the 45,000 hours of no
agenda education you to have
produced is more than worthy of
a PhD degree. I don't think that
would be proud to be known as
Sir Skyride. Doctor of media
deconstruction studies.
Adam Curry: Somehow I don't
think it's 45,000 maybe 4500
John C Dvorak: I said 45,000 But
it says 45,000 is note Oh,
Adam Curry: does it No, it
doesn't says 4500 But I say
John C Dvorak: 45 45,000 You
think it's 45,000? No, that's
Adam Curry: what you said. Oh,
nice.
John C Dvorak: What I said I
misread it. Okay, got it.
Adam Curry: Thanks for confusing
us sir. Sky right. You're
welcome sir. dude named Dr.
Kelly. Abbotsford British
Columbia. Oh, well, we're gonna
have to honor this. 730 cans and
avian. Yeah, we've pushed them
up here. That's 1000 in us I
guess we're all Yep, here it is.
John C Dvorak: A man is 1000
Canadian at Canada Navy and now
I have something to say here to
Dr. Kelly for his note first no
till in the morning
Adam Curry: Adam and John here's
my donation of 1000 Canadian
dollar at 730 USD when I heard
about receiving a Doctorate of
deconstruction, I knew I had to
have that title this 1000 also
upgrade me to Baronet Please
play the gun I need a Bitcoin
jingle thanks for keeping us
sane sir dude named Dr. Kelly
Knight of the Fraser Valley
before I play that tell us what
you wanted to say.
John C Dvorak: I don't know I'd
like to know what link he
clicked to donate this money
because it's one of the links
that hooks to the to the old
legacy account so he sent his
note and Jay sent me know saying
do I always have a record of
this guy's donations look in the
legacy accounting there it was
right in the top and I don't
know how you get there from
here.
Adam Curry: Maybe he still just
has that legacy account in his
PayPal. It hangs around
John C Dvorak: you might
something like that does go on
but it's just mystifies me
Adam Curry: Yeah. And so we're
still honoring this for so so
Canada Naviance can now become a
PhD on the cheap
John C Dvorak: well this was a
little gotcha that he brought up
obviously I was not unaware of
the idea I couldn't but no we
had honored we've been honoring
the count these these monies for
so I guess yeah, as you
mentioned on ws as such it's
gonna be a pain in the ass to
ship to anything that Canada
Adam Curry: as you mentioned on
D H unplugged, we got to be nice
to the Kansas aliens because we
went to war with them and they
kicked our ass. They did
Unknown: that saying that all
hell is gonna break loose and
you're gonna need a Bitcoin.
John C Dvorak: Indie no agenda
tribal meetup allocate from
Greenwood, Indiana. This is one
of the Indiana guys 345 That's
the money that came in. That's a
switcheroo. And it's a donation
for Tom Gould. He won the
raffle. QRP dekap Bay dam from
the Indiana no place best meetup
in the known universe courtesy
of Eminem, Mark and Maria. Vert
tus tunics mores Nan seperate
Latin there, what does that
mean? I have no idea. I mean,
everybody's virtuous until they
get drunk. No jingles? No karma,
but I would like a small shout
out shoot. Shout out to the
Revolutionary War Veterans
Association for Project
Appleseed. www. Appleseed.
info.org Okay,
Adam Curry: it's actually a
virtue has united and deaths
shall not separate it is the
Masonic Messiah from the Masons.
No, okay, I got it wrong. Aaron
Brzezinski is an Atewa Tennessee
333 dot 33 All he says is please
do douchey
Unknown: you've been de deuced
John C Dvorak: is another one
does the Portland meet up in
Portland? Nice he got out alive.
Switcheroo. Needless to say we
survive being doxxed by our
friendly neighborhood hater.
Friendly Neighborhood hater is a
symbol for connection and
protection. The donation
credited to Stephanie Stephanie
gets this one for future game
when we have to douchebags in
attendance that contributed to
our communal donation so we need
to D deuces.
Unknown: You've been D deuced.
Verse one. D deuced
John C Dvorak: with some good
karma, but he wants to mention
that since I've been blocked by
John's email on several
occasions, a quote John blocked
me jingle is in order if you
have one. Lol. Thanks for
keeping us sane. I don't know
what that is mystery to me.
Thanks for keeping us sane and
from getting us all jacked up by
the am 5am Stay safe.
Adam Curry: We do not have a
blocked jingle.
Unknown: You've got
Adam Curry: to look forward to
the show every Sunday and
Thursday spread the show out
over two days driving to and
from work. It's highly enjoyable
and definitely helped me keep a
grip on what Saturday I had left
during the pandemic. And then he
says he has a funny story about
Glenn Beck which is I did read
this. My lovely wife and I went
to an And Then There Were None
event in the Dallas Fort Worth
area of the event was a Glenn's
Museum. Next, the mercury
studios. We've talked about this
phenomenal Museum. He was the
keynote of the My wife is on the
board of the group. And so we
got VIP access. Glenn walked in
saw me smiled like we hadn't
seen each other for a while,
walked right up, shook my hand
and I said hi Glenn. Really easy
like I knew he'd come up to me
and he said hi back smiling.
Then I said not a joke. I give
my word as a non Biden. I said,
I really love it when you have
Adam curry on your show. What an
idiot I thought to myself, but
then he just started going off
about how awesome you are and
how smart you are, and whatnot.
It was very funny. Keep up the
good work. Next time I see him
I'll name drop Jhansi Dvorak.
John C Dvorak: Well, I've told
the story before. I caught them.
One of the episodes, and I
caught back live on the air
going on about how he thinks
you're his brother.
Adam Curry: Yes. from another
mother. Yes.
John C Dvorak: doppelganger.
Yes.
Adam Curry: We look so much
alike. Yeah.
John C Dvorak: And because he
just was very he's very
impressed with Adam curry.
Adam Curry: Let me tell you the
Glenn Beck audience has has
come. They're here. He has very
he's really helped. He is He has
helped with our audience, our
producer attendance. So we
appreciate that it's
John C Dvorak: a plus, is it
because we provide something
nobody else seems to provide?
Adam Curry: And Jeremy wants a
jobs card with a goat screen.
Unknown: Jobs, jobs, jobs and
jobs.
John C Dvorak: Let's vote for
jobs. Ashley Corollas need
Ville, Texas named for a town
congratulations on your 16 100th
episode. Thanks for
deconstructing the M five M and
the knowledge you to both carry
around in those big brains. You
have a shout out the saddle
tramp she's the bee's knees.
Peace be with you.
Adam Curry: No. Okay, and F
cancer that was the next one.
I'm sorry. I got confused. I
went You went too early. I'm
sorry. I went too early. I heard
sidled tramp and like oh, we're
good. We're saddled tramp and
went to the next one, which is
Eric Tolbert, or told bear
John C Dvorak: to bear. Olmert
Adam Curry: Holbert Topeka,
Kansas 333 33 Hello, longtime
listener, sporadic contributor,
please give me a deal
Unknown: you've been doing?
Adam Curry: Yes, you're right.
You're right. It's from the same
family. I would like to
congratulate my smokin hot wife
on becoming a dame on show 1600
Love you Dame Bessie. The T is
silent. We've been listening
since Adams ChIAT run days with
Brian and Susie. Oh, wow. Wow,
that is a long time ago. Please
give me an F cancer jingle and a
health karma for all who needed
thanks for keeping us all saying
the Mad farmer Eric Albert or
toll bear whichever one is
correct.
Unknown: You've got karma?
John C Dvorak: Do we come up to
sure James Fukumoto in Salem,
Virginia. 33333. been over a
year since my last donation the
bottle number of The Mailbox I
shared with my smokin hot
girlfriend was bottle 33. Time
to donate. Thanks for the great
show Sir James Fukumoto, Black
Knight,
Adam Curry: and then we have sir
Mr. Bob Dodd Billina Bob da
bilena San Diego California 333
Hey guys, sir Mr. Bob double
Lena here love the Ph. D. ID. I
have another one for those who
donated $2,000 Plus, they earned
the title His or Her Excellency.
Now we're fine. We're good
honorifics. So from now on. I
want to be referred to His
Excellency Mr. Bob Dobbs Alina,
I'll be the first rock on Ubu
brother just put it in your
donation note we'll be happy to
John C Dvorak: call anyone
excellency James Anderson's up
next call him that he's in
Vancouver, Vancouver but not
Vancouver. Canada is in
Vancouver Washington. Which is a
real smart money place to live
you get the no personal income
tax of Washington State and you
jump on the bridge you go right
to Portland and there's no sales
tax. With as welkeys Yeah, but
you can you can navigate them. I
see Emma John and Adam, Adam
cane Adam and John Forgive me
I've been a boner for too long.
And again, my contribution of
320 double 160 donation is the
tithing that I offer the BP itu
what uh, what is that clip of
some general talking about why
America became the world police
after World War Two. I would
like to find the entire speech
because that was Wesley Clark.
No, no. Oh, no, he's talking
about I'm pretty sure he's
talking about the speech by
Miley. Oh my Lea we played
that's what he talks about
specifically the world police
Miley or milli, Milli, milli
milli Milan. What did I think
Miley Cyrus? Did milli milli
Cyrus 1600 Night previous
accounting below please title me
Sir James at the Southwest
Washington as always ready
already night for hookers and
blow. I would like for jobs
karma, but I think it is more
important to send F 35 karma to
my son in the army and I think
so too. Sir. James is southwest
Washington.
Unknown: He's got karma.
Adam Curry: And with 316 33
Gaucho woodworking in Redondo
Beach, California. Happy 60th
anniversary and you never How to
Fight Gaucho wooden craft.com.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, I forgot to
mention her name in a recent
show. And who and new Scott
Anushka Anushka warty in
Lafayette California is right
around here. She could come to
the meetup Thank ya i Why Why
Yipes overdue. Sorry. Happy want
1600 I don't have a clever
number joke to make so I'll just
say this still enjoying no
agenda every Thursday and
sometimes every Sunday. give
gifts give CELTA something for
failure.
Adam Curry: teared? Oh,
John C Dvorak: it's always this
Dutch. Yes.
Adam Curry: It's a fairly I'd
say it's a fairly she teared.
John C Dvorak: So she came out
to under 50 bucks and she's
Associate Executive Producer.
Adam Curry: Also associate exec
with a great number two three
4.56 from Redondo West Mike
sislo. Ah, hello, Mike. I know
Mike his. His wife. Who is Dane
elemental gypsy of the manasota
key was stayed here.
John C Dvorak: The without Mike
without Mike.
Adam Curry: Yes, she is. She
arrived on Wednesday as she and
the keeper. A Tuesday I think Is
she in the keeper left
Wednesday. They're on a hiking
trip with six other women. I
think all of them are no agenda
listeners I believe is going on
as we speak as we speak. Yes, it
is just me and Phoebe in the
house. It is the chicks explorer
group. I think it's what they're
called. And Mike says seeing as
our wives are started some gang
out terrorizing parts of Utah.
Yeah, there Bryce Canyon. I felt
compelled or you know, yeah, I'm
a little gel. I felt yelled I
knew I get you with that one. I
felt compelled to get a donation
to the show in case you needed
to front some bail money. Keep
up the awesome work. And when
you run for mayor you got my
vote. Thanks for Mike Mike.
Thank you brother. Excellent.
And your your Dame is very, very
nice lady. We had we had a good
laugh with her. Just funny.
John C Dvorak: Zane Hart in
bars. Scrub a Queensland
Australia. The switcheroo is for
Daryl James make a note from
from his son, Zane Hart. He is
one of the OG day one listeners
and has been chipping away
towards knighthood since v four
v started hoping this may push
him over the line first and last
time I'm happy to be punched in
the mouth. Using this note
Stronach. You're a mando douche
bag. Douche bag
Adam Curry: Sorry, sorry, sorry.
John C Dvorak: Please play
please play all the karma ISOs
every single one of them at
least 2x speed because speed
casting is lit bitches
Adam Curry: now I'm not going to
do that but I did come up with
something else for him. I forgot
to do all the in the mornings in
a row
thought that was a lot better. I
think so to Justin the squeaky
growler guys in Hayden Idaho 201
Howdy gents. I'm donating in
honor of my daughter, Cameron
turning 10 on the 19th test
today. Who always asked to
listen to the birthday call outs
if possible. I'd like a D
douching.
Unknown: You've been D deuced.
Adam Curry: Along with a Pelosi
Let's vote for jobs and Obama
said jobs karma I guess. And a
Obama NO NO NO NO jingles Okay.
I'm going to do one of them.
Yes. Justin the squeaky car
washing grower guy of Carter
lane. Code Lane Idaho. You got
it. I've been watching you
Unknown: I love your jobs, jobs,
jobs and jobs.
John C Dvorak: Let's vote for
jobs. Karma. Ted home Meyer in
Rancho Santa Margarita,
California. 200. listening for
the show. listening for a little
while now. My smokin hot wife
Cindy. Hit me in the mouse. It's
good. Love what you to do keep
up the great work. Ted homebuyer
nice. No thank
Adam Curry: you, Ted. You wanna
do this next one since it's kind
of Linda Lou pad Ken.
John C Dvorak: Would Colorado.
Yes. Job search for a resume
that gets results go to Image
makers inc.com For all your
executive resume Job Search
needs does image makers Inc with
k.com or just find Linda LAPACK
and under the show's producer
list job here's the 1600 more
Unknown: jobs, jobs, jobs and
jobs for jobs
right
Adam Curry: then we have Forrest
Tucker Eagle River Arkansas 200
donation for show 1600 from
Eagle River Alaska request a de
douche
Unknown: you've been de deuced
Adam Curry: wants a jobs karma
and one jingle if time to get my
nation national anthem at the
end of show in honor of 1600
Pennsylvania Avenue here's to
four years of amygdala shrinkage
Thank you very much
Unknown: jobs, jobs, jobs and
jobs for jobs.
John C Dvorak: And Kyle Lewis in
Lyndhurst, New Jersey wraps
things up in his group with a
$20 Switcheroo see the attached
note dare crack button Buzzkill.
It this writing is just come to
my attention that I married a
douchebag Oh, this is
unacceptable for the good of
this marriage and my remaining
dignity deed douche my wife Erin
immediately.
Unknown: You've been de deuced
John C Dvorak: she put up with
me these 12 years dating back
when you crossed our first year
married on September 24. So give
her all the donation credit. No
agenda has become a staple
during our long car rides and I
have found the l ai search
engine to be boom boom. A boon
of information I think in
reference material add in
jingles M five in med
deconstruction original artwork
in the best meet up surround and
you can easily have the best
podcast in the universe. Thank
you for all your courage. Love
is led Kyle. Jingles. Burgundy?
Burgundy? John C. Dvorak boobs
and screaming dog karma. Let me
see. You still there?
Adam Curry: Yeah, yeah, I'm
still here. I'm looking for the
boobs.
John C Dvorak: Boobs. Boobs.
Boobs. Boobs. Boobs. I can just
say boobs.
Adam Curry: Now. Just funny is
funny if we have boobs. I got
boobs here. I got the boobs
here. You do? Yeah, I got the
boobs and what was this? What is
screaming dog?
John C Dvorak: It's just a
digestate good karma. No.
Adam Curry: Asian dog.
John C Dvorak: Oh, the Asian Law
dog is Boobs. Boobs. Boobs.
Boobs. Boobs. Boobs. Boobs,
boobs. boobs, boobs, boobs.
Boobs. Boobs, boobs, boobs boobs
Adam Curry: and the final
associate Oh no, that's it. That
was the last six hosts the
executive producer. We are going
to go through the list you want
to split this week? Just so
everybody knows. We really only
read the notes for executive and
Associate Executive Producers
that's really for just to give
you more show every single no
agenda episode. So if we screw
something up like people like
you didn't do it right you miss
something it's kind of at our
discretion. So I think that you
should be pretty strict with
with these John because everyone
has a note here. A D douching.
is always appreciated.
John C Dvorak: SEPTA de douching
is we'll get those and
Adam Curry: and we do need to
read Carl's or Watsky note
because he becomes a knight.
John C Dvorak: Once you start
then this is read read 10 I'll
read 10 You read 10 and I read
10 would be done.
Adam Curry: So he's a Niles,
Illinois this donation brings me
to knighthood is 160 dot 33. I'd
like my name to be sir elles que
tem and whatever's at the table
already has fine. Follow at El
que tem on no agenda social for
the worst memes on the internet.
Thank you for your courage. Oh
Vikon silver dude of the silver
dolphins 160 Thank you Kevin and
Priscilla O'Leary from Ramona,
California 160. These of course
are in an honors roll 161 60s
Yeah, for 1600s episode, sir
escape logic from Spring Hill,
Tennessee. cerveza. Florissant.
Colorado. Sir John from London.
Great Britain. Thank you.
Timothy Berkshires in
Cookeville, Tennessee. We have
me K MC with one six see Matt
Dixon Spring Hill, Tennessee
Linda Terry in Rochester, New
Hampshire. Simon Jiang in
Lawrenceville, Georgia. And
Jacob Vaughn Van Dusen in
Pittsburgh Pittsfield
Massachusetts who needs a dee
doo
John C Dvorak: dee doo SBT Good.
I'll take the lesser ones as we
go on with Ducey and Powell moto
Paula moto in Oviedo, Florida
144 Brianna in Lafayette,
Louisiana went 3333
Adam Curry: Brandon needs a D
douching. She comes from the
Glenn Beck show. There's proof
John C Dvorak: you've been de
deuced sir Karl in Cary, North
Carolina. 12345. Kiss Sherlyn
Phillips and Mead Washington
nice named 9940. Christian
ghoulish in Lake Land at Florida
at 86 with a D douche.
Unknown: You've been de deuced.
John C Dvorak: And here we go
with Kevin McLaughlin from
Concord, North Carolina. The
Duke of Luna lover of American
boobs was 808 with breast cancer
awareness month, fighting for
the top TAS the top TAs. Sir dan
in Alpharetta, Georgia also 808
and Edward Owens in Alameda,
California 808. Tyler gets in
Fort Wayne, Indiana at Chad
Larson in White Bear Lake
Minnesota. These are all 80s I
just do 80s I'll just list them
off and get to the end of 80s.
You take it Chad Larson and
White Bear Lake Chris anglers
are Chris in Ancaster, Ontario,
Jacqueline lense and Muskego
Muskego Muskego. Wisconsin,
Christopher Rubio in Irvine,
California, Rita Harrington and
sparks Nevada JMC services in
Milford, Michigan cheers to 16
Kevin Miller in Carrick on
Shannon in Ireland. There's our
Ireland and Ireland. Look, Sean
Milligan and then you've got
Adam Curry: Sean Milligan
Hamilton, Ontario, he says was
$75 Zippy rocks. Thank you.
David Jarman in North Tara Mara.
Turramurra I think it is Turnham
or a New South Wales Australia.
7117 Oh, no, it's Tara Mara.
Tara Mara,
John C Dvorak: there we go. Rob
Mara,
Adam Curry: North Terra Mara
Terry Boyles becomes a knight I
believe so this is 606 this is
small boobs, and says back on
July 7 2017, I started my lowly
$4 week donation now as of
Friday, October 13. I have
donated a total of 1312. I've
been a night for the last 78
weeks and didn't even realize
it. Time flies when you're
having so much fun. First
introduced to no agenda watching
cranky geeks. I knew John from
the days of PC mag would come
wrapped in plastic and when
opened floppy disks later CDs
was Fallout Oh joy. You would
have Adam as a guest on cranky
geeks with him Hawking his
latest brand ambassador product
what? What products that I Hawk
on cranky geeks? Something some.
The first few times I listened
to the podcast I thought you too
are a couple of conspiracy
theorists. But I'm glad I stuck
with it. And I learned the
truth. Thank you for all the
years of entertainment and
deconstruction. I'd like to be
known as surly of Renton I would
like some McCulley curry Korean
rice wine at the roundtable I
could use a de douching some
serious jobs caution
Unknown: you've been de deuced
macro Have you ever
Adam Curry: had Makalali since
I'm not sure what it is just a
good product doesn't sound like
it thanks again for all the
years and John sorry that sorry
the keyboard did not work out
for you. It could have could
have made you a millionaire Best
regards, Terry aka surly I'll
give you the series jobs karma
John has nothing to do with that
keyboard jobs,
Unknown: jobs, jobs and jobs
that
Adam Curry: people believe and
it's likely true that you
invented the DVORAK Keyboard.
small boobs from Sir Kevin
O'Brien O'Brien in Chicago,
Illinois, or Kevin McLaughlin
with the small boobs 606 Breast
Cancer Awareness Month saved the
hand warmers and there's Dame
Rebecca from Pinehurst with a
606 and she longs to meet Sir
Kevin McLaughlin someday. Well
now and bed
John C Dvorak: and Lewis content
ladies when they meet Kevin
McLaughlin Luis
Adam Curry: Conte is in receipt
a California that's home of The
Raven, James Edmondson South
Plainfield, New Jersey with
double nickels on the dime
Richard Futter from London Duck
Duck Well, nickels on the dime
Diem Roker 5510 Ellen Ellen
Becker from Wauwatosa, Wisconsin
5510 Sir by His grace hello
David, Jacksonville, Florida.
You stoked to be a part of the
movement? Frederick from the
hacker Amsterdam 55 Night
formerly known as Fred Fred
wood, Fred Friendswood, Texas 52
Sir Michael Anthony a lot of
indoor show mixtures Michael
Anthony Rosedale New York, and
he quit his daily cannabis
cough, caffeine and nicotine
simultaneously to optimize his
carnivore diet. Here's some
scratch that I saved Franklin
month to Rosa in Dodge City,
Kansas 5160 And Matthew drop co
in Li IRA or Li Li ra Ohio for
his late birthday turned 51 On
September 25, thank you for your
courage. It's pronounced e
Illyria. Illyria Illyria. Got
it. And Sir Sergeant postle 5033
from Miami Lakes Miami Lakes
Jeremy Whad one red one in
Seminole, Florida 5016 and John
will take us through the 50s
John C Dvorak: exactly Jaya and
these are all $50 donors name
and location starting with Joan
polls. in Hernando Beach,
Florida, Nathan Cochran in
Franklin, Tennessee, Tatiana
Prince in Hollywood, Florida,
Peter odo in Ridge New York,
Mike Gaul, McHale and dren and
Ren in Sweden Scott lavender in
Montgomery, Texas, gadget freak
10 in Western Springs, Illinois,
Alexandre ver de HO in Gig
Harbor, Washington, Luke Olsen
and Alexandria, Virginia where
you can't do the marriage. Cory
Bennett in Denver, Colorado
Fletcher Scaife and there's a
Skyfi escapes guide. I don't
know how to pronounce that name.
Wilston North Dakota, Joe Oswald
in Lithia, Florida, Chris Cowan
in Austin, Texas, Andrew gusik
in Greensboro, North Carolina,
Fabian bebber, or Bieber or
better be BB er, in Winnenden
Deutschland at Irwin, Irwin on
Sondra in Holland and vostre
vite
Adam Curry: word close Oh
surveyed veered and it's also
right to Dear Evan Hanson Grace
those two people Erwin and
Sondra
John C Dvorak: and birds in in
Sundra. Not eating and wrapping
it up. Wrapping it up. Baron
Allen being in Beaverton, Oregon
gets around used to be in
Oakland and the last on the list
is Tracy Sullivan in Tinley
Park, Illinois. Want to thank
these people for making the show
1600 a huge success. showing us
some appreciation and love.
Adam Curry: Yes. Oh yeah.
Donating is loving. We
appreciate that. And of course
everyone who came in under $50
For reasons of anonymity and
thank you for those who have
continuously been on those
sustaining donations. You see
right here we have a knight
coming up for dollars. So all
kinds of donations can get you
that coveted knight or Dame
ring. Now we don't have a
ceremony for the PhDs. I'm just
we are
John C Dvorak: going to put one
together. Okay. And we're going
to do a malt we're gonna do
bunches so there's gonna be may
be two groups of graduates
Adam Curry: just like a real
graduation ceremony. Yeah,
John C Dvorak: I love it exactly
the same. If you'd
Adam Curry: like to become a
producer of the no agenda show
you can still go to this address
vo red.org/in Orange try our
swanky new one at no agenda
donations.com And thank you for
producing episode 1600 Our
formula
Unknown: is this we go out yet
people in the mouth
Adam Curry: don't want to do the
title changes we'll do the
birthdays in a moment. title
changes today DMCC becomes
Baronet this name Nancy the
roadtrip girlfriend also Baronet
this and Sir dude named Dr.
KELLY BECOMES A Baronet. And
congratulations to all three of
you and thank you for supporting
the no agenda show an additional
$1,000.
Matthew dropped go turn 51 On
September 25. Happy Birthday
Matthew Justin the squeaky
growler guy wishes his daughter
care, Cameron. Happy Birthday
turns 10 Today, I think I said
Cameron earlier sir Kyle back as
your cow back wishes his smokin
hot wife Isabella Murcia, happy
birthday for tomorrow. And we
say happy birthday to Douglas
merry Happy Birthday Brett
Murray. Happy birthday from
everybody here the best podcast
in the universe. We have two
night notes for some nights who
will be knighting tonight
actually do we have two or just
one? I think we have one. Let me
see that I missed one
John C Dvorak: was one where you
missed a knighting and a person
needs to be anonymous. And it's
kind of
Adam Curry: anonymous spirit of
the north woods here driving
1077 miles from Tomahawk,
Wisconsin to Charlotte, North
Carolina to experience the
thirsty Third Thursday meet up
didn't want to show up as a
commoner did I miss this person?
John C Dvorak: No. Remember what
happened was the note came in
after the show.
Adam Curry: I thought I thought
I read this. Like Well,
John C Dvorak: we read I think
part of it was read but I don't
think the knighting part was
done or handled.
Adam Curry: It has to be redone.
Something was done incorrectly.
Okay, it was
John C Dvorak: yeah, we know
exactly what it is. And we can
talk about it after the show.
It's
Adam Curry: okay I'm struggling
for a night name. So for now
call me certainly not please
rustle up some pickled pike. An
old forester rye whiskey for the
roundtable I have that I'm gonna
just put that in here. Was there
some I think there was another
one was there another donation
that I missed here? Another make
good
John C Dvorak: I thought what
else is on that sheet?
Adam Curry: I don't see it.
Okay, then I guess we're okay.
John C Dvorak: I guess you're
probably okay if it's not on the
sheet and Okay,
Adam Curry: we're good. Well, we
do have some dame's we have a
dame and we have some night
Yikes. Yeah, I'm gonna need I'm
gonna need a like a huge massive
sword from you.
John C Dvorak: I got the big boy
here. The two hander. Whoa. That
Adam Curry: was big. All right
up on the podium. Bessie Tolbert
anonymous spirit or the
Northwoods Jonathan polar Bruce
Suam dude named Ralph Shuang
Pang. Jeff Lightner. James
Anderson, Carl was outski and
Terry Broyles you're all about
to become a night end knights
and dame of the no agenda show.
So I hereby pronounce to Kate v
as Dame Bessie. The T is silent
friend to all creatures great
and small. Certainly not sure
Jonathan or the fan mountain dog
nods sir out in backwoods sir
dude named Ralph sir why you
come now? Sir, Yes, sir. PhD of
the South southeastern mountains
of Pennsylvania, Sir James of
Southwest Washington, sir el que
tem, surly of Renton. And for
you, we've got the irregular
hookers and blow rent boys and
Chardonnay and quite an
assortment of stuff. connais
lays with a small glass of
colostrum, Cuban sandwiches and
cafecito is Chinese hotpot with
some Korean soju grass fed rib
eyes and Guinness Manhattan's
with river set right and medium
rare ribeyes McCobb, my
colleague Michael Lee, and
pickled pike and old forester
rye whiskey along with that, of
course, Rubenesque women and
Rosie Gates's and sakeI vodka,
salmonella, bong hits and
bourbon, sparkling cider and
escorts ginger ale and dribbles,
breast milk and pablum. And as
always, we have here at the
roundtable your mutton and
Unknown: me.
Adam Curry: Congratulations and
thank you so much for supporting
the no agenda show again, thank
you to our executive and
Associate Executive producers
for 1600 those titles are real
and you can proudly present
those at any place that
recognizes the things like the
credits, you know imdb.com Go
ahead you if you don't have an
account that you can open one
bigwigs are there as well put it
on your LinkedIn or in your
resume or just put on a business
card it picks up all kinds of
legal in bars. And thank you
again for supporting us the no
agenda show some of you for 1600
episodes. It is highly
appreciated. No one said
Well, we've got no agenda nation
out supporting us and
celebrating today on this
Thursday the 19th in North Idaho
sanity brigade, is about to get
underway at Selkirk Abbey in
Post Falls. We have the North
Georgia monthly also coming up
very soon at Cherry Street
brewing in Alpharetta, Georgia.
Charlotte's Thursday Third
Thursday this evening at seven
at edge Tavern in Charlotte,
North Carolina. The central Ohio
group comes together tomorrow at
five o'clock at Dempsey's food
and spirits in Columbus, Ohio.
On Saturday, the final Fibonacci
farewell one o'clock at Flipz
Patio Grill, Fort Worth Texas
Motorworks mica meet up that'll
be on Saturday as well at
Motorworks brewery and Brandon's
in Florida two o'clock. The you
know the thing meet up two
o'clock Starbucks What 21 920
highway 99 in Edmonds in
Edmonds, Washington. Oh boy,
that should be fun. That
Saturday also on Saturday, the
threat to democracy Awareness
Month meet up at three o'clock
at Crazy pins in Fort Wayne,
Indiana. And we have these
Saturday Milwaukee club 33.3
might be 33 33.3 at 3:30pm sent
Throw Lakefront Brewery in
Milwaukee Wisconsin. And also on
Saturday the northern Silicon
Valley get John out of the house
meet up and John will be there
at Club Mallard in Albany
California
John C Dvorak: that you
recommend people go to this one
because if I'm not mistaken I
haven't been there for that bar
for years but they have the best
looking coasters of any bar
anywhere and you should grab a
few. There's a Tip
Adam Curry: Tip from your
posters for your Meetup and the
South Jersey John Fetterman is
neck tumor Memorial. Four
o'clock Eastern at Miller's Ale
House in Mount Laurel Township,
New Jersey before we finish this
out, we do have one of those
fabulous meetup reports from the
indie group. This is their
October meetup there's a lot of
people hello it's Sir Martin
Unknown: de Maria from
Indianapolis meetup something
extraordinary is going to be
coming at you in December
December for you today looking
forward to see all the Midwest
people here and
if you want to fly in let us
know this is
Emily letting you know that
Brian was and I will be
attending the Brian with the I
Indianapolis meetup in December
all the single ladies out there
he is single and ready to
mingle. Bruce
from Indy Webalizer out
in the morning John Adams. I am
a Dutch reptilian and John If
you don't learn how to pronounce
your Dutch words are good to eat
your children
in the morning Sean from
Bloomington I dragged my brother
down here Gary here Bill Gates
now says that climate change
will kill the world look out
South Africa there's a new
patenting the vaccine coming
your way this is Mike the
POLYMATH easy peasy podcast
sorry Adam but you're not
allowed to stay on my couch
in the mornings on an atom it's
Kyle from Zionsville keep the
African news coming
in the morning Dane Trinity
having a great time in India
despite what Trevor says in the
morning this is Alicia thank you
for your courage John and Adam.
Hey guys, it's Diane in Indiana.
We are excited about your common
can't wait I
ordered from Indianapolis I
honorifics
are saya thank you for your
courage for
PBR street gang and I have
nominated Adam for an award in
Indy
Hi, this is Cindy from Carmel in
the morning thank you for your
courage and I must say everybody
has really nice shoes on today
here in the morning James wanted
deserve any simulator.
This is Shannon invading from
the north via a paraglider and
morning Tom not from Carmel home
of a jerk
around just as fly count of
Hamilton in the two pennies and
I want to wish everyone a happy
global wash your hands
Hi guys my name is him I work at
prodigy burger and I've had the
chance to serve these wonderful
people and I think we all had a
great time
Adam Curry: love those reports
Thank you Sir Mark and de Maria
and yes carrying the keeper will
be out there for a no agenda
slash Corinne the keeper meet up
on December 4 Looking forward to
it. And I guess Sir Brian with
an I will be there as well. Oh
boy. No agenda meetups. If
you've never been to one Do
yourself a favor right now is
the time that you need to hang
out with people. You need that
connection. It will give you
protection and you can calm down
calm down. Calm down. Look at
some people look at them in the
face. Look at their facial
expressions. You'll feel good
about it. No agenda meetup.com
If you can't find one near you,
then please start one yourself.
It's easy. Sometimes you go hang
out with Bom Bom you won't be
triggered everybody feels the
same. It's like a party like a
party people. It's just like a
party. It's trust me. It's like
a party.
John C Dvorak: It's almost like
a party. Do you have an idea for
a shows?
Adam Curry: I think I got a
couple of good ones actually. I
think a is it do I start? Is
that the Yeah, it was
John C Dvorak: mites are less
sensitive.
Adam Curry: dealio Okay, do it
for your penis. All right,
that's
John C Dvorak: nuts out.
Adam Curry: I am not woke. Mm
hmm. This feels good. Huh. And
this This is this is I think the
kicker? What does this have
Unknown: to do with podcasting?
John C Dvorak: Come on. I liked
that one. But I don't think I
think that I think it should be
more about the show.
Adam Curry: Well, that's why
like, what does this have to do
about the podcast? And that's
why I thought it was a good one.
John C Dvorak: Okay, well, I
have one about the show that I'm
not gonna skip the stupid one
because there's no good anyway.
But I think try generations.
Adam Curry: generations will not
forget. Hmm, okay.
John C Dvorak: Okay, well, then
here's one that refers to the
show. Not going.
Adam Curry: And we are not going
anywhere. Yeah, that's not bad.
Yeah.
John C Dvorak: And then the last
one is just because this show is
long and it's show 1600 Just a
round of applause.
Adam Curry: This has a real
please Clap vibe. I think not
going anywhere is pretty good.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, I do do
Adam Curry: I think I think
that's I think that's the winner
right there. That's the winner.
The winner
John C Dvorak: because we're not
going anywhere.
Adam Curry: We're not going
anywhere people.
John C Dvorak: I know we're
gonna be here on Sunday.
Adam Curry: Yes. Do you? Do you
have one last clip you want to
play? I do
John C Dvorak: have one less
clip which is interesting. It's
a suit to Dan update. So it
keeps us on Africa clip if you
haven't noticed. last clip of
the show six months
Unknown: of war in Sudan have
plunged the country into one of
the worst humanitarian
nightmares in recent history,
killing up to 9000 people and
displacing over 5 million. That
was the stark warning issued by
the United Nations which said at
least 25 million people in Sudan
are also in need of urgent
humanitarian relief.
Humanitarian Aid Relief has been
hindered by violence between the
Sudanese army and the rapid
support forces since fighting
broke out in April. The
healthcare situation is also
dire. As many medical facilities
and conflict areas have been
shuttered. Human rights groups
have condemned the ongoing
targeting and killing of
civilians and journalists. That
Committee to Protect Journalists
is demanding an investigation
into the October 10 killing of
Sudanese journalist Halima Idris
Salim, who died after RSF
fighters reportedly ran over her
with a vehicle while she covered
the conflict in the city of
undermined
Adam Curry: Nothing says let's
end the show on a high note by
someone getting run over that's
really nice and is it Sudan or
Sue Don
John C Dvorak: this done so this
is what's going on you know,
although everything is breaking
loose just gotta control and
this Diane is just a mess.
Adam Curry: I want to thank
everybody very much from the
bottom of my heart and my wife's
bottom as well thank you very
much for supporting us for 1600
episodes some of you you know
who you are for those who are
new for those who came over from
different appearances and I'm
just kind of stuck around and
take it out that this is a place
for sanity and for good and
perfect size amigos we thank you
for supporting us without you we
could not do it that's why
you're not listeners you're not
fans you are producers. And
don't you forget it thank you
John C Dvorak: yeah I second
debt
Adam Curry: by request we have
the get one nation national
anthem coming up sound guy Steve
with a classic riding with Biden
and Maddie j with a little look
back at some of the liquids John
drinks during the show from the
past episodes. And up next on no
agenda stream. We have planet
rage. Episode number 99. So stay
tuned for that coming to you. As
always from the heart of the
Texas hill country here in FEMA
Region number six in the morning
everybody. I'm Adam curry
John C Dvorak: in from Northern
Silicon Valley where everybody's
celebrating show 1600 Who else
can do that? I'm Josie Devorah
Adam Curry: we return on Sunday
and we are looking forward to it
in our 16 weeks here as we soon
will be celebrating 16 years
together as well and we never
had a fight see on 1601
Everybody and in the meantime
remember us it to vorak.org/na
or no agenda donations.com Until
then adios mofos or Hui Hui ants
Unknown: ladies and gentlemen
please rise for your demo nation
My name is Mo we are to be human
resources as in all lands from
the east to the west down the
land we
ready we are united and that's
what we did we stayed United
Adam Curry: American government
spend more money
Unknown: it matters. I'll be
honest with you, as always
promised every day all supply
and justify you agree with the
vote falsify. And justify for
years to come. All Americans
have repeatedly shown that they
will not tolerate anyone who
tries to take your country
backwards. We're going to be
okay. I call it Building a
Better America. By no news about
what's happening can seem
alarming to all Americans. But
the next few days, weeks and
months will be hard on my watch
To know whether we're going to
be okay. In the history of this
era is when America will be
weaker and the rest of the world
stronger. Everyone from students
to retirees to teachers proud
proud people pound for pound
ready to fight with every inch
of earners do they have this is
a real test is gonna take time.
It hasn't worked for working
people in this nation for too
long. All across America.
John C Dvorak: I get it. It's
one of
Unknown: my top priorities
getting Americans under control
and throughout our history to
cause more chaos. Every
administration says they'll do
it. Now everyone sees it
clearly. I really need to think
about this moment that our
character this generation has
formed purposes. A futures for
America as we stand ready to do
more if necessary. Think about
not looking to punish anybody.
All Americans have repeatedly
shown that they will not
tolerate anyone who tries to
take their country backwards.
That's great. And I agree. Oh,
what
Adam Curry: are you drinking?
John? What are you drinking?
What are you drinking? What are
you drinking? What are you
drinking? What are you drinking?
What are we drinking today?
John C Dvorak: Today's beverage
of choices. My last bottle of
Topo G Joe Pellegrino is
cinsaut. Just plain old polar
Okay, his polar unflavored
natural seltzer. Seltzer,
Unknown: Seltzer, seltzer.
John C Dvorak: Seltzer is
sparkling water and unfiltered
sparkling water with
electrolytes
Adam Curry: I'll take the opium
and warm orange juice please
John C Dvorak: I really like low
bandwidth, which is a bubbling
water from France through
shitters but that is the Blue
Bottle Perry which had the bad
dua sparkle would look quite
pure. What's it called the Troy
the crock. I said look, wow, the
quarry.
Adam Curry: The CRO
John C Dvorak: CRO rob the
chronic and the CRO CRO water.
Overpriced bubbly water in a
cat. Well, water can be very
tasty.
Adam Curry: It's heavenly. We
haven't tested yet since it has
no COVID
John C Dvorak: V eight sparkling
energy. orange pineapple drink.
more caffeine than a cola was
jacked up on this energy drink.
Adam Curry: You know that's good
drinking right there.
John C Dvorak: I mean, if you're
not drinking coffee right now
you're crazy. What about beer?
I'm going to crack open a beer
and then drink it down. All
right, a Bud Light. I'm drinking
Bud Light. 10 times better
Newcastle. A couple of glasses a
couple of high balls a tall
tumbler with no ice of Chivas
while there you go get your fat
sitting at the pool drinking
pina coladas No, bullet crap
just put it on the table with
drinks in the bottle
Adam Curry: hands around.
John C Dvorak: No I was under my
foot. You just sit in a pile of
cans you
Adam Curry: know every show when
you when you open up your drink
does that can go on?
Unknown: MoPhO vorak.org/n A and
we are not going anywhere.