John C Dvorak: rubbed me the
wrong way you get blocked.
Adam Curry: Adam curry Jhansi
Dvorak October 22 2023 This is
your award winning accumulation
media assassination episode
16 01 This is no agenda,
clutching my pearls and
broadcasting live from the heart
of the Texas country here in
FEMA Region number six in the
morning, everybody. I'm Adam
curry
John C Dvorak: from Northern
Silicon Valley, where we're
concerned that Canada is pushing
assisted suicide for babies. I'm
Jhansi Dvorak.
Adam Curry: It's about time they
got in on that on that action.
Baby killing is all the rage. So
it's like hey, we're not gonna
let a masa Israel have all the
fun. Is this really something?
Are they really doing assisted
suicide?
John C Dvorak: Back board I
think is to kubek medical board
is pushing it and they're trying
to get it through. Babies up to
one and
Adam Curry: the babies get to
decide is that how that worked
out?
John C Dvorak: Of course. No, I
did. This is this is a form of
abortion after the fact.
Adam Curry: Yes, it's post natal
abortion. Pap, you
John C Dvorak: look at it. I
don't like that baby.
Adam Curry: says like, look at
the nose on that
Unknown: kid. Yeah, no good. Oh,
Adam Curry: it's as red hair.
Oh, no, it's a ginger. Oh, hello
social media addicts. Remember
when social media was social
networking?
Unknown: Wow. Yeah.
John C Dvorak: I'm talking about
Wow. Which is that's kind of an
interesting while you're right.
I got a robo call today. Did you
know and it was it was the I
considered some someone who
coded it was very ironic. It was
a woman calling it was a robot
robot. Hi, I'm Eliza. Oh,
really? Yes.
Adam Curry: Wow, that's not
obvious. I'm Eliza. How are you?
i Oh, man. Now this this Israel
Hamas thing is perfect. I mean,
it's better than mask no mask
Vax Novak's could you know when
you say something like all of a
sudden you're a Nazi you it goes
a little further. Now you can
you can get in real trouble now.
You're anti Semite. Yeah. So,
but yes, it used to be social
networking. And I think that the
turn to social medias when they
brought in the algos?
John C Dvorak: Oh, you know, I
don't think so. I think it was
the social networking, I think
was always borderline passive.
Adam Curry: Right. There was no
comments. You're right. Yeah, it
was just, it was like a, like
Google Reader. That was that was
that was social? No, no,
John C Dvorak: I think Facebook
would be considered social
networking. And I think until
Twitter came along with micro
blogging, I think it was always,
Adam Curry: I think, I think
it's, I think it's the algo I
think it happened when the algo
was introduced. That's when
because media, look, networking
is just, hey, look, I'm
networking with some people. I'm
in a group. Yeah, following some
people, but Facebook. But then
Facebook got their feed their
news feed, and that was all algo
eyes. And then it became media.
I mean, media is always
dishonest. I think it actually
doesn't really even matter. I've
done some study. You know, we're
John C Dvorak: We're all ears.
Yes.
Adam Curry: So we've talked
about noster nostril, as you
call it. And a big discovery so
Nasir is this decentralized is
basically Twitter decentralized
and a lot of Bitcoin bros like
it because you can zap each
other with with little bits of
Bitcoin. But it's it's really
not all that great. And I think
the Bitcoin bros like it's
censorship resistant. Okay. So
there's really one, one app that
does this that does noster
really well. And this one app
got an investment or maybe just
to a stipend from Jack Dorsey.
So oz. Great. And that's called
Domus. That's the name of this
app. Get it Nostradamus. So the
Dominus guy. I know the dumbest
guy posts. He says, hey, you
know, we looked at our app store
stats. And it turns out that
after three months, 99% of the
people who've tried this app,
give up on it. And you know, it
was baffling to me. And I can
tell you why. Because you get on
this app and there's no action.
It's not yelling at you is not
giving you stuff to follow them
because there's no algos,
there's nothing. That's
John C Dvorak: a good point. I
don't know if the algos create
the action or not, but they sure
don't. They don't
Adam Curry: hinder it. There's
no highlighting there's no
trending. I like the
John C Dvorak: idea you're right
people yeah Lynnette each other,
that's where it's like watching
a fight.
Adam Curry: So and that is so
now entered no algos fight, but
we have mastered on. And I know
I've been. I've been looking
very closely at what's been
going on in our own Mastodon
server, which doesn't happen.
Yeah, and hates you now. But
that's what's that's what's so
interesting is it's like love
hate. It's everyone. Everyone
just needs that little that
little hit that little I had
posted something on any social
if someone commented whoa
doesn't agree with me that's
even better. No, it's like I say
something simple like I don't
like memes and now it's like a
hate meme don't hate means there
was a poll, Aaron er who runs
the whole? The whole instance
said no, we should have a mean
free Monday. Everyone's mad not
bad. You're addicts, you're
addicts is 100% addiction to
this, this is probably even a
better high than you get from
some drugs. Because the same
mechanism, this is what Silicon
Valley figured out decade ago.
It's is the end. So anything
that feeds that and again, this
Hamas Israel thing is fantastic.
Because you can just go back and
forth and call people names and,
and the algo throws it up in
your face. And it's great. I
mean, the troll room is a little
different. The troll room is
like, I'm gonna go to a party,
I'm gonna binge to like puke.
You know, that's kind of what
that is just you just throw some
bombs. And people you get
immediate feedback. I think and
yes,
John C Dvorak: I agree that is
different. I think it's still
social media, but it's of a
different sort.
Adam Curry: It's binging it's
like a binge fest, and I'm just
gonna go and cram as much dope
into me as I can until I puke
and then I'm good. And then
here's something else.
John C Dvorak: Well, it also
comes and goes, you don't dwell
on things right, bro. Yeah,
exactly. Well, I'm dwelling
factor. I think it's a big deal.
Adam Curry: But if you get
kicked off by me, you know,
that's like you're either a
general of the troll room, then
you have massive props. So and
then I've noticed something
else. Now I don't I don't have
this per se. But I've seen
friends and I think I think
women more than anything, maybe
I'm not sure. On text messages.
So they have a text message
thread. And they're just sending
memes back and forth about the
news. And you know, like thumbs
up has a good one. And but
there's no there's not like this
like meme ship. There's not even
a it's not even a friendship.
They just shoot memes back and
forth. It's a completely empty
relationship. It's like it's
like, sex without love. I don't
know what it is. This people
really need to sit down the
phones for a day. It's not
healthy. What's going on? Hey,
John C Dvorak: okay, talking to
the wrong guy.
Adam Curry: I know. I know. I
know. I know. Now,
John C Dvorak: of course I still
since December. You
Adam Curry: haven't touched your
phone. I know. You're a master.
John C Dvorak: I don't have an
account anymore. I'm gonna have
to. Yeah, I'm gonna try to get
back before No, no, no.
Adam Curry: But this is also why
you are now at five years old is
because you have not succumb you
have kept all of your all your
John C Dvorak: keeps the blood
pressure down.
Adam Curry: Exactly. You have
healthy blood pressure. You You
haven't worn out all of your
your brain cells. And what's the
you haven't you know, dopamine
you actually have for sex? Not
just for you I get you with that
one. No, so this is good. This
is that's why be like John cook
for yourself. Don't don't have
your phone and just don't use
your phone at all. Look at the
look at the trains.
John C Dvorak: Great dad goes a
train.
Adam Curry: And I think
personally the genius move and
not everybody can do this is
love your wife in a different
state. I mean, this is just you.
John C Dvorak: You've got an
always a winner.
Adam Curry: Anyway, so I've
figured a couple things out with
the with the M five M is already
abusing this entire situation.
And before we get to it though,
first we have to have these
because CNN is loving this. We
got ratings again, we got guys
with helmets. We got we got
chicks with flak jackets to say
media press. We have dangerous
situations. We got cool sound
effects. And what happened on
CNN this morning. I mean, you
could ask for a better ratings
Buster than this. So you are
Unknown: seeing this sort of
solidarity that was called for
by the way by from all over the
Arab world and the world of
like, but you were also seeing
the journalists gathered here
because this is kind of where
the crash happens. All right.
All right, you see that people
are very angry to do not like
recording the story. You hear
that?
Adam Curry: Yeah. All right. I
mean, that's dynamite for
ratings. Good job there in the
fields. Her name is what's your
name? Her name is? Sarah. So
what's your name? Sara Sidner. I
think Cersei there's good job
for a raise give her Erin
Burnett. Let's stir it up a
little bit. Come on, Aaron. Go
go go what we see
Unknown: Sarah dealing with on
the ground and Ramallah
obviously, you know, it is so
important, right? These are pro
Palestinian protests. But
there's also the perception of
where the media stands where
American media stands. You are
not welcome here. There is an
anger and resentment and a rage
and it is real real and it is.
It is a part of the story as
well pro Palestinian, anti
Israeli anti American, the this
John C Dvorak: right there for a
second. We have absolutely no
evidence that this whole thing
wasn't staged.
Adam Curry: Thank you very much.
And I'm going to show to you
that the probably was
Unknown: and it is important and
it is a part of the story as
well pro Palestinian, anti
Israeli anti American. The this
is this is often one big giant
soup. And it's very hard to pull
those strings apart as that
moment with Sarah I think just
illustrated so well.
Adam Curry: It's a soup I tell
ya. It's one giant soup. We
don't know what to do.
Unfortunately for CNN, ABC was
the first of the punch. Whenever
you really want to go over the
top with any type of attacking
force. You got to bring this in.
It's it's a good old friend of
the show.
Unknown: And we're learning that
Hamas terrorists who attacked
Israel may have been high on a
drug designed to make them feel
invincible. The drug Captagon
was reportedly found on the
bodies of terrorist and in the
vehicles used in the attack
Adam Curry: member our old
friend Captagon if it wasn't the
Russians, it was it's all I
forgot all about it. Yeah, on
the Captagon that drugged out
it's a powerful
Unknown: amphetamine known as
the poor man's cocaine. Experts
say to drug may explain some of
the extraordinary ferocity seen
in the attack. Former DEA Deputy
Chief of Staff Jim Crotty with
Captagon and other illicit
substances, they just tend to
strip people of all their
humanity. They do things that
they wouldn't ordinarily do.
There's very little to stop them
from committing all sorts of
atrocities. But drones makes
users take crazy risks, like
this terrorist wearing a helmet
cam who walked right into
Israeli gunfire.
Adam Curry: Yes. Hi, man.
They're all jacked up on poor
man's cocaine. We have this is
from I think this is maybe one
of your clips 2019 background
you're on Captagon
Unknown: Lebanon's Bekaa Valley
has a history of smuggling and
trafficking of all sorts, an
area where illegal activities
include narcotics Achmed is one
of those who transports and
sells that type of amphetamine
called Captagon Ichie been a
hugely popular drug in the
Middle East.
Adam Curry: Oh, so it's not just
for fighters. It's just in the
Middle East in general. All
right. Cannon ethylene always
bring back the Captagon if you
want to make it just a little
more fun there. Hi, man, the
crazy and everything was going
swimmingly well, and I've been
waiting for something to pop up
and there it was in DC. We had a
pro Palestinian protest. And
well, I happen to catch this on
local Fox five and I went down
the rabbit hole.
Unknown: Just days after
hundreds of arrests in the canon
building right here at the US
Capitol. More demonstrations
popping up on the National Mall.
Let's get to Stephanie Ramirez
joining us live. Steph, what is
the sentiment out there today?
People are marching in the pro
Palestinian ceasefire rally
there is no doubt if you don't
hear it out here. The calls for
a ceasefire in Gaza have
definitely increased I want to
show you a crowd here. This is a
organized protest that was
permitted for Around 100 people
but we're seeing today a little
bit different
Adam Curry: you don't need to
hear the whole report she said
it right there. This was an
organized protest professional
signs. Ha as a no agenda
conspiracy therapist This is
where we start the main sign was
want to second pray for the dead
fight. What was that pray for
the dead fight for peace. Now
this is typically fight like
hell for peace. That's when the
union's use it. But they didn't
find it appropriate to put hell
in here I guess. And these signs
were made by the if not now.
Movement organization who if not
now movement.org Quickly we are
if not now a movement of
American Jews organizing our
community for equality, justice
and a thriving future for all
our neighbors ourselves,
Palestinians and Israelis. We
are Jews of all ages with
ancestors from across the world
and Jewish backgrounds as
diverse as the ways we practice
our Judaism. Okay, so I'm trying
to figure out who's behind this
who's funding this and here is a
nice little bit in their in
their on their website after the
war ended now this was a
previous war that there were
protesting against the founders
joined the momentum organizing
community I didn't that didn't
ring any Bell. The same
community were sunrise movement
and by the people and many more
organized for a brighter future.
Wait a minute sunrise movement?
Isn't that those kids who go
we're going into Nancy Pelosi
his office. So I'm like, oh,
okay, so this is organized.
Let's go to the momentum
movement and momentum very
interesting little outfit here.
They we offer training and
support to movement organizers.
Momentum offers training and
support to hone organizers
skills in shifting public
opinion, developing a hundreds
of leaders and mobilizing by the
1000s we are committed to both
strengthening existing groups
and incubating new movement
organizations. They've got
resources, they've got guides,
they're a community of movement
leaders and they've apparently
no not apparently they have
organized this if If not now,
movement organization. So what
let's look at this they have a
donate button. Oh, guess who
this is? Not blue X blue. Of
course it's the Democrat Party.
X blue now.
John C Dvorak: Good one, good
one.
Adam Curry: So it's it's
politics. This is politics.
Let's get to the staff of this
organization. Because it's just
worth looking at. Ad yell
Polydor Advanced Training
Director pronouns she her. She's
responsible for driving? Oh no,
it gets better is responsible
for driving our advanced
training programs supporting the
build out of the leadership
development pipeline. Through
coaching. She leads the momentum
201 training and black momentum
Okay. Amanda sage, Interim
Executive Director, she's the
boss pronouns they she
John C Dvorak: is a she Oh,
Adam Curry: it gets better. As
momentums Interim Executive
Director Amanda guides the
team's institutional health
leadership team and fundraising
strategy and supports the
largest strategic director of
the direction of the
organization. They immigrated to
one ponad land as a little
toddler, and now live in Lenape
land aka Brooklyn.
John C Dvorak: When they're
renaming the towns now
Adam Curry: after the Indians
who they stole the land from,
when they're not or when they're
not organizing or wrapped in the
world of momentum. You can catch
them jamming out to live music,
reading sci fi in a local park
or cooking their mom's just one
recipes. Okay. We have the
Operations Coordinator, Brenda
Valladares Velez, what
John C Dvorak: is the point of
the show this one references at
some code. We've got code in
Adam Curry: Chinese. She's a
she's Chinese. Brenda Vala data.
John C Dvorak: She's Chinese and
concerned about the American
Indians.
Adam Curry: Yes, they are not
she they.
John C Dvorak: Brenda says she
they she I call her she
Adam Curry: Okay, well, Brenda
Valadez bellezza is the
Operations Coordinator. Her
pronouns are she her and Ella?
Ella. She is formerly an
undocumented immigrant from
Peru.
John C Dvorak: She should be
exported, exported.
Adam Curry: extradite I like
exported, recently moved from
Paterson, New Jersey to
Washington Heights. She loves to
travel and explore different
parts of the world watch
documentaries, video, chat with
loved ones, study law and cook
big meals. So this is all these
are all lesbians of color.
Maoists. Marxists. I love Delain
Andrea powerful she's managing
director pronouns they them,
them spelled th e m m e, them.
Delaine is a disabled black,
queer Jamaican who lives in
organises on the occupied lands
of the Council of the three
fires, the Ojibwe, Odawa and
Potawatomi nations in Chicago,
Illinois. They enjoy play. To
me, they enjoy playing soccer
being a plant Auntie whining, a
plant Auntie, I'm just replant
onto ESP la NTAO en ti a plant
Auntie whining In their waste
and absorbing all things, all
things AFUE and absorbing all
things afrofuturist, Octavia
Butler and Marvel universe this
is the whole page is filled with
this kind of people
John C Dvorak: that are complete
crackpots.
Adam Curry: And they're
organizing and training the
children of all these schools,
all these protests. It's all
part. It's all
John C Dvorak: political people.
It's
Adam Curry: all political and to
prove it, who shows up in the
Atlantic with an article titled
Netanyahu, his attack on
democracy left Israel
unprepared, none other than an
apple bomb, oh, our friend and
and says this summer I spent
several days in Israel talking
with people who were afraid for
their country's future. They
were not at that moment focused
on terrorism, Gaza or Hamas,
they feared something different,
the emergence of an undemocratic
Israel, a de facto autocracy.
I'm just skipping ahead. Thanks
to the financial and logistic
support of the Israeli tech
industry, the most dynamic
economic sector in the country
as well as to organize teams of
people coming from academia and
the Army Reserves. The protests
kept going for many months
successfully blocked many of the
proposed legal changes. This is
all about the fascist the
dictator Netanyahu. And here we
get into the meat of it. The
deep angry divides in Israeli
politics divides that are
religious and cultural, but that
were also deliberately created
by Netanyahu and his extremist
allies for their political and
personal benefit weren't just a
problem for some liberal or
secular Israelis. The people I
met believed the polarization of
Israel was an existential risk
for everybody is worse than
climate change. Earlier this
year, the head of Shin Bet the
Israeli domestic intelligence
service warned that Israeli
settlers who were attacking West
Bank Palestinians pose a
security threat to the country.
One member of Parliament from
net now whose Likud party
responded using language that
will sound familiar to
Americans. Quote, The ideology
of the left has reached the top
echelons of the Shin Bet the
Deep State has infiltrated the
leadership of Shin Bet and the
IDF. And here it comes. If
Donald Trump becomes president,
again, they made deliberately
set out to weaken the
institutions themselves. Yes,
this is exactly what we're
seeing here. This is all about
training the Democrats to make
sure that Trump doesn't get
elected. It's all about Trump
all about Trump. These protests
are about Trump, the all of this
stuff. These trainees are hate
Trump. They're all trans
Maoists. They're bad for America
and probably bad for your
children. Well, the whole thing
is about politics, all of it.
All of it. And some of it is
about obviously the military
industrial complex that's foxes
job really, you know, they're
supposed to, oh, CNN has the
generals on it like that. But
here's judge Jeanine
Unknown: In fact, I would say
bomb a bomb and then bomb again.
That's a new one.
John C Dvorak: It's a new one
that's totally new. Yeah,
Adam Curry: that's she's she's
completely gone back to her old
bomb bomb bomb again that she
has this she loves bombing
people.
Unknown: You have this one to
loading bomb stealing. You're
getting new pilots in. But
they're going in and they're
going in hard. They know that.
That their their existence
depends on this.
Adam Curry: She's she I think
she digs it, man. She's like,
Oh, yeah. So hot. They're gonna
go in hard. Hard. Here's the
last one.
Unknown: Somebody's going to
drop a new care. I don't know
who it is. But I don't want to
watch it.
Adam Curry: What does that even
mean? Judge Jeanine? Somebody's
gonna drop a nuke here. What is
wrong with these people? Got it
other than they're out there
doing any
John C Dvorak: help and things
as for sure. No, of
Adam Curry: course not. It's
horrible. It's horrible. And
social media playing right into
it is beautiful. The whole thing
is a perfect setup. Everybody's
spinning out. Oh, yeah, I'm
going crazy. So great. Oh,
there's we got to have a
telegram telegram
John C Dvorak: is both a
messaging and social media app.
People in the United States and
across the world. Use it to
video call and text message each
other or someone can set up a
group to send messages to
followers.
Adam Curry: By the way, Rumble
was already on the way out
telegram is next.
John C Dvorak: That second use
is what we've seen most during
the Israel Hamas war. When Hamas
attacked southern Israel on
October 7, their channel was
flooded with propaganda videos
showcasing their training and
the fight against the nearby
Israel Defense Forces. Both the
Hamas account and the one for
its military wing. The Al Qassam
brigades have grown
substantially since the war
began. The Hamas account has
gained more than 100,000
followers while brigade account
has fallen.
Adam Curry: So here is Deutsche
revelat. That was Scripps news.
That's just you know, they're
promoting it more than anything.
Deutsche chavalla is
John C Dvorak: I would mentioned
Scripps news is really is really
a very questionable source of
news. I've been watching the TV
feed, it's borderline
disgusting.
Adam Curry: Do you know who owns
most of Fredericksburg?
Unknown: Scripts? You bet.
Adam Curry: Oh, yep, yep.
John C Dvorak: You bet.
Adam Curry: I received it. I
remember
John C Dvorak: even when I said
I almost said 100% I stopped
myself.
Adam Curry: I know I'm working
on myself. I'm trying I'm trying
I really am. Yep, yep, yep, yep.
Yep. Yep. As far as I know, nice
people actually but the the news
is
John C Dvorak: long gone from
this system that
Adam Curry: don't run it
anymore. So here's Dorabella
telegraphing about telegram.
Unknown: Another front and the
fast evolving conflict between
Israel and Hamas is the one
found online. Disinformation is
running rampant across social
media where millions turn to get
real time updates. And with the
very real imagery or floods of
fabricated videos and photos
spread by both fake and real
accounts. The companies behind
giants like Facebook X and tick
tock say they've taken
additional steps to tackle
disinformation around the
violence. But the EU has
reprimanded social media
companies for not doing enough
and about all that we can now
speak to Caitlin chin Rothman,
she's with the Center for
Strategic and International
Studies, where she researches
the impact of technology on
geopolitics and society.
Caitlin, good to see you. Lots
of people these days getting
their information on social
media, With tensions running so
high. How are both sides in this
conflict using social media to
share views of the war,
we've seen? Both Hamas and the
Israeli government use posts on
social media quite often, Hamas
has been posting on a platform
called telegram which is less
popular in the United States in
the EU, but more popular in
other parts of the world, like
Russia and Ukraine. Telegram has
very loose content moderation
policies, which has allowed moss
to post very graphic or violent
images from its initial attack
on October 7,
I want to look a little closer
at telegram that you just
mentioned because it's used by
Hamas, not only to spread
propaganda, but also to recruit
new members now is an
internationally recognized
terror organization. By much of
the West at least, can the
platform be held accountable for
that.
So it's very difficult and have
very loose content moderation
laws, so platforms are generally
not held accountable for third
party content that users upload.
Now that is different. In other
countries, especially the EU,
which recently passed the
Digital Services Act. And the
online service, online safety
bill in the United Kingdom is
about to come into effect. Now,
Telegram has not seen as much
regulatory attention from the EU
or the UK, I think partly
because it's just not as popular
in in either jurisdiction. But I
think going forward, I would
expect governments to become
more interested in how telegram
operates, especially if we
continue to see violent
extremist content emerge on
these platforms in real time or
situations.
Adam Curry: This is the perfect
moment to clamp down on these
because of course we're in a in
an election season. A very good
moment to start clamping down on
this stuff because clearly,
telegram is a recruitment tool.
Yes, PBS has some short little
note here and all the horrible
things from social media
Unknown: to European Union press
to meta and tick tock to explain
what they're doing to block
disinformation about Israel
Hamas war Do you know air tech
giants were given one week to
respond? They could face
billions in fines if they don't
comply with a new law aimed at
protecting users from false
claims and other harmful
content.
Adam Curry: And this brings us
to a gripe a lot of people have
with me, but are you with me and
also with you? Me the Oh yeah.
Yes, you and this is because we
poo pooed and I would say
slammed the Westminster
declaration
John C Dvorak: da Qing was Adam
curry.
Adam Curry: Yes where Pearl
clutching I read an email Lord
Hi Imperator curry. Greetings
from FEMA Region Deep South New
Zealand. I need to take
John C Dvorak: Oh New Zealand,
this New Zealand In New Zealand
but they have What the hell's a
New Zealand are got to do With
anything that has to do with
this American
Adam Curry: ship is just
indicative of several emails and
tweets and tweets I
John C Dvorak: received. It
sounds sounds fake but go on
reading now it's
Adam Curry: not fake and you
just did a Kara Swisher but go
ahead. But go ahead go,
John C Dvorak: Wait a minute.
That was my invention now you're
crediting her with it.
Adam Curry: I need to take issue
with the tone of your no agenda
story and the Westminster
declaration. You are downright
snide and your trademark MTV
snare so new you know
John C Dvorak: him reading this
letter is snide. He already
shrewd straight up with other
things you
Adam Curry: are downright snide
with your trademark MTB sneer
was used to in effect on a group
of people merely highlighting
the censorship regimes being
installed in Oh, Western
democracies. Why wouldn't you be
supportive of this? I expected
immediate fierce pushback from
Jhansi Dvorak but nothing he
joined you, the snidely brothers
brothers in harm's
John C Dvorak: unkindly
brothers. I love it
Adam Curry: uncool in the gang.
Kiwi Paul,
John C Dvorak: I'm cool in the
gang. Holy mackerel. This guy
should be a copywriter.
Adam Curry: He's good. He's
good. He's good. So I we have
been doing this since episode
133. We have to do it every five
to six years. And we're going to
do it again. I will start off by
saying the Westminster
declaration was released on the
very day, the very day the FCC
voted and agreed to create new
rules for the reintroduction of
net neutrality. I'm sure it's
just a coincidence. Although I
say there's no coincidences in
the kingdom. And they say they
want article 19 to be observed
and adhered to, from the
Universal Declaration of Human
Rights. Now, any no agenda
person should immediately think,
Hmm, that's the United Nations
document, maybe not the best
thing in the world. But doesn't
matter. Let's look at article
19. Article 19 of the Universal
Declaration of Human Rights.
Everyone has the right to
freedom of opinion and
expression. This right includes
freedom to hold opinions without
interference and to seek,
receive and impart information
and ideas through any media and
regardless of frontiers. So
that's what you're really going
to bat over. May I remind you,
Glenn Greenwald, Mata Eb, these
are leftists, just because you
agree with them on lock downs
and vaccines and what doesn't
mean that they're not inherently
they they love government
regulation. That's what these
guys love they, they thrive on
it. You will not get free speech
from commercial platforms or
maybe from anything called a
platform at all. And what they
are calling for in my mind
because it coincides exactly
with the vote, which was three
to two is net neutrality. And we
have had so much pushback in the
past about our stance on net
neutrality. And people said, why
wouldn't you want it to be
neutral man? Because net
neutrality is as honest as the
sorry is always net neutrality
is as honest as the inflation
Reduction Act. Haven't we
learned these things by now?
When they call it something? It
means the opposite? Did you like
your cell phone alert from the
government? Did you everyone was
bitching and moaning about hey
man, the government taking over
my phone? That'll be on every
computer you own? If this goes
through, and this will lead to
digital ID that is the end game
of what they're really asking
for. Anonymity will end there
goes your trolling because they
want title to to adhere to the
internet. Now I listened to FCC
chair Rosen Borssele. She was on
the FCC panel back during Obama
when they went through this the
first time. And she is now the
chair. And I want to go through
a few things from her speech and
subsequently play a few
historical no agenda clips
because we've been through this
before. You don't want it. You
do not want the government with
their net neutrality is a trick
Unknown: but you know, the
pandemic did something else. It
made crystal clear that
broadband is no longer just nice
to have. It's nice to have for
everyone everywhere. It's not a
luxury. It's a necessity. It is
essential infrastructure for me
Modern life. No one without it
has a fair shot at 21st century
success. We need broadband to
reach 100% of us. And we need it
to be fast, open and fair.
Adam Curry: Okay, this is the
slogan, go get the bumper
sticker, get your T shirt fast,
open and fair. Now I've not I
don't have a huge argument with
the idea that everybody should
have broadband. For some reason
we've never been able to really
get it together. Even though
we've spent hundreds of millions
of dollars given that to
telephone companies to create a
broadband for everybody
broadband for all this goes back
to Obama. It just got stolen.
But a portion of the country
still doesn't have it. But
that's really the ruse using the
pandemic, all man. Well, without
broadband we couldn't leave.
John C Dvorak: When we do that,
is that lame is rousse? That
ruse is the one who can't wait,
what is brought what is one got
to do with the other COVID had
nothing to do with the you know,
Adam Curry: when we were locked
down. That's that's what she was
at this show. But
John C Dvorak: you go to school?
Yes,
Adam Curry: I chopped a whole
bunch out of this for obvious
reasons. So what she wants, he's
on par with the telephone
networks
Unknown: back in the era when
communications meant telephony
each and every call went
through. And the phone company
could not cut you off from your
call or decide to edit the
content of your Converse. What
Adam Curry: do you want to say
something here?
John C Dvorak: What world was
she living in? When you had to
put a quarter in and you hit the
you got the yak, yak, yak and
then you click, you're done.
They cut you off? What do you
mean, they never cut you off?
They cut you off all the time.
This so where does that debt
imaginary scenario come from?
Adam Curry: This is to trick
everybody into wanting this.
She's lying. I'll get to that.
Is it a blatant lie? Oh, there's
another Whopper coming up
Unknown: from your call or
decide to edit the content of
your conversation. Now fast
forward to the present.
Communications means a whole lot
more than just phone calls. It
means access to the internet,
because broadband is the most
important infrastructure of our
time.
Adam Curry: No the important,
important she's she's very
young, important.
Unknown: But as a result of the
previous FCCS decision to drop,
abdicate authority. The agency
charged with overseeing
Communications has limited
ability to oversee these
indispensable networks, and make
sure that for every consumer,
their access is fast
Adam Curry: note that she talks
about consumers if you're a
creator, screw you,
Unknown: open and fair. I think
that's not right. It's not
right. Because for everyone
everywhere to enjoy the full
benefits of the Internet age,
Internet access should be more
than just accessible and
affordable. The Internet needs
to be
Adam Curry: what is more than
just accessible and affordable.
John C Dvorak: Seems like
accessible. And affordability is
really what it's all about. Oh,
you want what more could you
want? Oh, hold
Unknown: on. And affordable. The
Internet needs to be open. And
that's what I want to talk it is
open
Adam Curry: now. No, she wants
when when the government says I
want it to be open, please read
that as I want it to be closed.
John C Dvorak: How is it not
open right now? No, wait,
Adam Curry: they want to close
it off? Yeah, I want to close it
off. Here we go. We're next
clip. Let's
Unknown: start in 2005. That was
when the FCC adopted its first
open Internet policy statement
which was built on policies that
had long been in communications
law and history. The agency made
clear that when it came to net
neutrality, consumers should
expect that their broadband
providers would not block
throttle or engage in paid
prioritization of lawful
internet traffic.
Adam Curry: And there's my
favorite word Yeah, there we go.
Not lawful content, lawful
internet traffic and I have a
copy if anyone I've marked it up
if you want to go through the
entire proposed rulemaking, 126
pages. The term lawful traffic
and lawful transfer is all over
this thing. This is the main
problem. This is the trick.
Unknown: In other words, your
broadband provider had no
business cutting off access to
websites slowing down Internet
services and censoring online
speech, which never
Adam Curry: happened.
John C Dvorak: There's not one
example of that your broadband
brought the broadband internet
provider just provides the
broadband he doesn't. He's not
Twitter, they barely do
Unknown: that. Your broadband
provider was not allowed to play
favorites like steering you fast
to some online service that
hadn't given them a payout. It's
never happened, and assigning
you to a bumpy road for those
who have not offered, the same
never
John C Dvorak: happened. You're
right. This is all bullcrap. But
But I hope you get to the end
here because I want to know go
is your spiel about lawful
Adam Curry: now we're getting to
that this is a presentation.
These clips are all very short.
It's an important presentation.
And the next part is her
explanation of why title to the
same regulation for your phone,
your phone line. And there's
regulation, there's a lot of
stuff you can do on the phone.
And the government, I think I'm
pretty sure the government
completely can hear and do
anything they want on your phone
networks. But we need title two
now for the internet. Here's why
Unknown: title two is the part
of the law that gives the FCC
clear authority to serve as a
watchdog watchdog over the
communications marketplace and
look out for the public
interest.
Adam Curry: Okay. I'm from the
government. I'm here to help.
Title two
Unknown: took on special
importance in the net neutrality
debate, because the courts have
ruled that the FCC has clear
authority to enforce open
Internet policies. If broadband
internet is classified as a
title to service,
Adam Curry: very important what
she's saying here, not saying
that the Court said you should
you should be doing this. They
say if it is classified as title
two, then the FCC has absolute
authority over the internet.
Just trust uncle Adam and Uncle
John, you don't want this.
Unknown: And providing a strong
foundation for net neutrality
rules is a good reason to
support classifying broadband
internet as a title to service.
But again, there are downstream
consequences that flow from the
agency retreating from title to
Adam Curry: downstream
consequences that flow that
doesn't sound healthy,
Unknown: and they need
attention. So let me explain.
Back to the pandemic, it made
clear that broadband is
essential infrastructure for
modern life. access to the
internet is now access to
everything gets access to
everything. And common sense
tells us that the nation's
leading communications watchdog
should have the muscle it needs.
Adam Curry: Muscle must
John C Dvorak: you give me a
high blood pressure?
Adam Curry: I got a ball you
don't have a phone. I need to do
something to kill. Yeah. Yes,
you want to say something?
John C Dvorak: You know,
listening to this is very
annoying, because I know that
other people were laughing must
be laughing it out. And I would
include the people that signed
that document. Yes, I lapping it
up not realizing that it is a
trick we're getting complete.
We're getting to the trick trick
getting
Unknown: to the trick should
have the muscle it needs to
protect consumers and make sure
their internet access is fast,
open
Adam Curry: and fair. Now to a
big lie. Here's a big lie.
Unknown: On one issue after
issue classifying broadband as a
title to service would help the
FCC serve the public interest
more efficiently and
effectively. So let's start with
public safety. And it's remanded
the FCC has decision to rollback
net neutrality. The court found
the agency's disregard of its
duty to analyze the impact of
public safety renders the
decision arbitrary and
capricious. I agree. Here we go.
The record before the court
demonstrated that when
firefighters in Santa Clara,
California, were responding to
wildfires, they discovered that
the wireless connectivity on
their command vehicle was being
throttled.
Adam Curry: Lie, that's a lie,
because we reported on this in
Episode 1079, November 21 2018.
Let's go back and let's listen
to what the story really was.
And was it not Verizon, that
came into a very bad light?
Because they cut off the
firefighters in California
because they had run out of
data? Bastards. That's was
Verizon, correct? I believe so.
And so the so these guys had the
they couldn't use their account,
they had to switch to a
different account according to
the Verizon rep, because they'd
run out of data. And of course,
these guys have they're fighting
fires and they needed data. And
so it was it was a bad PR story
for Verizon. Let me just go back
and listen to what the FCC
Chairwoman lied
Unknown: the record before the
court demonstrated that when
firefighters in Santa Clara,
California, were responding to
wildfires, they discovered the
wireless connectivity on their
command vehicle was being
throttled. It
Adam Curry: was not being
throttled. So she's lying. As
usual, liars. All right. So what
else? What do they really want
to do? Well, well, you know,
we're not just here to make sure
you get cheap and affordable
broadband. No
Unknown: Good cybersecurity
security SEC is actively
involved in federal interagency
cybersecurity planning,
coordination and response
activities. You want the expert
agency with all sorts of
knowledge about network
technology to be sitting at that
table
John C Dvorak: at the stop it in
Michigan. So this FCC, there's
so hot shit, blended done
anything about to 10 or 20, robo
calls I get a day,
Adam Curry: I'm glad you asked
Unknown: then look at privacy.
The law requires
telecommunications providers to
protect the confidentiality of
the proprietary information of
their customers. That means
these providers cannot sell your
location data, among other
sensitive information. Well, I
suppose not machines currently
extend to phone service
customers, but not to broadband
subscribers, because title two
does not cover the ladder. Does
that really make sense? Do we
want our broadband providers
selling off where we go and what
we do online? Scraping our
service for a payday Oh, new
artificial intelligence models
doing any of this without our
permission?
Adam Curry: Yeah. So you were
one clip ahead of me. Exactly.
The robocalls still continue,
they have done nothing with
their title to authority to stop
that nothing, no,
John C Dvorak: nothing zip and
they could do something if they
wanted to. And And meanwhile,
this bowl credit, this other
stuff is all bull crap. The
providers aren't tracking us.
Apple might be tracking us.
Google might be tracking us
these are providers.
Adam Curry: So I pulled two
clips. So we don't have to, you
know, just because we're lazy.
We don't have to really go over
everything all over again. You
see what happened? What is this?
What is this?
John C Dvorak: But I may revisit
my old columns. I've been
writing about this for a decade.
Adam Curry: This is no agenda
episode 950. And that is from
that is from July 27 2017.
John C Dvorak: This is Greg
Wald, and he's a Republican from
Oregon. And he is the Hayes and
this is an oversight
subcommittee. But he's actually
the head guy of the Energy and
Commerce Committee. He's the
chair and he is a very powerful
person. And just listen to the
question he asked this is net
neutrality basics opening,
including Comcast
Unknown: AT and T, Verizon and
Charter Communications, inviting
each of them to come and testify
before our full Energy and
Commerce Committee. It's time
for Congress to legislate the
rules of the internet, long game
of regulations and litigation.
And make no mistake given the
importance of this public policy
debate. And the work we need to
do as a committee. It is
essential that we hear directly
from the country's top internet,
and edge provider leaders who
frequently speak out publicly
about rules of the internet. His
time they came before us and
directly shared their positions,
and answered our questions.
Adam Curry: Wow. Yeah, I think
there's some subtext, there
Unknown: is a little more than
subtext. Time to stop
Adam Curry: this, these series
of tubes.
John C Dvorak: That's the guy
when he said, quote, it's time
for Congress to legislate the
rules of the internet Boom
shakalaka. Could it be any more
clear? Does anybody out there
listening
Adam Curry: to podcast licenses
coming? That's what will happen
with net neutrality. That's what
happens with title two, it's
time to legislate the rules of
the internet, hate speech is
already illegal in 49 states,
whatever that means. Now, to the
genesis of our reporting, we go
back to 2009. No agenda, Episode
133. And this brings back the
Core term here the fifth
principle of non discrimination.
The fifth principle is one of
non discrimination stating that
broadband providers cannot
discriminate against particular
Internet content or
applications. This means they
cannot block or degrade lawful
traffic over their networks or
pick lawful traffic. Okay, so
that means they're gonna have to
sniff it. I mean, it's all in
here, right? You can just see
what they're doing lawful
traffic, what is lawful traffic?
Okay, all traffic is lawful.
It's
John C Dvorak: so I think we
should just sorry that we should
declare that the last 20 years
was the golden age of porn. It's
all
Adam Curry: over. It's all over.
That's right. They cannot
disfavor an internet service
just because it competes with a
similar service. This principle
will not prevent broadband
providers from reasonably
managing their networks during
periods of network congestion.
For example, it may be
appropriate for providers to
ensure that very heavy users do
not crowd out everyone else,
like BitTorrent users. And this
principle will not constrain
efforts to ensure a safe, secure
and spam free internet
experience. I don't want a safe,
secure spam free internet
experience. I want porn. I want
popups. I want all kinds of
viruses. That's what makes the
internet cool. And there it is.
We've been doing this for 16
years. You don't want your
Westminster declaration from a
bunch of bunch of, by the way,
the Westminster declaration.
Isn't that bizarre, like against
catechism or something that was
like, it's like a bunch of
atheists hijacking some
religious vibe. I
John C Dvorak: have no idea. But
you do not. It was a reference
to something else. You don't
Adam Curry: want net neutrality.
It sounds great. But just
remember net neutrality is as
honest as the inflation
Reduction Act.
John C Dvorak: Well, let's get
back to the this lawful thing,
which is a pet peeve of yours
and I think is the crux of the
basis. That's the crux, which is
torrents will be illegal you
have a Tory packet sniffer tour
will be illegal season sees the
door Torian whatever you want to
call it. Yeah, advertising, it
sees it says up nap no good.
This means anyone out there who
thinks you're gonna download
music or or big giant files from
each other, or I think they'll
probably put the archive.org got
a business and everything in
between. This whole thing is a
Adam Curry: it's always about
copyright. Of course, it's
always driven by the movie or
the movie companies. Yeah, they
always
John C Dvorak: losing 10 cents
or a buck. Because you know,
there's somebody's downloaded an
old copy of some movie from the
30s. And they could have
probably maybe big somebody,
there's no available copy of it.
But you know, Turner Classic
Movies likes to play it once a
year. And so you're you're
you're taking money for even
though they don't do
advertising, but you're still
taking their bread and butter
away. I mean, this whole thing
is always about the movie
industry. It's about the the,
it's about the content to cut
the copyrighted content and how
it's, I own it, I get to do what
I want with it.
Adam Curry: So throughout this
entire document, these are the
things you need to be looking
out for. And this is their
proposed rules. And this will
take a little bit, but they've
gone through the initial hurdle
of and that was three weeks
after the speech and that was on
the 19th. So it was on our last
show day they voted three to two
good to go. We're gonna go move
forward with the rulemaking
process the same day those
Yahoo's came out with their with
their Westminster declaration,
in order to fit the technical
and economic realities of the
broadband ecosystem. The
restrictions on blocking and
discrimination will be made
subject to an exception for
quote, reasonable network
management, allowing service
providers the freedom to address
legitimate needs, such as
avoiding network congestion and
combating harmful or illegal
content. Well, go look at go I
mean, this is this is exactly
what you don't want. Because
it's open to interpretation.
What is harmful?
John C Dvorak: Yeah, vibe
antivax information that was
accurate about the about the
about the vaccine. Is that
harmful force? Of course, people
think it is. So So you know, you
have one group of people that
think that information is good
and valuable. And another group
say, Oh, it's terrible. It's
making people so they're
reluctant to take the VAX.
Adam Curry: Additionally, we
propose to reinstate a general
conduct standard that would
prohibit practices that would
cause unreasonable interference
or unreasonable disadvantage to
consumers or edge providers. So
what is reasonable? They don't
define it, of course, no, you
can't define it. No. And then
it's safeguarding national
security. So the NSA is going to
be in the network, they're going
to have to be able to safeguard
it's for your protection. All of
this is for your protection.
Commission's efforts in
coordinating with coordination
with other agencies will be
protecting the nation's
communications network from
entities and equipment and
services. That pose I mean,
listen to this equipment and
services that pose threats to
national security and law
enforcement. Someone's using
graphene OS. Orange Alert.
Orange Alert. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Someone has a non approved
device. Yep. Yep. Someone has a
non approved device connected to
it. And we these efforts will be
pursued into Presidential Policy
Directive 21. But go look at
that. That's a doozy, which
tasked the commission FCC with
identifying communication sector
vulnerabilities, and working
with industry and other
stakeholders to address those
vulnerabilities and increase the
security and resilience of this
critical infrastructure within
the communication sector. And
here's my favorite. Another
initiative is the Commission's
inquiry into vulnerable
vulnerabilities threatening the
security and integrity of Border
Gateway Protocol, which impacts
the transmission of data from e
mail, e commerce and bank
transactions, two interconnected
Voice over IP and 911 calls. The
Commission noted that border
gateway protocols initial
design, which remains widely
deployed today does not include
security features to ensure
trust in the information it is
used to exchange. This is going
after DNS. They want DNS they
want they want to be able to
disconnect your entire network
segment.
John C Dvorak: See, they want to
be able to pull the plug in who
they don't like yes and who they
don't like. It allows
Adam Curry: a bad network actor
to deliberately falsify BGP
reachability information to
redirect traffic to itself
through a specific third party
network, which means that's what
they want to do, but you said
being self Alright, man, we
should be able to redirect us
and prevent traffic from
reaching its intended recipient.
reclassification would provide
the commission with additional
authority to address BGP
vulnerabilities. There's enough
dudes named Ben out there who
know that this is nuts so so
when we have these these
intellectual Dark Web people all
lefties Brett Weinstein all all
leftists who are saying hey,
man, we should be able to we
shouldn't be kicked off of
Twitter or Facebook. And that
should be fair we should about
to say we want to say you're
gonna get it you're gonna get
exactly what you want. get
exactly what you want.
John C Dvorak: I wonder who is
behind that thing? I don't
believe it was tyy or Greenwald
or not guys who initiate face
these things. Had to be someone
else that's
Adam Curry: a good point. I'm
just
John C Dvorak: one of those get
there's a there's a troublemaker
in that group. You got to get
got the
Adam Curry: well crowd riled up.
Well, it's Greenwalt anti EB are
leading the charge at the top of
the list.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, that's what
you'd put if I was putting
something together like that,
that those are the two guys they
got two big numbers. They got a
lot of attention to themselves.
They seem legit in every way. I
would put them at the top of the
list too. But I would, I'd be
there's got to be somebody that
organized this and it wasn't
them.
Adam Curry: That's a good plus,
look at the list again. So Ty EB
Shallenberger
John C Dvorak: Shellenberger
sounds more like it.
Adam Curry: Yeah, Shallenberger.
And he Well, he's he went to
court. I mean, and again, I
agree with a lot of the things
Shellenberger has said and done.
Yeah, but he's, but he's
misguided. Jonathan Haidt, ha ha
IDT. He's, he's written a lot
about bad things that happen to
people with social networks. I'm
Steven Pinker. These that's his
partner. I think Julian Assange
is on here.
John C Dvorak: To get him to
sign anything.
Adam Curry: I don't know Tim
Robbins is on onboard. He's
right at the Robins. I think Tim
Robbins. I doubt it. John Cleese
biggest Wait. Hey, man, we need
to leave Oliver Stone all left
this?
John C Dvorak: Yeah, the Oh
yeah. All of them.
Adam Curry: Jordan Peterson,
Barry Weiss, Peter Hitchens.
Niall Ferguson. Yanis Varoufakis
a Marxist.
John C Dvorak: Yeah. Open
Marxist. Yeah. So that is a
couple open Marxists on there.
Yeah. Yeah. So yeah, there's no
right what name one right
winger? I mean, you might make
the argument that Peterson is
kind of a right winger, but I
don't know I don't know. But he
but there's name a you know,
some. You have classic, classic,
classic classic people listed on
there. But you don't have the
classic people on the right.
There's nobody
Adam Curry: no, no, they needed
a John C Dvorak and Adam curry
on this list and they if there's
money in it
John C Dvorak: a lot of these
people are very well put your
names off these things. People a
lot
Adam Curry: of these people are
wealthy too. Not all but many of
them are
John C Dvorak: quite well and
one last thing about the net
neutrality thing we have to
remember because they keep
saying it's got to be fair and
you know cheap. I use one of my
networks is Sonic. Sonic has two
programs. They have a gigabit
and they have a two gigabit.
Well, I have to pay more for the
two gigabit that would be kicked
off That's kicked off the planet
because I, there's no why would
it? That's unfair gotta have to
pay more to get to a higher
speed free. Everything would be
downgraded faster your speeds
will go down with net neutrality
fast, open and fair. So it
because everyone has to have the
same speed, it's a way of
leveling the playing field,
meaning you're gonna get
whatever the minimum is.
Adam Curry: Is everyone happy
with their telephone service?
Now that's under Title two.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, I'm still
getting the calls, I get a call
from Eliza.
Adam Curry: The robot had that
so that worked really well.
Anyway, I put a link in to open
internet.gov, the archive.org
version because that was the
previous you can just you can go
review. That was the previous
website. That's gone now of
course. Yeah, you got to spam
free internet. No, if someone's
telling you, you can get a spam
free internet than they are
sniffing packets or doing
something.
John C Dvorak: That's a lie.
What they're doing is lying
there.
Adam Curry: Because they want
control. And even the
Republicans as you heard,
they're ready for it. Yes, it's
time to moderate that thing. And
why are they doing it? They're
doing it now because they want
to get stuff rammed through so
they can control elections.
control what's going on during
elections? It's obvious.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, so they can
keep Trump out.
Adam Curry: It all comes back
down the Trump. She's a Wesleyan
grad. Exactly. Well,
John C Dvorak: let's talk about
the campaign then. With a little
overview. This is the clip is
1024 campaign is about 2024 Just
put the one in there for you by
accident.
Unknown: And not a Democrat may
soon enter the 2024 presidential
race challenging President Biden
for the nomination. This comes
as a new poll today shows former
President Trump is leading over
Biden and a potential 2024
matchup. Entities area and past
our house and election update
back my bipartisan pathways to
Congressman Dean Phillips is
reportedly planning to enter the
2024 presidential race.
Political reports the Minnesota
Democrat could challenge
President Biden for the
Democratic nomination. Phillips
is reportedly laying the
groundwork in key early states,
paving the way for the
announcement of his presidential
run. This comes as a new poll on
Friday shows former President
Trump is leading over Biden in a
potential 2024 matchup. The new
Emerson College poll shows that
47% of voters say they'd vote
for Trump 45% say they're
supporting Biden, less than 10%
are undecided. The same poll
gives Trump an even stronger
lead when it comes to young
voters. Emerson found that Trump
leads Biden by 11 points in
voters in their 30s. Just on
Friday, Trump attacked Biden on
truth social for the president's
handling of International
Affairs. Trump says the Israel
War started because of the Biden
administration and their
policies of weakness and
appeasement. He added this is
true also with Ukraine, Russia,
which would never have started
under the Trump administration
and many other hotspots around
the globe that could easily lead
to big problems and deaf.
Meanwhile, Republicans with less
approval in the polls are
fighting each other, especially
Florida Governor Ron DeSantis,
and former South Carolina
Governor Nikki Haley. The two
went back and forth all week
long on the issue of taking in
refugees from Gaza. Now just on
Friday, Haley released a new
campaign at directly targeting
DeSantis
Adam Curry: I find it very
interesting that she still is
out there and trying to get some
some
John C Dvorak: actions get big.
She's got big Silicon Valley
money behind I think she has big
oil money behind her too. Yes,
she's got money. She got lots of
money that she hasn't got she
Money doesn't buy charisma.
Charisma. She
Adam Curry: got her asthma.
John C Dvorak: She hasn't got
that she hasn't got enough of
that to get by. Which is a shame
for her. But I don't like her
policies anyway. She's really
anti Trump. She's pro war. She
might as well be a neocon. He's
Adam Curry: very pro war. Yeah.
John C Dvorak: The law McGann
Adam Curry: the big anti Trump
news that we had to stop, you
know, breaking news by the way,
notice that all the NBC channels
they're you know, they're all
pro Palestine and it's not
because they hate Jews or care
about Palestinians. It's because
Trump that's their base their
their viewers are the people who
are mind controlled by these by
this this outfit to go out and
protest. It's all it's all
antitrust. It's all political,
has they? They're actually the
worst people in the world
because they really don't care.
Either way. They don't care
who's killed or who's whose
babies heads are chopped off
faster than the other. They
don't care. It's about Trump.
And boy where the network's
happy with this news Sydney
Unknown: Catherine Powell she
was at the center of Donald
Trump's effort to overturn his
2020 laws publicly pushing
outlandish claims of election
fraud and privately meeting with
the former president inside the
White House. But tonight, just
one day before her trial was set
to begin, Sidney Powell pleading
guilty and agreeing to cooperate
with prosecutors. Miss Powell.
Do
you understand the charges that
are against you here today?
Do Paolo spread the false
conspiracy theory Georgia
election machines were
controlled by Venezuela even
pointing a finger at the
country's former dictator Hugo
Chavez, who was dead.
This was exported from Venezuela
and by Maduro and by Mr. Chavez.
This is the consummate foreign
interference in our election in
an Oval
Office meeting on December
18 2020. Powell allegedly
suggesting Trump name her
special counsel to investigate
election fraud. In that same
meeting, Trump and his team
allegedly weighed seizing voting
machines, even declaring martial
law. As part of her plea deal.
Powell is now required to
testify against her co
defendants, including the former
president.
Adam Curry: So that's the ABC
version and by the way, what she
so what she pled guilty to a
plea deal, which is probably
what she needed to do to not,
you know,
John C Dvorak: yeah, I have I
have another clip about the
other guy who just did the plea
deal after she did. And if you
listen, if you listen to it, and
read between the lines is the
Georgia clip says Georgia, if
you read between the lines or
listen between the lines, these
guys are doing this just to say
I mean they're not getting any
jailer and they're doing it to
save their their
Adam Curry: day go broke
pocketbook. I only have Georgia
plea bargain too. Is there a
one?
John C Dvorak: Unfortunately no.
Unknown: A northern Georgia
defendant cuts a deal attorney
Ken Chesbro gets five years
probation and exchange for
cooperating with prosecutors.
That leaves 16 defendants
including former President Trump
in the Fulton County Rico case.
Here's more from Legal
Correspondent Arlene Richards.
Another day another plea deal.
Third defendant in the sprawling
Georgia election racketeering
case pleads guilty. He's the
second attorney to do so but the
only one to accept a felony
charge.
How do you plead to count 15
conspiracy to commit filing
false documents in indictment
number two three sc 188947.
Guilty guilty
attorney Ken Chesbro was facing
six felony charges in the
election fraud case brought by
prosecutor Fani Willis against
19. Defendants father,
prosecutor said she would have
shown at trial.
Adam Curry: I thought it was
Fanny now it's funny. It's funny
how I love Yes,
Unknown: several other
defendants entered into a
criminal conspiracy to cause
certain other co conspirators
including David James Shaffer,
Sean mica, fair Thrasher steel
and Kathleen Austin Latham to
falsely hold themselves out as
the duly elected and qualified
electors for the President and
Vice President from Georgia
following the November 3 2020
presidential election.
Adam Curry: This is interesting.
So I think Georgia is one of the
few places where you can be you
can put a whole bunch of things
together and then call it a
conspiracy. So these conspiracy
charges that that Sidney Powell
pled guilty to are misdemeanors,
I mean, she's she got like,
$5,000 fine. And it was
literally to commit
international interference with
performance of election duties.
By him know what that means.
Sydney, this,
John C Dvorak: this, this is one
of those situations where people
should realize that if the
government insert, especially
state governments that are
corrupt at the point at the
district attorney at the
district attorney level, and
they just want to go after you
by dumping stuff on you, and
they have an amenable judge
can't be it because most judges
that aren't you know, amenable
to this sort of thing that you
said they just throw the case
out immediately. So we got
better things to do with our
time. But you had that
situation. The perfect kind of
the perfect storm. Your screwed
Adam Curry: friend of ours went
to jail for 18 months over
something stupid or
John C Dvorak: yeah, very
similar that da had a grudge.
Adam Curry: Yep. And had a
relationship with the with the
prosecution. Yep, there's no
harm, no financial harm, but off
off to the big house. CBS their
version, Sidney Powell, the
conspiracy peddling FORMER
ATTORNEY FOR FBI the way we do
hang with criminals is kind of
cool to say when we're
Unknown: President Donald Trump
sat in a Fulton County courtroom
today and admitted to her role
in the breach of voting systems
in Georgia. Are you
pleading guilty today because
you agree that there is a
sufficient factual basis that
there are enough facts that
support this plea of guilty? And
then
Powell was sentenced to six
years probation will pay 1000s
in fines and write an apology
letter to this citizens of
Georgia
Adam Curry: love that. You have
to write on the blackboard 50
times I will not commit this bad
conspiracy
Unknown: along with Trump. She
was one of 19 defendants in the
case brought by district
attorney Fadi Willis finally
agreed to testify truthfully
against her co defendants at
future trials.
If I'm Donald Trump, or I'm
Donald Trump's lawyer, I would
certainly not be happy.
Beyond Georgia Power was a
central figure in pushing
Trump's false election denial
claim.
President Trump won by a
landslide. In a now
infamous December 2020 Oval
Office showdown, Powell pushed
to cease voting machines to look
for fraud. And although Trump
entertained her conspiracy
theories, some White House
lawyers were appalled.
What they were proposing,
I thought was nuts, pounds
impact that's not
Adam Curry: the same as being
appalled. He thought it was
nuts. He wasn't appalled
Unknown: by thought was nuts.
How's impact on Trump and others
in the case could be
significant. You were
ever in the room with Sidney
Powell. You are very, very
nervous.
Adam Curry: Now what you notice
from the reporting and I had to
go in I had to look for about 10
minutes to find out what she
actually pled guilty to all of
this is they make it sound like
she committed some horrible
offense and they just, you know,
they don't actually tell you
what she pled guilty to. And
here's the final one from NBC
tonight.
John C Dvorak: That last one was
ABC when I was CBS. Last one was
CBS. CBS. I just want to mention
your comment about that was nuts
and saying that was appalled. He
guy was appalled when he wasn't
that's very different, I think
is a great example of slanted
coverage.
Unknown: NBC tonight once an
attorney then a co defendant now
a cooperator. How do
you plead to the six counts of
conspiracy to commit
Adam Curry: once an attorney has
she been disbarred? I don't
think she's been disbarred. Has
she been just I don't
John C Dvorak: think so. What is
it in her day? Then? The bar
dispersion not to a judge. You
know you're a criminal
Unknown: Knight once an attorney
than a co defendant now a
cooperator. How
do you plead to the six counts
of conspiracy to commit
intentional interferes with all
forms of election duties
Adam Curry: guilty. So that was
interesting. NBC puts it right
at the top of the report,
Unknown: Sidney Powell, one of
19 charged alongside the former
president in a sprawling
conspiracy to overturn the 2020
election results in Georgia
pleading guilty to six reduced
charges in court today, just as
jury selection for her trial was
set to begin tomorrow.
Do you agree that there is a
sufficient factual basis that
there are enough facts that
support this plea of guilty and
then
Adam Curry: see what they're
doing? This is great.
Unknown: Remarkable about face
for one of Mr. Trump's fiercest
defenders. I'm going
to release the Kraken
pushing the basis.
John C Dvorak: Oh, well done.
Not really crack and go. Kudos
Adam Curry: kudos for NBC on the
crack.
John C Dvorak: Very good edit
Gerawan gorilla
Unknown: bout face for one of
Mr. Trump's fiercest defenders.
I'm going to release the Kraken
often pushing baseless
conspiracy theories the last
election,
President Trump won by a
landslide, we are going to prove
it.
Instead, she's now admitted to
helping organize the breach of
sensitive voting equipment in a
rural elections office agreeing
as part of the new plea deal
with prosecutors to write an
apology letter to the people of
Georgia handover documents to
investigators and come clean
about all that she knows about
her former client as Mr. Trump
continues to fight the charges
against him
Adam Curry: here to testify
truthfully, against any so this
is interesting. So the the voice
over here says to come clean
about all what everything she
knows and come clean. No. The
only thing because right it's
followed by the truth. You will
testify truthfully as part
Unknown: of the new plea deal
with prosecutors to write an
apology letter to the people of
Georgia hand over documents to
investigators and come clean
about all that she knows about
her former client as Mr. Trump
continues to fight the charges
against him
here to testify truthfully,
against any and all co
defendants in this matter at any
upcoming proceedings.
Pals testimony, likely an asset
for the Fulton County DA who has
now managed to secure two guilty
pleas so far,
Adam Curry: I mean to testify
truthfully doesn't mean that's
an advantage to the prosecution.
No, it
John C Dvorak: could be a
disadvantage, and she's probably
Adam Curry: thought of yeah,
I'll testify truthfully. Yeah,
sure.
John C Dvorak: Why wouldn't you?
That's what you do. That's what
you're supposed to do. That's
what happens when he pledged to
testify. And
Adam Curry: once you have a plea
deal, that's it. They can't
renege on that. I don't think
yeah, they can unless you're
Hunter Biden.
John C Dvorak: No, they can they
can Oh, there's a lot of
different ways you don't watch
enough criminals TV shows. I
don't
Adam Curry: don't Sorry. No
good.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, they can
renege. But they won't. They
don't have time for it because
it's costing them money too.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, they just You
know, make it sound like she's
got some the goods, she has the
goods gonna come clean and turn
and turn in trunk beds because
he was obviously wringing his
hands going, here's what we're
going to do, ladies. I don't
think so.
Adam Curry: That was good. I
love that. Let's see, of course,
we had on the last show day we
had President Biden doing his
primetime message. What did you
think his jacked up factor was?
John C Dvorak: I gave him a five
it was low. I
Adam Curry: agree. I was
expecting more jaggedness. But
around four minutes, he started
to stutter and he was coughing.
John C Dvorak: Oh, they didn't
keep him on long. Was very don't
get enough juice. They don't
leave money they have to if they
give him a good hotshot just
below enough to kill him. He'll
go even on our good hotshot.
Yeah.
Unknown: All right. Here's ABC
News reports night, for the
first time the US has taken
military action in this war to
defend
Adam Curry: I'm sorry, that's
not the right one. That's not
the right one. Here is CBS.
That's what I'm
Unknown: we're going to begin
with a very forceful message
from President Biden last night.
Did you see it? He's urging the
American people to rally around
Israel and Ukraine. The
President made his case last
night in a rare primetime
address from the Oval Office.
You're rare? No kidding. He
argued that the US should not
should not let partisan politics
get in the way of billions of
dollars of new aid to those
countries. A clear message to
Congress
the president speech comes as
the US faces criticism in the
Arab world for supporting
Israel, and its controversial
bombing campaign in Gaza, with
the possible ground invasion
looming. For more on this
critical moment in global
politics. Let's bring in ED
O'KEEFE who is at the White
House, Edie? Good morning.
Nate, good to see you for the
first time last night the
President tied together the
conflict in Ukraine and the
conflict in the Middle East.
Alright, stay us engagement,
John C Dvorak: how many times
you're getting it could mean
you're gonna pass off the story.
Adam Curry: What do you mean,
pass it off?
John C Dvorak: That one guy
comes on and he passes off to
number two and number two passes
off to number three? Do they
ever tell us the story? Yes.
Unknown: Let me share with you
why making sure Israel and
Ukraine succeed is vital for
America's national security.
President Biden in a rare Oval
Office primetime
Adam Curry: address how many
times that's a rare, so rare, so
rare, very rare. It's very rare,
very rare, very rare,
Unknown: laid out the stakes for
Americans and he has some
convincing to do rare steaks. As
new CBS polling finds more than
half of Americans disapprove of
how the president's handling the
Israel Hamas conflict. And
notably, a third of Democrats
disapprove, which creates a
challenge as he prepares to ask
to spend billions more to defend
Israel.
Adam Curry: That's a third of
Democrats there. They're the
mind controls. But that is your
30% of mind control people and
Ukraine.
Unknown: Hamas and Putin
represent different threats. But
they share this in common. They
both want to completely
annihilate in neighboring
democracy.
And well, Russia's invasion of
Ukraine stretches into nearly
its 20th month, the President
gave some of his most expansive
comments yet justifying
continued US support.
If we walk away and let Putin a
race for Ukraine's independence,
would be aggressors around the
world be emboldened to try the
same
Mr. Biden is set to ask Congress
today for roughly $100 billion
in emergency spending over the
next year. It includes $60
billion to support Ukraine,
around $14 billion for Israel
and a $5 million VIG and the
rest would support Indo Pacific
countries including Taiwan
against Chinese aggression, plus
billions more US border security
and disaster relief
is a smart investment that's
going to pay dividends for
American security for
generations.
To Smith comes as overall
Americans strongly support
sending humanitarian aid to
Israelis and Palestinians, and
then using diplomacy to try to
end the conflict.
By caution the Government of
Israel not to be blinded by
rage.
Adam Curry: The President I love
the editing jobs here
Unknown: at Tyrion aid to
Israelis and Palestinians and
then using diplomacy to try to
end the conflict by COVID
John C Dvorak: Government
Unknown: of Israel not to be
blinded by rage.
The President also denounced
attacks on innocent Palestinians
abroad and he went home
recalling the brutal murder this
week of a six year old Muslim
boy from the Chicago there it is
efficiency a Palestinian
American was stabbed to death by
his family's landlord and I hate
crime attack.
And all you heard it because
you're you're hurting. I want
you to know I see you. You
belong. And I want to say this
to you. You're all America. He's
talking to the base
and he reiterated dual global
conflicts are a direct threat,
even worlds away.
American leadership is what
holds the world together.
American alliances are what keep
us America safe.
Adam Curry: Yeah, real safe.
John C Dvorak: There's no I have
I have dead date shoptech Today
Have a 13 second continuous
Biden from speech. And I brought
here odd comment. And there's
something about the wind when
you piece it together listening
to it this way, it's got an odd
moment,
Unknown: I'm going to send to
Congress, an urgent budget
request to fund America's
national security needs to
support our critical partners,
including Israel and Ukraine is
a smart investment that's going
to pay dividends for American
security for generations. It's
going to
Adam Curry: pay dividends.
John C Dvorak: How's it going to
pay dividends?
Adam Curry: Well, it's going to
pay dividends perfectly.
Everyone who invest in the
Ukraine rebuilding project is
going to have it
John C Dvorak: doesn't mean that
we're going to get all that
business.
Adam Curry: What a president
lying. No, of course not. But we
know that the consultant said
you got to get in now get out on
the ground on the ground floor
because the money's coming. The
60 billion, this is what it's
for. And there's a 5 billion
vague in there somewhere that I
think goes to James Biden, this
is also corrupt. I thought that
Israel Hamas was the this was
the big one. This is the big
war. This is what we really used
to be afraid of. But no most of
the money goes to Ukraine. Don't
I don't get it anymore. Now now,
of course, the President's
speech did not did not do the
right thing at all. And Bolton
came out. The mustache fart
sniffer.
Unknown: The principal threat to
peace and security in the Middle
East today and for some years
back has been Iran. In the
current circumstance. They're
the ones who have armed and
trained and equipped and
financed Hamas. They've done the
same with Palestinian Islamic
Jihad. They've done the same
with Hezbollah. They've done the
same with the Syrian military.
And remember just yesterday,
demonstrating again, they've
done it with the Houthi rebels
in Yemen. a US destroyer in the
Red Sea destroyed several cruise
missiles and I think some drones
heading north in the Red Sea
probably toward Israel. So the
hoodies wouldn't have any rocks
to rub together. If it weren't
for the equipment. Iran has
given them Iran as the central
factor here. and last night the
president's address which was
fine as far as it went, did not
address that crucial point. How
can you have a strategy if you
don't know what the main threat
is? In fact,
I would say bomb bomb bomb
again.
Adam Curry: Yes, this is he's
talking about the Hootie, Hootie
and the Blowfish. I don't know.
It's who fees you mustache jerk.
The
Unknown: real question is do you
want to deal with the threat
from Iran? Or do you want to
pretend that it doesn't exist?
The administration has gone out
of its way right. Pretend that
it doesn't exist, including its
chief Iran negotiator, Rob
Malley being having his security
clearance suspended in April by
the State Department's
Diplomatic Security Bureau that
the chief negotiator under
security investigation. It's
just unbelievable.
Somebody's got to drop a new
tear. I don't know who it is,
but I don't want to watch
Adam Curry: Yes, this is how we
draw Iran into the conflict is
with it's crazy. The hoodies
hoodies in the blowfish up
there. They got drones. They got
cruise missiles. I mean, there's
got to be Iran right
Unknown: tonight. For the first
time the US has taken military
action in this war to defend
Israel.
Adam Curry: Yeah,
Unknown: with the hoody see us
has Kearney a guided missile
destroyer in the northern Red
Sea shooting down three land
attack cruise missiles and
several drones. They say were
launched from Yemen, possibly
towards Israel by Iran passively
forces
Adam Curry: this is just this is
ABC, of course Martha Raddatz.
These people are war mongers.
They are paid off and completely
under control by the military
industrial complex.
John C Dvorak: They have the
idea, by the way, that from
Yemen, where they're having the
time of their lives, you know,
fighting against the Saudis.
They're going to waste a missile
and shit and send it toward it
for some reason what with with
our defenses right there.
They're going to send it to her
toward Israel just randomly. It
doesn't make any sense.
Unknown: We cannot say for
certain what these missiles and
drones were targeting, but they
were launched from Yemen heading
north along the Red Sea,
potentially towards targets in
Israel.
John C Dvorak: I get potentially
we're not sure surely maybe we
can be sure.
Unknown: People believe and it's
likely true. The US is
bolstering its firepower in the
region, a second carrier strike
group joining us warships
already in the Mediterranean and
additional fighter aircraft also
being sent all meant as a
deterrent.
We aim to send a strong message
intended to deter a wider
conflict to bolster regional
stability and of course to make
it clear that we will protect
and defend our national security
interests
and tonight real concern for US
forces in the region with
attacks against US bases in Iraq
and Syria in the past 24 hours.
And another today. One drone
shot down. No injuries reported.
Tractor sheltering in place in
Iraq died of cardiac arrest.
John C Dvorak: Ah, some guided
heart attack. Yeah. Contractor.
Yep. Hey, buddy. If you don't
like it in the Middle East get
out do Yeah. Well, I got most of
my clips from Al Jazeera because
they seem to be trying to be
objective.
Adam Curry: Okay, well, you know
what Ron? Ron DeSantis says, I
wouldn't trust anything from Al
Jazeera.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, well, he. I
don't know where you can't get
reasonable coverage from anybody
but Al Jazeera and I hate to say
that, but let's start with the
Gaza convoy, which has been a
fiasco report. From Al Jazeera.
This is war Gaza convoy report
Unknown: as more convoy of 20
trucks carrying food and
medicine have entered Gaza
through the Rapha crossing from
Egypt and unloading their
desperately needed cargo. But
rights groups say the aid won't
even make a dent in terms of
relief for the 2.3 million
Palestinians. As Harry Fawcett
reports.
They'd been standing ready for
days and at last the first
lorries carrying desperately
needed supplies or on the move
from Egypt into Gaza, just 20 of
them what aid agencies are
calling a drop in the ocean,
when a sustained reliable supply
is what causes people require a
well I
can not have that amount and we
hope this is the beginning and
that's efficient aid will arrive
sad and there would be global
pressure to stop the aggression
on Gaza,
food, water and medicine. We're
all unloaded that new fuel part
of Israeli conditions barring
anything it says could aid
Hamas. And the border was closed
again immediately. No way out
for those with foreign
passports, who had been told to
gather there, among them. The
mother in law of Scotland's
First Minister Hamza Yusuf
people of Gaza want to live they
can in the know you even believe
there's no air they suffered,
watch the children play in the
day and cry in the evening. My
heart is broken.
Adam Curry: But at least Algeria
is learning how to use that
trauma based entertainment that
the meal
John C Dvorak: what is what are
these weird people doing in
Gaza? Like that woman that Irish
woman who's the mother or
daughter or sister of some Irish
you know, diplomat, I guess
we've noticed this and they let
you know they let the two
American hostages go you know,
Adam Curry: you know do you have
any any clips on that because
that whole thing smells very
fishy
John C Dvorak: I only have a
couple of congressmen and I have
a I was looking I there was a
clip I want to get I don't have
it but there is that thing
stinks Yeah Right yeah. And in
fact what that does these clips
here this to two more hostages
tale is worth playing because
they've decided they're going to
release a couple more and they
just really say we don't want
them using this for propaganda
and so they so LG zero brings on
a complainer who's a Hamas guy
going out? Yeah, these guys.
They won't do anything. We try
to help them and we're, you
know, we're getting no, just
play this
Unknown: in Gaza and the
military wing of Hamas says
Israel has refused to accept its
offer to release to more
captives. Ghassan brigades says
it wanted to release the
captives on humanitarian grounds
and without conditions. The
Israeli Prime Minister's Office
has responded saying that they
will not address quote false
Hamas propaganda and will
continue to work to bring all
captives and those missing back
home. Earlier my colleague
Felipe attivo, spoke to Hamas
spokesman coloured Allah
Khademi. He says there were no
clear reasons for Israel to
reject that proposal,
or they were to captives with
the custom brigade and due to
severe humanitarian position. We
decided to hand them over to the
families through the brothers in
Qatar, and that's what we have
informed them last night
Adam Curry: were these hostages
in Qatar.
John C Dvorak: No, I don't think
so. They're gonna get into
Qatar. And this whole redist
report just emphasizes what's
wrong with the first dose to
those first two, that girl and
her mom who were praised as as
supporters of BLM and part of
the movement.
Adam Curry: This reads like a
UFC script. The whole thing,
doesn't it?
John C Dvorak: Yeah, it does.
It's really, really lame. And
when you listen to this guy
going on,
Adam Curry: I want to roll it
back again. I want to hear
exactly what he said. What am I
want
John C Dvorak: to mention Even
if you're going to religious
release some you don't have to
what is this real got to do with
it just let them go
Unknown: and humanitarian
position. We decided to hand
them over to the Who
Adam Curry: is this guy who's
this guy talking?
John C Dvorak: This is the Hamas
spokesperson, okay. This is the
Baghdad,
Adam Curry: backed Baghdad Bob.
I forgot about him.
Unknown: And they were two
captives with the custom brigade
and due to severe humanitarian
position, we decided to hand
them over to their families,
through the brothers in Qatar,
and that what we have informed
them last night without anything
in return. But unfortunately,
the government of Israel, they
refuse to take them. And that is
also proof our ideas that this
this occupation, this Israeli
government is not serious and is
not ready to stop this blood
sitting. Continuous situation.
Did the Israelis tell the
catteries we're negotiating
these releases? They tell them
why they refuse to take these
two captives.
We didn't receive anything on
that. Wait a minute.
Adam Curry: So our best friend
in the region refuses to take
hostages who are Americans?
John C Dvorak: No, these are no
these weren't Americans are just
a call randos
Adam Curry: Oh, randos. Okay,
it's just randos. Well, who
cares about the randos?
John C Dvorak: Well, I don't
even believe any of this story.
The whole thing seems fishy.
Yeah. And Israel thinks is
bogus. And so they just don't
want to deal with it. Why don't
you just give them to the Qatar
Qatar ease? I mean, there's
other things you can do with
them. But okay, let's play part
two.
Unknown: Okay. You say they were
released, you wanted to release
them because of severe
humanitarian conditions, what
conditions besides you? Were
they injured were they
nothing, there's nothing I can
share with friends over here.
More than what has been come
with the statements of our VEDA
that those two captives they
were in the custody of Alka sand
brigade. And due to their
position to the humanitarian
position, we decided to hand
them over to refute the lies of
the Israeli governments about
our fighters and their high
morals and high values, that
they respect the prisoners and
the captives. And they deal them
as guests. They will live as our
other people live in in Gaza.
But again, I mean, the Israeli
government, they are not
serious. Previously, we have
announced that we are having
four prisoners before this war.
And the Netanyahu government
refused to talk anything about
the swab and they're exchanging
the prisoners and today, we are
having hundreds of them still,
we are we have offered to hand
over those captives who are in
severe humanitarian condition
for a sole reason of
humanitarian reasons that we
wanted to return them to their
families but the government's
they are not serious on that
they want to continue killing
our children. They want to
continue bombardment, the houses
the the Safe Families in their
homes, and they live bombardment
of mosques, hospitals, churches,
and they want to continue all
over like that. And
unfortunately, it looks that the
the the American government is
supporting their position. And
if I can just interrupt you for
a second just to get a bit more
from you on this. You see, Hamas
al Qassam brigades were prepared
to release those captors, with
severe humanitarian conditions
and pass on brigades have said
they want to do this free of
charge with nothing in exchange.
Adam Curry: This is weird. The
guy won't explain what the
extreme actions are as a
strategist.
John C Dvorak: By the way, this
one's kind of like Al Jazeera
during this reporting. They
actually have reporters in
Israel all over the place and in
Gaza all over the place. And
they're giving us material
that's kind of funny. Do they
have this? Do they have
Adam Curry: flak jackets on with
media? No.
John C Dvorak: This one says to
more second round and he brought
somebody else in to talk more
BS. And this is continues this
analysis or non analysis or
whatever you want to call it. I
just found it kind of
interesting.
Unknown: How is this playing out
on the ground with the public in
Israel?
So Emily, this is interesting,
because we saw something
relatively new happening. We'll
compare it to what's been going
on the past few weeks. Saturday
evening, you had a protest
hundreds of people in Tel Aviv
good Gathering in front of the
Ministry of Defense, many of
them were relatives of those who
are being held captive by Hamas
inside of Gaza. And there was a
level of anger being
demonstrated to the government
here that we've not yet really
seen, up until this point, many
of these relatives essentially
saying that the Israeli
government is not doing enough
to ensure the release of these
of these captives that they
would like to see the government
do more that they would like the
government to implement a
ceasefire until the captives are
released. And in fact, they were
also calling on the
international community to step
in, and help more to ensure that
these captives can be freed.
Now, beyond that, we're also
hearing more about public what
with the international
Adam Curry: community.
John C Dvorak: They find that
peculiar this whole report now
this report, we don't have any
of this from Western media with
the protests in Tel Aviv. No,
well, then he brings in some
polling that was done in there.
Adam Curry: We finished the
clip, I want to hear the rest of
the clip. I'm just I just stop
it just like, What's he talking
about? It's
Unknown: our release. And in
fact, they were also calling on
the international community to
step in, and help more to ensure
that these captives can be
freed. Now, beyond that, it
Adam Curry: sounds like a play.
This is some kind of, you know,
some play like, hey, you know,
look, it's they're trying to do
PR, but they're talking to the
wrong
Unknown: media outfits are also
hearing more about public
opinion, public opinion,
different aspects of the war
right now, in Israel. So we've
heard from a polling institute
called, we're polling the war
now, Gump. And they released a
survey that found, among other
things, first, that around 57%
of Israelis support a plan to
exchange families held by Hamas,
with Palestinian children held
in Israeli jails survey also
weighed.
Adam Curry: These Israelis have
children in jails,
John C Dvorak: at seams, so if
you want to stop that clip, and
play this crazy screed of stats
that this American Palestinian
woman had on again off of Al
Jazeera, and I think, let me see
if I can find that. It's too
many clips,
Adam Curry: craziest read of
stats, this
John C Dvorak: is great. This
woman is being grilled one way
that she's going back and forth
with this interview. And she
just goes off on the, on the
interviewer on Al Jazeera. And
she has a screen of like, just
stat. I
Adam Curry: got it here. I got
it here. Okay,
John C Dvorak: play this
Unknown: Israel right now, let's
not forget, there are 5500
Palestinians in Israeli jails,
with 1300, of whom
administrative detention held
without charges without evidence
without trial. Since 1967,
Israel has imprisoned over a
million Palestinians. So when we
talk about numbers when we want
to talk about civilians being
captured when we talk about
civilians being killed, okay,
there's over a million
Palestinians who have been in
Israeli military prison since
1967. And 80,000, Palestinians
killed since 19. Sorry, 67. So,
I mean, yes, we can, we are
opposed to civilians being used
in any way and being killed. But
let's keep things in perspective
here. And let's look at the
larger picture and who is really
putting the people, innocent
civilians captive for decades,
including now we're seeing it in
Gaza. But they've done this
collective punishment against
Palestinian people in the West
Bank and Gaza for decades,
including shutting off water and
destroying water lines to
Palestinian cities, including
building a apartheid wall,
including implementing ways, you
know, cutting off cities from
one another, including
imprisoning children in Israeli
military prisons, without their
parents or legal representation.
So I mean, context is extremely
important. Let's not forget who
the king of propaganda is in
this situation.
Okay. We appreciate your passion
on these issues. Dana, worry,
Hutchinson, a Palestinian
American rights activist, thanks
for your time.
Adam Curry: Thank you. Well,
well now.
John C Dvorak: So they had some
kid they have kids, I guess. But
what did that mean? 17 year
olds, 16 year olds. Five, you're
also could
Adam Curry: have just meant, you
know, behind the wall in Gaza,
you can say well, you know, lots
of people say
John C Dvorak: like, same same
coming over that you want to
finish this. I do want to
Unknown: finish us with
Palestinian children held in
Israeli jails survey also found
that around 57% of Israelis
support a plan to create
humanitarian corridors for
children in Gaza, managed by the
UN. And furthermore, it found
that 54% of Israeli say
compliance with international
humanitarian law isn't
necessary, including precautions
to minimize harm to children
when at war with Hamas. Now if I
can just unpack that last D.
This is quite remarkable,
because this is saying that
there's a majority of Israelis
54% According to this survey, so
They're saying that compliance
with international humanitarian
law is not necessary, including
when it pertains to minimizing
harm to children when it applies
to war with Hamas.
Adam Curry: I did get some
feedback from one of our
producers about the term unpack
and its origin. And the thinking
is that it comes from Peggy
McIntosh, a 1989 essay about
white privilege, titled white
privilege unpacking the
invisible knapsack that could be
the origin of this
John C Dvorak: funny bit in the
back unpack Well, I want to
point out something in that
guy's going on and on with his
numbers. He elegir Zero has been
doing a pro a bunch of
programming on the bloodthirsty
Nate that last little thing he
having just play a little bit of
d&d 50 fall I just say what it
is. 54% of Israelis polled don't
give a shit about war crimes. So
Adam Curry: what is this
polling? It was at a call out?
Did they have people on the
internet poll?
John C Dvorak: No, there was
some company mentioned that you
mentioned to her
Adam Curry: but I understand
there's a company they did go
John C Dvorak: details of
polling. People just say
polling, it's sick. They're
polling the war. But the thing
is, is that Al Jazeera has been
promoting the idea of Israelis
as bloodthirsty demons and I
will rise anti semitic and I
have to go into well, it's Al
Jazeera. And I have to they did
their special report I don't
have any clips from it, but it's
fascinating. They clipped a
bunch of the what I would call
Israeli Hicks people living in
the you know out in the middle
of nowhere someplace in the
hills. You know, it's the same
kind of thing that we do in our
meeting where we try to get some
guy talks like this he's got a
mission to some front and I'm
sorry I'm talking to foreign
correct cat dog. Oh, my dude
mitten. No, no, no,
Adam Curry: no no this this is
the guy this is the guy
John C Dvorak: these guys got so
they have these fans and the way
they presented it was very good
and so far as propaganda is
concerned they they have these
literally beautiful Israeli
girls who are Hicks. Oh, loud in
the the only good Arabs a dead
Arab I don't care if we shoot
every Arab if they come to the
house, and we shoot them it's
okay. She goes on and on like
this. Then they bring on another
beautiful girl and she's just
bloodthirsty and so so the Algis
are is kind of doing this kind
of thing. And I'm watching this
going wow, this is really good
stuff. But let's
Adam Curry: kind of Google are
you
John C Dvorak: deconstructing
your I think it's fascinating.
So here's this two more round
second round two
Unknown: and this is really
reflective of the mood right now
in Israel because you have so
much anger and shock still at
what happened on October 7 When
that Hamas attack occurred and
there is so much anger driving
all of this you have poll after
poll in Israel in which people
are saying predominantly that
they want the Israeli government
to go in and destroy Hamas Emily
Adam Curry: you know it's times
like this when the media has
just lost lost their their
marbles and all they want and
all media around the world they
just want blood they want
explosions, they want strife
they want disagreement the bank
they want is money in the bank.
And I think the curry Devorah
Consulting Group can help people
while making bank ourselves by
resurrecting our game show win
lose orj everybody has time to
play around win lose. Who's
gonna get it this time? Well the
hot Israeli lady kills him
Palestinian or the other way
around. Find out tonight. Lose
orj
John C Dvorak: just the thought
Yeah, the problem with our game
shows all it has is the opening
jingle I always
Adam Curry: have a game show.
John C Dvorak: We do have a real
Adam Curry: game show we have a
stinger that's all we have. We
don't we don't have a format or
a station to broadcast on. But
the idea is meant
John C Dvorak: it is. There was
another guy that came out a guy
named Daniel Levy. And I have a
clip from him he
Adam Curry: Oh yes. I played
this Daniel levy guy he was the
was the former negotiator or
Ambassador
John C Dvorak: yeah he's one of
those guys is in and around in
and around
Adam Curry: former yes former
Israeli You peace negotiator.
That's yeah. And
John C Dvorak: he was on with
another one of these interview
shows on AlJazeera called bottom
line and he came on and he was
on forever, yak, yak, yak yak in
a way. And he did. And he was
saying is this is going to be
bad news for this person is bad
news for Netanyahu had bad news
for this and bad news for that.
But he came up with a little
like, again, I'll use the word
screed about this being bad news
for the United States because
Biden is a fuckup. And this
whole situation is not good.
Unknown: America looks like an
outlier, not like a model to be
emulated. But like a country
that is fundamentally getting
his priorities wrong and doesn't
care when there is a boomerang
effect across much of the rest
of the world. We are seeing an
America that looks like a war
mongering nation. And I worry
for that I worry for that
reputation.
Adam Curry: What do you mean, we
didn't have that reputation
already? Isn't that isn't that
our reputation?
John C Dvorak: I thought that
was always our reputation. We're
a war mongering nation
Adam Curry: that I mean, that's
what most people in the rest of
the world look at us as that's
why
John C Dvorak: we got to keep
Trump out.
Adam Curry: Because he'll stop
all the wars. That's no good.
Speaking of that, we got a note
from one of our Jewish
producers. And I say this
because I don't want to give her
name way because a little
personal note, but you know,
she's had some issues in temple
with vaccine stuff back in the
day. And so she's written us
quite openly. And this is just a
lighthearted note. She says, I
hope you're well want to share a
story that happened this week,
when the Israel conflicts began,
I tuned into Ben Shapiro. Of
course, that's all the Jews
immediately go to Ben Shapiro,
American Jews, because I
understand why I figured he
would have boots on the ground
reports. I'm not a regular
listener of his anymore, but
this warranted some attention.
In the middle of one is one of
his reports, he began talking
about President Trump. Now
Shapiro has never been a Trump
supporter, but he admits he will
vote for him if he's a nominee
in the next election, but he
began to criticize Trump for
Trump's alleged castigation of
Netanyahu when the attacks
began, Shapiro was furious about
how Trump could use the events
to boost his own ego and agenda.
I just listened. I didn't think
much of it until I heard John's
deconstruction of Brooks and
Dunn. on Episode 1599, Shapiro
had used the exact same
decontextualized clip of Trump
that Brooks and K part had used.
I was so flabbergasted the next
day on the way to school, I
forced my husband and children
to listen to the whole segment.
My kids listen, I knew anyway,
but the husband doesn't. At the
end of the deconstruction my
husband turned to me and said, I
think I'm ready to start
listening to your no agenda,
guys. Now. Another marriage save
another man. Yes, yes. Yes. So I
didn't
John C Dvorak: know that
Shapiro, you said same misguided
clipped, chopped up clip.
That's, that's, that's, that's
bad. That's bad. That's really
bad. My last allergy zero thing
I want to play is that they were
going on and on about, there was
this long, kind of a
presentation. And they had this
little bit at the end where,
where Biden is out in the lawn
or someplace and somebody says,
What are you going to do what's
going on? Bla bla bla bla bla,
Biden says, I'm talking to
Israel. Just talk to him. I just
talk to Israel. Well, they had
an under boots run boots on the
ground guy, it AlJazeera who,
even though didn't call by now,
in person on the show, he calls,
he calls by not as a liar for
talking to saying he's talking
to Israel, and he's not. And I
just thought it was so funny to
listen to this guy go on and on
with all his details about how
this is bullshit. And this is
Biden called out for BS.
Unknown: Let's go to sushi,
hyper tansy, who's in Washington
DC for us, you have quite a
brief statement, what should we
make of it?
I think perhaps that he's loved
the lesson from Friday night
when he was asked the question
as to whether Israel should
pause the any ground invasion in
order to allow more captives to
be released? And he said, Yes.
And I think it was almost within
the hour that the White House
put out an urgent statement
saying, Oh, no, President Biden
didn't hear the question. He
just thought the journalist
asked whether he hoped that more
hostages should be released. So
now this time, at least he
didn't make the same mistake. He
simply said he was talking to
Israel. However, we've looked at
the full reports and the
readouts from Saturday, and he
hasn't talked to the Israelis.
According to those on Saturday.
He did talk to the Prime
Minister Netanyahu on Friday
where the issue of the captors
was raised no conversations with
Israelis, as far as we can tell
yet as far as from any official
announcements in the White
House. On Saturday, he did talk
to his national security team
about the latest on the Gaza
war. Incidentally, we did just
also hear that Tony Blinken, the
US Secretary of State, talked to
the Qatari Prime Minister and
the foreign military Foreign
Minister thanking them for their
mediation efforts with the
release of the to us captives
but also discussing further
efforts to secure the release of
all the other captives.
Okay, lots of moving parts
thanks for bringing us up to
speed she had pretends he in
Washington DC so go ahead
John C Dvorak: I just think this
is a little bit you know a
little kind of in the weeds a
bit but at the same time at
least he called Biden out for
his BS or mean he doesn't do
okay whatever you say
Adam Curry: there's gambling
going on. Yes. Our media is is
it's compromised. I don't really
understand do people white
people even watching this
because of the addiction we
talked about the top of the show
they just people need outrage
they need they need I need to be
triggered I need to you know
actually this was a this was an
interesting report. Hate say but
it was MSNBC and they have their
own reasons behind it which I
think I can deconstruct it comes
into the the loneliness factor
that we were talking about the
other day, all of a sudden,
loneliness is on the on the
menu, loneliness, loneliness,
what's going on with loneliness.
This, this is about well, this
is a doctor and she's got a book
we'll just set it will set her
up here MSNBC now for the last
two weeks or so painful and
shocking images of war have been
hard to avoid images showing
pain, destruction and horror. On
television, you can flip the
channel or turn it off
altogether. But on this on your
phone, the endless scrolling can
really have an impact on your
mind and your psychology. If you
are like me, you have felt it.
Let's bring in Dr. Su Verma, she
is a board certified
psychiatrist and she's author of
fourth of the forthcoming
practical optimism the art
science and practice of
exceptional well being. Yeah. So
this is for you parents. I know
the parents out there and you
know your kids see you your kids
are not stupid, they see you
scrolling you give them
scrollers they're probably the
kids are probably more
proficient at looking at your
browser history than you are.
Dr. Berman. These are dartle
times we're wondering what you
think the the biggest impact is
of seeing these images over and
over again on all our minds.
Unknown: Yes, so you know,
repeated exposure to graphic
stressful violent images can
produce anxiety, depression, and
a feeling of helplessness. Not
to mention anger, frustration,
and just feeling like we're very
conflicted and and passive as a
result. And I feel like when I
talk to my patients that
helplessness feels so profound,
and for different people,
helplessness can manifest in
different ways. Some people may
tend to turn to substances that
people are doomed scrolling, so
they continue to look for
violent images. Some people turn
to cyber bullying, because they
feel so angry, and they need to
lash out on somebody, they don't
know where to take it out. So
it's these are very challenging
times. Indeed, for a lot of
people, even if we're so far
away.
Adam Curry: Yes, I think this is
exactly the behavior I see
exhibited on no agenda social,
that people just get mad at
anything is I need to get mad. I
need to get mad because I'm mad
about something I can't do what
is going on or something. I just
feel I feel anxious. I'm mad,
I'm mad. I'm mad. How does this
work for children is also just
so casual at the moment, I was
speaking earlier with a
technology company that tracks
the behavior of young people
online and did one they all do
that dude, they were showing me
how quickly a child can go from
one innocent YouTube search for
something entertaining to maybe
something educational about
Israel to something absolutely
unwatchable within a span of a
few minutes and then go back to
business. As usual. I'm
wondering what do you think the
impact is of this sort of casual
exposure, especially on the
developing brain? Oh, it gets
very fine citizens, upstanding
members of society.
Unknown: Yeah. So you know, the
casual exposure can be
dangerous, because if a young
child doesn't have the context
around it, and they, they don't
necessarily even have the
language to be able to express
what they're going through. And
at the same time, they're
watching these images, and
they're thinking that this could
be happening to me, like they
don't have the context of okay,
this is not exactly in my
neighborhood, but it feels so
real. And this sort of 24 hour
24/7 exposure. It's not like we
have to go out to get it. It's
coming to us, as you said. And
the other thing is like casual
exposure also causes numbness
and desensitization. It's a form
of what we call cyber overload
or digital overload when the
brain is hit with so much
information, even if the
information isn't violent, but
just constant news coming to us.
Our brain wants to shut down and
it shuts down by saying, You
know what, I don't really care.
There's nothing I can do about
it. And that's the last thing
that we want. We want to be able
to have some sort of healthy
balance between what I say my
patients often say, Do I want to
be happy? Or do I want to be
informed? Because it seems like
we can't be happy and informed
at the same time, unfortunately.
Adam Curry: I mean, this is
obviously taking place on MSNBC
who themselves are huge
violators of what you're showing
on television. I mean, it was
only a few years ago when Janet
Jackson's nipple was the most
shocking thing we saw. And now,
thanks, everybody, thanks for
the telegram videos. mean this
it is not good. It is you can
John C Dvorak: sear the why wait
a minute, you're the one who
wants to put on television
executions.
Adam Curry: Okay, hold on a
second, we'll get to my purse.
This is dead. That's a different
story. That's a television
format. And we don't even have a
jingle for it like when loser
drone. I'm saying that with
social media. And it doesn't
matter if it's x or Facebook or
Mastodon or telegram. Telegram,
I think is actually the worst.
It Real telegram is really,
really, really toxic. And
John C Dvorak: it's not it's not
that thank tic TOCs pretty bad
keeping
Adam Curry: telegram is it's all
bad. And we're professionals.
We're older. We've grown up with
this. We understand why, for
some reason, were able to look
at it with some distance. It
doesn't affect me. But I see I
see my brothers and sisters have
no agenda nation affected, and
they used to not be so affected
by this stuff.
John C Dvorak: And I see your
sisters literally.
Adam Curry: My sisters. Yes.
Yeah. All right. You got me
confused with Andrew Horowitz.
Okay, last quick. I feel like
John C Dvorak: this is the best
Adam Curry: important thing to
contrast also between, you know,
happiness and informed when it
comes to it really being
important to inform people with
the most jarring images, right?
I mean, back when we first saw
images of war during Vietnam,
for instance, right, it shaped
our perception of that conflict,
it was utterly shocking to see
those images. But now, with
social media and with
smartphones, it seems like
something has changed. I wonder
what you think, you know,
obviously, there's this
individual effect. But what is
the sort of social effect you
think of becoming desensitized
as it seems we're being
Unknown: lack of empathy is
what's happening is that when we
feel so passive, helpless, angry
about things that, you know,
whether they're close to home or
far from home, we end up
becoming more passive, right.
And so sometimes we think that
like putting comments online,
while they are very helpful, and
can be educating some people, a
lot of the comments,
unfortunately, are negative or
angry and hostile and create
more and more divide. So there
is a very delicate balance. And
I feel like empathy is so
important and being able to talk
to people from very different
points of views. I'm seeing so
much clash and divide between
within families within friends
circles, and it's very hard time
right now to be able to get
yourself informed because you're
only hearing things from a
certain perspective.
John C Dvorak: So what you heard
there was an anti Trump screed
Of course there is anti empathy
is a yes, buzzword codeword for
Adam Curry: Trump. So here's
what I'd like to suggest for no
agenda nation, I call for a JCD
Monday. Be like, I
Unknown: mean, be like
Adam Curry: JCD, put your phone
in a drawer, a drawer, leave it
there and leave it there for all
of Monday. And I command
everyone to go to a no agenda
meet up. You can talk about
whatever you want. But you need
to be in social contact with
real people. I'm saying we need
to love each other. If only in
our own community. This I can
see we're breaking people are
people. I don't care about
anybody else. I don't care about
anyone else's listeners. We have
producers and they're breaking.
Be like JCD be like spike be be
like my campaign be like John be
like JCD put your phone in the
drawer on Monday. And go to a
meet up find a meet up this week
or next weekend. It's it's good
for you. So I went to
John C Dvorak: the meetup. Yes.
Tell us how was it? It was
great. We had about 35 people
the guy who's organized it is
Elizabeth Warren Rohnert Park,
and he's a new organizer and he
wants to do these meetups more
often he's a nice guy and the
group was great, good looking
group. And there was a there was
a Scott Adams look like it was a
socialist kid who came up says
hey, I'm a socialist. No way you
guys ragging on socialist I
agree with most of what you're
saying but yeah, hate
socialists. And what did you
submit? I tried to explain but
he didn't listen. And but he
donated so that's good, but but
there you go, but this is the
point of socialist donation. No,
you got something going Right
Adam Curry: yeah but this is
good so I'm glad that he came
good on him yeah I'm cool he's a
good guy nice guy because he
felt safe that's why he felt
safe in that environment this is
very good.
John C Dvorak: Oh yeah it was
the bars nice has been redone
since I was there less than I
don't know how long many years
ago it's nice now it's a pretty
was everybody's drinking What
are you drinking? Beer? Mostly
beer is a beer if it was a beer
Beer Bar Hill. Okay. Is a beer
bar. They had a bunch of beer on
tap including really good pills
nurse
Unknown: and any hotties Yak?
Yeah.
John C Dvorak: So he's a hottie
or two or three any spooks?
Maybe, maybe
Adam Curry: you're not it's not
a complete meet up until you've
spotted the fella there
John C Dvorak: may be I mean,
it's possible that one guy was
because he had everything going
on, you know, the kind of
sketchy background they kind of
look as possible. That was a
spook.
Adam Curry: Got a breaking news,
breaking news, breaking news
from our lawyer who has been
following the Missouri versus
Biden trial. Oh, yes. And there
is and he's been. I love this
guy. He's a pro bono. Of course,
he's a producer. And he's just
sending me updates. He goes
through all the documentation,
all the briefs that are being
filed. It's reams of paperwork.
He loves doing it. And I want to
read his report. Justice Alito
referred the government's motion
for a stay to the full court.
Now, just to remind you, this is
the state of Missouri suing the
Biden administration. I think
it's the Biden ministration, not
just Biden, personally, for
threatening social media
companies to take down content,
threatening them with Hey, you
know, we got section 230, you're
killing people with this video
with you're missing
disinformation. And as we've
learned that the courts are even
saying this is the most
egregious violation of the First
Amendment rights ever in
American history. And the media
really doesn't report on it
much, because why would they?
They're in Biden's pocket and
they hate social media
companies. So Alito has referred
the government's motion to full
stay with the full court. This
is not unheard of, but
definitely not the norm. To make
things even more unusual. The
Supreme Court treated the motion
for stay as a cert petition.
This cuts out an entire step
from the Supreme Court review
process. So the bottom line,
Supreme Court has accepted the
case for review. Remember, now
this went from the from the
Missouri court, which I don't
remember but circuit that is it
went to the Supreme Court,
instead of kicking it back. Now
it goes to the Supreme Court for
review, it will determine
whether the district court and
by extension, the Fifth Circuit
Daigo got it right. In
condemning the Feds laundering
of censorship. The media has no
choice now, but to report on
this. Hopefully, you are well
equipped to get a jump on
things.
John C Dvorak: Okay, well, we'll
see.
Adam Curry: Yes. And he says,
And he attached for my reading
pleasure, the supreme court's
order, which includes a dissent
from justices Alito, Thomas and
Gorsuch, who wanted to deny the
state altogether. It's a very
short five pages take a look and
see the point in a nutshell,
Alito, Thomas and Gorsuch are
worried what will happen in the
next election. And that's really
what this is about, is what can
be done from the White House
during the next election. Can
they you know, hey, Trump's a
criminal.
John C Dvorak: Take it off, or
something like that. Those are
conservative judges.
Adam Curry: I know. But I'm not
sure exactly what to
John C Dvorak: I want a
clarification on this. Okay.
Adam Curry: Both point of order.
Point of order.
John C Dvorak: So I got some
China News, China clips kind of
kind of China, kind of China. We
haven't talked about much, but I
think we should.
Adam Curry: Yeah, they're not in
play right now. But okay. I
mean, we have ramped up dad's
John C Dvorak: time to start to
look at it. Okay, good point.
Good point. Let's start with
wielding a sword we I got two
series of clips. One is on
illegal Bio Lab in California.
Adam Curry: This story has been
around you know, but of course,
of course this happened months
ago. But now it's it's getting
some attention
John C Dvorak: and the rest of
it the guy's disappeared to
Unknown: go and arrest over the
illegal Chinese Bio Lab in
California. It contained
bacterial viruses such as SARS,
COVID and HIV. Now authorities
say they've arrested a man NTDs
David Lam speaks with an epic
Times reporter who spent several
weeks uncovering the web of
connections tied to the Reedley
California lab.
Steve is first with the epic
times. Thank you for joining me
today. What's the significance
of this arrest? Do we realize
that the people behind this
company they have a very
complicated and complex
background and very troubling
background. They have been
involved With several companies
in at least 10 countries that we
have looked at, and they've all
been in trouble with the law,
the mastermind of his operation
is someone by the name of Jesse
Zhu. He's the one that controls
all of these companies. So Jesse
do this as a 62 year old man
that is a Chinese citizen, and
formerly lived in Clovis. So
what are some of the charges
that he's facing? He's actually
a Canadian citizen as well. So
the charges for what which was
arrested yesterday are
manufacturing and distributing
unbranded medical devices that
are not registered with the FDA.
And also for making false
statements to the FDA, including
his name, he, he, he uses a fake
identity, these are just still
charges. If convicted, he could
be in jail for x up to eight
years. How did this illegal
operation was running for so
long before it came into the
public's eye, or the code
enforcement officer? What see
what they do is they they move
from city to city, they change
company names. And as I realized
yesterday, they even change
identity names of the people. So
universal Meditec, which was the
main company that was involved
with the Bio Lab, has been going
through Fresno, Tulare, Reedley
back to Fresno back to Tulare,
back to really
Adam Curry: now is, is my
understanding that the illegal
medical devices were in fact
tests like COVID tests.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, they never
mentioned this specific share,
they just kept going on. What I
thought was interesting about
this is the description of the
guy changing names and
locations. About 10 years ago,
we had a Chinese producer, maybe
12 years ago, we had a Chinese
producer who had corresponded
with quite a bit and he told me
that this is the way you do
business in China, if you're, if
you're a criminal. And these
criminal groups get together and
they create companies that did,
these are the guys who produce
aircraft parts
Adam Curry: funny, this is how
the Biden's operate to.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, this is
very funny. You produce aircraft
part your illegal aircraft parts
with phony certificates, and you
do business as long as you can.
And as soon as they they get
wind of what you're up to you
close shop, move, change your
name moved to a different city
and start doing the same thing.
And you do this over and over
and over again, you could do it
free. According to him. This guy
says you could do this forever.
In China as long as he because
it's just it's just the way it
is as long as it goes on here
now
Adam Curry: Oh, no doubt what we
have no moral authority over any
other country
John C Dvorak: versus the
purchase, carry character.
Unknown: All of these people
controlling these companies are
also very closely related to
companies in China that are
related also to this Jesse do
person. But all of this was not
regulated was not approved by
the FDA. Going back to the
background of the Canadian
companies. Jesse Zhu and his
companies have been sued by by
the Canadian entities. They've
been sued several times up to
$330 million dollars for damages
done to those companies. Now he
didn't pay a penny of that he
found ways around it and legal
loopholes, Steve Espers with the
epic times. Thank you so much
for joining me. Thank you for
having me. Yeah.
John C Dvorak: Which brings us
to the second series of clips,
which is this is not reported in
this country. As far as I can
tell. I don't know anything
about this. I heard it on the
New Tang Dynasty. This is the
graphite story you know about
the graphite story.
Adam Curry: This is not
graphene, but graphite.
Graphite. Graphite is graphite.
John C Dvorak: Graphite is a is
a form of carbon one of the many
forms of carbon diamonds one of
them okay, and it's used a lot
in it turns out who new battery
in the same in the semiconductor
business and in batteries in
particular.
Adam Curry: Okay, no wonder it's
a China story.
Unknown: China is planning to
restrict exports of a crucial
mineral used to make Evie
batteries. officials announced
today that permits will be
required for certain graphite
products. He spoke to entity
business host Don MA for more.
Don Ma, thank you so much for
joining us.
Yeah, thanks for having me
today.
Before we get to the China part,
give us a little bit of the
background here.
Sure. First of all, China is the
world's top producer of
graphite. And according to the
US Geological Survey, China
accounts for two thirds of the
growth global supply. China also
refines more than 90% of the
world's graphite into material
used virtually in all Evie
batteries. So you know China is
an important player here in this
front. And the reason why
graphite is important as because
graphite is the largest Evie
battery component by weight, and
almost double the amount of
lithium in an Eevee battery. But
besides EVs graphite is also
commonly used in the
semiconductor aerospace,
chemical and steel industries.
And top buyers of graphite are
Japan, the US and a couple of
other countries. What doesn't
Adam Curry: China have that we
need?
John C Dvorak: Get it? How does
China out has outmaneuvered us?
In everything we're just sit
around flat footed are scions of
industry who make 2030 $40
million a year as CEOs don't do
crap about it because they're
incompetent. And here we go
again. And this is all because
we cut because Biden cut the
supply of AI chips, mostly from
Nvidia to China. So now now you
got you got to you get these
chips. Is that going to be good
for us? So you can't have the
chips. And so China just says
okay, you can't have the
graphite as part two.
Unknown: And now why is China
limiting exports of this crucial
mineral.
So according to the official
statement, as for national
security reasons, China's
commerce ministry said the move
was to ensure stability of the
global supply chain and
industrial chain, and to better
safeguard national security and
interests. It added that it was
not targeting any specific
country. But that's the official
reason. But some analysts are
questioning whether you know,
this is a tit for tat measure
against the US, because
Washington on Tuesdays said it
plans to halt shipments of more
advanced artificial intelligence
chips to China. And three days
later, here we are at Beijing
officials announcing these
graphite curves. So the timing
may be curious to some of the
Dutch
Adam Curry: press was just
reading yesterday, they're
complaining about how ASML who
do the lithography for chips,
they the Dutch government now
has no say over what goes to
China. It's all Washington.
Yeah, they've completely
capitulated. And they didn't. So
that's all part of this tit for
tat was. So what does this mean?
Ultimately, no one gets chips
and you keep your laptop.
John C Dvorak: I mean, it's
gonna, likely the machines are
built to last. I think there's a
last. I think there's a third
clip here, there is
Unknown: an on that last part,
what will be the impact of these
curves,
right. So under these new
restrictions, which will take
effect in December, China is
going to require exporters to
apply for permits to ship
certain types of graphite. And
the curves are actually similar
to those placed on chip making
metals gallium and germanium
from a few months ago. And from
what we've seen with that, those
restrictions, they have
effectively choked off exports
of those metals and pushed up
prices outside of the country.
So that's a reference. But what
analysts are also saying is that
the impact could be that the
average price of graphite will
continue to rise in the future.
But this control is not a
complete ban, and there has been
no significant impact on any
industry during the previous
temporary controls. And this
also raises the question,
though, of how dependent on
China does the US want to be in
the context of the
electrification of vehicles and
potentially highlights the need
for the West to perhaps have
independent supply chains and
self sufficiency in both raw
materials and downstream
components?
Adam Curry: Forget the chips for
a minute the jobs forget the
jobs won't this time it this
should tank the already stupid
Evie market can we just already
Can we just say that this is
dumb that this was a bad idea
and everybody who bought into
the electric vehicle is going to
get screwed? Your battery's a
third the cost of the vehicle.
No one wants to buy your car
secondhand. You might as well
lease it so you're leasing the
battery? I mean, isn't this all
just a dumb idea what won't we
just go back to explosive
engines combustion engines
John C Dvorak: Well I hope so
but you know they've they've
promoted this very well and you
get a superstar promoters like
Elon Musk doesn't help things
doesn't help. You know what
should be I mean,
Adam Curry: I know I see. Like I
see nothing but EVs on the lots
everywhere. Hundreds of EVs
unsold that people don't want
them anymore.
John C Dvorak: Well, actually,
even in China. There's these
photos that these people have
taken with drones have these
huge piles of unsold EVs that
are backing up now from these
Evie companies, because China's
making
Adam Curry: two or three and
these boundaries, they keep
exploding everywhere. It's
annoying. You can't
John C Dvorak: put them in your
garage. You to blow up the
garage and warehouse, you're
going to charge you got to put a
wire out to the car out and
sitting in the driveway. Does
that make sense? When kids would
come by you know, and you know,
throw it in a bucket or
something. I mean, you just
didn't know when to do we
haven't seen the vandalism yet.
Adam Curry: Before we take a
break a follow up on a clip that
we played in March from two of
my favorite radio guys. weenie
in the bud from Russia. I forget
their actual vo Vanya, those
guys. Oh, Vaughn and Alexis
Vaughn Lexus in the morning. And
they hoax Fifi Lagarde, the
director of the Euro European
Central Bank into admitting that
a digital Euro a central bank
digital currency was on the way
a reminder. Well, I have a
question about it, and they
pretended to be Zelinsky. And
she was all like Linsky and she
was primping her hair before the
call. Like who I came, I'm gonna
be talking to Lindsay, this is
when he was still hot news.
Unknown: I'm also a good user of
electronic money. So my
question, you're introducing the
electronic era as I know, so,
how can I be up? How can
switching to an electronic
currency help?
But two things Number one, it
will be decided in October. So
we are preparing the ground, we
want to be ready. We want to be
trained, but it will not be
decided until October 23. The
reason I'm personally convinced
that we have to move ahead is a
situation like the one we are in
now. We are dependent on a
supply of gas by a very
unfriendly country. I don't want
Europe to be dependent on an
unfriendly country's currency,
for instance, I don't know, you
know, the Chinese currency, the
Russian currency, the whatever,
or dependent on a friendly
currency but which is activated
by a private corporate entity,
like, you know, Facebook or like
Google or anybody like
Adam Curry: I'm user of Bitcoin
to Okay. Okay. Then he goes in
all that. So she said, October
23, we're laying the groundwork
and then she went into such so
like, oh, you know, it'll be
like, there'll be limited people
can you know, if we won't track
you unless you spend over 300
euros, then them all sudden the
the machines wake up and will
track you and don't worry, you
won't sell your information.
What I like about Fifi is she
doesn't mess around. They made
the decision five days early on
October 18. The digital
Unknown: euro is on the move.
Yesterday, the Governing Council
of the ECB approved the opening
of the preparation phase, it
will be a journey, and we will
walk the journey together with
the legislator. All European
institutions will be involved to
make sure that Europe is
equipped with the currency of
the future. Cash is here to
stay. You will have all options,
cash, and digital cash digital
cash. So what does it mean for
you? For consumers? It will be
free and easy to use everywhere
in the euro area. All of that,
of course is subject to the
legislative process. Cash or
digital. The choice will be
euros. You Euro your choice.
Yeah,
Adam Curry: your Euro your
choice. Yeah, but we want to
make sure you choose the digital
option and we are already going
out and doing some weak ass
advertising.
Unknown: Imagine a digital
single payment solution that can
be used for any kind of payment
throughout the euro area. Guess
what? It could become a reality.
The digital Euro. Easy, safe,
fast, reliable digital money
from the European Central Bank
at your fingertips whenever you
need it. How would it work?
You've gone for a meal with a
friend and you want to split the
bill. Simple. Open the digital
Euro wallet on your smartphone.
Check your balance. Enter the
amount of pay your friend
confirm your transfer. Your
friend will receive the money
instantly free of charge. It
doesn't matter which country
you're in or who your payments
provider is payments are still
made instantly even offline.
It's also easy to use the
digital Euro at your favorite
local shops. Gotta unlock your
device, place it on the terminal
authenticate, make the payments
online or offline. If you want,
you can also use a physical
card. What about e commerce? The
digital euro is also available
when you're buying something
online via digital or physical,
the euro will always be a euro
and have the same value
irrespective of format. Let's
embrace the digital era. Digital
Euro.
Adam Curry: That's right. And
every digital Euro comes with a
digital ID.
John C Dvorak: Let me get this
straight here. So I'm at a
restaurant. Now in the olden
days, I want to split the bill
with somebody we throw our cards
down both of us. Yeah. And the
restaurant takes care of it.
Give us a couple separate bills.
Simple ups, it couldn't be
easier.
Adam Curry: That's not true. You
always made me pay with a
company card.
John C Dvorak: Generally
speaking,
Adam Curry: he won't admit it.
You're always made me pay.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, cuz you had
the you had the MVNO company
card. Yeah, that was dynamite.
luceplan What's the point we're
going to bvo times good times,
those days are over. So but the
point is you normally go out
with somebody wants to throw the
cards down, it's all day. Now.
Instead, I gotta give a phone on
me. I gotta open the phone. I
got to scroll through my apps
and get this app up, and I gotta
find it. And then I gotta log
in. And then I gotta click on
something. I gotta find the
other guy's name. And I gotta
send him some money. And then he
pays the bill. This is like
ridiculously complicated
compared to throwing the card
down and letting the restaurant
take care of the the complexity
Adam Curry: this will never work
because you left your phone in
the drawer. And that's how you
get out of paying the bill it's
a bonus for
John C Dvorak: you duel for me
yeah nuts arguing about that
part but of course this heart
that we're not gonna work well I
Adam Curry: liked it David
promote anything it'll do
offline. How does that work? How
does it do offline payments with
does it connect to the internet
later? I mean, I'd have to
obviously that seems kind of
odd.
John C Dvorak: No, the whole
thing it has to have a it has to
have some thing in the car. It
has to be a chip card chip smart
card that has information in the
chip that kind of alludes to the
fact that you have a bunch of
money in your account.
Adam Curry: Well the two things
to look out for are one the
digital ID that will come with
this that's just a given and to
the possibility to European
Central Bank's into is a bank
digital money from the central
bank is classified as a cbdc and
they will be able to inflate or
deflate the money supply at will
take it take your money away.
Yeah, they could cut you off.
It's a beautiful thing. Yay
Europe you're good to go. You're
it's your Euro your choice. And
with that, I'd like to thank you
very much for your currency in
the morning to you the man who
put the C and B like JC D please
talk to my friend on the other
on the one on the Mr. John
John C Dvorak: C Bucha graph in
here so as to what David's
nights out there
Adam Curry: in the morning to
the control room. Hello.
We got 2077 on the troll counts
20770. I'm noting these and
we're 223 into it.
John C Dvorak: Yes, hello.
Adam Curry: Everything with us
just low.
John C Dvorak: Less low is very
low. Average on Sundays 24.
Adam Curry: Low t we got low T
low trolls low T. But anyway, we
love our trolls. Because they're
here. This is the only place
where it's healthy for you to
binge. And to get all your
triggering immediately. Just do
it. Do it. Do it only for three
hours, twice a week. That's what
we recommend and just stay off
of everything else. Put your
phone in the drawer be like JCD
you can join the trolls at the
troll room troll room.io or use
a modern podcast app. You'll
want one eventually. You can you
can trust me on that. Do you
know that John Stewart got
cancelled by Apple? His podcast?
John C Dvorak: He quit. Okay,
Adam Curry: there were creative
differences over China and ai
John C Dvorak: do we talked
about this in the last show?
Adam Curry: No. No, we didn't
talk about maybe maybe you
talked about it on DHL
unplugged. I haven't heard DHL
blog this week.
John C Dvorak: Anyway, you gotta
cancel these out. Yeah, get
Adam Curry: them on podcast that
podcast apps.com pod verse now
does Android Auto and I think
they're going to do Car Play or
something like that. So these
things are getting pretty good.
Getting pretty modern doing
things. Well. I
John C Dvorak: did. came up with
dinner that's what it was
because another Gao quit this
guy he did. The team left is a
new startup that's that's headed
creatively by John Lasseter out
of Disney he was the guy was who
was cancelled from Disney for
being too much of a hugger in
Calif in Southern California. Oh
my god. Oh no, he's hugging
these women constantly go and he
did a start up but this guy's
Apple hired him on and they they
all walked off in a huff and
went to Netflix for more money.
No to Apples can't keep it
together. They're gonna eat at
the by Disney. I mean they their
creativity.
Adam Curry: Can they even make a
joke? Can I even make chips
without the graphite?
John C Dvorak: So they're not
making the chips or designing
the chips. Oh, okay. So to the
foundries to get the graphite. I
think
Adam Curry: Apple's heyday may
be over. What do you think?
John C Dvorak: Well, the thing
is a couple of things. Since
we're talking about it, one JC
has the latest version three
that about the newest of the new
folding Samsung phones. The
phone? Yeah, it's a killer.
Adam Curry: What is the benefit
of a folding phone?
John C Dvorak: Oh, it's just a
vis smaller when you fold it up,
it hangs up on your folded down
you get to slam it down. It's
works like a champ. It's got a
terrific screen. It's a it's
just a marvelous product. I
would say that the second day
when it's taken share away from
Apple. The second thing is the
Huawei phone in China is killing
apple. Hmm. They're getting beat
up badly on their phone and then
they're not in fact, we talked
about this at the dinner table
when we talked about Jon
Stewart, which was why didn't
apple and if Steve Jobs was
running the place still that
folding phone that Samsung has
would have been an Apple phone.
Adam Curry: Yeah, I don't know.
I mean, I liked the
John C Dvorak: idea of having
got a touchscreen laptop for
God's sake. I liked
Adam Curry: the idea of rage
quitting your phone like the old
flip phone days like scroll.
Yeah, like slap it closed. I
kind of like that.
John C Dvorak: That's you can do
that with his phone.
Adam Curry: I stopped still
using my light phone mainly.
Yeah, that's
John C Dvorak: fine. I'm trying
to get any phone so I'm just
telling you what I'm observing
from other you know what's going
on. I like the Samsung folding
phone I don't have one. I don't
intend to get one I'm probably
too expensive and
Adam Curry: twit is really
missing out on you they need you
these are time because they're
going to be all googoo gaga over
that thing. And they need us
they need you to go I don't want
that phone and to change the
language to Korean Russians even
better i favorite trick my
favorite Jhansi divorce a great
John C Dvorak: trick for people
that don't know that trick I'll
tell you because anyone can do
this to anybody asked to borrow
someone's phone quickly go to
the settings go to the languages
and turn the language to Chinese
and then give them to us from
back and back to the homescreen
and back to the home screen and
then you're good to go
Adam Curry: and then your
friends for life you did that to
me once and I was I was a bit
disturbed by it I don't remember
what phone that was but I
remember you doing this and I
was like
John C Dvorak: yeah, that's a
good guy. It's funny. Yeah it
made you very popular with the
kids it makes you know it unless
you know how to get back to the
settings and sometimes they have
the icons will help you and it
but if but with some phones
especially earlier like 10 years
ago these phones were such that
you didn't have you couldn't
figure out how to get the
language back and you had to go
basically to your computer go
online and you know look it up
and it was very annoying I was
surprised I didn't get punched
Adam Curry: Have you never been
punched for just being you know
amazing amazing.
John C Dvorak: I haven't I have
a it's my attitude
Adam Curry: has no one I've just
come a sucker punch you just for
being you know,
John C Dvorak: you'd think yeah,
I don't want to put it in
anyone's mind. I'm on my guard
for sucker punches
Adam Curry: we so tomorrow you
can you can follow us but there
will be nothing happening. Um no
agenda social because everyone
will be doing it taking a JCD be
like JCD day. Put your phone in
the drawer tomorrow but on
Tuesday you can follow John C
Dvorak at no agenda social.com
Adam at no agenda social.com And
yes then not interact with us um
um, I'm going to try and I
interact
John C Dvorak: you with two
people I blocked both of you I
saw
Adam Curry: John's like I'm
always on no agenda social. I
see your no agenda social. What
are you talking about black. I
know what you were mad.
John C Dvorak: They were going
after you and the show the
studio From people, and they're
gonna lie down and one of them
who's I thought was a friend of
the show and some female and she
said, I can't remember who she
is.
Adam Curry: This is the one who
said, but I just stopped
donating. That's my face
John C Dvorak: that Yes, that
one. She says, Well, I still
listen to the show. But I
stopped donating because she was
very arrogant about it, because
this other guy was going on this
show stinks. And I said, What
are you even on no agenda social
for to tell us at the show
sting? I think I blocked that
guy. And I blocked her,
Adam Curry: I think is that she
said, I just get back at him by
by not donating to the show. And
I said, I used the Jhansi
Dvorak, I said, noted. And I
thought that would be the end of
it. And then she got really mad.
I'm like, I gave all my money to
you. I know rather what
John C Dvorak: she'd already
said she stopped doing that,
too. She's that she's overboard.
For all practical purposes, you
should have blocked her
Adam Curry: block. I only
blocked that one guy because he
just filled up my timeline just
annoying. Yeah, it doesn't
matter. I'm just lurking now
John C Dvorak: rubbed me the
wrong way you get blocked.
Adam Curry: Value for value is
the proposition. If you find no
value, then don't support the
show. If you do find value, then
support the show.
John C Dvorak: You don't quit
grousing, if you don't support
you know, just don't support the
show. Yeah. Is that setting
grousing and trying to get other
people not to support to show
that's what I don't like that's
what I blocked her for. She was
going on. She was firstly trying
to keep donations away from the
show.
Adam Curry: And that stopped her
you think about you blocking her
know
John C Dvorak: that they have to
listen to okay.
Adam Curry: Just even tomorrow
don't even Oh, she
John C Dvorak: wrote get to see
any of the fabulous memes that I
post.
Adam Curry: Oh, god, you're you
have not posted any memes. I
haven't seen any memes from you.
Yeah, I posted it because oh,
there's only one guy I like who
posted it? And it's weird. But I
like the guy. No. Baray I think
it is p post classic muscle cars
like that. I like those. That's
John C Dvorak: like Food Wars
memes. He does a lot of them. He
gets newsletter material from
him. Well, good
Adam Curry: for you. Yeah. So
throughout the years, people
have supported the show in many
ways, time and talent is a big
one. You can organize a meetup.
And then you really I mean,
you're doing it for no agenda,
nation no matter what. But when
you organize a meetup, you're
doing it for your brothers and
sisters. So you really need to
if you can organize a meetup,
that's a great way to help.
There's so many different ways
you can help getting other
people to listen. But not
helping is telling people not to
donate. And that's not time.
That's not a help helpful value
for value. No, it's negative.
It's negative value is envy,
envy for V. Now artwork we love
because it first of all, it's an
act of love, because artists are
putting their their creativity
out there, ready to be
criticized, which is our way of
loving you back. It is true,
because you normally do stuff on
spec, you don't hear anything
from anybody. They just ignore
you don't even get a phone call
back. And when we'd love to
having a new piece of art for
every single episode is great.
It gets people's attention. It
looks good when you post it, it
looks great in the podcast apps.
And we do have, you know, rules
and stuff that we need to adhere
to like, Yes, I go to read it
and we'd like stuff that pops
but that we break those from
time to time. And of course,
whenever there's a special
episode like the last one,
episode 1600 That's when you can
be pretty sure that we're going
to go for something that boasts
about the fact that it's 1600
episodes and Sir Suge, aka faux
Diddley, he did that and then
some and brought us the Infinity
artwork of 16 years. 1600
episodes. You liked it right off
the bat, you went straight for
it and said, I like this one.
John C Dvorak: Yeah, I like it
because I liked the use of
infinite perspective. And
vanishing point. I'm sorry.
Here's what I meant. Vanishing
Point. I think he used it well,
and we were talking about you
know, the vanishing point has
something to do with some of the
issues in the show is great.
Great.
Adam Curry: We looked at a
couple other pieces. I did keep
coming back to Parker Polly's
tramp stamp, but I don't know
why. I thought it was well
executed. The sweet 16 And what
else by the way, you can follow
this and no agenda art
generator.com You can also
upload anyone can participate in
this. You're more than welcome.
Also, a lot of these show up in
our chapters and those modern
podcast apps. I liked to have
something that I liked. I can't
remember what it was.
John C Dvorak: He really liked
much.
Adam Curry: No, I did. Did. I
can't remember. I don't know um,
look.
John C Dvorak: It was a lot of
art but it was was to do a
complaining about certain. I
don't remember who Oh, he first
of all decided we're going to
use 16.
Adam Curry: Yeah, I know what it
was it was capitalist agenda,
whose art was really if you blow
it up the 60s down at the bottom
of the page. The 1600 is kind of
peeling off this cube. It's
flowing over. I really liked
that piece. Yeah, that's a piece
I'd like to have on my wall. I
mean, I
John C Dvorak: I'd frame that
that was the light to
dimensionality. Yeah,
Adam Curry: thank you. But it's
somehow it doesn't work. I'm not
sure why it is something just
doesn't work in a small format.
I guess. They had to he did two
of them. You know, something,
John C Dvorak: it has his moment
and
Adam Curry: has had his moment.
However, we do want to thank Bo
Diddley for bringing us the
artwork for episode number 1600.
And the title of that one was
unpackage. We just heard one
theory where that came from. We
appreciate that very much. And
thank you to all the artists for
what you do. It is highly
appreciated. Now there's Phoebe,
ABC something or somebody. Tina
is still out. She's still in
Utah. That's
John C Dvorak: where you go to
overloaded the show with Eclipse
today,
Adam Curry: but you're the one
with the Eclipse.
John C Dvorak: No, I know. But
I'm saying you had a
presentation. You had deep
dives. You had a follow up you
had you looked into this group
of screwballs. And you had the
information even this is what
happens. Are you complaining?
No, I was fine. I was just
relaxing. But it was very
entertaining. It was
educational. It's educational.
Have
Adam Curry: a new schedule. I
got up early this morning. I'm
getting up early again. Oh, good
for you. Yeah. So I had had more
work and I did some You're
right. I did do some of the work
yesterday, right? Yeah.
John C Dvorak: The show gets
better. We're sitting there
bored. I guess so.
Adam Curry: Let's Yeah, let's
thank the treasurer. We have a
lot of PhDs in coming today
which is good to see we kick it
off with Brandon Jansen. Just as
US does not have a state in his
so I don't know where he's from.
John C Dvorak: But he Jaden D I
don't know
Adam Curry: where he has a note.
John C Dvorak: Came into it
though check and he came with a
check for some amount and then
$4 into dollar bills. We have a
$2 bill thing going on with the
show. And one of our one of our
executives or one of our
producers dropped off $222.22
And all the dollars were
introduced 110 $2 bills. Pow
Adam Curry: well this is a 1601
incident eight for his
conspiracy therapist sir Parson
of Florence sent us a card happy
anniversary card no agenda show
was true. The best podcast in
universe sincerely Future.
Future knights from Captain
Planet. This is hard to read.
You have the note there in front
of you. Handwritten notes I do
have the note if you read the
card, but then the note is
because he has Oh sir conspiracy
therapists or Parson Florence
John C Dvorak: Yes. I knew this
note was trouble when it came
in. Jay couldn't read it. But
it's in longhand and it is not
unreadable by probably let me
try to read it. I'd like to 1000
at this instant night my
spiritual therapists or Parson
of Florence whoever serves
probably have night already. The
remainder going towards my
future and knighting to be
determined tried listening to no
agenda after Adams first Rogan
Rogan donation appearance.
However, it was not ready for to
I was not ready to absorb the
information and analysis.
Adam Curry: Yes, you have to be
ready for this. Yes, true.
John C Dvorak: I agree. Fast
forward to the beginning of 2023
after six shots No, I didn't say
that. I was I was feeling lost
with my previous worldview.
Having been shattered after all
the relentless psyops beating me
down you both still sounded
crazy, but but only because I I
was in fact I was the crazy one
Oh, ah he gave KK he woke up. I
went back to twitch January
2022, and proceeded to listen to
all the years episodes. In
addition to brought me up to
date with the current episodes.
This helped me snap out of it
basically Holy crap. These guys
are on to skip the scams. He
says to himself, and he went on
and on he goes on I don't want
to read the whole thing.
Ignorance is bliss, but luckily
I've come to be I've come to
realize that it is better to
know With the truth, tend to be
comforted with lies. The first
step is admittedly that I've
been duped. I've been duped
which is not easy but but
improving while this note will
not be complete without a shout
out to my beautiful and
endlessly patient wife, my life
would only would truly be
meaningless without her. And our
boys thanks for the 21 years
babe an important part of the
note you are the light of my
life My reason is all scrambled
here at the bottom. My reason
for living? Sincerely a faithful
and future night Godspeed to
all.
Unknown: That's beautiful man
and he wants some karmic jangles
some good karma here. You've got
karma. Oh, wait.
Adam Curry: He also needs jobs
karma and baby making karma?
Well, we'll throw in a goat to
make that jobs,
Unknown: jobs, jobs and jobs.
That's Volker jobs.
Adam Curry: Karma All right,
then we have Keith Gibson with
1000 I don't have a note from
Keith Do you have a no try?
John C Dvorak: I want to say
that Keith is actually sir Kay
good this spring sir keg of the
spring. Okay, he I could not
find he's written before. So he
does I got his name. So he
hasn't said anything and for
this so we'll give him a double
up.
Adam Curry: Yep, double up,
Carmen is you go sir. Okay,
you've
Unknown: got
Adam Curry: grab the next one
then to make it easy. Kevin
Popovich 1000. These are all PhD
years. In The Morning John Adam.
Thanks for the bi weekly dose of
deconstruction and sanity in a
world of enlarged amygdalas and
experts who base their
professional opinions on what
many believe and what is most
likely true. It's it's always a
relief to watch fellow critical
thinkers and deconstructionist
straddle dimensions to reach the
point where all Wardlow world
lines meet. With enough
fortitude will and reflexes we
can reach the true end. With
this donation, I reach
knighthood. I'd like to be
knighted Sir Kevin Knight of the
reading of the reading Clover
READING A reading we think
reading Clover or the reading
Clover is just it's gotta be
reading it must be reading. I'd
like to request homemade Thai
pepper infused vodka and katsu
curry to be added to the round
table if there's Hey, I made
that. That's why we have it in
stock. Yeah, Reason is lit. He
says Well, thank you, Kevin.
Reason
John C Dvorak: and so my first I
should say before I do that, my
first batch of Thai pepper and I
get some Thai pepper some some
Hmong at the farmers market who
make some of the hottest type
peppers. In fact, the last
batch, they said Be very careful
with because they're actually
ghost peppers. No, no, because
because the mom had planted some
nearby ghost peppers. And they
interbred with the pollination.
So they're extremely they're
actually in danger. dangerous,
very dangerous, because it can
now so the first batch of Thai
pepper I made, which I still
have from like, 15 years ago, I
put like 10 of these Hot Thai
chilies in there. Yeah. One you
use 111? Not 10
Adam Curry: All right. All
right. So you live
John C Dvorak: Derek J Vickery
is up. Dear Linda Lou packin for
high also $1,000. So he'll be a
triple threat with the PhD,
executive producer and added to
it. All right. I recently
received my PhD in media
deconstruction with a minor in
sound effects. Do you have a
sense of current job market for
these skills? Congrats John and
Adam and the NA producers for
1600 episodes and 16 years.
Thank you.
Adam Curry: Oh, how incredibly
nice. Thank you. Derek Boggs
1000 Gentlemen, thank you for
your courage. I donated 1564 and
my name was misspelled in the
credits. Could you please
correct this? Well, yes, of
course. I would like to be
knighted sir Derek protector of
section 707707 I'm not sure what
707 He knows we don't he knows
huntsmen karma from my business
please. Well, doesn't really
exist but I can do on on the
fly. Fire barriers LLC. You got
it. Top blue tidy
Unknown: algae education.
You've got karma.
John C Dvorak: Derek pepper in
Northfield, New Jersey. 1000.
Another triple threat. Three
bagger night name sir air air
rock rock A R O C rock, a
defender of the aisle re readout
of the Brigantine home of pepper
Cove beach food at the round
table, some Tom Lau and make
Kong whiskey. Okay, way too low
Adam Curry: Yes, very funny.
Bang ding out. Okay. Dark Lady
dazu her dozer does her da Z Hu
R 1000 I'd like to be Dark Lady
dozer demon dragon of the
Undercity Thank you. You got it
done. Consider it done.
John C Dvorak: Brandon Jorgensen
another $1,000 winner. First
timer here love you guys and
everything you do.
Unknown: Oh thank you. Very
nice.
Adam Curry: Arne Lauren not I
heard I heard Arne Lauren not
what he heard he heard sounds
weird.
John C Dvorak: Do we had a kid
in school is named a her in a
Adam Curry: hurry and it really
does today don't get beat up a
lot kick. Seems like they just
ate her and would $1,000 No note
we have a note from Edgar I
don't have I don't have any her
in here you come with your W
karma. Karma.
John C Dvorak: And then we have
Linda who gets credit for it.
And it was Linda but as Linda
Yes, I think it is Linda. The
684 This is the donation from
the meet up at the mallard club
684 She was the lucky winner.
She and she needed a deed
douching we got
Adam Curry: bad deed deuced and
then we have Sir Chris and Dame
Christian from Walnut Creek
California switcheroo please
credit this executive producer
ship to my best friend since
grade school Sir William messing
of Bainbridge Island below
celebrating a double nickel
birthday today October 22nd. I
could not think of a better
president than an executive
producer credit on the best
podcast in the universe. Happy
Birthday bill. Please throw him
a goat karma for good health and
happiness. Congrats on 16 years
of media deconstruction all the
best to you and the no agenda
family. Sir Chris and Dame
Kristen of Carmel by the sea.
Unknown: You've got
Adam Curry: Armand switcheroo is
in is in. It's in.
John C Dvorak: Andrew a Katolik
is 33333 self proclaimed longest
time d bag. So I don't know if
you DEGUS he doesn't want to D
douching.
Adam Curry: Yeah, well, so yes
or no?
John C Dvorak: I would say no.
Because he wants to be a self
proclaimed longtime douchebag.
Adam Curry: Okay. No, it is
then. That's it. That's his
whole note.
John C Dvorak: As far as I know,
yeah.
Adam Curry: Wait, didn't he
didn't Okay? Unless you can find
Well, I don't know. I don't have
anything. Russell Davidson 333
dot 23 Fort Collins, Colorado. I
haven't donated in a few years
since I gave up sending checks
after a second check was
apparently lost in transit to
Elsa Rito. I don't like giving
PayPal any money but I know Zell
doesn't work from my bank to
yours. And I also haven't made
the effort to set up a pop money
account yet either. Given my
lapse and donations, please do.
You've been D deuced. Give me a
yet karma for an upcoming elk
hunt. Thank you for your
courage. Russell Davidson. Yeah,
karma for you.
Unknown: You've got Harma
John C Dvorak: bouquet. This is
the other new. Okay, we're at
Zach Williams. Can you find this
note?
Adam Curry: Well, isn't that on
the notes that we got here?
John C Dvorak: I have it. Yes.
Adam Curry: I believe I have it
here. Hold on a second. Yes,
Zach Williams, John. John, but
I'll read it 333 We hope you
enjoy this gift with family and
friends. You have been
encouraging part of my Thursdays
and Sundays my kids shout John
Cena of divorce Chuck, every
time they hear your voice,
whether whether you're whether
or not you've given another Hey
kids, a kids. Whether you know
listening, whether you know it
or not, you're making an impact
on generations. Very sincerely,
thank you for your courage
blessing from Zach Williams.
From the little truth company
little truth.org and find in
close you'll find first edition
number 30 of production to
hardcovers two coloring books.
Wow.
John C Dvorak: Okay, yeah,
little truth.org Go check it
out.
Adam Curry: And he says it says
if you go to little truth.org
discount code IETF 10 For no
agenda nation 10% Guess discount
on my first children's book The
Great Unknown. There you go. And
he wants we're all going to die.
And a little girl yay. Second,
where's my where's the little I
put the little girl in the in
the closet.
Unknown: You might not
John C Dvorak: to go. Okay, and
that was was that that's
Adam Curry: Yeah, exactly. But
for Chris it's a switcheroo.
John C Dvorak: Okay, so we have
Ba Cerise Meister and Sluss
altos another attendee at the
meetup I'm in need of a severe D
douching.
Unknown: D deuced. Severe to
John C Dvorak: me with 300 300
Hey John, what would happen if I
give carnivorous plants some
ammonium nitrate? I don't know.
I don't know about it. They
probably won't like it. Nothing
guy was yet to feed it with a
spoon. That's the problem. I
want to give a shout out to my
favorite podcast app RSS radio
by durata software not part of
the podcasting 2.0 Echo system
but hoping it will be. It was
one of the first apps to offer
silence, skip and provide an
equalizer was really cool as you
can group your podcast into
different categories that you
create. That sounds familiar.
And if you like the episodes
artwork, the app shows you the
URL of the image for
downloading. The app can also
display chapters and live stream
if you have a link. I got my PMP
certification so I'm going to
get a job as calm I need one.
Thanks sincerely, sir rich
Meister. Yeah.
Adam Curry: And as the developer
to check out podcast and 2.0
functionality,
Unknown: jobs, jobs, jobs and
jobs. That's burger jobs.
Adam Curry: Francisco Ramos is
in Temecula, Temecula, Temecula,
Temecula, Temecula, California
23456. Love that number. Good
morning, John Adam. I've been
listening to the podcast since
Adams appearance on Joe Rogan
back in September 2020 Rogan
donation I was tired of being a
douche. And I it happens and
decided to contribute some of my
treasure to the best podcast in
universe thank you both for all
you do. Please give me an
American made de Deus none of
that China made junk. De deuced
and I would also like China is a
foe. Oh, okay, a another you
might die. How often does that
happen? Another you might die
and a noodle gunging Go? Well,
we got all of that for you.
Respectfully, Francisco Ramos
from Temecula, California, my
name is as HoH you might die and
the jingle in the face with my
noodle gun you
John C Dvorak: get to my pasta
Glock locked and loaded. Now I
have certain black ammo in
Crockett California 23456. And
there's no note from him and I
can find it. So this gives him a
double up karma
Unknown: you've got
John C Dvorak: I want to get
this next one. This is Mr.
Montague who is at the meetup.
And he's the one who dropped off
$111 bills. $2 Bill nice. I like
it. I like a diamond to pen a
table of dimes and two pennies.
And it's a row of ducks. He
wants health karma for his mom's
broken leg. But I should mention
he's also the guy. As far as I
know, who did a whole slew of no
agenda stickers, which we gave
out to everybody that we could
and they are dynamite. They're
mostly little covers that are
about one inch by one Angelo's
show album art and some other
stuff. And they're just really
it is nice. They're not it was a
nice gesture.
Adam Curry: Alright sir Montauk.
Thanks for going to the meetup.
We appreciate you.
Unknown: You've got karma.
Adam Curry: Sir Don Francis
Chandler, Arizona 222 dot 16. In
the morning Adam and John this
donation is in honor of my
smokin hot wife Dame Stephanie
and the Explorer chicks gang
currently wreaking havoc across
the state of Utah.
John C Dvorak: It may be a
fellow traveler. Yes.
Adam Curry: Dude, you miss the
special meetup. It may be added
to the bail Fund started by Sir
Mike in the last episode at your
discretion. I too must admit to
feeling somewhat jail Adam,
congratulations on 1600 Plus
shows and 16 years from Sir Don
Francis Thank you very much sir
Don. I feel like you my brother
now we are brothers brothers in
this mess.
John C Dvorak: Kiwi Rick in ball
and Western Australia. And he is
this has to be bumped up because
it's actually amounts to $345.67
what we do in Australian dollars
even though it's $208.82 was
wrong with Australia a lot.
Congratulations on your
anniversary from Perth. Isn't
Perth. Please de douche me.
Unknown: You've been de deuced
John C Dvorak: got me to the
birthday list. I'm 48 on October
22. You might want to check
because this is a lot of stuff
for Jada doing she may miss this
one. The donation also brings up
my knighthood please dubbed me
Sir Richard of the lands down
under I would humbly request
Bangers and Mash along with the
usual accoutrements of the
roundtable. Man I have a 33 is
the magic number jingle and a
result of my now former New
socialist slash Marx's boss, who
unceremoniously moved me on can
I always have the best of the
best jobs Carmen love is lit.
Kiwi Rick?
Adam Curry: Yes and then this is
no problem for Jay. She's on she
got him on both lists 33 magic
magic
Unknown: jobs, jobs, jobs and
jobs for jobs
Adam Curry: well, I'd love to
take the last one but it's about
our Yeah, you're getting
John C Dvorak: Linda Lubetkin in
Lakewood, Colorado with jobs
karma for a resume that gets
results go to Image makers
inc.com For all your executive
resume and job search needs
that's Ingres make. Yeah. I
almost made it. Oh, hold on,
hold on, hold on, hold on.
Unknown: John, we're gonna have
to take that one over again.
John C Dvorak: A special spot
could you is trying to break the
record for time. Jobs karma for
resume that gets results go to
Image makers inc.com. For all
your executive resume and job
search needs, that's image
makers Inc with a k.com or just
fine ilinden lapangan. You can
find her she's under the job.
The show's producer list
Unknown: jobs, jobs, jobs and
jobs.
John C Dvorak: Showdown
continues,
Adam Curry: does thank you all
to these executive and Associate
Executive producers and PhD
years we have a special ceremony
for you to hand out to your your
PhDs, although I'm looking for a
bit of help with the imaging if
anyone feels feels that they
could they're up to that. These
are credits that are real
recognized across the
entertainment industry, you can
probably display them on your
LinkedIn on your resume. Or go
ahead if you don't have an IMDB
account, because you're already
in the entertainment industry.
Many big weeks who produced the
show are you can now become one
imdb.com. All of that is
completely legal, correct and
good. And a reminder that we
only guaranteed read the notes
for execs and Associate
Executive producers sometimes
we'll stop and we'll grab one on
the way down and John is going
to take us through the 50s right
now.
John C Dvorak: Exactly. That
start with who's at the top of
the list. To run Vargo and
Hoffman Hills Illinois. 160.
Dame Shopska salad. Hey, go in
Shazam. UK. I'm looking for some
D douching. Here. Counter San
Francisco is at the meetup. 160
bucks. Dan Malley in Fremont,
California. 113 Matt Grisham in
Zephyrhills, Florida 105
Adam Curry: This is our star
Hill HAMP they got 11% from
every sale using the 22%
discount code duckets 22 at Star
Hill hemp so there you go.
John C Dvorak: In eon Oh, yeah.
Was Did you know that in Bera
beverage or beverage I'm sorry,
it's beverage beverage or
average in Long Branch New
Jersey 101 33. In another in
fields $100 Patricia S. Lewis in
Merced, California. 100 She's
got a birthday card and a
biscuit for a birthday always
give me a biscuit on my
birthday. That's
Adam Curry: for for his
birthday. For Parker Mitchell's
birthday from his Mimi from his
Mimi
John C Dvorak: is Mimi is Mimi
Marin, a Mandalay was at the
meetup. $100. Sure, lavish was
at the meetup. And I promised
him when I was talking chatting
with him that I would say the
following. Behind the schemes
live Monday night on the no
agenda stream 730 PST
Adam Curry: second, there's a
second part to that.
John C Dvorak: Oh, I don't think
he was the second part read does
he? Okay, that'd be start over
behind the scheme's live Monday
night. I know agenda stream at
7:30pm Join lavish for the BTS
spooky hour. Monday, October 23.
Good work. Brian Lillard and
prosper Texas at 888. Kevin
McLaughlin comes in 808 Breast
Cancer Awareness Month. Feel for
lumps Savior bumps. K Mer in
Vancouver, Washington 808. John
Siebert in Auburn, California he
came down from Auburn to go to
the meetup. Oh, no. And he and
he came in with 808 Very cool.
Kyle posi AK pase pase pase ek
in Hannibal, Missouri. Sar in
hard dirt is 805 and It's a
Barnhart donation. It needs a D
douching. You got your Barnhart
guy?
Adam Curry: Yeah, I got a
Barnhart. Gosh. You've been de
Deus Barnhart, donation.
John C Dvorak: Go please. Brian
Belen and Ashbery, New Jersey
AD. He does have a comment I
want to say best show. Dakota
Cole in Sherwood Oregon at an
issues with the notes from this
person. David Jarman in North
Tora mudra in New South Wales,
Australia. 7990 Hurray. Adam
said it correctly. Sir Rick in
Arlington, Washington 6996. Deer
Kevin McLaughlin is back with
606 breast Breast Cancer
Awareness Month. Saved the
blouse bunnies saved the blouse
bunnies
Adam Curry: that blouse bunnies
John C Dvorak: Eric hauls in
Richmond, Texas. 55 defied
Nicolas Oman in Thief River
Falls Minnesota to defy for defy
Barry Henry in Rancho Palos
Verdes days. 5242 Forest Martin
5005 Andrew Benz and Imperial
Missouri 5005. Matt Illingworth
in Montclair, New Jersey 50 And
these are all 50s. Now we're
gonna wrap this up pretty
quickly. Slightly top heavy
today. Matt Killingsworth in the
railing worth in Montclair, New
Jersey Robert case and mill
spring, North Carolina, Michael
Manzella and hopping Hopkinton,
Massachusetts, Matthias mill
chin ski in Hawthorne,
California Daniel laboy in Bath,
Michigan Julian Robinson Aptos
Nicholas route of which in
Harpers Ferry West Virginia.
Michael Bennett event day in
Yonkers, New York needs a de
douching you've been de deuced
Robert Hannon Poway, California
Michael site Cora in New
Richmond, Wisconsin, Tatiana
Prince in Hollywood, Florida,
Patrick, Sir Patrick and Macomb
in New York City. Leanne Shipley
and Covington, Washington and
last but not least, Michael
stadium Parts Unknown. These are
all the people that made show
1601 a reality.
Adam Curry: We thank you all
very much. Also everyone under
$50 We don't mention you for
absolute anonymity. And you may
be on one of the many sustaining
donations as a lot of them you
can find that our new donation
website which is no agenda
donations.com Or of course the
old trusty one four.org/and A
short list on the birthdays
Baronet Nathan Lee Minar foster
Miller Foster, which is Mike
Riley a happy birthday it
apparently is his birthday today
one of our favorite no agenda
artists are Chris and Dame Kurt
Kristen, with Sir William
messing a happy birthday for
today and kiwi returns 48 Happy
birthday from everybody here the
best podcast in the universe.
And now I would like to welcome
our new PhDs to the podium. We
do this in one big ceremony and
we hand them out right away so
they can flip that tassel to the
other side. Welcome new doctors
of deconstruction Brandon
Janssen, Keith Gibson, Kevin
Popovich, Derek J Fisker Derek
Boggs, Eric tambor Dark Lady
does your brand and your organs
and and a ham Lauren on you are
now official PhD graduates
doctors in deconstruction Okay,
so this is where I need some
ending or something I'm working
well you
John C Dvorak: know, we didn't
do the last group. We did
ceremony
Adam Curry: we know I didn't
have the ceremony ready.
John C Dvorak: You want it?
Well, Kate was the last group
gonna get their little
presentation
Adam Curry: on the next show.
Okay, because I wasn't prepared
for it. And that's fine because
I didn't even want to overlook
them. You forgot to have a
meeting. We didn't forget. We
didn't forget we just didn't
have the meeting. We have a make
good correction. Who was this
from? If you would make a quick
correction if possible during
John's reading of my note with
25% or 33% off kitchen and
bathroom cabinets. He said if
you live in Pennsylvania, please
correct this to the lower 47
states. I thought this 49 lower
states anyway, this is not 80380
it's not available in commie
Fornia do tend to to tax
implication so it's 47 I should
John C Dvorak: owe 40 Because
the California call me foreign
why?
Adam Curry: Because you call me
so that's why we have one Indane
we have a couple of nights so
let us bring out the blade or
run in your blades. Hello good
got your blade you got your Hold
John C Dvorak: on Wait Here you
go
Adam Curry: up on the podium
please does also Brandon's
conspiracy therapist Kevin
Popovich Derek Boggs, Eric
pepper and kiwi rake all of you
about no not about you are now
Damon knights no agenda
roundtable I hereby pronounce
the KT esteemed Dark Lady does
Sue or demon dragging a demon
dragon of the under city Parson
of Florence or Kevin Knight of
the reading Clover sir Derek
protector of section 707 Sir
Eric rock defender of the aisle
readout of Brigantine home of
pepper Cove beach and Sir
Richard into the lands down
under for you hookers and blow
rent boys in Chardon, a Thai
pepper infused vodka with katsu
curry, some Tom Lau and may calm
whiskey bangers and mash and of
course, because of mutton and
meat here for you, but you know
that you got all your goodies
here while you head over to no
agenda rings.com. This is also
where you can head over if you
have a PhD and you will find
ways to get that into your
possession for the night. And
Dame today. You have the
handsome night and Dame ring
which comes with wax to seal
your official correspondence
with and of course, all of these
have a certificate of
authenticity. And thank you very
much for supporting your no
agenda show.
Unknown: No one.
Adam Curry: All right, we got to
meet up reports. No, actually we
have one meetup reporting. What
do we have now? This is odd.
something was going wrong with
the meetup reports. Let me see.
I think this Oh, I'm getting an
error on that one. Let me see if
I can play it like this. See if
this works. Oh, second. No, that
was Dempsey's food and spirits.
Well, for some reason that one
failed. Sorry about it. So we'd
have to resend that to me.
Here's the October North Georgia
meetup report.
Unknown: In the morning, Adam
and John sir Bob here and
bringing you a meetup report
from the north Georgia monthly
meetup. It was another
successful meetup and we had
three new slaves show up and
possibly a KGB spook. I'll toss
them around, see what anybody
has to say. Thank you for your
courage and Happy Anniversary
guys.
Hey, Dr. Sir. microts. Got
questions for John about this
PhD program. Those count as
continuing education, credits,
and honorary degree. And I need
to also find out about some
student loan possibilities.
Thank you for what you do.
Thanks for putting it out all
the time. I love you guys. I
listened a lot. Keep safe. Stay
safe. John, This is Sam. We've
talked in the morning. Thank you
so much for what you do and I
love you guys. Keep at it. Shawn
here thanks for decolonizing my
amygdala
in the morning Ben here go to a
meet up. Jay here in Alpharetta
where today we learned if you're
going to walk into the bar and a
tinfoil hat so that your fellow
douchebags recognize you make
sure you're at the right bar
I'm that one person joined after
Adam second appearance and Megan
Kelly in the morning
Adam Curry: I love the great
reformer messy. But you know
what? You know what these people
were not upset trigger than auto
like the gags the gags were
funny. They sounded a little bit
of nice abbreviated that had a
nice connection. They're from
all over the map all over the
world, all kinds of different
backgrounds. That's what no
agenda meetups are about. And
you You deserve it. You deserve
to go to a meet up if you want
to go in today and you're in
Michigan. You can still make the
Michigan local one. Douchebag
Pat's birthday party at Red Dog
Saloon in Milford or Thursday,
the Mile High meet up that'll be
at Lincoln's Roadhouse in
Denver, Colorado. Here's what's
coming up. In the next couple of
days. We got Toronto Victoria
BC, we got Epping new hamster I
must be new New Hampshire, New
Hampshire, I guess. Virginia
Starr, Idaho, Pennsylvania,
California, Switzerland, Zurich
on the 28th we get Ireland on
the 29th. Very nice. Good to see
you. There. We got Albuquerque,
New Mexico again on the 12th.
Fredericksburg, Virginia, not
Texas on the 12th as well.
Baffin doll on the 12th of
November in the Netherlands, we
have SQL so we have Alabama,
Huntsville on the 18th
stillbirth, the Netherlands on
the 30th Indianapolis on the
fourth of December. That's
right, the keeper and I will be
attending, looking forward to
that one as well. No agenda
meetups, they give you
connection and that always leads
to protection. If you can't find
one near you start one yourself
They're easy no agenda
meetups.com
Unknown: go hang out with Dyson
days. You won't be triggered.
You want to be where
everybody's safe. Bye
Adam Curry: All right, you go
first. You're well,
John C Dvorak: you're only have
two. Okay, I have a couple and I
made him kind of, you know?
Lame. No, I made you one of them
just did that generic I would
say they're evergreen. Oh, okay.
Evergreens Yes. Now one of them
may not be good for the show.
Let's start with that one
despicable it's despicable
Adam Curry: and corrupt it's not
bad it's not
John C Dvorak: boring. And the
other one is the is the
Evergreen if you can't come up
with anything good this has to
go in thank you so much for
joining us today.
Adam Curry: Wow Wow, you gotta
you got to make that you got to
monetize that came through on
left chan thank you so much for
joining us today. It's a little
out of balance. Sorry, what
cancels for technical reasons. I
think this bowl, but I have I
have a couple to select from and
I think I have winners here.
Unknown: The algorithms are
running everything it turns out.
Adam Curry: Little long.
Unknown: But what do you know?
Adam Curry: Oh my god. That was
really stressful. Too long. This
I think this is the one podcast
canceled. I think that's that's
good. You'd
John C Dvorak: run this with
last time
Adam Curry: podcast canceled. I
didn't run that one. Okay, I
will
John C Dvorak: go with I like
it. I like actually like all
four years.
Adam Curry: Oh, do podcast
cancel. Okay, I have a I have an
Africa clip for the end of show
but I am overriding the after
the one Africa clip end of show
for
John C Dvorak: this week before
I do Africa in the show. I got
two clips about Biden in the
smoking gun.
Adam Curry: Oh, brother. Really?
You're going to bring the whole
show down?
Unknown: No, it's not that bad.
Okay.
John C Dvorak: Look for
something. Okay. I could do a
Ukrainian update.
Adam Curry: Now. What's this a
bummer. Look, it's it's three
hours and 12 minutes. You're
trying to elongate the show. I
can put this off. I think you
should put that off because I
have an entertainment clip.
John C Dvorak: Okay, we'll go
with you. And we'll do what you
what you say you have the
control. I
Adam Curry: have the con George
Clooney. Let's
Unknown: talk about George
Clooney. He wants to see actors
back at work. So he's putting
his money where his mouth is.
The Oscar winner and other top
Hollywood stars are offering a
proposal worth $150 million
dollars to encourage sag AFTRA
to end the strike that just
started in July now. Clooney
spokesperson confirms the offer
it would remove the cap undos
from the union's highest
earners, raising an extra 150
million over the next three
years for member benefits. Sag
AFTRA, President Fran Drescher
doe went on Instagram, she
thanked George Clooney for the
quote, extremely generous offer.
But she also elaborated it does
not impact the contract that the
actors actually want. She said
that under the law,
contributions for pension and
health funds of a federally
regulated Labor Union must come
from employers. It can't come
from the people who are the
members of that union. It has to
come from from the employers. So
talks between striking actors
and major studios. They broke
down last week the actor strike
will markets 100 day tomorrow.
So So French, of course, she
acknowledges that it's a
generous offer. But because
there are things that the actors
are looking for that have to do
with AI that have to do with
streaming and residuals, the 150
million that's just cash doesn't
address those
other facilities saying I'm just
trying to help. Yeah. And
I think that they welcome that.
It is tough, though, to hear I'm
coming up with $150 million. No,
thanks. But no, thanks
for Yeah, Thanks for Thanks. But
yeah, but But I understand the
point she's making as well, if I
have other issues that need to
be addressed, can't they do
both?
Right? Because it's like, okay.
We'll be happy to say yeah,
like, let's not talk about the
things that are really on the
table. And that
removes the studio from their
responsibility. Why can't you do
both?
We're looking forward to now
we'll just say thank you,
George. For your pocket.
Adam Curry: You know, he's back
on the say you get some
distraction.
He's coming back. He's coming
back. He's making a comeback.
What are you drinking at the end
of the show?
John C Dvorak: Well, I got this
from the meetup Lagunitas. Hoppy
refresher. I have to get up my
game now that somebody made a
mockery of my commentary. And
this is one of these is a beer
into show mixes.
Unknown: This is a beer. No,
it's
John C Dvorak: a hoppy,
refreshers water that pop
flavored
Adam Curry: What's the hoppy
refresher show title?
John C Dvorak: Happy refresher.
Adam Curry: We have endless show
mixes from Steve Jones, Dr. AI
and Jesse Coyne Nelson, and
thank you to our indoor show
mixers as always, we love you.
And coming up next I know agenda
stream before the scheme's V for
V boost of a music show with
blueberry and lavish. Could it
get any better than that? I
don't think so. No, I hope you
enjoyed your media
deconstruction for today. We
look forward to meeting you here
again on Thursday. Remember,
Monday is JC D phone free
Monday. And go to a meet up,
William, coming to you from the
heart of the Texas hill country
here in FEMA Region number six
in the morning, everybody. I'm
Adam curry
John C Dvorak: and from Northern
Silicon Valley where Believe it
or not, it's raining. I'm Jesse
Devorah.
Adam Curry: We return on
Thursday right here on no
agenda. Remember us at the
vorak.org/na no agenda
donations.com Till the next time
adios mofos who we who we
answered voices,
John C Dvorak: voices, voices
pounding, pounding ourselves in
the face. Face to fist best.
Best and you can't stop yourself
for and you're starting to hear
voice voices because your voice
Adam Curry: seems like there's
something going on. And just
letting yourself become become
one night he tried to knock
himself out
John C Dvorak: on your voices,
voices. Because we'll be caught
fist pounding yourself in the
face with your own fist, fist
Adam Curry: to his knuckles,
knuckles to his face and
compounded compounded over and
over and over again. Because it
seems like there's something
going on going on
Unknown: going little by little.
John C Dvorak: Just letting
yourself become become become
become
Adam Curry: Somehow I don't
think it's 45,000 maybe 4500
John C Dvorak: I said 45
desperately says 45,000 as note
Adam Curry: doesn't know doesn't
says 4500 But I say
John C Dvorak: 45 45,000 Using
his 45,000 uses oh nice what I
said I misread it. Okay, got
Unknown: it gathered in masse
it's a memo that describes how
we're going to take out seven
countries in five years. Which
is at
Black Massey is
John C Dvorak: when I first came
to office one of the first
meetings I had was at the
Pentagon with generals evil
minds that blood destruction
Unknown: Bolton has always said
let's go to war but he's not the
one who's gonna go on the
forefront. He's a coward
destined structure. The leaders
of Iran are racketeers behind
every problem is Iran what you
said 2016 and liked it when you
said no more stupid wars.
You got a roll president in the
White House surrounded by these
Uber hawks that thirst for
another war with Iran.
International Atomic Energy
Agency has never found Iran in
contravention of stipulations in
the deal.
John C Dvorak: If Iran wants to
find that will be the official
end of Iran never threaten the
United States. Again, I'm not
Unknown: somebody that wants to
go into war in the United States
heading towards another Middle
East showdown, this time with
Iran.
MoPhO boruch.org/in a podcast
cancelled